"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525537","2016-06-27","HM Treasury","2016-06-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of instituting a common standardised approach for calculation of risk weights in the capital requirements regulation for banks and building societies, including new entrant banks less than five years old.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40819","40819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525538","2016-06-27","HM Treasury","2016-06-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what correspondence he has had with (a) the Competition and Markets Authority, (b) the Prudential Regulation Authority and (c) new entrant banks about the internal ratings-based approach and the standardised approach for risk weights in capital requirements regulation; and if he will place a copy of that correspondence in the Library.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40820","40820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525539","2016-06-27","Department for Transport","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much revenue has been retained as a result of refunds for cancelled vehicle tax only being given for any full months of remaining tax since October 2014.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40797","40797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525540","2016-06-27","HM Treasury","2016-06-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of the systemic financial risk from tranching of securitised assets.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40812","40812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525541","2016-06-27","HM Treasury","2016-06-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of the (a) benefits to the economy and (b) systemic financial risks from synthetic securitisation.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40813","40813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525542","2016-06-27","HM Treasury","2016-06-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of the European Parliament Committee on Economic and Monetary Affairs' draft report on the proposal for a regulation on securitisation and creating a European framework for simple, transparent and standardised securitisation; and whether he supports the Committee's proposal to increase risk retention from five per cent to 20 per cent based on a vertical slice of securitised assets.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40814","40814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525543","2016-06-27","HM Treasury","2016-06-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what correspondence his Department has had with (a) the Commissioner for Financial Stability, Financial Services and Capital Markets Union and (b) UK banks on the European Commission's proposed regulatory framework for simple, transparent and standardised securitisation; and if he will place a copy of that correspondence in the Library.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40815","40815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525544","2016-06-27","HM Treasury","2016-06-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the risks to financial stability from the European Commission's proposed regulatory framework for simple, transparent and standardised securitisation; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40816","40816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525545","2016-06-27","HM Treasury","2016-06-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of the results of the Current Account Switching Service for personal current account holders with overdrafts.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40817","40817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525546","2016-06-27","HM Treasury","2016-06-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of a FCA-regulated monthly maximum charge on unarranged overdrafts for personal current accounts.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40818","40818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525547","2016-06-27","HM Treasury","2016-06-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the funding was of the Invest to Save Budget from 1999 to 2010.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40804","40804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525548","2016-06-27","HM Treasury","2016-06-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many projects were funded by the Invest to Save Budget between 1999 and 2010.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40805","40805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525549","2016-06-27","HM Treasury","2016-06-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many evaluation reports HM Treasury's Invest to Save Budget Unit produced between 1999 and 2010.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40802","40802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525550","2016-06-27","HM Treasury","2016-06-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to revise references to handicapped people in Schedule 8 to the Value Added Tax Act 1994.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40740","40740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525551","2016-06-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what plans his Department has to engage with representatives from the Alevi community in Britain.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40794","40794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525552","2016-06-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 14 June 2016 to Question 39438, if his Department will keep an annual record of locations visited by Ministers and officials of his Department in the future; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40722","40722"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525553","2016-06-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether his Department has made an estimate of the number of families in Bradford who will move home as a result of pay to stay provisions of the Housing and Planning Act 2016 during the current Parliament.","Biography information for Judith Cummins","Judith Cummins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40687","40687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525554","2016-06-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the replacement rate of housing association properties sold through right-to-buy in each year since the launch of that policy; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40701","40701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525555","2016-06-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether the Government plans to bring forward proposals in the Neighbourhood and Planning and Infrastructure Bill to remove the requirement for developers to carry out archaeological and wildlife surveys before starting housing projects.","Biography information for Gordon Henderson","Gordon Henderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40705","40705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525556","2016-06-27","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions he has had with the Gambling Commission and the Remote Gambling Association in the last 12 months on the progress of the online multi-operator self-exclusion scheme.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40753","40753"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525557","2016-06-27","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what progress has been made on the development of the multi-operator self-exclusion scheme since 17 February 2016.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40754","40754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525558","2016-06-27","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether a decision has been made by the Gambling Commission, his Department and the Remote Gambling Association about who will manage the online multi-operator self-exclusion scheme when it is established.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40755","40755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525559","2016-06-27","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what the timetable is for the Digital Economy Bill.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40758","40758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525560","2016-06-27","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what involvement UK armed forces have had with EU battle groups in the last three years; and how many UK armed forces personnel the Government has pledged to commit to those groups.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40712","40712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525561","2016-06-27","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will eliminate the cost of adapting Type 45 destroyers to operate in warm waters.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40706","40706"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525562","2016-06-27","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what proportion of ongoing maintenance on the UK P-8 Poseidon has been conducted in the US under US International Traffic in Arms Regulations.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40672","40672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525563","2016-06-27","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the current value of contracts is between his Department and Boeing and Boeing UK; and what proportion of work under those contracts is carried out in the UK.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40670","40670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525564","2016-06-27","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the P-8 Poseidon will be capable of carrying UK Storm Shadow and other manufactured munitions.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40671","40671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525565","2016-06-27","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the cost of the UK P-8 Poseidon programme is; and what proportion of work share under that programme will be delivered through the UK defence industry.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40673","40673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525566","2016-06-27","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what he plans the UK operational in-service date for the P-8 Poseidon will be.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40684","40684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525567","2016-06-27","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that armed forces recruits aged between 16 and 19 without a GCSE in mathematics or English are prepared for later life outside the armed forces.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40822","40822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525568","2016-06-27","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what progress has been made on the upgrade of a Voyager aircraft for transporting senior Ministers; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40743","40743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525569","2016-06-27","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department considers that the use of cluster munitions is always unlawful under international humanitarian law because of their indiscriminate nature.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40776","40776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525570","2016-06-27","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many armed forces personnel handed in a formal notice of resignation in each month between January 2010 and January 2014.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40777","40777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525571","2016-06-27","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which of the UK's allies has aircraft which are capable of refuelling P-8 Poseidon aircraft to be procured by the UK.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40783","40783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525572","2016-06-27","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether P-8 Poseidon aircraft to be procured by the UK are capable of being refuelled by the RAF's Voyager K2/K3 aerial refuelling tanker aircraft.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40784","40784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525573","2016-06-27","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills on the P-8 Poseidon programme.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40785","40785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525574","2016-06-27","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department made an assessment of the potential merits of procuring an alternative to the P-8 Poseidon maritime patrol aircraft before the decision on that procurement was made.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40788","40788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525575","2016-06-27","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he expects the contract to be signed between his Department and Boeing to deliver the UK's P-8 Poseidon aircraft.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40789","40789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525576","2016-06-27","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what proportion of the P-8 Poseidon programme is covered by the US International Traffic in Arms Regulations.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40790","40790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525577","2016-06-27","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many UK (a) flight crew, (b) ground crew and (c) intelligence analysts have served on US P-8 Poseidon aircraft under the Seedcorn exchange programme; and what the cost to the UK public purse has been of deploying those people since the start of that programme.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40781","40781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525578","2016-06-27","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the cost of training UK crew and maintenance personnel for the P-8 Poseidon aircraft to be procured by the UK; and where he expects that training to take place.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40782","40782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525579","2016-06-27","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, where the engines for the P-8 Poseidon aircraft to be procured by the UK will be manufactured.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40786","40786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525580","2016-06-27","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what future ground surveillance capabilities his Department plans to develop for the P-8 Poseidon programme.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40787","40787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525581","2016-06-27","Department for Education","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to improve the capacity of schools and colleges to support children and young persons who are experiencing mental illness.","Biography information for Judith Cummins","Judith Cummins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40742","40742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525582","2016-06-27","Department for Education","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which Commissioner would make the decision in a case where a multi academy trust operating in one region wished to expand by adding a school in another region.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40823","40823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525583","2016-06-27","Department for Education","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 15 June 2016 to Question 40258, what the minimum number of responses is for results for a school to be published on Parent View.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40825","40825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525584","2016-06-27","Department for Education","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 15 June 2016 to Question 40256, what steps she is taking to ensure that a school which is not required formally to consult about academy conversion takes into account the views of local stakeholders.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40826","40826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525585","2016-06-27","Department for Education","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if her Department will take steps to ensure STEM-qualified teachers are exempt from the £35,000 income threshold for settlement for non-EU workers.","Biography information for Carol Monaghan","Carol Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40844","40844"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525586","2016-06-27","Department for Education","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to ensure schools continue to recruit and retain non-EU nationals in STEM subjects who do not meet the £35,000 income threshold for settlement.","Biography information for Carol Monaghan","Carol Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40845","40845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525588","2016-06-27","Department for Education","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what powers she has to prevent multi-academy trusts from expanding faster than their capacity to maintain a strong record on school improvement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40854","40854"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525589","2016-06-27","Department for Education","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she made an assessment of the potential merits of providing additional funding to schools with high teacher vacancy rates for teacher salaries.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40663","40663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525590","2016-06-27","Department for Education","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much her Department spent in the last five years on the provision of English language teachers for students recently arrived in the UK with little knowledge of that language.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40710","40710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525591","2016-06-27","Department for Education","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will publish the pass rates for the year one phonics screening check by the birth month of the pupils.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40721","40721"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525592","2016-06-27","Department for Education","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of the number of children in (a) Bradford South constituency and (b) Yorkshire and the Humber who do not meet the expected levels of speech and communication skills in the Early Years Foundation Stage assessment.","Biography information for Judith Cummins","Judith Cummins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40686","40686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525593","2016-06-27","Department for Education","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 6 June 2016 to Question 38401, whether she plans to publish her response to the School Teachers' Review Body report on teachers' pay from September 2016 and the draft 2016 School Teachers' Pay and Conditions document for consultation and information before 14 July 2016.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40698","40698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525594","2016-06-27","Department for Education","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will take steps in response to the findings of the report published by the Children's Commissioner and the NSPCC in July 2016, on a quantitative and qualitative examination of the impact of online pornography on the values, attitudes, beliefs and behaviours of children and young people, to ensure that all children have access to age-appropriate PSHE at school.","Biography information for Mrs Maria Miller","Mrs Maria Miller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40699","40699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525595","2016-06-27","Department for Education","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many Civil Service employees of her Department were based in Coventry in each of the last five years; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40726","40726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525596","2016-06-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will issue a response to EDM 211, 2016 Report by UN Commission of Inquiry on Human Rights in Eritrea, tabled on 14 June 2016.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40682","40682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525597","2016-06-27","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what proportion of trade negotiators employed by the EU are UK nationals.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40709","40709"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525598","2016-06-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 18 May 2016 to Question 37099, if the Government will support an independent investigation into allegations of attacks on Syrian asylum seekers by Turkish border guards.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40734","40734"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525599","2016-06-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 18 May 2016 to Question 37099, if the Government will support a public call on the government of Turkey to end the closure of its border with Syria.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40731","40731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525600","2016-06-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effect of the retaking of Sirte on Daesh; and what steps his Department is taking to help restore stability to that city.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40711","40711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525601","2016-06-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, which cases of people detained in China were raised during the state visit of President Xi Jinping in October 2015; and what assurances and undertakings were given in respect of those cases.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40717","40717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525602","2016-06-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the Government has taken steps to ensure that any UK Trade and Investment deals with China announced during President Xi's visit to the UK of 2015 are consistent with the UK's obligations and stated commitments under the National Action Plan on Business and Human Rights.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40715","40715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525603","2016-06-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what human rights objectives the Government set for the state visit of President Xi Jinping to the UK in October 2015; and what progress has been made on achieving those objectives.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40716","40716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525604","2016-06-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will issue a response to Early Day Motion 116, Slavery in Mauritania.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40798","40798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525605","2016-06-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the conclusions of the report The lawfulness of the authorisation by the United Kingdom of weapons and related items for export to Saudi Arabia in the context of Saudi Arabia's military intervention in Yemen by Professor Philippe Sands QC and others, published on 11 December 2015.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40800","40800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525606","2016-06-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the human rights situation in Eritrea.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40775","40775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525607","2016-06-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the criteria are for the Government to recognise a Palestinian state.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40778","40778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525608","2016-06-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the extent to which the Alevi community in Turkey has the right to exercise freedom of religious expression; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40792","40792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525609","2016-06-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment his Department has made of the human rights situation of the Alevi community in Turkey; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40793","40793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525610","2016-06-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Turkish counterpart on the treatment of minority religious groups in Turkey.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40795","40795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525611","2016-06-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the European Court of Human Rights' ruling of 26 April 2016 on religious discrimination against the Alevi community in Turkey.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40791","40791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525612","2016-06-27","Department of Health","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he plans to take in response to the decision by the Care Quality Commission to issue a warning notice to North Middlesex University Hospital NHS Trust regarding the standard of care in the emergency department at that hospital; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40745","40745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525613","2016-06-27","Department of Health","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to increase awareness of risk reduction and prevention of dementia; and what information he holds on the effect of (a) alcohol, exercise and weight and (b) other risk factors; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40806","40806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525614","2016-06-27","Department of Health","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he plans to take in response to the announcement by Health Education England that it will not allow postgraduate training to continue in North Middlesex University Hospital NHS Trust's emergency department because of concerns about support and supervision of trainee doctors at that hospital.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40749","40749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525615","2016-06-27","Department of Health","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what representations officials, advisers and Ministers of his Department have made to the Chief Executive and Chair of North Middlesex University Hospital NHS Trust since May 2015 on the standard of care in that hospital's emergency department.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40747","40747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525616","2016-06-27","Department of Health","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with NHS England on that body's efforts to recruit additional accident and emergency specialists from other hospitals in London to work in the emergency department at North Middlesex University Hospital NHS Trust.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40746","40746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525617","2016-06-27","Department of Health","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 22 January 2016 to Question 22462, if he will place in the Library a copy of NHS England's report on individual funding requests for palivizumab.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40748","40748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525618","2016-06-27","Department of Health","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has carried out of the effect of the closure of the emergency department at Chase Farm Hospital in 2013 on other hospital emergency departments in (a) Enfield and (b) North London.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40744","40744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525619","2016-06-27","Department of Health","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to address the decline in cervical screening uptake in the 25 to 29 age group.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40772","40772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525620","2016-06-27","Department of Health","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment his Department has made of the barriers that prevent women from attending cervical screening.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40773","40773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525621","2016-06-27","Department of Health","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to increase cervical screening rates among (a) women with learning disabilities and (b) women in deprived communities.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40774","40774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525622","2016-06-27","Department of Health","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 24th May 2016 to Question 37256, on the WHO framework convention on tobacco control, when he expects to take a decision on whether the delegation will be led by Ministers in his Department.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40741","40741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525623","2016-06-27","Department of Health","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what correspondence his Department has received about data on adjusted deaths per beds rates in care homes since January 2014.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40809","40809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525624","2016-06-27","Department of Health","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many prosecutions have been instigated by NHS Protect in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40810","40810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525625","2016-06-27","Department of Health","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people were employed by NHS Protect at each Civil Service pay grade in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40811","40811"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525626","2016-06-27","Department of Health","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the answer of 8 June 2016 to Question 38977, which health and higher education delivery organisations he is consulting to determine the baseline against which the additional 10,000 increase in training places is measured; and when he will publish further details of the baseline.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40829","40829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525627","2016-06-27","Department of Health","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the answer of 15 June 2016 to Question 40208, whether the estimated additional 10,000 student places are sufficient to meet current and future year demands.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40830","40830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525628","2016-06-27","Department of Health","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the answer of 15 June 2016 to Question 40208, what assurances he has received that the additional 10,000 students will be accommodated with clinical placements by healthcare providers without compromising the quality of the experience on those placements.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40831","40831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525629","2016-06-27","Department of Health","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the answer of 15 June 2016 to Question 40208, what bodies he consulted on the number of the additional student places for nurses; and what discussions he had with healthcare providers who arrange clinical placements for student nurses.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40832","40832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525630","2016-06-27","Department of Health","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he plans to respond to the letter of (a) 3 June 2016 from the right hon. Member for Enfield North and (b) 10 June 2016 from the hon. Member for Edmonton on the emergency department at North Middlesex University Hospital NHS Trust.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40835","40835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525631","2016-06-27","Department of Health","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the answer of 15 June 2016 to Question 40208, if he will publish the information used to estimate the level of unmet demand in order to establish the figure of an additional 10,000 student nurse places.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40833","40833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525632","2016-06-27","Department of Health","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policy of the findings of the Care Quality Commission's recent inspection report for North Middlesex University Hospital NHS Trust on the (a) level and (b) grade of staff in the accident and emergency department.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40843","40843"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525633","2016-06-27","Department of Health","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 6 June 2016 to Question 38191 on fertility: medical treatments, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the issues highlighted in the report in that Answer; and if he will write to clinical commissioning groups in England to highlight the findings of that report and the importance of delivering IVF services consistent with the NICE guidelines.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40847","40847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525634","2016-06-27","Department of Health","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 13 June 2016 to Question 40017, on NHS: drugs, what the value is of the five contracts listed in that Answer.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40704","40704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525635","2016-06-27","Department of Health","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of parliamentary scrutiny of the Chief Medical Officer's guidelines on levels of alcohol intake which recommend significant changes to those levels.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40718","40718"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525636","2016-06-27","Department of Health","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the reasons are for his policy on women requiring different advice to men on levels of calorie intake yet being given the same advice on their levels of alcohol intake.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40719","40719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525637","2016-06-27","Department of Health","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make it his policy to place incentives into NHS dentistry contracts to encourage NHS dentists to practice in areas with significantly above average numbers of oral and dental health issues.","Biography information for Judith Cummins","Judith Cummins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40688","40688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525638","2016-06-27","Department of Health","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the largest financial contracts between the NHS and private companies were in each of the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40702","40702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525639","2016-06-27","Department of Health","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 13 June 2016 to Question 40024, on NHS: drugs, what the most recent price paid per pack by the NHS was for each of the drugs listed in that Answer.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40703","40703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525640","2016-06-27","Department of Health","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with Public Health England on the effect of the revised Eatwell Guide on milk and dairy consumption by children.","Biography information for Simon Hoare","Simon Hoare","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40723","40723"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525641","2016-06-27","Department of Health","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions Public Health England had with child nutrition organisations on the development of the revised Eatwell Guide.","Biography information for Simon Hoare","Simon Hoare","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40725","40725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525642","2016-06-27","Department of Health","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions Public Health England had with dairy organisations on the development of the revised Eatwell Guide.","Biography information for Simon Hoare","Simon Hoare","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40724","40724"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525643","2016-06-27","Department of Health","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the annual cost to NHS services is of purchasing products used in the management of continence care.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40739","40739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525644","2016-06-27","Department of Health","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of doctor staffing levels in the emergency department at North Middlesex University Hospital NHS Trust.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40761","40761"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525645","2016-06-27","Department of Health","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent representations he has received from (a) Health Education England, (b) the General Medical Council and (c) the Care Quality Commission on the standard of treatment provided to patients at North Middlesex University Hospital NHS Trust's emergency department; and on what dates he received those representations.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40762","40762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525646","2016-06-27","Department of Health","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what contingency plans his Department has for the event of the closure of North Middlesex University Hospital NHS Trust's emergency department.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40763","40763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525647","2016-06-27","Department of Health","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what meetings he plans to hold with (a) Health Education England, (b) the General Medical Council, (c) the Care Quality Commission and (d) the leadership of North Middlesex University Hospital NHS Trust to discuss the standard of treatment in that hospital's emergency department.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40750","40750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525648","2016-06-27","Department of Health","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of the standard of treatment in North Middlesex University Hospital NHS Trust's emergency department.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40751","40751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525649","2016-06-27","Department of Health","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that the emergency department at North Middlesex University Hospital NHS Trust is able to guarantee patient safety; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40764","40764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525650","2016-06-27","Department of Health","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 8 June 2016 to Question 38977, on health professions: training, whether the figures provided take into account the number of applications each potential student can make.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40736","40736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525651","2016-06-27","Department of Health","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the implications for his Department of findings of Health Education England's briefing paper on its inspection visit to North Middlesex University Hospital NHS Trust's emergency department in March 2016.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40752","40752"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525652","2016-06-27","Department of Health","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of the number of contracts for sexual health services that include requirements to provide ongoing education and training.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40660","40660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525653","2016-06-27","Department of Health","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what measures are in place to regulate the prices of everyday drugs sold to the NHS by pharmaceutical companies.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40648","40648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525654","2016-06-27","Department of Health","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress has been made by the East Midlands Ambulance Service on reducing patient handover times to local hospitals.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40649","40649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525655","2016-06-27","Department of Health","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps are being taken to improve staff morale at the East Midlands Ambulance Service.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40650","40650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525656","2016-06-27","Department of Health","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps are being taken to address understaffing at the East Midlands Ambulance Service.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40651","40651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525657","2016-06-27","Department of Health","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what awareness-raising activities his Department has undertaken in support of Diabetes Awareness Week 2016.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40652","40652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525658","2016-06-27","Home Office","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of Advance Passenger Information was checked and acted upon in real-time for passengers leaving the UK in the latest period for which figures are available; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40675","40675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525659","2016-06-27","Home Office","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many immigration and asylum officials of her Department have been seconded to (a) Greece, (b) Italy and (c) France since the beginning of May 2016.","Biography information for Yvette Cooper","Yvette Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40668","40668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525660","2016-06-27","Home Office","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications to the Disclosure and Barring Service were made by people living in London in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40679","40679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525661","2016-06-27","Home Office","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that non-EEA family members of UK citizens have equal rights of travel within the EU when travelling with their UK citizen family member who has not exercised his or her rights under the Free Movement Directive, 2004/38/EC as do those who have exercised such rights.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40664","40664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525662","2016-06-27","Home Office","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many persons of interest have been found to have left the UK when it has not been possible to check and act upon Advance Passenger Information in real-time since April 2015; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40674","40674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525663","2016-06-27","Home Office","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many road policing officers there have been in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40656","40656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525664","2016-06-27","Home Office","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people who overstayed their visa have been identified leaving the UK in each month since 8 April 2015; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40676","40676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525665","2016-06-27","Home Office","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what information her Department holds on whether the National Crime Agency plans to investigate the UK office of the law firm Mossack Fonesca.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40662","40662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525666","2016-06-27","Home Office","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what training and assistance the UK Border Force provides to transport carriers and port operators who are required to collect Advance Passenger Information to identify false documents; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40677","40677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525667","2016-06-27","Home Office","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate her Department has made of the number of minors in Calais who are eligible to claim asylum in the UK under the Dublin III arrangements for family reunion.","Biography information for Yvette Cooper","Yvette Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40665","40665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525668","2016-06-27","Home Office","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate her Department has made of the number of asylum-seeking minors in France with family members in the UK.","Biography information for Yvette Cooper","Yvette Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40666","40666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525669","2016-06-27","Home Office","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many officials of her Department are on secondment in France to assist with the identification of potential requests for the UK to take charge of an asylum-seeking child in France.","Biography information for Yvette Cooper","Yvette Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40667","40667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525670","2016-06-27","Home Office","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many foreign nationals who were granted student visas before the removal of the post-study work visa are still accredited as students in the UK.","Biography information for Ian Blackford","Ian Blackford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40659","40659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525671","2016-06-27","Home Office","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 10 May 2016 to Question 36436, what progress she has made on (a) reflecting on the recommendations of other parties on the rollout of independent child trafficking advocates and (b) that rollout.","Biography information for Mr David Burrowes","Mr David Burrowes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40759","40759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525672","2016-06-27","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will take steps to respond to the findings of the report published by the Children's Commissioner and the NSPCC in June 2016, on a quantitative and qualitative examination of the impact of online pornography on the values, attitudes, beliefs and behaviours of children and young people, to ensure that children are not able to view pornographic material on (a) social media and (b) any other platform.","Biography information for Mrs Maria Miller","Mrs Maria Miller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40700","40700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525673","2016-06-27","Home Office","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what information her Department holds on the relationship between the number of road policing officers and the number of road offences.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40730","40730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525674","2016-06-27","Home Office","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average time taken was to process Disclosure and Barring Service checks for (a) standard and (b) enhanced disclosures between 1 January and 31 March 2016.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40824","40824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525675","2016-06-27","Ministry of Justice","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Oral Answer of 14 June 2016, Official Report, column 1617, on EU Prisoner Transfer Directive, to which EU member states the 102 prisoners transferred from England and Wales under the EU prisoner transfer agreement have been transferred.","Biography information for Crispin Blunt","Crispin Blunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40801","40801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525676","2016-06-27","Home Office","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have been arrested and charged with offences relating to girls under 18 years of age reported as missing to the police in each year from 1998 to 2005.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40779","40779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525677","2016-06-27","Home Office","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many girls under 18 years of age were reported missing in each year from 1998 to 2005; how many of those girls were subsequently found; and how many investigations into those girls' cases are ongoing.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40780","40780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525678","2016-06-27","House of Commons Commission","2016-06-15","To ask the Rt. hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington representing the House of Commons Commission, whether any pedestrian entry points to the Parliamentary Estate are restricted to particular categories of passholder, and if so what those restrictions are at each point.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40799","40799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525679","2016-06-29","Department for International Development","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment her Department has made of the merits of the Investment Case prepared by the Global Fund to fight AIDS, tuberculosis and malaria in preparation for its replenishment conference on 16 September 2016.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40765","40765"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525680","2016-06-27","Department for International Development","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment her Department has made of the effect of bilateral investment treaties between the UK and developing countries on the ability of (a) infant industries and (b) small and medium-sized enterprises in such countries to contribute to poverty reduction.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40852","40852"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525681","2016-06-27","Department for International Development","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment her Department has made of the effect of bilateral investment treaties between the UK and developing countries on the Government's ability to meet its commitments to the Sustainable Development Goals.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40853","40853"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525682","2016-06-27","Department for International Development","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment her Department has made of the potential effect of investor state dispute settlement mechanisms on the ability of legal systems in developing countries to support the achievement of the sustainable development goals.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40841","40841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525683","2016-06-28","Department for International Development","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department has taken to promote LGBT rights in developing countries in this Parliament.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40848","40848"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525684","2016-06-27","Department for International Development","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what plans she has for future funding from her Departmental budget for women's rights organisations in developing countries.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40760","40760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525685","2016-06-27","Department for International Development","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the effect of the de-listing of the Saudi-led coalition in the UN Secretary-General's report on Children and Armed Conflict, published in April 2016, on civilian protection and the wider humanitarian situation in Yemen.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40771","40771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525686","2016-06-27","Department for International Development","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to tackle food insecurity in Southern Africa.","Biography information for Alex Salmond","Alex Salmond","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40683","40683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525687","2016-06-27","Department for International Development","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether she plans to support the International Trade Centre's She Trades initiative; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40678","40678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525688","2016-06-27","Ministry of Justice","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many appeal tribunal decisions in relation to re-assessments of entitlement of disability living allowance for children found in favour of the claimant in the last three years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40647","40647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525689","2016-06-27","Ministry of Justice","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many rejected mandatory reconsiderations submitted in relation to re-assessments of entitlement of disability living allowance for children resulted in an appeal tribunal being conducted in the last three years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40645","40645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525690","2016-06-27","Ministry of Justice","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many appeal tribunal decisions in relation to re-assessments of entitlement of disability living allowance for children found in favour of the Department for Work and Pensions in the last three years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40735","40735"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525691","2016-06-27","Ministry of Justice","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will publish new guidance on assisting transgender people in prison.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40689","40689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525692","2016-06-27","Ministry of Justice","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the cost to the public purse was of replacement prison cell doors because of damage by prisoners in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40846","40846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525693","2016-06-27","Ministry of Justice","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what his policy is on (a) consulting on and (b) piloting future planned reforms of the civil courts structure.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40849","40849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525694","2016-06-27","Ministry of Justice","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the finding of Lord Justice Briggs in his report entitled, Civil Courts Structure: Interim Report, published in December 2015, that personal injury should be excluded from the Online Court.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40850","40850"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525695","2016-06-27","Ministry of Justice","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the report by Lord Justice Briggs on his report entitled, Civil Courts Structure: Interim Report, published in December 2015, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the finding in paragraph 5.23 of that report.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40851","40851"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525696","2016-06-27","HM Treasury","2016-06-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many criminal and restorative justice programmes were funded by the Invest to Save Budget.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40803","40803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525697","2016-06-27","Northern Ireland Office","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what steps she plans to take in response to the Police Ombudsman for Northern Ireland's statutory report into the murders at the Heights Bar, Loughinisland on 18 June 1994, published on 9 June 2016; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40821","40821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525698","2016-06-27","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2016-06-15","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, whether any non-UK EU nationals were sent postal votes in error for the upcoming EU referendum.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40714","40714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525699","2016-06-27","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2016-06-15","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what steps the Commission is taking to ensure that any non-UK EU nationals who were issued polling cards in error for the EU referendum will not be able to vote in that referendum.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40713","40713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525700","2016-06-27","Department for Transport","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 31 May 2016 to Question 37855, on the London to Brighton railway line, if he will commit in principle to upgrade the Brighton main line, prior to the High Level Operating Statement in 2017.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40697","40697"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525701","2016-06-27","Department for Transport","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to (a) assess and (b) address the effect on rail services of the infrastructure bottleneck at Croydon.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40728","40728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525702","2016-06-27","Department for Transport","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much his Department has allocated for Network Rail to produce a feasibility study on the Brighton Mainline Upgrade; and whether he plans for that funding to continue up to 2020.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40737","40737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525703","2016-06-27","Department for Transport","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions his Department has had with airport operators on responding to incidents involving unmanned drones and aircraft.","Biography information for Martin Docherty-Hughes","Martin Docherty-Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40768","40768"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525704","2016-06-27","Department for Transport","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions his Department has had with the Scottish Government on the near collision between an unmanned drone and a passenger aircraft above Clydebank on 6 March 2016.","Biography information for Martin Docherty-Hughes","Martin Docherty-Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40769","40769"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525705","2016-06-27","Department for Transport","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions his Department has had with West Dunbartonshire Council on the near collision between an unmanned drone and a passenger aircraft above Clydebank on 6 March 2016.","Biography information for Martin Docherty-Hughes","Martin Docherty-Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40770","40770"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525706","2016-06-27","Department for Transport","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of what land is required in (a) the Croydon area and (b) other areas to allow for the Brighton Mainline Upgrade; and whether he plans to safeguard that land for transport purposes.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40729","40729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525707","2016-06-27","Department for Transport","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many incidents involving unmanned drones and aircraft in the proximity of UK airports have been reported in each month in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Martin Docherty-Hughes","Martin Docherty-Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40766","40766"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525708","2016-06-27","Department for Transport","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what guidelines there are for the flying of unmanned drones in the proximity of airports.","Biography information for Martin Docherty-Hughes","Martin Docherty-Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40767","40767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525709","2016-06-27","Department for Transport","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if his Department will promote the provision of seating facilities in public places to encourage walking.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40653","40653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525710","2016-06-27","Department for Transport","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to promote park and stride schemes.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40654","40654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525711","2016-06-27","Department for Transport","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which types of lorries are being used for the delivery of High Speed 2 projects.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40655","40655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525712","2016-06-27","Department for Transport","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions his Department has had with airline operators in response to incidents between unmanned drones and passenger airlines.","Biography information for Martin Docherty-Hughes","Martin Docherty-Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40657","40657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525713","2016-06-27","Department for Transport","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions his Department has had with the Scottish Government on the issue of resilience in the event of a drone collision with a passenger airline in Scottish airspace.","Biography information for Martin Docherty-Hughes","Martin Docherty-Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40658","40658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525714","2016-06-27","Department for Transport","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he has investigated, in his Department's work assessing the reasons for delays and cancellations on the Brighton Mainline, whether or not GTR are preventing staff who took part in recent strike action from working overtime; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40669","40669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525715","2016-06-27","Department for Transport","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he has issued (a) an enforcement order, (b) a provisional enforcement order or a remedial plan notice against Govia Thameslink Railway.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40837","40837"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525716","2016-06-27","Department for Transport","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to encourage ecological diversity along the alignments of motorways and railways.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40838","40838"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525717","2016-06-27","Department for Transport","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the Govia Thameslink Remedial Plan, published on 26 May 2016, which sections of the Freedom of Information Act 2000 related to each redaction in the published version of that document.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40834","40834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525718","2016-06-27","Department for Transport","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent reports he has received on the practice of restricting staff that have recently been on strike from working overtime on (a) Govia Thameslink Railway and (b) other rail franchises.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Mr Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40796","40796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525719","2016-06-27","Department for Transport","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the answer of 13 June 2016 to Question 39848, what the estimated cost to the public purse was of preparing and publishing the Hendry report on Replanning Network Rail's Investment Programme, published on 25 November 2015.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40828","40828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525720","2016-06-27","Department for Transport","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the answer of 13 June 2016 to Question 39849, what his Department's expenditure other than Network Rail expenditure was on the level crossing reform programme in the last Parliament; and how much such expenditure is budgeted in this Parliament.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40827","40827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525721","2016-06-27","Department for Transport","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if his Department will introduce a time scale that insurance companies must comply with for responding to correspondence relating to car accidents.","Biography information for Ben Howlett","Ben Howlett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40840","40840"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525722","2016-06-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many mandatory reconsiderations were submitted in relation to entitlement to disability living allowance for children in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40842","40842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525723","2016-06-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many families have accessed support from the (a) Child Maintenance Service and (b) Child Support Agency in each (i) parliamentary constituency and (ii) local authority in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Peter Grant","Peter Grant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40836","40836"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525724","2016-06-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate has he made of the (a) number and (b) value of programmes commissioned under his Department's Dynamic Purchasing System in (i) Dudley, (ii) the Black Country and (iii) the West Midlands.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40808","40808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525725","2016-06-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of existing claimants of disability living allowance for children were re-assessed and awarded a lower rate of entitlement in the last three years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40646","40646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525726","2016-06-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 27 May 2016 to Question 38024, how many visits to the Pensions Wise website were by consumers seeking pensions advice for personal use.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40756","40756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525727","2016-06-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many referrals of child maintenance debtors to credit reference agencies have been made since the power to do so was introduced in March 2015.","Biography information for Ms Karen Buck","Ms Karen Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40757","40757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525728","2016-06-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many mandatory reconsiderations for re-assessments of entitlement to disability living allowance for children were (a) upheld and (b) rejected in the last three years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40696","40696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525729","2016-06-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many assessments for disability living allowance for children have been conducted in the last three years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40695","40695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525730","2016-06-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what information his Department holds on the number of (a) assistance dogs that are in service and (b) people who are waiting for assistance dogs; and if he will take steps to ensure that demand for assistance dogs is met.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40692","40692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525731","2016-06-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what percentage of disability living allowance for children re-assessments resulted in a change in the award entitlement in the last three years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40693","40693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525732","2016-06-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many re-assessments for people already receiving disability living allowance for children have been conducted in the last three years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40694","40694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/528711","2016-06-27","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans his Department has to maintain a military presence on the site of Kneller Hall in Whitton.","Biography information for Dr Tania Mathias","Dr Tania Mathias","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 905491","905491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/528712","2016-06-27","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent assessment he has made of the security benefits of procuring four Successor submarines.","Biography information for Iain Stewart","Iain Stewart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 905490","905490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/528713","2016-06-27","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent assessment he has made of the progress of the international campaign to defeat ISIS/Daesh.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 905495","905495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/528714","2016-06-27","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to protect members of the armed forces from bullying, sexual abuse and other crimes.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 905488","905488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/528715","2016-06-27","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to protect the armed forces from persistent legal claims.","Biography information for Scott Mann","Scott Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 905497","905497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/528716","2016-06-27","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to promote the welfare of armed forces personnel.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 905494","905494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/528717","2016-06-27","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to support British jobs and industry through its procurement process.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 905492","905492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/528718","2016-06-27","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the projected increase in defence spending during this Parliament.","Biography information for Gareth Johnson","Gareth Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 905493","905493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/528720","2016-06-27","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to improve the standard of housing for service personnel.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 905484","905484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/528989","2016-06-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what discussions he has had with the devolved administrations on implementation of the Apprenticeship Levy.","Biography information for Kirsty Blackman","Kirsty Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 905554","905554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/528990","2016-06-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps the Government is taking to improve broadband access for small businesses.","Biography information for Alex Chalk","Alex Chalk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 905555","905555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/528991","2016-06-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to support British steelmaking.","Biography information for Glyn Davies","Glyn Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 905557","905557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/528992","2016-06-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what his plans are for the future of the Land Registry.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 905556","905556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/528993","2016-06-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that customers are able to receive utility and other bills in paper form on request.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 905552","905552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/528994","2016-06-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to facilitate customers switching suppliers in consumer markets.","Biography information for Jake Berry","Jake Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 905549","905549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/528995","2016-06-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the Government's strategy is for increasing the number of apprenticeships.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 905550","905550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/528996","2016-06-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much the Post Office has spent on refurbishing the Crown Post Office premises in Paisley since January 2010.","Biography information for Mhairi Black","Mhairi Black","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 905548","905548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529339","2016-06-29","Department for International Development","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what programmes her Department supports related to children and religious fundamentalism; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Graham Allen","Mr Graham Allen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 905515","905515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529340","2016-06-29","Department for International Development","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of her Department's work in South Sudan.","Biography information for Sir Oliver Heald","Sir Oliver Heald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 905513","905513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529341","2016-06-29","Department for International Development","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to support the education of girls in developing countries.","Biography information for Antoinette Sandbach","Antoinette Sandbach","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 905516","905516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529342","2016-06-29","Department for International Development","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assistance her Department is providing to Sri Lanka.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 905514","905514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529343","2016-06-29","Department for International Development","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assistance her Department has provided to separatist occupied areas of eastern Ukraine in the last two years.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 905517","905517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529344","2016-06-29","Department for International Development","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent assessment she has made of the effect of UK aid in Syria.","Biography information for Tom Elliott","Tom Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 905519","905519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529345","2016-06-29","Department for International Development","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to ensure cross-departmental coordination of implementation of the Sustainable Development Goals.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 905521","905521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529346","2016-06-29","Department for International Development","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what representations she has made to non-governmental organisations which receive funding from her Department on senior management salaries in those organisations.","Biography information for Derek Thomas","Derek Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 905518","905518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529347","2016-06-29","Department for International Development","2016-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the potential effect of the outcomes of the Anti-Corruption Summit in May 2016 on developing countries.","Biography information for Maggie Throup","Maggie Throup","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 905520","905520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524899","2016-06-27","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to increase accessibility to university buildings for disabled students.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40494","40494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524900","2016-06-27","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to ensure that universities are offering disabled students appropriate levels of support.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40492","40492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524901","2016-06-27","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what representations officials, advisers and Ministers of his Department made to the Competition and Markets Authority on the date of publication of its final report on the energy market.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40499","40499"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524902","2016-06-27","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether he or any of his Ministerial colleagues were consulted by the Competition and Markets Authority on the date upon which it plans to publish its investigation into the energy market.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40500","40500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524903","2016-06-27","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will conduct a review into the effect of the use of payment intermediaries on pay transparency before the end of 2016.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40487","40487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524904","2016-06-27","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 13 June 2016 to Question 39321, what progress his Department has made on plans to diversify the civil service.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40488","40488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524905","2016-06-27","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to tackle late payment of suppliers by businesses.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40643","40643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524906","2016-06-27","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department is taking to implement the recommendations in the first report of the Extractive Industries Transparency Initiative, published in April 2016.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40619","40619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524907","2016-06-27","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the maximum duration should be for a degree apprenticeship.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40634","40634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524908","2016-06-27","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to reduce the gap in apprenticeship completion rates for people who are Black, Asian and Minority Ethnic.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40636","40636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524909","2016-06-27","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what his policy is on whether the cost of degree apprenticeships are supported from the proceeds of the apprenticeship levy.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40637","40637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524910","2016-06-27","Cabinet Office","2016-06-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what processes are in place for strengthening partnerships between law enforcement agencies in the UK and elsewhere in order to tackle international corruption.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40582","40582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524911","2016-06-27","Cabinet Office","2016-06-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what discussions his Department had with business and professional services companies before the Anti-Corruption Summit on 12 May 2016.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40614","40614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524912","2016-06-27","Cabinet Office","2016-06-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether there is a designated team of staff in his Department working solely on anti-corruption issues.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40532","40532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524913","2016-06-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what progress he has made since the Anti-Corruption Summit of 12 May 2016 on implementing the Government's plan to establish central registers of beneficial ownership in the Overseas Territories and Crown Dependencies.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40547","40547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524915","2016-06-27","Cabinet Office","2016-06-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will publish the terms of reference for the Inter-Ministerial Group on Anti-Corruption.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40548","40548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524916","2016-06-27","Cabinet Office","2016-06-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, who is leading the negotiations with the Overseas Territories and Crown Dependencies on sharing beneficial ownership information.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40613","40613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524917","2016-06-27","Cabinet Office","2016-06-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what plans he has to appoint a new Charity Commissioner to replace Peter Clarke.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40510","40510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524918","2016-06-27","HM Treasury","2016-06-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will discuss with the banking sector steps to ensure that individuals seeking to switch their current account are able to access their historical transaction data to better enable them to secure a similar overdraft to their existing one with a new provider.","Biography information for Julian Knight","Julian Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40577","40577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524919","2016-06-27","HM Treasury","2016-06-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether any of the successor organisations to the Money Advice Service will have a specific remit to promote financial education amongst young people.","Biography information for Julian Knight","Julian Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40576","40576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524920","2016-06-27","HM Treasury","2016-06-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether any successor organisations to the Money Advice Service will have a remit to promote financial capability amongst the public.","Biography information for Julian Knight","Julian Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40579","40579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524921","2016-06-27","HM Treasury","2016-06-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the Answer of 18 January 2016 to Question 20373, what criteria he has used to assess the level of competitiveness in the motor insurance market.","Biography information for Rob Marris","Rob Marris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40503","40503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524922","2016-06-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 7 June 2016 to Question 39850, what proportion of the senior civil servants in the Cities and Local Growth Unit of his Department are working on devolution issues are based in London.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40529","40529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524923","2016-06-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 13 June 2016 to Question 39850, what the (a) location and (b) number at each location is of the 60 officials based in six local teams across the country.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40530","40530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524924","2016-06-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to paragraph 7 on page 2 of the National Planning Policy Framework, published in March 2012 whether his Department has made an assessment of the extent to which the UK's carbon budgets and 2050 climate target is taken into account by planning authorities when making planning decisions.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40534","40534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524925","2016-06-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will wait until the Committee on Climate Change report on the compatibility of UK onshore petroleum with meeting UK carbon budgets and the Government's response is published before taking any decision to reverse (a) the planning decision against fracking made by Lancashire County Council and (b) any other planning decisions that are made by local authorities concerning the extraction of shale gas.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40551","40551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524926","2016-06-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what requirements his Department places on local authorities to demonstrate that their Local Plans will meet identified national house-building need.","Biography information for Michael Tomlinson","Michael Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40585","40585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524927","2016-06-27","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to tackle nuisance calls and text messages.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40601","40601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524928","2016-06-27","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether he met the Minister for the Cabinet Office to examine the options for extracting greater public value from Channel 4 between 4 September 2015 and 24 September 2015.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40504","40504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524929","2016-06-27","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department plans to review the role of the Ministry of Defence Police in safeguarding the Trident nuclear deterrent.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40484","40484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524930","2016-06-27","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much the budgeted expenditure is in (a) 2016-17 and (b) 2017-18 on facility improvements at Faslane to support the Trident renewal programme.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40509","40509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524931","2016-06-27","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what training and logistical support the armed forces have provided to Iraqi forces to combat the threat from Daesh in Iraq in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40486","40486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524932","2016-06-27","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much has been invested in facilities at Barrow-in-Furness to support the Trident renewal programme in 2015-16.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40506","40506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524933","2016-06-27","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the budgeted expenditure is in (a) 2016-17 and (b) 2017-18 on facility improvements at Barrow-in-Furness to support the Trident renewal programme.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40507","40507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524934","2016-06-27","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much has been invested on facilities at Faslane to support the Trident renewal programme in 2015-16.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40508","40508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524935","2016-06-27","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will provide details of what (a) ships and (b) aircraft by (i) type and (ii) number are allocated to the Very High Readiness Task Force in 2016-17.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40549","40549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524936","2016-06-27","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent guidelines he has issued to members of the armed forces on registering with a doctor.","Biography information for Steven Paterson","Steven Paterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40612","40612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524937","2016-06-27","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assistance, education and training the Government is providing to the Burmese Army; and whether the Government provides training on human rights and humanitarian obligations.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40600","40600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524938","2016-06-27","Department for Education","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to ensure that all 18 year olds leaving school have the skills to prepare a high quality CV.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40527","40527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524939","2016-06-27","Department for Education","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 27 May 2016 to Question 37443, what guidance her Department provides to school admission authorities on engaging with those people that the Schools Admissions Code requires them to consult.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40533","40533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524940","2016-06-27","Department for Education","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what procedures her Department has in place to scrutinise any possible conflicts of interest that Ofsted inspectors may have when inspecting primary schools; how many Ofsted inspectors are involved in the conversion of primary schools to academies in either an advisory or developmental capacity; and whether Ofsted inspectors are required to inform head teachers that they have an interest in the development of academies prior to conducting an inspection.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40495","40495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524941","2016-06-27","Department for Education","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether Ofsted inspectors are required to have experience of teaching in primary schools prior to becoming an inspector.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40496","40496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524942","2016-06-27","Department for Education","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 8 June 2016 to Question 40028, on investigations into unregistered schools, how many investigations her Department is currently carrying out into unregistered schools in England.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40497","40497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524943","2016-06-27","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether she plans to make a statement to the House on the publication of the final report into the energy market from the Competition and Markets Authority.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40501","40501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524944","2016-06-27","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what representations officials, advisers and Ministers in her Department made to the Competition and Markets Authority on the date of publication of its final report on the energy market.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40517","40517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524945","2016-06-27","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether she or any of her ministerial colleagues were consulted by the Competition and Markets Authority on the date on which it plans to publish its investigation into the energy market.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40518","40518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524946","2016-06-27","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 23 May 2016 to Question 39080, if she will make it her  policy to lay the Committee on Climate Change report on the compatibility of UK onshore petroleum with meeting UK carbon budgets and the Government's response before Parliament prior to any decision is taken to reverse (a) the planning decision against fracking made by Lancashire County Council and (b) any other planning decisions that are made by local authorities concerning the extraction of shale gas.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40552","40552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524947","2016-06-27","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what consideration she has given to extending the support of biomass after 2027 to treat it equally with other low-carbon technologies.","Biography information for Nigel Adams","Nigel Adams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40554","40554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524948","2016-06-27","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 9 June 2016 to Question 39039, whether she will place the results of the Civil Nuclear Constabulary May 2015 Wellbeing Survey in the Library.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40555","40555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524949","2016-06-27","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, when her Department plans to publish the terms of reference for its Triennial Review of the Coal Authority; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40621","40621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524950","2016-06-27","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, with reference to the Answer of 12 May 2016 to Question 36652 on biofuel, whether her Department has undertaken to consider whether it is appropriate for biomass conversions to compete alongside offshore wind or the allocation pot for established technologies.","Biography information for Nigel Adams","Nigel Adams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40628","40628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524951","2016-06-27","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment she has made of the potential effect of a vote to leave the EU on the involvement of UK organisations in (a) the European Safeguards Research and Development Association and (b) the European Nuclear Safety Regulators Group.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40602","40602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524952","2016-06-27","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, with reference to the European Council decision of October 2014 on a Climate and Energy Policy Framework to set EU-wide energy targets for 2030, what assessment she has made of the potential effect of a vote to leave the EU on the UK (a) reducing greenhouse gas emissions by at least 40 per cent by 2030, (b) making the target for renewable energy at least 27 per cent and (c) meeting the indicative energy efficiency target of at least 27 per cent.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40603","40603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524953","2016-06-27","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to (a) ratify the Cape Town agreement and (b) otherwise tackle illegal, unreported and unregulated fishing in the High Seas.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40627","40627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524954","2016-06-27","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether she plans to prohibit the import of trophies from any CITES  Appendix I or Appendix II listed species.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40644","40644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524955","2016-06-27","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the Answer of 19 January 2016 to Question 22080, when the Environment Agency will be consulting on the proposals to modernise the rod licence service.","Biography information for Simon Hart","Simon Hart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40642","40642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524956","2016-06-27","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 13 June 2016 to Question 39933, how much funding has been allocated to anti-beaching initiatives; and which countries have been identified as containing beaching hotspots.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40493","40493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524957","2016-06-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will raise the issue of attacks on and murders of people with albinism with his counterparts in sub-Saharan African countries.","Biography information for Mark Pritchard","Mark Pritchard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40481","40481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524958","2016-06-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Democratic Republic of Congo counterpart on ensuring that elections in that country are open and transparent.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40472","40472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524959","2016-06-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to ensure the constructive engagement of the Saudi-led coalition with the UN on the question of its de-listing as a state or armed group that violates children's rights during conflict.","Biography information for Jo Cox","Jo Cox","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40580","40580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524960","2016-06-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his Bahraini counterpart on the prison sentence handed down to Sheikh Ali Salman; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40624","40624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524961","2016-06-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what estimate his Department has made of the number of British nationals living (a) outside the UK and in the EU and (b) outside the UK and the EU; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40539","40539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524962","2016-06-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the potential role of the UK in reducing the number of people trying to cross the Mediterranean in dangerous circumstances; and what plans he has to tackle the issue of deaths in the Mediterranean of people attempting to make that crossing.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40520","40520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524963","2016-06-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with the government of Bahrain on the imprisonment of Sheikh Ali Salman in that country.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40543","40543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524964","2016-06-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with the government of Bahrain on recent travel bans imposed on Bahraini citizens.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40544","40544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524965","2016-06-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the government of Bahrain on the re-arrest of Nabeel Rajab in that country.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40545","40545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524966","2016-06-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the government of Bahrain on the suspension of the main Shia opposition group in that country.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40546","40546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524967","2016-06-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to his Burmese counterpart on (a) releasing people detained for the exercise of their human rights and (b) dropping charges pending against those who are facing imprisonment simply for the exercise of these rights.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40598","40598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524968","2016-06-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what his Department's five-year strategy and vision statement objectives are for (a) South Georgia and South Sandwich Islands and (b) Ascension Island.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40622","40622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524969","2016-06-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the effect of the temporary removal of the Saudi-led coalition from the UN's list of states and armed groups that violate children's rights during conflict on the integrity and effectiveness of UN Security Council measures on children and armed conflict.","Biography information for Jo Cox","Jo Cox","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40581","40581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524970","2016-06-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many officials are employed in (a) his Department's London offices and (b) the UK's global diplomatic network work on climate security.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40591","40591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524971","2016-06-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his Bahraini counterpart on restrictions on freedom of assembly and expression in that country.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40596","40596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524972","2016-06-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his Bahraini counterpart on the relocation of citizenship of Bahraini nationals.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40595","40595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524973","2016-06-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to ensure that the Burmese government relaunches the Prisoner of Conscience Affairs Committee or establishes a new Committee with a mandate to review the cases of people charged or deprived of their liberty for the exercise of their human rights.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40597","40597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524974","2016-06-27","Department of Health","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 28 April 2016 to Question 35252, how many staff within the scope of the HM Treasury guidance on senior off-payroll engagements were paid off-payroll in (a) NHS trusts in 2013-14 and (b) NHS foundation trusts in 2012-13.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40583","40583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524975","2016-06-27","Department of Health","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Answer of 28 April 2016 to Question 35252, when he expects data to be published on the number of off-payroll staff within the scope of the HM Treasury guidance on senior off-payroll engagements in NHS foundation trusts in 2014-15.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40584","40584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524976","2016-06-27","Department of Health","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidance (a) his Department and (b) NHS England have provided to Sustainability and Transformation footprint teams on involving university providers in the development of Sustainability and Transformation Plans.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40616","40616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524977","2016-06-27","Department of Health","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of ending the NHS bursary system on the Capital Nurse project in London.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40617","40617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524978","2016-06-27","Department of Health","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the effect on the role of chief nursing officer will be of the decision to abolish the nursing, midwifery and allied health professionals policy unit.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40630","40630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524979","2016-06-27","Department of Health","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that survivors of female genital mutilation are better protected from cervical cancer.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40632","40632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524980","2016-06-27","Department of Health","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, for what reasons his Department discontinued the nursing, midwifery and allied health professionals policy unit; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40631","40631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524981","2016-06-27","Department of Health","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which people and organisations his Department consulted (a) before and (b) after the announcement of 25 November 2015 to end NHS bursaries for nursing, midwifery and allied health professional students.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40535","40535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524982","2016-06-27","Department of Health","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many secondary breast cancer nurses there are in England.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40536","40536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524983","2016-06-27","Department of Health","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of the potential number of redundancies which will result from the decision to abolish the nursing, midwifery and allied health professions policy unit.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40537","40537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524984","2016-06-27","Department of Health","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he plans additional changes in funding for child and adult mental health services.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40521","40521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524985","2016-06-27","Department of Health","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the incidence of cervical cancer for women over 50 years old was in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Teresa Pearce","Teresa Pearce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40522","40522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524986","2016-06-27","Department of Health","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of women aged 50 or older received cervical screening in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Teresa Pearce","Teresa Pearce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40505","40505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524987","2016-06-27","Department of Health","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether any patients were sent out of Cornwall for kidney dialysis treatment in each of the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40516","40516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524988","2016-06-27","Department of Health","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of the number of healthcare professionals trained to fit intra-uterine methods of contraception.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40524","40524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524989","2016-06-27","Department of Health","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans the Government has to ensure that people diagnosed with secondary breast cancer have access to a clinical nurse specialist as part of their care.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40561","40561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524990","2016-06-27","Department of Health","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many additional providers his Department estimates will enter the higher education sector to deliver health, nursing and midwifery courses in the academic years (a) 2017-18, (b) 2018-19, (c) 2019-20 and (d) 2020-21.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40566","40566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524991","2016-06-27","Department of Health","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients with a diagnosis of secondary breast cancer have a named clinical nurse specialist as part of their care in (a) England and (b) Ellesmere Port and Neston constituency.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40559","40559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524992","2016-06-27","Department of Health","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if the Government will ensure that enough nurses in future train to be clinical nurse specialists for (a) cancer, (b) breast cancer and (c) secondary breast cancer.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40560","40560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524993","2016-06-27","Department of Health","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, who will be responsible for higher education placements for (a) allied health, (b) nursing and (c) midwifery in 2017-18.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40562","40562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524994","2016-06-27","Department of Health","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that medical personnel are trained to carry out appropriate smear tests for female genital mutilation survivors.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40641","40641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524995","2016-06-27","Department of Health","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department plans to allocate additional funds to resource the 10,000 additional student placements for nursing, midwifery and allied health courses that his Department estimates will be created following the switch to student loans; and whether he plans to nominate any bodies to which these funds may be allocated in the academic years (a) 2017-18, (b) 2018-19, (c) 2019-20 and (d) 2020-21.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40563","40563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524996","2016-06-27","Department of Health","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department plans to ring-fence funds to resource the 10,000 additional student placements for nursing, midwifery and allied health courses that his Department estimates will be created following the switch to student loans.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40564","40564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524997","2016-06-27","Department of Health","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he plans to issue guidance on the additional placement numbers for nursing, midwifery and allied health courses to be made available by 2017-18.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40565","40565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524998","2016-06-27","Department of Health","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 23 May 2016 to Question 37279, if he will make it his policy to ensure there is a formal public consultation on every Sustainability and Transformation Plan footprint.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40553","40553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524999","2016-06-27","Department of Health","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Department's Framework for Sexual Health Promotion in England, published in March 2013, what steps he has taken to ensure that arrangements are put in place for continuing professional development of the sexual health workforce.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40556","40556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525000","2016-06-27","Department of Health","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of the number of alternative providers entering the higher education sector to deliver health, nursing and allied health courses which will be (a) private and (b) for-profit.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40557","40557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525001","2016-06-27","Department of Health","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many civil service employees of his Department were based in Coventry in each of the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40574","40574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525002","2016-06-27","Department of Health","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with appropriate clinical bodies on the potential use of oxygen bubbles and nutrients as part of treatment for cancer.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40473","40473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525003","2016-06-27","Department of Health","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions he has had with appropriate clinical bodies on the effectiveness of treatment with statins for people aged 60 and over.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40476","40476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525004","2016-06-27","Department of Health","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he expects the balloon device to be available through the NHS for people with diabetes.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40477","40477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525005","2016-06-27","Department of Health","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many women have been diagnosed with MRKH syndrome in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40478","40478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525006","2016-06-27","Department of Health","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with appropriate clinical bodies on the provision of ovary transplants.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40479","40479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525007","2016-06-27","Department of Health","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect of prescription charges on the ability of people with long-term medical conditions to manage their condition effectively.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40490","40490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525008","2016-06-27","Department of Health","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many kidney transplants took place by region for which the source of the donated kidney was (a) cadaver, (b) a relative and (c) altruism in each of the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40515","40515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525009","2016-06-27","Department of Health","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients from Cornwall who were able to access a kidney transplant took the option of conservative care in each of the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40513","40513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525010","2016-06-27","Department of Health","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the need to provide additional kidney organ donation surgery as a result of the change to an opt-out system in Wales; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40514","40514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525011","2016-06-27","Department of Health","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which locations have provided renal dialysis in Cornwall; how many dialysis patients attended each such location; what transport charges were made to patients attending each location in each of the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40512","40512"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525012","2016-06-27","Home Office","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that local police forces have sufficient resources and powers to deal with the misuse of scrambler bikes on public roads.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40485","40485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525013","2016-06-27","Home Office","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the number of convicted football hooligans who have surrendered their passports (a) voluntarily and (b) otherwise in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40541","40541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525014","2016-06-27","Home Office","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when the Government plans to respond to the consultation on unexplained wealth orders.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40618","40618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525015","2016-06-27","Home Office","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what mechanisms there are to support discussions between members of the Common Travel Area on the operation of that area.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40610","40610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525016","2016-06-27","Home Office","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many meetings she and ministers of her Department have had with their Irish counterparts on the Common Travel Area arrangements since 2010.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40606","40606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525017","2016-06-27","Ministry of Justice","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with which other EU countries the UK does not have arrangements for the return of non-UK nationals to prisons in their country of origin.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40607","40607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525018","2016-06-27","Department for International Development","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 5 March 2014, to Question 902851, what steps her Department has taken to ensure that the 12 collaborative TB-HIV activities recommended by the World Health Organisation are being implemented through its bilateral programmes; and what assessment has been made of the effect to date of the steps taken.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40615","40615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525019","2016-06-27","Department for International Development","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what support her Department is giving to Eastern Kachin and Northern Shan states in Burma.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40599","40599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525020","2016-06-27","Department for International Development","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to reduce the number of attacks on and murder of people with albinism in sub-Saharan African countries.","Biography information for Mark Pritchard","Mark Pritchard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40480","40480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525021","2016-06-27","Ministry of Justice","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to his Department's survey on legal aid for domestic violence victims in private family law cases, what plans his Department has to launch a full consultation on that subject.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40498","40498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525022","2016-06-27","Ministry of Justice","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been (a) convicted and (b) jailed for football hooliganism in each of the last 20 years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40540","40540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525023","2016-06-27","Ministry of Justice","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department is taking to improve the provision of meaningful employment to prisoners in all categories of prison.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40526","40526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525024","2016-06-27","Ministry of Justice","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the cost to the public purse was of the case in the Court of Appeal (civil division) on appeal from High Court Queen's Bench Division, Divisional Court between the Queen (on the application of Rights of Women) and the Lord Chancellor and Secretary of State for Justice, 2015, Ewhc 35 (Admin).","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40550","40550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525025","2016-06-27","Ministry of Justice","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps the Government has taken to provide guidance to unrepresented defendants.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40571","40571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525026","2016-06-27","Ministry of Justice","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of unrepresented defendants were unrepresented because they (a) failed to meet the legal aid merits test, (b) failed to meet the legal aid means test and (c) chose to defend themselves in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40572","40572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525027","2016-06-27","Ministry of Justice","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many unrepresented defendants there were in the (a) magistrates' courts and (b) Crown courts.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40573","40573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525028","2016-06-27","Ministry of Justice","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what reforms have been put in place in the six early adopter reform prisons to tackle (a) self-harm, (b) prisoner on prisoner violence, (c) assaults on staff and (d) use of new psychoactive substances; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40611","40611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525029","2016-06-27","Ministry of Justice","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will publish the criteria used to select the six early adopter reform prisons.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40567","40567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525030","2016-06-27","Ministry of Justice","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when he plans to publish the Prison Reform Bill.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40568","40568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525031","2016-06-27","Ministry of Justice","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many men have been found guilty of offences under Section 53A of the Sexual Offences Act 2003 as amended by Section 14 of the Policing and Crime Act 2009 since 1 April 2010; and what sentence was imposed in each such case.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40623","40623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525032","2016-06-27","Ministry of Justice","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the cost to the public purse was of repairs to cells and prisoner accommodation required because of acts of arson in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40569","40569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525033","2016-06-27","Ministry of Justice","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps the Government has taken to monitor the proportion of defendants who are unrepresented.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40570","40570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525034","2016-06-27","Northern Ireland Office","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many non-UK nationals have been transferred from a prison in England and Wales to a prison in Northern Ireland in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40604","40604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525035","2016-06-27","Northern Ireland Office","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what recent discussions she has had with the Northern Ireland Executive on the proposed British Bill of Rights.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40608","40608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525036","2016-06-27","Northern Ireland Office","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what discussions she has had with the Northern Ireland Executive on arrangements for the return of non-UK nationals to prisons in their country of origin.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40609","40609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525037","2016-06-27","Northern Ireland Office","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what recent representations she has received on the membership of the Parades Commission.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40605","40605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525038","2016-06-27","Northern Ireland Office","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what recent assessment she has made of the potential terror threat to the UK posed by people entering Northern Ireland via the land border with the Republic of Ireland.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40483","40483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525039","2016-06-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the oral contribution of the Prime Minister of 11 April 2016, Official Report, columns 23-26, on the Panama Papers, whether UK law enforcement agencies will have automatic access to central registers of beneficial ownership, or equivalent platforms, in the Overseas Territories and Crown dependencies once those registers or platforms have been established.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40531","40531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525040","2016-06-27","Department for Transport","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many of his Department's civil servants were based in Coventry in each of the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40542","40542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525041","2016-06-27","Department for Transport","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many responses his Department has received to the open consultation on the InterCity West Coast rail franchise to date; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40538","40538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525042","2016-06-28","Department for Transport","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make it his policy to bring the date at which a motor vehicle is treated by the Government as historic for MOT purposes into line with the date at which the Government regards a vehicle as historic for vehicle excise duty purposes; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40519","40519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525043","2016-06-27","Department for Transport","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what proportion of trains (a) cancelled and (b) delayed have not seen Govia Thameslink Railway financially penalised in the last three years.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40640","40640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525044","2016-06-27","Department for Transport","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the pothole fund may be used to reward the use and development of innovative resurfacing practices by local authorities.","Biography information for Alex Chalk","Alex Chalk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40625","40625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525045","2016-06-27","Department for Transport","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to promote the use of talking buses in (a) the UK, (b) the West Midlands and (c) Solihull.","Biography information for Julian Knight","Julian Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40578","40578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525046","2016-06-27","Department for Transport","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to increase cycling provision in Dorset.","Biography information for Michael Tomlinson","Michael Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40575","40575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525047","2016-06-27","Department for Transport","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much his Department has received in credit card fees from people renewing vehicle tax online in the years (a) 2013-14, (b) 2014-15 and (c) 2015-16.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40558","40558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525048","2016-06-27","Department for Transport","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he plans to issue the invitation to tender for the South Western rail franchise; and whether the delay to date in issuing it will affect the scheduled dates for the award and start of the franchise agreement.","Biography information for Mrs Maria Miller","Mrs Maria Miller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40511","40511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525049","2016-06-27","Department for Transport","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions he has had with airline companies on the provision of bad or adverse weather training for airline staff.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40474","40474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525050","2016-06-27","Department for Transport","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions he has had with airline companies on the provision of training for pilots on the use of radar.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40475","40475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525051","2016-06-27","Department for Transport","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 14 June 2016 to Question 39602, what assessment he has made of the extent to which carrying out roadworks consecutively would reduce annual average individual journey times.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40489","40489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525052","2016-06-27","Department for Transport","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, for what reasons representatives of HS2 Ltd told residents of Rixton at a recent meeting in Culcheth that a viaduct would definitely be built in their parish.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40491","40491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525053","2016-06-27","Department for Transport","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 8 June 2016 to Question 39128, how the conversion of the Great Western Main Line Class 801 units to bi-mode diesel operation will be funded; and how his Department will recover such conversion costs.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40482","40482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525054","2016-06-27","Department for Transport","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 14 June 2016 to Question 40199, whether the modelling was (a) carried out in-house by Network Rail or (b) outsourced by Network Rail to another party; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40629","40629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525055","2016-06-27","Department for Transport","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when his Department expects the Bus Services Bill draft statutory guidance to be published.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40586","40586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525056","2016-06-27","Department for Transport","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when his Department expects the Bus Services Bill impact assessments to be published.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40587","40587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525057","2016-06-27","Department for Transport","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to paragraph 4.30 of his Department's Bus reform workshops: background document, published in September 2015, if he plans to devolve the bus service operators grant to those local authorities granted franchising powers in the Bus Services Bill.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40588","40588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525058","2016-06-27","Department for Transport","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer to Question 39527, (a) for what reasons and (b) what the evidential basis is for the decision that the commissioning and provision of bus services should be kept separate.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40589","40589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525059","2016-06-27","Department for Transport","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what representations he has received from (a) private bus operators, (b) municipal bus operators and (c) local authorities on Clause 21 of the Bus Services Bill.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40590","40590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525060","2016-06-27","Department for Transport","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, under what circumstances financial penalties could be levied against Govia Thameslink Railway for (a) punctuality problems and (b) cancellations.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40638","40638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525061","2016-06-27","Department for Transport","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the cost to the public purse has been of Network Rail paying fines to Govia Thameslink Railway under the Track Access Agreement in the last three years.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40639","40639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525062","2016-06-27","Department for Transport","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that the taxi driver licensing process provides more awareness to taxi drivers of the requirements to take guide and other service dogs in their vehicles.","Biography information for Julian Knight","Julian Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40620","40620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525063","2016-06-27","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to the report, Boys to Men: The under achievement of young men in higher education, published by the Higher Education Policy Institute in May 2016, what steps the Government is taking to increase (a) the level of achievement of young men in higher education and (b) male entry rates into higher education.","Biography information for Karl McCartney","Karl McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40523","40523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525064","2016-06-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many (a) consultancy firms and (b) people have been employed by his Department to work on the Universal Credit programme in (i) the 2015-16 financial year and (ii) this financial year to date; and how much his Department has spent on those firms and people in those financial years.","Biography information for Dame Margaret Hodge","Margaret Hodge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40525","40525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525065","2016-06-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make it his policy to reimburse personal independent payment (PIP) claimants for any additional costs those claimants incur between (a) an appeal or mandatory reconsideration being applied for and (b) a decision being overturned on the award of the enhanced rate mobility component of PIP.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40528","40528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525066","2016-06-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Answer of 10 May 2016 to Question 35981, in what proportion of cases where his Department requested evidence from a healthcare professional to inform a work capability assessment was the claimant awarded employment and support allowance in (a) 2013-14, (b) 2014-15 and (c) 2015-16.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40626","40626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525067","2016-06-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many employment and support allowance claimants in Hove have been reimbursed for travel to the Lewes Assessment Centre since November 2015.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40502","40502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525068","2016-06-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many of his Department's full-time equivalent officials have been working on Access to Work policy and administration in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40633","40633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525069","2016-06-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether people who may be eligible for support through Access to Work are informed of this when they enter the Work Programme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40635","40635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525070","2016-06-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many requests from his Department for evidence to inform a personal independence payment (a) assessment and (b) mandatory reconsideration were (i) made and (ii) responded to by GPs and other professionals in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40592","40592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525071","2016-06-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will publish the data his Department holds on requests, decisions and outcomes for mandatory reconsideration of personal independence payments.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40594","40594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525072","2016-06-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Answer of 10 May 2016 to Question 35981, in what proportion of cases where his Department made no request for evidence from a healthcare professional to inform a work capability assessment was the claimant awarded employment and support allowance in (a) 2013-14, (b) 2014-15 and (c) 2015-16.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40593","40593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524635","2016-06-27","Home Office","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment she has made of the morale of police officers (a) nationally and (b) at force level; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40270","40270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524636","2016-06-27","Home Office","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to (a) attract, recruit and retain high-quality police officers and (b) offer such officers career development.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40271","40271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524637","2016-06-27","Home Office","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment has been made of the adequacy of staffing levels in Police Public Protection Units at (a) UK and (b) force level.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40272","40272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524638","2016-06-27","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to the report by Lord Heseltine, entitled Tees Valley: opportunity unlimited, published in June 2016, recommendation 6.6.7, whether he plans to devolve responsibility for the Apprenticeship Grant for Employers to the Tees Valley Combined Authority.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40293","40293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524639","2016-06-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the new Apprenticeship Levy on the number of apprenticeship start-ups from September 2016.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40284","40284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524640","2016-06-27","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 3 June 2016 to Question 37744, on property: ownership, on what date (a) his Department will begin to consult on the detail of the policy and (b) that consultation will end.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40364","40364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524641","2016-06-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether his Department has made an estimate of the potential number of jobs which will be replaced by automation over the next two decades.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40325","40325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524642","2016-06-27","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the operational readiness of the Student Loans Company to administer postgraduate loan applications between June and October 2016.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40420","40420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524643","2016-06-27","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether a dedicated hotline for postgraduate loan applicants will be established by the Student Loans Company.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40421","40421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524644","2016-06-27","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the expected take-up of postgraduate loans by (a) UK and (b) EU students in (i) 2017-18 and (ii) 2018-19; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40422","40422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524645","2016-06-27","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the additional staffing and resources required by the Student Loans Company for administration and postgraduate loan applications from October 2016.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40423","40423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524646","2016-06-27","Cabinet Office","2016-06-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many women aged under 50 died as a result of breast cancer in England in (a) 2012, (b) 2013 and (c) 2014.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40468","40468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524647","2016-06-27","Cabinet Office","2016-06-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many women died as a result of breast cancer in England in (a) 2012, (b) 2013 and (c) 2014.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40469","40469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524648","2016-06-15","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many copies of The Gazette at what cost are printed each day.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40336","40336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524649","2016-06-27","Cabinet Office","2016-06-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many meetings of the Inter-Ministerial Group on Clean Growth have discussed the fifth carbon budget since November 2015; and which departments have been involved in those meetings.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40408","40408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524650","2016-06-15","Home Office","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the Civil Contingencies Unit has made an assessment of the implications for its CBRNE defense policies of the findings of the PRACTICE EU project on the different public reactions to industrial or transport accidents and terrorist incidents, referred to in oral evidence to the Science and Technology Committee on 7 June 2016.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40413","40413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524651","2016-06-15","Cabinet Office","2016-06-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, where the planned International Anti-Corruption Coordination Centre will be based.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40310","40310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524652","2016-06-15","Cabinet Office","2016-06-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, on what date the Inter-Ministerial Group on Corruption last met.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40311","40311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524653","2016-06-27","Cabinet Office","2016-06-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether the Anti-Corruption Champion is paid a salary for that role.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40277","40277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524654","2016-06-27","HM Treasury","2016-06-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to reduce the amount of correspondence not yet dealt with at the HM Revenue and Customs Stamp Duty office.","Biography information for Gordon Henderson","Gordon Henderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40407","40407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524655","2016-06-15","HM Treasury","2016-06-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, for what reasons the income of the highest-earning parent is used to assess eligibility for child benefit rather than the joint incomes of both parents.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40400","40400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524656","2016-06-15","HM Treasury","2016-06-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment he has made of the potential effect on the UK economy of the increase in corporate debt in China.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40326","40326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524657","2016-06-15","HM Treasury","2016-06-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many enquiries have been made by hon. Members to HM Revenue and Customs on tax credits claims by (a) e-mail, (b) telephone and (c) letter in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40335","40335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524658","2016-06-27","HM Treasury","2016-06-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 26 May 2016 to Question 38066, what the (a) number, (b) current responsibilities and (c) current locations are of any National Savings and Investment roles undertaken by employees of Atos which are planned to be off-shored.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40453","40453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524659","2016-06-27","HM Treasury","2016-06-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make an estimate of the effect on the public purse of the effects on the life chances of residents of the services and support provided through supported housing; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Peter Aldous","Peter Aldous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40419","40419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524660","2016-06-15","Church Commissioners","2016-06-13","To ask the right hon. Member for Meriden, representing the Church Commissioners, if the Church of England will make an assessment of the effect of austerity on communities in the most deprived areas as measured by the English Indices of Deprivation 2015.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40353","40353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524661","2016-06-15","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment his Department has made of the effectiveness of local authorities in processing and deciding planning applications within recommended timescales.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40381","40381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524662","2016-06-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he expects his Department to submit a final estimate of the damage caused by flooding in the South Lakes area to the European Commission as part of the UK's application to the EU Solidarity Fund.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40274","40274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524663","2016-06-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of housing benefit payments is made to non-British nationals in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40442","40442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524664","2016-06-27","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of moving television from broadcast spectrum to other delivery mechanisms.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40428","40428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524665","2016-06-27","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the effect of telephone design on whether the mobile coverage detailed in Ofcom's published maps of coverage is attainable.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40424","40424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524666","2016-06-27","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will publish a long-term spectrum plan for broadcast television.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40425","40425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524667","2016-06-27","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of common coverage planning for mobile services similar to that undertaken by the broadcast industry.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40426","40426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524668","2016-06-27","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment his Department or Ofcom has made of the effect on consumers of data leakage (a) between applications on a consumer device and (b) between a consumer's device and application servers.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40427","40427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524669","2016-06-15","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, in how many local authority areas in (a) London and (b) England broadband speeds are below the recommended speed as advised by Ofcom.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40317","40317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524670","2016-06-15","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether 77th Brigade's full operating capability has been met.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40346","40346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524671","2016-06-15","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what expertise on Russia is required of members of the 77th Brigade; what the operational deployment standards are of that brigade; and how many members of that brigade were recruited from the Reserves.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40340","40340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524672","2016-06-15","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many members of the (a) Royal Navy and (b) Royal Air Force are deployed to the 77th Brigade.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40342","40342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524673","2016-06-15","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which languages to what level members of the 77th Brigade speak.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40341","40341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524674","2016-06-15","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the doctrine and concepts are of the 77th Brigade; and how those doctrines and concepts were developed.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40343","40343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524675","2016-06-15","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what discussions he has had with his (a) US counterpart and (b) other NATO counterparts on the role of the 77th Brigade.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40344","40344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524676","2016-06-15","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what (a) exercises and (b) deployments the 77th Brigade has conducted in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40345","40345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524677","2016-06-15","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many and what proportion of aircraft in the Voyager surge fleet has been used by the Royal Air Force in each month since the first aircraft of that fleet was delivered.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40378","40378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524678","2016-06-27","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the oral contribution of the Minister of State, Earl Howe, House of Lords Official Report, 27 April 2016, column 1202, when the new crime registrar for the service police will be appointed.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40402","40402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524679","2016-06-27","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the oral contribution of the Minister of State, Earl Howe, House of Lords Official Report, 27 April 2016, column 1201, and his announcement of a review by the Service Justice Board into the procedures for handling allegations of sexual assault in the armed forces, what the (a) current membership of the Service Justice Board is and (b) terms of that review are.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40403","40403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524680","2016-06-15","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what changes his Department plans to make to the size of the workforce of the Ministry of Defence Police.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40416","40416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524681","2016-06-15","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the annual cost is of safeguarding the Trident nuclear deterrent.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40417","40417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524682","2016-06-15","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the effect of changes to the size of the workforce of the Ministry of Defence Police on (a) public safety and (b) safeguarding the Trident nuclear deterrent.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40414","40414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524683","2016-06-27","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what information his Department holds on which organisations have offered mental health support to veterans in (a) England, (b) Merseyside and (c) Liverpool in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40418","40418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524684","2016-06-15","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Ministry of Defence Police officers are employed in safeguarding the Trident nuclear deterrent.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40415","40415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524685","2016-06-27","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the oral evidence given by Duncan McPhee to the Defence Committee on 7 June 2016, HC221, at Question 120, what discussions his Department has had with other public bodies on increasing the number of apprenticeships in the shipbuilding industry; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40449","40449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524686","2016-06-27","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the oral evidence given by Lord West of Spithead to the Defence Committee on 7 June 2016, HC 221, at Question 20, what current budget is allocated to procurement of and building Type 26 frigates; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40450","40450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524687","2016-06-27","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the oral evidence given by Sir Mark Stanhope to the Defence Committee on 7 June 2016, HC 221, at Question 3, what anti-submarine warfare capability is planned for the general purpose frigates; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40451","40451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524688","2016-06-27","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the oral evidence given by Peter Roberts to the Defence Committee on 7 June 2016, HC 221, at Question 22, what the timetable is for (a) procurement of the Type 26 frigates and (b) cutting steel on those frigates; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40452","40452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524689","2016-06-27","Department for Education","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 23 May 2016 to Question 37381, if she will publish the pre-opening costs of free schools by each category of expenditure commonly incurred in the pre-opening stage.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40438","40438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524690","2016-06-15","Department for Education","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to close attainment gaps between the best and worst performing local authority areas as judged by GCSE and A Level results.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40393","40393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524691","2016-06-15","Department for Education","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what information her Department holds on the number of young people who are cared for in (a) local authority-run and (b) private or voluntary sector children's homes in each local authority area.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40397","40397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524692","2016-06-15","Department for Education","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many special needs schools offer (a) before-school care, (b) after-school care and (c) both before and after-school care in England; and what proportion of special needs schools each of those numbers represents.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40399","40399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524693","2016-06-15","Department for Education","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how her Department collects the vacancy rates of individual (a) maintained schools and (b) academies.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40352","40352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524694","2016-06-15","Department for Education","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many foreign languages have been available at (a) GCSE and (b) A-Level in each of the last 10 years; and how many such languages will be available at both levels of examination in each of the next three academic years.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40316","40316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524695","2016-06-15","Department for Education","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what funding her Department has allocated to schools in (a) Calderdale and (b) West Yorkshire to tackle bullying in the last (i) 12 months and (ii) five years.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40382","40382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524696","2016-06-15","Department for Education","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment her Department has made of the number of teachers who have left that profession in each of the last five years; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40307","40307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524697","2016-06-15","Department for Education","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what comparative assessment she has made of trends in teachers' salaries and the average salary in the UK in each of the last five years; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40302","40302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524698","2016-06-15","Department for Education","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will estimate the cost of providing free school meals to children of people in receipt of universal credit upon the full roll-out of that benefit; and what the cost was of the provision of such free school meals to children of people in receipt of benefits prior to the roll-out of universal credit.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40283","40283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524699","2016-06-15","Department for Education","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the extent of changes in the workload of teachers arising from the new Key Stage 1 and Key Stage 2 testing regime.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40285","40285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524700","2016-06-27","Department for Education","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether any limits are placed on the funds academies can spend on marketing.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40298","40298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524701","2016-06-27","Department for Education","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much was spent by academies on marketing and public relations in each of the most recent five years for which figures are available; and how much of that spending came from (a) public funding and (b) other sources.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40299","40299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524702","2016-06-27","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate she has made of the proportion of UK energy consumption that was supplied by other countries in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40278","40278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524703","2016-06-27","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate she has made of the proportion of UK energy consumption which will be supplied from other countries in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40279","40279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524704","2016-06-27","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if she will require EDF Energy to restore the land cleared and prepared for the construction of the Hinkley C nuclear plant to its previous condition in the event of the EDF Board deciding not to take a Final Investment Decision on the plant.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40372","40372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524705","2016-06-27","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the implications for Government policy on carbon capture and storage (CCS) are of the decision not to proceed with the CCS Commercialisation Commission.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40370","40370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524706","2016-06-27","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate she has made of the cost of energy imports by the UK in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40363","40363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524707","2016-06-15","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps the Government is taking to bring the cost of pre-payment meters into line with other payment methods such as direct debit.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40314","40314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524708","2016-06-15","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many UK Government officials and from which departments attended the Bonn intersessional UN climate meeting in (a) May 2016, (b) October 2015 and (c) June 2015.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40401","40401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524709","2016-06-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, which authorities she has directed since May 2015 to prepare a report assessing and managing their level of climate risk under Section 62 of the Climate Change Act 2008.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40434","40434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524710","2016-06-15","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 7 June 2016 to Question 38382, whether the European Commission's proposal of 10 June 2016 on ratification of the Paris Agreement has changed the Government's timeline for UK ratification of that agreement.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40432","40432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524711","2016-06-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to encourage local authorities to adopt proactive enforcement policies to help combat fly-tipping.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40394","40394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524712","2016-06-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to encourage recycling by local authorities.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40395","40395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524713","2016-06-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 7 June 2016 to Question 38501, when she plans to finalise the budget allocation for the Waste and Resources Action Programme for the financial years beyond 2016-17; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40412","40412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524714","2016-06-27","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many gamma interferon tests for bovine TB were conducted in the (a) high risk area, (b) low risk area and (c) edge area of England in each year between 2009 and 2015.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40362","40362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524715","2016-06-27","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when she expects her Department to have collated and put in a format ready to send all the information required by the Certification and Accreditation Administration of the People's Republic of China following its inspections of UK pig trotter production plants in April 2015.","Biography information for Graham Stuart","Graham Stuart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40355","40355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524716","2016-06-27","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when she expects to have obtained all the information required by the Certification and Accreditation Administration of the People's Republic of China for the final response to the inspection report in connection with the export of pig trotters to China.","Biography information for Graham Stuart","Graham Stuart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40356","40356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524717","2016-06-27","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether the British delegation to the G20 agriculture ministers' meeting held on 3 June 2016 in China raised with its Chinese counterparts the matter of the continued delay to the implementation of the protocol allowing pig trotters to be exported from the UK to China.","Biography information for Graham Stuart","Graham Stuart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40357","40357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524718","2016-06-15","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he plans to extend the remit of his Department's Blacknest verification centre to verify nuclear disarmament and warhead dismantlement.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40354","40354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524719","2016-06-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with the Brazilian government on ensuring adequate security for the Rio 2016 Olympic and Paralympic Games.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40396","40396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524720","2016-06-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the oral contribution of the Minister for Europe of 8 June 2016, Official Report, column 136WH, when his Department last made representations to Saudi Arabia to encourage abolition of the death penalty in that country; and at what level those representations were made.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40433","40433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524721","2016-06-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the oral contribution of the Minister for Europe of 8 June 2016, Official Report, column 136WH, when his Department last made representations to Saudi Arabia expressing concern about the extent of the application of the death penalty in that country.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40437","40437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524722","2016-06-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the oral contribution of the Minister for Europe of 8 June 2016, Official Report, column 137WH, when the cross-departmental programme expenditure funding to support Yemen's national de-mining institution will be released.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40435","40435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524723","2016-06-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of whether the Sudan's National Intelligence and Security Services had a role in the recent deaths of student protestors.","Biography information for Mark Durkan","Mark Durkan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40436","40436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524724","2016-06-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to China on retracting its law on the management of foreign NGOs, passed on 28 April 2016; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40454","40454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524725","2016-06-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received of Turkish members of parliament being verbally abused, physically assaulted and threatened with murder within the parliament of that country; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40471","40471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524726","2016-06-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the oral contribution of the Minister for Europe on 8 June 2016, Official Report, column 137WH, what representations the UK has made to Saudi Arabia to accede to the Convention on Cluster Munitions; and on what dates those representations were made.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40456","40456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524727","2016-06-15","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the oral contribution of the Minister for Europe on 8 June 2016, Official Report, column 137WH, when the UK last maintained cluster munitions held by Saudi Arabia.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40457","40457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524728","2016-06-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the oral contribution of the Minister for Europe of 8 June 2016, Official Report, column 136WH, whether his Department has made representations to Saudi Arabia requesting that the death sentences issued to Ali Mohammed al-Nimr, Abdullah al-Zaher and Dawood al-Marhoon be commuted.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40441","40441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524729","2016-06-27","Department of Health","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the budget is for GP services in (a) Southampton, (b) NHS West London Clinical Commissioning Group (CCG), (c) NHS North Manchester CCG and (d) West Hampshire CCG in 2016-17.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40465","40465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524730","2016-06-15","Department of Health","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many new GP registrations there were in (a) Southampton City, (b) NHS West London, (c) NHS North Manchester and (d) West Hampshire Clinical Commissioning Group in 2015-16.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40458","40458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524731","2016-06-27","Department of Health","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of spending on GP services in (a) Southampton City and (b) other clinical commissioning group areas with similar levels of deprivation has been allocated to drug and alcohol abuse services in 2016-17.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40466","40466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524732","2016-06-27","Department of Health","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of spending on GP services in (a) Southampton and (b) other clinical commissioning group areas with similar levels of deprivation has been allocated to teenage pregnancy services in 2016-17.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40467","40467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524733","2016-06-15","Department of Health","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average cost to the public purse was of an appointment to see a GP in (a) Southampton City, (b) NHS West London, (c) NHS North Manchester and (d) West Hampshire Clinical Commissioning Group in 2015-16.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40459","40459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524734","2016-06-15","Department of Health","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 10 June 2016 to Question 39260, what factors determine the target allocations for primary care funding.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40460","40460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524735","2016-06-27","Department of Health","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans his Department has to improve breast cancer survival rates for women in England.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40470","40470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524736","2016-06-15","Cabinet Office","2016-06-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the life expectancy is of residents of the (a) Southampton City, (b) NHS West London, (c) NHS North Manchester and (d) West Hampshire clinical commissioning group areas.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40461","40461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524737","2016-06-15","Department of Health","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is able to take to redistribute funding from clinical commissioning groups that are over their target allocation.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40462","40462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524738","2016-06-15","Department of Health","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of residents of the (a) Southampton City, (b) NHS West London, (c) NHS North Manchester and (d) West Hampshire clinical commissioning group areas are BME.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40463","40463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524739","2016-06-15","Department of Health","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients are supported by (a) NHS West London, (b) NHS North Manchester and (c) West Hampshire Clinical Commissioning Group.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40464","40464"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524740","2016-06-27","Department of Health","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when the Joint Committee on Vaccination and Immunisation will next report to his Department on the cost-effectiveness framework for vaccinations.","Biography information for Mark Durkan","Mark Durkan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40439","40439"
