"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416831","2015-09-09","Department for Transport","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, where the modification to include a buffet car in standard class of the IEP train sets for the East Coast line will be (a) manufactured and (b) assembled.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8719","8719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416832","2015-09-09","Department for Transport","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment has been made of the effect to the delivery timetable for IEP trains for the East Coast line of the modifications to include a buffet car in standard class.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8720","8720"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416833","2015-09-08","Department for Transport","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the time taken for Hitachi to modify IEP trains for East Coast to include a buffet car in standard class.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8889","8889"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416834","2015-09-08","Speaker's Committee for the Independent Parliamentary Standards Authority","2015-09-04","To ask the hon. Member for Broxbourne, representing the Speaker's Committee for the Independent Parliamentary Standards Authority, how IPSA measures levels of productivity of its staff.","Biography information for Philip Boswell","Phil Boswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8700","8700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416835","2015-09-08","Speaker's Committee for the Independent Parliamentary Standards Authority","2015-09-04","To ask the hon. Member for Broxbourne, representing the Speaker's Committee for the Independent Parliamentary Standards Authority, what steps IPSA has taken to increase the productivity of its staff.","Biography information for Philip Boswell","Phil Boswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8701","8701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416836","2015-09-08","Department of Health","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to promote alcohol counselling to prevent alcohol-related crime.","Biography information for Philip Boswell","Phil Boswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8568","8568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416837","2015-09-08","Home Office","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what research her Department (a) has commissioned and (b) has planned on the amount of crime committed while the offender is under the influence of (i) alcohol and (ii) Class A drugs.","Biography information for Philip Boswell","Phil Boswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8569","8569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416838","2015-09-08","Cabinet Office","2015-09-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what proportion of crimes are committed while the offender is under the influence of (a) alcohol and (b) Class A drugs.","Biography information for Philip Boswell","Phil Boswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8570","8570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416839","2015-09-08","Speaker's Committee for the Independent Parliamentary Standards Authority","2015-09-04","To ask the hon. Member for Broxbourne, representing the Speaker's Committee for the Independent Parliamentary Standards Authority, how IPSA measures how efficient its processes are for hon. Members and their staff to register expenses.","Biography information for Philip Boswell","Phil Boswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8401","8401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416840","2015-09-08","Speaker's Committee for the Independent Parliamentary Standards Authority","2015-09-04","To ask the hon. Member for Broxbourne, representing the Speaker's Committee for the Independent Parliamentary Standards Authority, what steps IPSA has taken to make its processes more efficient for hon. Members and their staff.","Biography information for Philip Boswell","Phil Boswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8402","8402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416841","2015-09-08","Speaker's Committee for the Independent Parliamentary Standards Authority","2015-09-04","To ask the hon. Member for Broxbourne, representing the Speaker's Committee for the Independent Parliamentary Standards Authority, if IPSA will consult the Scottish Parliament Corporate Body on making its processes more efficient.","Biography information for Philip Boswell","Phil Boswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8403","8403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416842","2015-09-08","Speaker's Committee for the Independent Parliamentary Standards Authority","2015-09-04","To ask the hon. Member for Broxbourne, representing the Speaker's Committee for the Independent Parliamentary Standards Authority, what plans IPSA has to measure the average number of working hours spent by hon. Members and their staff per month on registering expenses with IPSA.","Biography information for Philip Boswell","Phil Boswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8404","8404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416843","2015-09-08","Speaker's Committee for the Independent Parliamentary Standards Authority","2015-09-04","To ask the hon. Member for Broxbourne, representing the Speaker's Committee for the Independent Parliamentary Standards Authority, in how many instances IPSA has suspended the credit card of an hon. Member.","Biography information for Philip Boswell","Phil Boswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8405","8405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416844","2015-09-08","HM Treasury","2015-09-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will take steps to close the tax avoidance scheme known as the Mayfair tax loophole.","Biography information for Philip Boswell","Phil Boswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8465","8465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416845","2015-09-08","Prime Minister","2015-09-04","To ask the Prime Minister, whether the Wilson Doctrine (a) applies and (b) has in the past applied to Members of the devolved assemblies and UK Members of the European Parliament.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8501","8501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416846","2015-09-08","Prime Minister","2015-09-04","To ask the Prime Minister, whether the Security Services have intercepted any communications by (a) Members of the Scottish Parliament, (b) Members of the Welsh Assembly, (c) Members of the Northern Ireland Assembly and (d) UK Members of the European Parliament.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8494","8494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416847","2015-09-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department is taking to help people to stop receiving unsolicited mail.","Biography information for Dr Tania Mathias","Dr Tania Mathias","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8744","8744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416848","2015-09-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether he plans for the extension of the Right to Buy scheme to housing associations to encompass fully mutual housing co-operatives.","Biography information for Dr Tania Mathias","Dr Tania Mathias","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8745","8745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416849","2015-09-09","Department for Education","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what threshold for (a) individual and (b) household earnings she plans to introduce to determine eligibility for the Government's 30 hours free childcare scheme.","Biography information for Dr Tania Mathias","Dr Tania Mathias","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8746","8746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416850","2015-09-09","Department for Transport","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to publicise the ending of the paper counterpart to driving licences; and what arrangements are in place to support drivers who do not have access to a computer to access information about their penalty points.","Biography information for Dr Tania Mathias","Dr Tania Mathias","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8747","8747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416851","2015-09-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether means-testing for the purpose of calculating benefits is calculated using income before or after deductions for pension contributions are made.","Biography information for Dr Tania Mathias","Dr Tania Mathias","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8949","8949"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416149","2015-09-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-09-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he plans to take to reduce youth unemployment.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 901150","901150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416866","2015-09-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-09-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he plans to publish statistics on the number of people with disabilities claiming benefits who take their own lives.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 901165","901165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416867","2015-09-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-09-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the statistics on people who died after claiming employment and support allowance published by his Department on 27 August 2015; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 901163","901163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416868","2015-09-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-09-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what support his Department provides to young people seeking work.","Biography information for Mims Davies","Mims Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 901166","901166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416869","2015-09-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-09-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether the Health and Safety Executive has carried out research into the potential risks associated with hydraulic fracturing.","Biography information for Tom Elliott","Tom Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 901170","901170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416870","2015-09-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-09-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the statistics on people who died after claiming employment and support allowance published by his Department on 27 August 2015; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 901169","901169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416871","2015-09-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-09-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans he has to tackle youth unemployment.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 901167","901167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417396","2015-09-08","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the change in the number of employment tribunal claims made since July 2013.","Biography information for Hannah Bardell","Hannah Bardell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 901230","901230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417397","2015-09-08","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to improve the provision of education in prisons; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Antoinette Sandbach","Antoinette Sandbach","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 901234","901234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417398","2015-09-08","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to ensure that people eligible for legal aid are able to access such aid.","Biography information for Meg Hillier","Meg Hillier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 901231","901231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417399","2015-09-08","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the (a) cost effectiveness and (b) level of use of the Public Defender Service.","Biography information for John Pugh","John Pugh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 901235","901235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417400","2015-09-08","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the recent investigations into alleged misuse of public money by private providers that held contracts with his Department.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 901229","901229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/419003","2015-09-16","Wales Office","2015-09-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what assessment he has made of the effect in Wales of the Government's measures to support businesses.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 901184","901184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/419004","2015-09-16","Wales Office","2015-09-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what plans the Government has for the future of the block grant to Wales.","Biography information for David Mowat","David Mowat","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 901183","901183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/419005","2015-09-16","Wales Office","2015-09-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what discussions he has had with Ministers in the Welsh Government on equality and diversity training in health and social care in Wales.","Biography information for Ben Howlett","Ben Howlett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 901182","901182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391677","2015-09-07","Attorney General","2015-07-21","To ask the Attorney General, what his policy is on the circumstances in which his Department should pursue a case of contempt of court, and when such action should be pursued by a private individual.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8308","8308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391678","2015-09-07","Attorney General","2015-07-21","To ask the Attorney General, with reference to recent representations from the hon. Member for Nottingham South on the case of Heather Peto, if he will undertake an investigation of whether his Department followed its processes fully in that case.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8309","8309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391679","2015-09-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what licences have been issued to (a) Instro Precision, (b) Ferranti Technologies and (c) Elite KL for exports for the use of the Israeli Defence Force or other elements of Israel's security forces on what dates since 1 January 2010; and what the date of each such licence was.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8285","8285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391680","2015-09-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department is taking in negotiations on the Transatlantic Trade and Investment Partnership (a) to protect and (b) to ensure benefits to the UK entertainment industry.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8257","8257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391681","2015-09-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what his policy is on retaining full public ownership of the Met Office; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8269","8269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391682","2015-09-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether officials in his Department have worked to assess the feasibility of a sale of his Department's stake in Ordnance Survey Ltd.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8270","8270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391683","2015-09-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether any officials in his Department have examined the feasibility of privatising the Land Registry.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8271","8271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391684","2015-09-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what his policy is on retaining full public ownership of the Land Registry; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8272","8272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391685","2015-09-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will bring forward regulations to clarify the legal protections that third party companies receive with regard to stock and stock lists which are held by online retailers; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8232","8232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391686","2015-09-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the cost to the British economy of the EU Working Time Directive in the most recent year for which data is available.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8197","8197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391687","2015-09-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate his Department has made of the total amount that will be available to ring-fenced science and research funding organisations in each of the next five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8265","8265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391688","2015-09-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if his Department will conduct a review into the adequacy of capital investment spending as part of the science research budget allocation; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8264","8264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391689","2015-09-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the Employment Regulations Act 1999 (Blacklists) Regulations 2010.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Mrs Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8281","8281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391690","2015-09-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether any officials in his Department have worked on assessing the feasibility of privatising the Met Office.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8350","8350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391691","2015-09-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will make an assessment of (a) the implications for his policies of the French government's proposed introduction of carbon reporting obligations for institutional investors under Article 48 of the Energy Transition Law and (b) the potential merits of introducing similar legislation in the UK; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8352","8352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391692","2015-09-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of February 2015 to Question 222681, what licences have been issued since 1 January 2010 to UAV Engines Ltd for equipment other than UAV engines or components for exports for the use of the Israeli Defence Force or other elements of Israel's security forces; and on what date each such licence was issued.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8353","8353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391693","2015-09-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, for how long UK citizens are required to reside in the UK in order to be eligible for student finance.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8171","8171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391694","2015-09-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps Companies House is taking to enforce the Overseas Companies Regulations 2009; and how many prosecutions have been made under those Regulations to date.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8192","8192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391695","2015-09-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what representations he has received on proposed changes to the number of student places offered in art and design foundation diplomas.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8209","8209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391696","2015-09-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether it is his policy that the science ring-fence will remain in place.","Biography information for Lord Davies of Gower","Byron Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8211","8211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391697","2015-09-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether it is his policy to retain full public ownership of Ordnance Survey Limited; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8212","8212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391698","2015-09-07","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he is taking to increase tourism and tourism-related jobs in Merthyr Tydfil and Rhymney.","Biography information for Gerald Jones","Gerald Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8219","8219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391699","2015-09-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the reasons are for the distinction, made in the Annexes to his Department's response, published in March 2015, to its consultation on Support for Post-Graduate study, between taught Masters students who are studying via distance learning and part-time taught Masters students for the purposes of the new postgraduate loans scheme proposed for England; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Iain Stewart","Iain Stewart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8357","8357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391700","2015-09-07","Cabinet Office","2015-07-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Written Statement of 20 June 2015, HCWS153, on Freedom of Information, whether the Freedom of Information Commission is a public authority subject to the Freedom of Information Act 2000.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8184","8184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391701","2015-09-07","Cabinet Office","2015-07-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Written Statement of 20 June 2015, HCWS153, on Freedom of Information, what plans he has to issue an order under section 4 or 5 of the Freedom of Information Act 2000 in relation to the Freedom of Information Commission.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8185","8185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391702","2015-09-07","Cabinet Office","2015-07-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many and what value of procurement contracts central Government Departments hold with suppliers in each (a) region and (b) parliamentary constituency.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8130","8130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391703","2015-09-07","Cabinet Office","2015-07-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many full-time equivalent staff in all Government departments and agencies in total were working on climate change adaptation in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12, (c) 2012-13, (d) 2013-14 and (e) 2014-15; and if he will estimate the likely number of such staff in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8333","8333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391704","2015-09-07","HM Treasury","2015-07-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 20 July 2015 to Question 6496, how much of the £800 million referred to in that Answer is allocated as additional spending in the Budget.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8292","8292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391705","2015-09-07","HM Treasury","2015-07-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 16 June 2015 to Question 2813, whether the Civil Service Recruitment Principles were followed in the appointment of his Department's Director of Communications.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8296","8296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391706","2015-09-07","HM Treasury","2015-07-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to paragraph 3.29 of his Department's document, A country that lives within its means: Spending Review 2015, published in July 2015, what proportion of the total amount of public sector land to be disposed he expects to be contributed by each department.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8341","8341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391707","2015-09-07","HM Treasury","2015-07-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the number of main carers of each gender in each region and constituent part of the UK who receive child tax credit.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8248","8248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391708","2015-09-07","HM Treasury","2015-07-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what his policy is on duty exemption for small-scale producers; and what he took of EU directives when forming that policy.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8255","8255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391709","2015-09-07","HM Treasury","2015-07-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will estimate the potential number of jobs that would be created by a reduction in VAT for the tourism industry.","Biography information for Gerald Jones","Gerald Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8199","8199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391710","2015-09-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what his policy is on the future of Companies House; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8235","8235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391711","2015-09-07","HM Treasury","2015-07-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether officials in his Department has worked on assessing the feasibility of privatising the Royal Mint.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8236","8236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391712","2015-09-07","HM Treasury","2015-07-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether it is his policy to retain full public ownership of the Royal Mint; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8237","8237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391713","2015-09-07","HM Treasury","2015-07-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent estimate his Department has made of the value of the (a) Royal Mint, (b) Land Registry, (c) Ordnance Survey, (d) Met Office and (e) National Air Traffic Services.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8238","8238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391714","2015-09-07","HM Treasury","2015-07-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, which Minister in his Department authorised the pay rises for his Department's senior executives in 2014-15.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8274","8274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391715","2015-09-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, for what reasons the new Living Wage does not apply to those under 25.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8275","8275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391716","2015-09-07","HM Treasury","2015-07-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will meet the Tenant Farmers' Association to discuss its proposals for taxation of agricultural land to encourage longer term farm business tenancies.","Biography information for Neil Parish","Neil Parish","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8278","8278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391717","2015-09-07","HM Treasury","2015-07-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to paragraph 2.11 of the Spending Review 2015 (Cm 9112), how many of the two million jobs referred to in that paragraph are part-time.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8289","8289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391718","2015-09-07","Department for International Development","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what the UK contribution was to the World Bank in (a) paid in capital and (b) callable capital in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8134","8134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391719","2015-09-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the effect of the introduction of the National Living Wage on charitable residential care homes who do not benefit from the reduction in corporation tax rates.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8140","8140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391720","2015-09-07","HM Treasury","2015-07-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, for what reasons he proposes to reduce the upper limit of compensation payments for the Financial Services Compensation Scheme.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8142","8142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391721","2015-09-07","HM Treasury","2015-07-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what financial measures he has introduced to help residential care homes for elderly people run by charities since 2010.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8143","8143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391722","2015-09-07","HM Treasury","2015-07-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many residential care homes for elderly people are exempt from corporation tax.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8144","8144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391723","2015-09-07","HM Treasury","2015-07-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the Summer Budget 2015, what advice his Department received from the Office of Budget Responsibility on the fiscal effect of policy changes to the classification of Registered Social Landlords.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8193","8193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391724","2015-09-07","HM Treasury","2015-07-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, on what the fines imposed on the Information Commissioner's Office for excessive pay rises will be spent.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8190","8190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391725","2015-09-07","HM Treasury","2015-07-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what progress his Department has made on its review of  business rates; and what the projected timetable is for that review.","Biography information for Mr Marcus Fysh","Marcus Fysh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8204","8204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391726","2015-09-07","HM Treasury","2015-07-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 20 July 2015 to Question 6496, how much of the £800 million referred to in the Answer will be invested in each year of the present Parliament.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8217","8217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391727","2015-09-07","HM Treasury","2015-07-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the likely trends in the mis-selling of pension products in Scotland arising from the introduction of new pension flexibilities on 6 April 2015.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8173","8173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391728","2015-09-07","HM Treasury","2015-07-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he made in advance of the Summer Budget 2015 of the effect on the UK's carbon footprint of applying the climate change levy to renewable electricity.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8150","8150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391729","2015-09-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of 18 to 21 year olds in Copeland constituency that will no longer be entitled to housing benefit following measures announced in the Summer Budget 2015.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8176","8176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391730","2015-09-07","HM Treasury","2015-07-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he has made an assessment of any potential link between the introduction of tax-free childcare and the (a) cost and (b) demand for childcare by providers.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8179","8179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391731","2015-09-07","HM Treasury","2015-07-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what legal rights the UK has to reclaim potential losses brought about by the use of the European Financial Stabilisation Mechanism to bail out Eurozone states.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8305","8305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391732","2015-09-07","HM Treasury","2015-07-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the statement in his speech to the Confederation of British Industry on 20 May 2015 that the Government plans to merge UK Financial Investments and the Shareholder Executive into one organisation; what his proposed timetable is for that merger.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8318","8318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391733","2015-09-07","Department for Transport","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will provide guidance to local authorities considering planning applications for cruise terminals on the comparative merits of berthed cruise ships receiving energy supplies from onshore sources and generating their own energy from diesel fuel.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8223","8223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391734","2015-09-07","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many Public Health Funerals have been conducted in (a) Copeland constituency and (b) Cumbria in each of the last 20 years.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8227","8227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391735","2015-09-07","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much unspent section 106 money each district and unitary council had as of 21 July 2015.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8137","8137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391736","2015-09-07","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 4 February 2015 to Question 222794, what progress his Department has made on exploring what further support can be offered to leaseholders.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8244","8244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391737","2015-09-07","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department is taking to support museums in making exhibitions at national museums based in London accessible to school children in remote constituencies.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8186","8186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391738","2015-09-07","Ministry of Defence","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that economic instability in parts of the Eurozone does not have a detrimental effect on the defence-industrial relationship between the UK and (a) Italy and (b) other EU member states.","Biography information for Mr Marcus Fysh","Marcus Fysh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8205","8205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391739","2015-09-07","Ministry of Defence","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many British arms (a) the Government and (b) British companies have sold to Iraqi military forces to combat ISIL.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8245","8245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391740","2015-09-07","Ministry of Defence","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what discussions he has had with Cabinet colleagues, prior to receiving the Freedom of Information Act application by Reprieve, on whether a statement should be made to Parliament on British servicepeople embedded in allies' forces operating in the Middle East.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8196","8196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391741","2015-09-07","Ministry of Defence","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the strength of the Mountain Leader Training Cadre was in each quarter since Q1 2010.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8280","8280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391742","2015-09-07","Ministry of Defence","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many and in which countries British military personnel were embedded in (a) each of the last five years and (b) 2015 to date.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8364","8364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391743","2015-09-07","Ministry of Defence","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, in which countries British military personnel embedded with US forces are currently taking part in active duty.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8367","8367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391744","2015-09-07","Ministry of Defence","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what his Department's expenditure has been on British troops embedded with foreign or international forces in each of the last five years; and what proportion of that expenditure was defined as overseas development aid.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8366","8366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391745","2015-09-07","Department for Education","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate her Department has made of the number of pupils entered for GCSEs in (a) Gujarati, (b) modern Hebrew, (c) Bengali and (d) Mandarin Chinese in each year since 2009.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8252","8252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391746","2015-09-07","Department for Education","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will take steps to ensure the sustainability of designated teaching schools when funding is withdrawn due to a non-exceptional Ofsted inspection.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8260","8260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391747","2015-09-07","Department for Education","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Minister of State for Education's Answer of 8 July 2015 to Question 4880, on academies, which academies had their funding arrangements changed under that procedure.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8250","8250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391748","2015-09-07","Department for Education","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will provide guidance to head teachers and governors of primary schools on the appropriateness of head covering for girl pupils in order to help tackle rickets.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8222","8222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391749","2015-09-07","Department for Education","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many school governors have been removed from office under section 128 of the Education and Skills Act 2008 in each month since June 2008.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8135","8135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391750","2015-09-07","Department for Education","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of school leavers entered (a) further education and (b) apprenticeships in (i) Copeland constituency and (ii) Cumbria in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8188","8188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391751","2015-09-07","Department for Education","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what support is available for early years settings where Ofsted inspections have identified a need to improve provision for children with speech, language and communication needs; and from which sources such support is provided.","Biography information for Nick Smith","Nick Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8156","8156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391752","2015-09-07","Department for Education","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what legal duties local authorities have to support early years settings in the identification of, and support for, children with speech, language and communication needs.","Biography information for Nick Smith","Nick Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8177","8177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391753","2015-09-07","Department for Education","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will maintain the staff-child ratio in children's centres for the duration of this Parliament.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8178","8178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391754","2015-09-07","Department for Education","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the effect of the recent change in entry requirements to NVQ Level 3 Childcare on the recruitment of childcare apprentices.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8172","8172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391755","2015-09-07","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what changes the Government has made to building regulations relating to renewable energy in the last five years.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8180","8180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391756","2015-09-07","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment she has made of the potential economic benefits of investment in renewable energy resources in the next 10 years.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8181","8181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391757","2015-09-07","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment her Department has made of the effect of carbon emissions from England's upland and lowland peatlands.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8152","8152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391758","2015-09-07","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps she plans to take to ensure the UK stays on course to meet its targets to reduce the use of coal and other fossil fuels.","Biography information for Mr Nick Clegg","Mr Nick Clegg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8182","8182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391759","2015-09-07","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what proportion of the electricity produced in the UK derives from each principal method of electricity production.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8218","8218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391760","2015-09-07","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what proportion of the UK's electricity was derived from renewable sources in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8214","8214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391761","2015-09-07","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what proportion of the UK's energy was derived from renewable sources in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8215","8215"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391762","2015-09-07","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many accredited renewable energy generators operate in (a) Hampstead and Kilburn and (b) London in each of the last four years; and how many Renewables Levy Exemption Certification Ofgem issued in those areas in those years.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8254","8254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391763","2015-09-07","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment she has made of the effect of recent reports stating that Toshiba has overstated its profits on that company being involved in building a new nuclear complex in West Cumbria.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8273","8273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391764","2015-09-07","HM Treasury","2015-07-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if the Government will commission an analysis of the potential effect on the UK renewable electricity generation companies of its proposed removal of the Climate Change Levy exemption for renewable power.","Biography information for Margaret Greenwood","Margaret Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8368","8368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391765","2015-09-07","HM Treasury","2015-07-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if the Government will commission a detailed analysis  of the potential effect on the electricity bills of public sector consumers on the proposed removal of the Climate Change Levy exemption.","Biography information for Margaret Greenwood","Margaret Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8365","8365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391766","2015-09-07","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what discussions she has had with Lancashire Council, Wyre Council, environmental groups and local residents' associations prior to the decision being taken to overrule the rejection of a planning application for gas storage made by Halite Energy in Preesall, Lancashire.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8359","8359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391767","2015-09-07","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what discussions she has had with her colleagues in the Department for Communities and Local Government and the Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs prior to the decision being taken to overrule the rejection of a planning application for gas storage made by Halite Energy in Preesall, Lancashire.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8360","8360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391768","2015-09-07","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment her Department has made of the potential effect of the proposed closure of the Renewables Obligation to onshore wind on the cost of capital for (a) onshore wind projects and (b) wider renewables investment.","Biography information for Dr Phillip Lee","Dr Phillip Lee","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8290","8290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391769","2015-09-07","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the implications are for her Department's policy of the findings relating to the overcharging of customers set out in the summary report of the investigation being undertaken by the Competition and Markets Authority into the energy market in Great Britain published on 7 July 2015.","Biography information for Philip Boswell","Phil Boswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8356","8356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391770","2015-09-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the total value was of her Department's flood and coastal erosion risk management assets in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12, (c) 2012-13, (d) 2013-14 and (e) 2014-15; and what estimate she has made of the likely value of such assets in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8323","8323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391771","2015-09-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what guidance her Department makes available to farmers on the management of arable field margins to provide benefits for wildlife.","Biography information for Mrs Maria Miller","Mrs Maria Miller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8343","8343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391772","2015-09-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent estimate her Department has made of the national annual mortality burden of nitrogen dioxide.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8334","8334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391773","2015-09-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the net change was in the value of her Department's flood and coastal erosion risk management assets in each of the last five years; and what estimate she has made of the likely change in that value in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8324","8324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391774","2015-09-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the Supreme Court judgment in the case of R (on the application of ClientEarth) v Secretary of State for the Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, by what date she plans to publish an updated consultation on local air quality management.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8335","8335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391775","2015-09-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the total value was of public forest estate land sold in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12, (c) 2012-13, (d) 2013-14 and (e) 2014-15; and what estimate she has made of the likely value of such land sold in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8325","8325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391776","2015-09-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to her Department's news story, Environment Secretary calls for fewer inspections to make CAP simpler for farmers, published on 21 July 2015, what the scope is and what the evidential basis is for her call for a review of the Integrated Administration and Control System.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8339","8339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391777","2015-09-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the potential effect of the six-year flood and coastal erosion investment programme on risk of loss of life from flooding.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8330","8330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391778","2015-09-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many full-time equivalent staff were working on climate change adaptation in her Department in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12, (c) 2012-13, (d) 2013-14 and (e) 2014-15; and if she will estimate the likely number of such staff in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8331","8331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391779","2015-09-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to her Department's news story, Environment Secretary calls for fewer inspections to make CAP simpler for farmers, published on 21 July 2015, what policies are included in the overhaul of the greening requirements she requested.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8361","8361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391780","2015-09-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the total value was of land owned by National Park authorities that was sold in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12, (c) 2012-13, (d) 2013-14 and (e) 2014-15; and what estimate she has made of the likely value of such land in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8326","8326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391781","2015-09-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to her Department's news story, Environment Secretary calls for fewer inspections to make CAP simpler for farmers, published on 21 July 2015, what assessment she has made of the potential environmental effects of a reduction in (a) the number of inspections to check Ecological Focus Areas and (b) the overall number of CAP inspections.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8340","8340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391782","2015-09-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what payments have been made under Schedule 9A, Part 5, Paragraph 25(1) of the Wildlife and Countryside Act 1981 as amended by the Infrastructure Act 2015 to date.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8328","8328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391783","2015-09-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the threshold is for compensation payments under Schedule 9A, Part 5, Paragraph 25(2) of the Wildlife and Countryside Act 1981 as amended by the Infrastructure Act 2015.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8329","8329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391784","2015-09-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much has been allocated for the payment of compensation in respect of species control agreements and orders under Schedule 9A, Part 5, Paragraph 25(1) of the Wildlife and Countryside Act 1981 as amended by the Infrastructure Act 2015.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8327","8327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391785","2015-09-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to her Department's news story, Environment Secretary calls for fewer inspections to make CAP simpler for farmers, published on 21 July 2015, what assessment she has made of the potential effect of a reduction in (a) the number of inspections to check ecological focus areas and (b) the overall number of CAP inspections on progress towards meeting the biodiversity 2020 targets.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8362","8362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391786","2015-09-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many full-time equivalent staff were working on climate change adaptation in her Department's agencies in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12, (c) 2012-13, (d) 2013-14 and (e) 2014-15; and if she will estimate the likely number of such staff in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8332","8332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391787","2015-09-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment she has made of the population size of foxes.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8276","8276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391788","2015-09-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when her Department plans to roll out the badger cull policy to other regions beyond the trial culls in Somerset and Gloucestershire.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8226","8226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391789","2015-09-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when her Department plans to publish the full terms and conditions of the (a) Countryside Stewardship: higher tier, (b) Countryside Stewardship: mid-tier, (c) Woodland Capital Grants 2015, (d) Facilitation Fund and (e) Water Capital Grants 2015, grant schemes.","Biography information for Wendy Morton","Wendy Morton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8228","8228"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391790","2015-09-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when her Department plans to start the next round of trial badger culls in (a) Somerset and (b) Gloucestershire.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8225","8225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391791","2015-09-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether she plans to make changes to the compensation offered to farmers whose stock is affected by avian flu.","Biography information for James Cartlidge","James Cartlidge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8154","8154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391792","2015-09-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to reduce carbon emissions from England's upland and lowland peatlands.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8153","8153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391793","2015-09-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she plans to take to implement the Voluntary Code of Practice on Contractual Relations in the dairy industry for milk buyers.","Biography information for Calum Kerr","Calum Kerr","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8128","8128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391794","2015-09-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans her Department has to implement the recommendations of the Farm Animal Welfare Committee opinion on the use of CCTV in slaughterhouses to assess the welfare of farmed animals, published on 3 February 2015.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8138","8138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391795","2015-09-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the Special Mission Immunity status pilot, whether any new policies or procedures have been introduced in response to the outcome of that pilot.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8148","8148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391796","2015-09-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the prospects of implementing a two state solution in Israel and Palestine arising from the demolition of the Palestinian village of Susiya.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8174","8174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391797","2015-09-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the implications for (a) his policies and (b) Israel's compliance with the Fourth Geneva Convention of the demolition of the Palestinian village of Susiya.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8175","8175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391798","2015-09-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effect of lifting the UN arms embargo on Iranian access to conventional arms and how it will impact the security of that region.","Biography information for John Howell","John Howell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8183","8183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391799","2015-09-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his European counterparts to ensure that economic instability in parts of the Eurozone does not have a detrimental effect on the defence-industrial relationship between the UK and (a) Italy and (b) other EU member states.","Biography information for Mr Marcus Fysh","Marcus Fysh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8206","8206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391800","2015-09-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has recently received requests from officials in the Kurdistan region of Northern Iraq to discuss with them the establishment of an independent Kurdish state; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8243","8243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391801","2015-09-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of Syria's compliance with UN Security Council Resolution 2118 on ending its chemical weapons programme.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8247","8247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391802","2015-09-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 16 July 2015 to Question 6693, what recent discussions he has had with the Egyptian government on (a) freedom of opinion and expression, (b) freedom of peaceful assembly and association and (c) the position of civil society in that country.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8363","8363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391803","2015-09-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, which pieces of EU legislation adopted in each of the last five years met the conditions to be subject to qualified majority voting in the Council of the EU or the European Council.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8304","8304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391804","2015-09-07","HM Treasury","2015-07-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he has made an assessment of the potential effect on the number of EU migrants coming to the UK of the reforms of tax credits and the introduction of a living wage announced in the Summer Budget 2015; and whether he plans to take these measures into account in his discussions with EU states on reforming the EU's rules on freedom of movement.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8303","8303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391805","2015-09-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, further to the Conclusions of the European Council of 25 and 26 June 2015 paragraph 14 relating to the UK's EU renegotiation programme, what technical work the Council plans to undertake before it reports back in December; what the (a) composition and (b) mandate of the working group is; and whether it is planned that national parliaments will be able to contribute to the work of that group.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8302","8302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391806","2015-09-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his EU counterparts about amending article 122 of the Treaty on the Functioning of the European Union to ensure that it cannot be used as a legal basis for Eurozone bailouts.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8301","8301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391807","2015-09-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, which EU treaty articles would need to be amended or deleted in order to allow the UK not to be bound by the current or future EU social and employment legislation or rulings of the European Court of Justice in the same area.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8300","8300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391808","2015-09-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his Iranian counterpart on the human rights situation in that country.","Biography information for Guto Bebb","Guto Bebb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8299","8299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391809","2015-09-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when he next plans to convene his Human Rights Advisory Group.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8298","8298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391810","2015-09-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to the Colombian government to request that due process is observed in proceedings following the arrests of social activists (a) Esmer Montilla, (b) Samuel Rojas, (c) Ramiro Ateortua and (d) Ingrid Pinilla on 15 and 16 July 2015.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8320","8320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391811","2015-09-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received on whether the Colombian government has recently taken steps to ensure that human rights activists in that country are given full legal protection and are not arrested as a result of their work.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8319","8319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391812","2015-09-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received on (a) the shooting dead in Buenaventura, Colombia, on 20 July 2015, of two boys by paramilitary gangs and (b) how it was possible for those shootings to take place in a street heavily supervised by the Colombian armed forces; and if he will make representations to the Colombian authorities on that matter.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8321","8321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391813","2015-09-07","Home Office","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Conclusions of the European Council of 25 and 26 June 2015 paragraph 4(e), whether the UK is legally bound by the agreement to participate in resettling 20,000 displaced persons.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8358","8358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391814","2015-09-07","Department of Health","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure access for NHS patients to innovative new medicines that have received marketing authorisation before their assessment from NICE.","Biography information for Mrs Pauline Latham","Pauline Latham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8316","8316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391815","2015-09-07","Department of Health","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the recent Royal College of Obstetricians and Gynaecologists audit which reported that more than half of all obstetric units tested some or all pregnant women for group B Streptococci using tests not designed specifically to detect group B Streptococci, what the Government's plans are to introduce Public Health England's recently updated UK Standards for Microbiology Investigations, B58 Detection of carriage of Group B Streptococci; and what the planned timescale is for that introduction.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8291","8291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391816","2015-09-07","Department of Health","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will request that NHS England clarify the mechanisms available for manufacturers of medical technologies to appeal against a negative specialised service commissioning policy decision.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8282","8282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391817","2015-09-07","Department of Health","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions he has had on the availability of nivolumab for melanoma patients through the Cancer Drugs Fund.","Biography information for Mrs Pauline Latham","Pauline Latham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8315","8315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391818","2015-09-07","Department of Health","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will request that NHS England publish the criteria for approving a specialised service commissioning policy.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8283","8283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391819","2015-09-07","Department of Health","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the (a) proposed timescale and (b) scope will be of the Government's consultation on its proposed reduction of £200 million in the funding of public health.","Biography information for Mr David Burrowes","Mr David Burrowes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8349","8349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391820","2015-09-07","Department of Health","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions he has had with charities representing people with Duchenne muscular dystrophy on the availability of the drug Translarna; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8342","8342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391821","2015-09-07","Department of Health","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidance his Department has issued (a) to ensure that (i) health professionals involved in the care of pregnant women and (ii) pregnant women are informed about group B Streptococcus and (b) on effectiveness of tests used within the NHS to detect carriage of group B Streptococcus.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8354","8354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391822","2015-09-07","Department of Health","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many Child and Adolescent Mental Services inpatient Tier 4 beds were available in each region and in each of the past four years; and what the average waiting time was for such a bed in each such region in each such year.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8249","8249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391823","2015-09-07","Department of Health","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of the total amount made available to ring-fenced science and research funding organisations in each of the next five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8266","8266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391824","2015-09-07","Department of Health","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether NHS England has a responsibility formally to respond to requests from NHS trusts to undertake joint investigations into serious incidents.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8234","8234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391825","2015-09-07","Department of Health","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information his Department holds on the reasons why a request from Lancashire Care NHS Foundation Trust for NHS England to participate in a joint serious incidents investigation has not yet received a formal response; and what assessment he has made of the implications for the conduct of such an investigation arising from the time taken to respond to that request.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8233","8233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391826","2015-09-07","Department of Health","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what actions his Department is taking to monitor the consumption and distribution of Miracle Mineral Solution.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8198","8198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391827","2015-09-07","Department of Health","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the relationship between the size of GP surgeries' patient lists and (a) the proportion of their funding and (b) the overall level of funding allocated under the Minimum Price Income Guarantee.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8253","8253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391828","2015-09-07","Department of Health","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to regulate Disney's use of logos, branding and product placement during its involvement in the Change4Life partnership.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8277","8277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391829","2015-09-07","Department of Health","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the latest diagnosis rate for dementia is in (a) England and (b) Wales; and if he will reintroduce the publication of a monthly update of such rates in England.","Biography information for Dr James Davies","Dr James Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8286","8286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391830","2015-09-07","Department of Health","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will request that NHS England publish a timeline for the re-publication of a commissioning policy on (a) microprocessor knees, (b) multi-articulating prosthetic hands and (c) custom made silicon covers.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8279","8279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391831","2015-09-07","Department of Health","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect of the reduction in funding allocation for public health in 2015-16 on public health in (a) the London region and (b) England.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8263","8263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391832","2015-09-07","Department of Health","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he plans to increase the budget of the NHS to meet the cost of making the NHS a full seven days a week service.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8261","8261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391833","2015-09-07","Department of Health","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to collect data on the average yearly earnings of GPs employed by the NHS by (a) local authority and (b) parliamentary constituency.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8262","8262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391834","2015-09-07","Department of Health","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department plans to hold a public consultation on its proposed reduction in the funding allocation to public health for 2015-16.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8259","8259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391835","2015-09-07","Department of Health","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, on how many occasions Clinical Commissioning Groups have not provided funding for a new drug treatment within three months of its approval in a NICE technology appraisal in each year since 2009.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8251","8251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391836","2015-09-07","Department of Health","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of resources available to (a) adult mental health services, (b) child and adolescent mental health services to provide people who are survivors of (i) current and (ii) historic child sexual abuse with therapeutic and other support services in each of the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8221","8221"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391837","2015-09-07","Department of Health","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what reports he has received on the progress of the business case being developed by West Norfolk Clinical Commissioning Group for providing specialist psychological support based at the Colman Hospital for patients with muscular dystrophy and neuromuscular conditions; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8208","8208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391838","2015-09-07","Department of Health","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to his contribution on 16 July 2015, Official Report, column 1112, and with reference to the contribution of the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State in his Department in the House of Lords on 9 June 2015, Official Report, column 283, what his policy is on the exploration of alternative charging systems or different funding systems for the NHS; if he will make it his policy not to bring forwards proposals in the present Parliament to (a) introduce and (b) plan for further charging for healthcare or related services currently provided on the NHS; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8216","8216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391839","2015-09-07","Department of Health","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) new cancer medicines and (b) new indications of existing cancer medicines are expected to be licensed between July 2015 and 31 March 2016.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8162","8162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391840","2015-09-07","Department of Health","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his estimate is of the number and proportion of (a) consultants, (b) nurses, (c) physiotherapists, (d) pharmacists, (e) pathologists, (f) phlebotomists, (g) radiographers, (h) porters, (i) receptionists, (j) administrators, (k) health care support workers and (l) discharge service staff in (i) England, (ii) London, (iii) the Whittington Hospital NHS Trust and (iv) University College Hospitals NHS Foundation Trust who usually worked on a Wednesday in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8166","8166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391841","2015-09-07","Department of Health","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his estimate is of the number and proportion of (a) consultants, (b) nurses, (c) physiotherapists, (d) pharmacists, (e) pathologists, (f) phlebotomists, (g) radiographers, (h) porters, (i) receptionists, (j) administrators, (k) health care support workers and (l) discharge service staff in (i) England, (ii) London, (iii) the Whittington Hospital NHS Trust and (iv) University College Hospitals NHS Foundation Trust who usually worked on a Saturday in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8167","8167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391842","2015-09-07","Department of Health","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to tackle childhood obesity.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8168","8168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391843","2015-09-07","Department of Health","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he plans for a new system for the reimbursement of cancer drugs to be in place by April 2016 when the current Cancer Drugs Fund is proposed to end.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8164","8164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391844","2015-09-07","Department of Health","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans his Department has to support the NHS and local government to work together to improve the identification of (a) people caring for people living with and beyond cancer and (b) other carers and their needs.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8159","8159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391845","2015-09-07","Department of Health","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans his Department has to ensure that healthcare professionals identify (a) people caring for people living with and beyond cancer and (b) other carers and signpost them to available services and support.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8160","8160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391846","2015-09-07","Department of Health","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients were admitted by Lancashire Care hospitals in 2014; and how many of those admissions were to (a) NHS facilities, (b) privately-run facilities in Lancashire, (c) named NHS facilities and (d) named private facilities outside Lancashire.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8139","8139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391847","2015-09-07","Department of Health","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of elderly residents of residential care homes run by charities who receive subsidised care from the operating charity.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8141","8141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391848","2015-09-07","Department of Health","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many contracts have been awarded to the University of York by (a) his Department and (b) NICE since 1999; and how much funding has been allocated through each such contract by (i) his Department and (ii) NICE since 1999.","Biography information for Mr Steve Baker","Steve Baker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8145","8145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391849","2015-09-07","Department of Health","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the reasons are for the delay in publishing the May 2015 referral to treatment waiting time data for King's College Hospital NHS Foundation Trust; and what action he plans to take to ensure that such data is published as soon as possible.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8129","8129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391850","2015-09-07","Home Office","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people reported (a) lost and (b) stolen passports to the Passport Office in 2014; and how many of those people were issued with a replacement.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8136","8136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391851","2015-09-07","Home Office","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what amount of resource has been available to the police to (a) protect children from sexual abuse, (b) carry out investigations in relation to (i) current and (ii) historic child sexual abuse cases in each of the last five years; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8220","8220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391852","2015-09-07","Home Office","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much was paid out in compensation (a) in total and (b) per case to victims of racial abuse by police officers in London in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8224","8224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391853","2015-09-07","Home Office","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will meet the hon. Member for Dudley South and a delegation of civic, faith and business leaders from Dudley to discuss the effect that demonstrations by far-right organisations are having on community life and trade in that town.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8203","8203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391854","2015-09-07","Home Office","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of applications for permanent leave to remain from people who have had discretionary leave to remain status (a) in each age group and (b) with each level of educational qualification for at least 10 years.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8258","8258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391855","2015-09-07","Home Office","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many UK counter-terrorism police staff are based in Turkey.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8311","8311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391856","2015-09-07","Home Office","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications for refugee family reunion under the Part 11 Immigration Rules resulted in the (a) grant of entry clearance to children under 18 and (b) refusal of entry clearance to female children under 18 from the same family in (i) 2014-15 and (ii) 2015-16 to date (A) in total and (B) in the case of families originating from (1) Syria, (2) Afghanistan and (3) Iran.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8295","8295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391857","2015-09-07","Home Office","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many Syrian refugees granted asylum in the UK were studying in the UK at the time their asylum application was made in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8239","8239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391858","2015-09-07","Home Office","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications for Refugee Family Reunion (under Part 11 Immigration Rules) have resulted in the granting of entry clearance to children under 18 and the refusal of entry clearance to female children over 18 from the same family (a) in total and (b) for families originating from (i) Syria, (ii) Afghanistan and (iii) Iran in the last two years for which records exist.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8377","8377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391859","2015-09-07","Home Office","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she has any plans to reintroduce tier 1 post-study work visas for students completing their studies at Scottish universities.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8346","8346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391860","2015-09-07","Home Office","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she has any plans to open the tier 3 category of visas to new applicants.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8345","8345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391861","2015-09-07","Home Office","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate her Department has made of the number of UK nationals who have crossed into Syria from the Turkish border and have since returned to the UK in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8312","8312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391862","2015-09-07","Home Office","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent representations she has made to her Turkish counterpart on developing a joint strategy to prevent UK nationals crossing over the border with Turkey into Syria.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8313","8313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391863","2015-09-07","Home Office","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions (a) she, (b) other Ministers in her Department and (c) officials in her Department have had with the Surveillance Camera Commissioner about compliance to Principle 1 of the Surveillance Camera Code of Practice 2013 by local authorities in England and Wales.","Biography information for Guto Bebb","Guto Bebb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8297","8297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391864","2015-09-07","House of Commons Commission","2015-07-21","To ask the Rt. Hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington representing the House of Commons Commission, whether options other than remaining in the Palace of Westminster have been considered for the long-term future of the House.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8344","8344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391865","2015-09-07","House of Commons Commission","2015-07-21","To ask the Rt. Hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington representing the House of Commons Commission, whether consideration has been given to ensuring that there will be adequate provision for every hon. Member to attend proceedings and take part in proceedings in the Chamber following the restoration and renewal of the Palace of Westminster.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8348","8348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391866","2015-09-07","Department for International Development","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what the total value was of projects funded by her Department to improve or conserve biodiversity in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12, (c) 2012-13, (d) 2013-14 and (e) 2014-15; and what such spending is expected to be in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8337","8337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391867","2015-09-07","Department for International Development","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what her Department's total spending on projects to improve or conserve biodiversity was in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12, (c) 2012-13, (d) 2013-14 and (e) 2014-15; and what such spending is expected to be in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8338","8338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391868","2015-09-07","Department for International Development","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what her Department's total spending was on climate change adaptation in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12, (c) 2012-13, (d) 2013-14 and (e) 2014-15; and what that spending is expected to be in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8336","8336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391869","2015-09-07","Department for International Development","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether the Government is providing any financial support to the Iraqi Government (a) in loans, (b) through the international development budget and (c) through other international bodies to support reconstruction of areas recaptured from ISIL.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8246","8246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391870","2015-09-07","Department for International Development","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what the total value was of projects funded by her Department on climate change adaptation in each year since 2010-11; and how much is planned to be spent in each year up to 2019-20.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8284","8284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391871","2015-09-07","Department for International Development","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what reports she has received on the levels of malnutrition in camps for internally displaced Rohingya in Rakhine State, Burma; and what aid the UK Government is providing to those camps.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8213","8213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391872","2015-09-07","Department for International Development","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much of the £32 million of aid pledged by the UK at the Cairo Donor Conference in 2014 to cover disposal of unexploded ordnance, rubble clearing and reconstructive surgery has been disbursed to date; and how much more such aid is planned to be sent in future.","Biography information for Michelle Donelan","Michelle Donelan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8210","8210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391873","2015-09-07","Ministry of Justice","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will introduce sentencing guidelines to stop taxis and private hire vehicles from refusing to carry guide dogs.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8187","8187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391874","2015-09-07","Ministry of Justice","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much was spent each month on the (a) maintenance and (b) running costs of court buildings that have been closed in the period up to their disposal since 2010.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8165","8165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391875","2015-09-07","Ministry of Justice","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many of each type of application listed on the HM Tribunals Service website were made to the Residential Property (First Tier) Tribunal for cases relating to leasehold in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8294","8294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391876","2015-09-07","Ministry of Justice","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people in England and Wales are serving imprisonment for public protection sentences.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8287","8287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391877","2015-09-07","Ministry of Justice","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will make it his policy to reinstate immigration legal aid funding for unaccompanied children.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8200","8200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391878","2015-09-07","Ministry of Justice","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what his Department's latest estimate is of the number of juveniles who reoffend within a year of their release from custody.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8201","8201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391879","2015-09-07","Ministry of Justice","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the cost benefits of restorative justice through projects run by the Restorative Justice Council.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8202","8202"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391880","2015-09-07","Ministry of Justice","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Written Statement of 16 July 2015 on HM Courts and Tribunals Service, HLWS108, what estimate he has made of job losses arising as a result of his proposals to reduce the cost of the court estate.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8373","8373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391881","2015-09-07","Ministry of Justice","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Written Statement of 16 July 2015 on HM Courts and Tribunals Service, HLWS108, what assessment he has made of the time that would be required by citizens, under the proposed changes to the court estate, to reach their required court by public transport.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8372","8372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391882","2015-09-07","Ministry of Justice","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much his Department spent on maintenance or improvement of courts which have been scheduled to be closed in the last five years; and what costs were incurred in planning future improvements to those courts which will now be written off.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8351","8351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391883","2015-09-07","Ministry of Justice","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Written Statement of 16 July 2015 on HM Courts and Tribunals Service, HLWS108, what costs incurred on future improvements to courts proposed for closure will now be written off.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8370","8370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391884","2015-09-07","Ministry of Justice","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Written Statement of 16 July 2015 on HM Courts and Tribunals Service, HLWS108, what proportion of the savings made by reducing the cost of the court estate will be re-invested in that estate; and in what ways will it be re-invested.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8371","8371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391885","2015-09-07","Ministry of Justice","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Written Statement of 16 July 2015 on HM Courts and Tribunals Service, what criteria will be used to determine which civic and other public buildings can be used for hearings.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8369","8369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391886","2015-09-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will allow a free vote on any division in the House on the Government's proposed changes to Sunday trading regulations.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8288","8288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391887","2015-09-07","Prime Minister","2015-07-21","To ask the Prime Minister, which (a) Muslim and (b) non-governmental groups he consulted on the policies announced in his five-year counter-extremism strategy announced on 20 July 2015.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8132","8132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391888","2015-09-07","Prime Minister","2015-07-21","To ask the Prime Minister, which (a) Muslim and (b) other non-governmental groups he consulted on his counter-extremism speech made on 20 July 2015.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8133","8133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391889","2015-09-07","HM Treasury","2015-07-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the Answer of 24 March 2015 to Question 228461, what steps he is taking to ensure that micro-businesses are not disadvantaged by Directive 2008/8/EC on EU VAT for digital services sold across borders; what progress he has made on getting the best deal for British firms; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8355","8355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391890","2015-09-07","Department for Transport","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what timetable is planned for the electrification of the Barking to Gospel Oak line; what forecast he has made of the cost of that electrification; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8322","8322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391891","2015-09-07","Department for Transport","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he has had discussions with (a) Transport for London and (b) transport authorities in other countries on establishing Transport for the North.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8146","8146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391892","2015-09-07","Department for Transport","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 20 July 2015 to Question 6967, what funding has been allocated to each project for each year under the heading, Funding for projects in addition to the agreed Rail Investment Strategy, given in the Answer of 9 July 2015 to Question 5694.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8163","8163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391893","2015-09-07","Department for Transport","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions his Department had with Northern Rail on the use of the Class 37 rolling stock on the Carlisle-Barrow-Lancaster rail line.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8127","8127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391894","2015-09-07","Department for Transport","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the likely effect of the delayed electrification of the TransPennine rail route to planned upgrades to the Midland Mainline; and what contingency plans he has put in place to mitigate such effects.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8170","8170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391895","2015-09-07","Department for Transport","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will take steps to improve the safety of the Ilminster bypass on the A303; and if he will direct the Highways Agency to revisit this matter in the light of recent serious accidents on that road.","Biography information for Mr Marcus Fysh","Marcus Fysh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8207","8207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391896","2015-09-07","Department for Transport","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what (a) work has been carried out and (b) expenditure has been made on work to electrify and upgrade the Chase Line from Walsall to Rugeley Trent Valley to date.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8229","8229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391897","2015-09-07","Department for Transport","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether electrification of the Chase Line from Walsall to Rugeley Trent Valley is included in the projects paused as part of the assessment of the High Level Output Specification.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8230","8230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391898","2015-09-07","Department for Transport","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 16 July 2015 to Question 6793, whether he has seen or requested a copy of the list of projects that would be stopped or refused which was referred to on page 3 of Network Rail's Board minutes of 25 November 2014.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8231","8231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391899","2015-09-07","Department for Transport","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what his Department policy is on retaining the Government's stake in National Air Traffic Service Holdings; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8268","8268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391900","2015-09-07","Department for Transport","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether an official in his Department has examined the feasibility of (a) partially and (b) wholly selling his Department's share of National Air Traffic Service Holdings.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8267","8267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391901","2015-09-07","Department for Transport","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what metric his Department uses to assess the risk-assessed level of staffing at coastguard operations centres; and what assessment he has made of those risk-assessed staffing levels using this metric at each of the coastguard operations centres in the period from January 2015 to July 2015.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8374","8374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391902","2015-09-07","Department for Transport","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what proportion of staff at the National Maritime Operation Centre at Fareham had attained the qualification level required for the Centre to reach full operational capacity by December 2015 by 21 July 2015.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8376","8376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391903","2015-09-07","Department for Transport","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what proportion of the staff required for the National Maritime Operation Centre in Fareham to reach full operational capacity by December 2015 had been appointed by 2 July 2015.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8375","8375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391904","2015-09-07","Department for Transport","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 20 July 2015 to Question 7273, when he was first advised that a decision on whether to pause major projects may have to be taken.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8317","8317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391905","2015-09-07","Department for Transport","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking as part of his Department's current review of noise policy to ensure that (a) tranquillity and (b) densely populated areas are clearly defined in Civil Aviation Authority guidance.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8293","8293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391906","2015-09-07","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what work the Government is doing to tackle discrimination against the Gypsy and Traveller communities.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8256","8256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391907","2015-09-07","HM Treasury","2015-07-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of recent changes to tax and tax credits on the income of women who choose to stay at home to care for children.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8240","8240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391908","2015-09-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many jobseekers have been sanctioned in Bethnal Green and Bow constituency in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8241","8241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391909","2015-09-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many times he has met the Children's Commissioner for England in each year since his initial appointment as Secretary of State.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8242","8242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391910","2015-09-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether the publication of data on people who have died whilst waiting for a decision about a social security claim will be back-dated to the last available date of November 2011.","Biography information for Natalie McGarry","Natalie McGarry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8195","8195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391911","2015-09-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the proposed changes to housing benefit entitlement for people aged 18 to 21 announced in the Summer Budget 2015 on levels of homelessness.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8310","8310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391912","2015-09-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether he consulted the Children's Commissioner for England on the redefinition of measures of child poverty.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8314","8314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391913","2015-09-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether he has undertaken or commissioned research into the potential effect on gender equality of the provisions of the Welfare Reform and Work Bill.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8347","8347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391914","2015-09-07","Department of Health","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans his Department has to support carers who are also in full or part-time employment.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8191","8191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391915","2015-09-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will publish statistics on sanctions for job seekers allowance and employment support allowance by (a) council, (b) marital status, (c) gender, (d) people with children, (e) carers and (f) age.","Biography information for Dr Eilidh Whiteford","Dr Eilidh Whiteford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8189","8189"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391916","2015-09-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether he is planning to appeal against the Information Commissioner's decision on the publication of data on people who have died while waiting for social security claims decisions.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8194","8194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391917","2015-09-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what his policy is on whether employment and support allowance claimants who are unable to continue with a Work Related Activity Group for health reasons will be awarded their previous level of benefit or be reassessed.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8169","8169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391918","2015-09-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 23 June 2015 to Question 3126, if he will make it his policy to record the number of claimants receiving benefits pertaining to a mental health condition who are assessed as fit to work based on an assessment wholly on their physical health.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8151","8151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391919","2015-09-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department has taken to inform claimants what documentation of relevant mental health conditions they may be required to bring to confirm their capacity to work; and what steps he plans to take on that matter in the next three months.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8149","8149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391920","2015-09-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what work his Department is undertaking to estimate the likely return on investment in the Access to Work Programme.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8161","8161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391921","2015-09-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what forecast his Department has made of the likelihood of fewer than five per cent of children living in material deprivation and low income by 2020-21.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8147","8147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391922","2015-09-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what consultation took place between his Department and HM Treasury before the Summer Budget 2015 on the introduction of an apprenticeship levy.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8155","8155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391923","2015-09-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he intends to reply to the letter to him dated 15 June 2015 from the right hon. Member for Manchester Gorton on Mr D Ward.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8157","8157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391924","2015-09-07","Department of Health","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans his Department has to increase support for (a) people caring for people living with and beyond cancer and (b) other carers.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8158","8158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391925","2015-09-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average length of time was a claimant with a DS1500 form had received (a) personal independence payment, (b) employment and support allowance and (c) attendance allowance on the last date for which figures are available.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8123","8123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391926","2015-09-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many terminally ill people were reassessed for (a) personal independence payment, (b) employment and support allowance and (c) attendance allowance in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8124","8124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391927","2015-09-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people claiming attendance allowance did so using a DS1500 form in 2014.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8125","8125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391928","2015-09-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many DS1500 forms were submitted in 2014.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8126","8126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391929","2015-09-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when his Department will respond to the letter dated 20 May 2015 from the hon. Member for Dudley North, reference ZA14622, on the bidding process for training contracts offered by his Department.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8131","8131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391930","2015-09-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether the (a) minimum wage and (b) living wage are considered as an income for the purposes of a self-employed claimant declaring income below that level for (i) universal credit, (ii) working tax credit and (iii) housing benefit.","Biography information for Ms Karen Buck","Ms Karen Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8307","8307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391931","2015-09-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, in what cases the minimum wage is assumed as income for self-employed claimants declaring income below that level for (a) universal credit, (b) tax credit and (c) housing benefit.","Biography information for Ms Karen Buck","Ms Karen Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8306","8306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391271","2015-09-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what value of export credit guarantees has supported (a) ship manufacturing and (b) marine engineering in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8001","8001"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391273","2015-09-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what forecasts the Government has made of steel (a) production and (b) demand in the next 20 years; and from which countries he expects the UK will import steel to meet that demand.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8053","8053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391276","2015-09-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will take steps to ensure that students studying abroad whose studies are interrupted by conflict have access to student finance on returning to the UK.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8085","8085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391278","2015-09-07","Cabinet Office","2015-07-20","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Written Statement of 20 June 2015, HCWS153, on Freedom of Information, whether the terms of reference of the Commission on Freedom of Information will permit it to consider the appropriate scope of the commercial confidentiality exemption under section 43(2) of the Freedom of Information Act 2000.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8035","8035"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391280","2015-09-07","Cabinet Office","2015-07-20","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Written Statement of 20 June 2015, HCWS153, on Freedom of Information, whether the Commission on Freedom of Information's terms of reference will permit it to consider the effective application of the provisions of the Freedom of Information Act 2000 to private companies that are providing under contract any service whose provision is the function of a public authority under section 5(1)(b) of that Act.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8036","8036"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391282","2015-09-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to increase the number of people employed in engineering from low income backgrounds; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8008","8008"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391284","2015-09-07","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate he has made of the value of the Government Art Collection.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7957","7957"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391290","2015-09-07","HM Treasury","2015-07-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the potential contribution of self-employed people to achieving the objectives set out in his Department's document, Fixing the Foundations: Creating a more prosperous nation, published in July 2015.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7913","7913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391294","2015-09-07","HM Treasury","2015-07-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people in Scotland have made use of the new pension flexibilities introduced on 6 April 2015.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7915","7915"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391296","2015-09-07","HM Treasury","2015-07-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people in Scotland have received guidance from the Pension Wise guidance service (a) face-to-face, (b) by telephone and (c) online.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7916","7916"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391299","2015-09-07","HM Treasury","2015-07-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people in Scotland who have made use of the pension flexibilities introduced on 6 April 2015 received guidance from the Pension Wise guidance service (a) by telephone, (b) face-to-face and (c) online.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7917","7917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391301","2015-09-07","HM Treasury","2015-07-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will publish his Department's research on the effect of his policies on tax-free childcare on the labour market.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7920","7920"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391303","2015-09-07","HM Treasury","2015-07-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what his policy is on the taxation of high sugar and high salt food and drinks.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7965","7965"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391306","2015-09-07","HM Treasury","2015-07-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what support his Department is providing to promote the growth of the FinTech industry.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7976","7976"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391308","2015-09-07","HM Treasury","2015-07-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent estimate he has made of levels of household debt in households where at least one adult is in work.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8019","8019"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391310","2015-09-07","HM Treasury","2015-07-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what meetings he has had with Leeds City Region Local Enterprise Partnership since the 2015 General Election; and what plans he has to meet with that organisation before 15 August 2015.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8040","8040"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391312","2015-09-07","HM Treasury","2015-07-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to paragraph 1.288 of the Summer Budget 2015, what process he plans for the establishment of new Enterprise Zones; and by when he plans to open the next bidding round for such zones.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8043","8043"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391314","2015-09-07","HM Treasury","2015-07-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to his statement of 29 April 2015 to the Dewsbury Reporter, whether it is his policy to establish an Enterprise Zone for Dewsbury; and what targets he has set for the process of establishing such a zone to (a) commence and (b) be concluded.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8044","8044"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391316","2015-09-07","HM Treasury","2015-07-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what support the Government is providing to (a) mutual savings banks and (b) credit unions in (a) the UK, (b) Scotland and (c) Coatbridge, Chryston and Bellshill constituency.","Biography information for Philip Boswell","Phil Boswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8051","8051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391318","2015-09-07","HM Treasury","2015-07-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will conduct an assessment of the potential effect of proposed changes to tax credits and housing benefit in the Summer Budget 2015 on the number of abortions in the UK.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8088","8088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391320","2015-09-07","HM Treasury","2015-07-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 20 June 2015 to Question 6981, whether agricultural vehicles used for journeys of more than 1.5 kilometres on public roads will be exempt from paying Vehicle Excise Duty.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8082","8082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391322","2015-09-07","HM Treasury","2015-07-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will publish a distributional analysis of the effect of the measures announced in the Summer Budget 2015 on people in each income group decile.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8089","8089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391324","2015-09-07","HM Treasury","2015-07-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will publish a distributional analysis of the effect of the Summer Budget 2015 for (a) 2015-16 and (b) 2016-17.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8090","8090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391326","2015-09-07","HM Treasury","2015-07-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the terms of reference are for his Department's forthcoming review of debt administration.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8110","8110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391328","2015-09-07","HM Treasury","2015-07-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the timetable is for his Department's forthcoming review of debt administration.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8111","8111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391330","2015-09-07","HM Treasury","2015-07-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether his Department's joint legal review of debt administration with the Insolvency Service plans to address long-standing issues within the debt advice sector.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8112","8112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391332","2015-09-07","HM Treasury","2015-07-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether his Department plans to implement a statutory scheme for the regulation of debt management services.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8113","8113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391334","2015-09-07","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what investment in infrastructure the Government plans to make in (a) Copeland constituency and (b) Cumbria as part of the Northern Powerhouse initiative.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8098","8098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391336","2015-09-07","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many (a) whole time, (b) retained and (c) control firefighters were employed by each UK fire and rescue service in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8101","8101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391338","2015-09-07","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what risk assessment he has made of the proposed merger of the Dorset and Wiltshire fire services.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8102","8102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391340","2015-09-07","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on front-line services of the merger of the Dorset and Wiltshire fire services.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8103","8103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391342","2015-09-07","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to protect mature trees in urban areas; and what support his Department provides to local authorities for such protection.","Biography information for Mr Nick Clegg","Mr Nick Clegg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8007","8007"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391345","2015-09-07","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to section 9.15 of HM Treasury's policy paper, Fixing the foundations: creating a more prosperous nation, published on 10 July 2015, Cm 9098, what steps he is taking to ensure proposals for automatic planning permission for brownfield sites include adequate provisions to enable local authorities to ensure new homes meet affordable housing standards under section 106 of the Growth and Infrastructure Act 2013.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8021","8021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391347","2015-09-07","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to section 9.15 of HM Treasury's policy paper, Fixing the foundations: creating a more prosperous nation, published on 10 July 2015, Cm 9098, what steps he is taking to ensure proposals for automatic planning permission for brownfield sites ensure that local communities are consulted on such developments; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8022","8022"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391349","2015-09-07","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to section 9.15 of HM Treasury's policy paper, Fixing the foundations: creating a more prosperous nation, published on 10 July 2015, Cm 9098, what steps he is taking to ensure proposals for automatic planning permission on brownfield sites enable local authorities to provide for adequate infrastructure in such applications.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8023","8023"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391352","2015-09-07","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to section 9.15 of HM Treasury's policy paper, Fixing the foundations: creating a more prosperous nation, published on 10 July 2015, Cm 9098, what steps he is taking to ensure proposals for automatic planning permission for brownfield sites include adequate provisions to enable local authorities to ensure new houses meet quality and space standards.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8020","8020"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391354","2015-09-07","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to encourage building on brownfield sites.","Biography information for Mr Nick Clegg","Mr Nick Clegg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7993","7993"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391356","2015-09-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will set a target for tree planting by 2020.","Biography information for Mr Nick Clegg","Mr Nick Clegg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7994","7994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391358","2015-09-07","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to encourage young people to stand for local elections.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7958","7958"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391361","2015-09-07","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the proportion of social housing in England which is affected by Stachybotrys chartarum and Aspergillus niger; and what steps his Department is taking to tackle incidence of such molds.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7905","7905"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391363","2015-09-07","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many families are in the Troubled Families programme; and what estimate he has made of the average cost to the public purse for each family which has participated in that programme to date.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7919","7919"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391367","2015-09-07","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how much funding the BBC has received from the EU in the last five years; and what conditions were attached to the use of such funding.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7907","7907"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391372","2015-09-07","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many incidents at betting shops relating to fixed-odds betting terminals police officers have attended in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7897","7897"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391373","2015-09-07","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent estimate he has made of the number of fixed-odds betting terminals in Sheffield, Heeley constituency.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7898","7898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391374","2015-09-07","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of the player protection measures on fixed-odds betting terminals introduced in April 2015.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7921","7921"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391375","2015-09-07","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether the Government plans to announce a spectrum auction by 2020.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8013","8013"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391376","2015-09-07","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment his Department has made of the increase in the amount of radio spectrum which will be made available to the private sector by 2020.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8014","8014"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391377","2015-09-07","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent estimate he has made of the number of people who participate in watersports.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8028","8028"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391378","2015-09-07","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department is taking to encourage more young people to participate in watersports.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8029","8029"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391379","2015-09-07","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions he has had with the Northern Ireland Executive on support for Ulster-Scots (a) language, (b) culture and (c) history.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8030","8030"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391380","2015-09-07","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what conversations his Department has had with National Gallery (a) staff, (b) management and (c) other relevant stakeholders on the National Gallery's decision to privatise its security service.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8061","8061"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391381","2015-09-07","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, when he plans to reply to the letter to him dated 4 June 2015 from the right hon. Member for Manchester, Gorton with regard to Nikita Standekwick.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8122","8122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391382","2015-09-07","Ministry of Defence","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the UK's airborne early warning aircraft capability is for air and maritime threat to the UK.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8118","8118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391383","2015-09-07","Ministry of Defence","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what airborne early warning aircraft capability he plans will be available to the new aircraft carriers joining the UK fleet.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8119","8119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391384","2015-09-07","Ministry of Defence","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what search and rescue capability exists within the RAF covering missing aircraft in the North Atlantic.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8120","8120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391385","2015-09-07","Ministry of Defence","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that UK security assistance to the government of Nigeria to tackle Boko Haram is not diverted or misused for corrupt ends.","Biography information for Stephen Phillips","Stephen Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8069","8069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391386","2015-09-07","Ministry of Defence","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what conditions are attached to the receipt of security assistance from the UK by the government of Nigeria.","Biography information for Stephen Phillips","Stephen Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8070","8070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391387","2015-09-07","Ministry of Defence","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Written Statement on UK Embedded forces, Official Report, HCWS149, 20 July 2015, what provision he has made with the Syrian government for the repatriation of UK military personnel flying missions over Syrian territory in the event of an allied aircraft containing UK personnel being shot down.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8081","8081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391388","2015-09-07","Ministry of Defence","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the conditions attached as part of the arrangement whereby the government of Nigeria receives security assistance from the UK includes a requirement (a) that individuals accused or convicted of corruption will be prevented from participating in military training and (b) for budget transparency.","Biography information for Stephen Phillips","Stephen Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8071","8071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391389","2015-09-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department is taking to ensure the non-diversion of controlled goods to Nigeria.","Biography information for Stephen Phillips","Stephen Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8072","8072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391390","2015-09-07","Ministry of Defence","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many members of the US armed forces have been embedded in the UK armed forces in each month since May 2010.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8058","8058"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391391","2015-09-07","Ministry of Defence","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many members of the British Special Forces were embedded with US operations against ISIS in (a) Iraq and (b) Syria in each month since May 2014.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8059","8059"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391392","2015-09-07","Ministry of Defence","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 13 July 2015, Official Report, column 580, whether the Government has sought permission from the Syrian government for Royal Air Force intelligence surveillance and reconnaissance aircraft to operate over Syria; and when such permission was granted.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7946","7946"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391393","2015-09-07","Ministry of Defence","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the cost to his Department's budget has been of the use of HMS Enterprise in the Mediterranean.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7982","7982"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391394","2015-09-07","Ministry of Defence","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many people based in Cumbria his Department has employed in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7964","7964"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391395","2015-09-07","Ministry of Defence","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will extend his Department's criteria for admission to training for sensitive officer roles to include citizens of countries that are signatories to the UKUSA Agreement who are resident in the UK.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7926","7926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391396","2015-09-07","Department for Education","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many state-maintained primary schools in England have no male teachers on their permanent staff.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7906","7906"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391397","2015-09-07","Department for Education","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what guidance her Department issued to primary school head teachers on working with pupils who wanted to fast during Ramadan.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7927","7927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391398","2015-09-07","Department for Education","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when the Government plans to issue guidance on progress of pupils with SEN.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7928","7928"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391399","2015-09-07","Department for Education","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many childminders have registered with childminder agencies to date.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7899","7899"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391400","2015-09-07","Department for Education","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her Department's target was for the number of childminders to register with childminder agencies.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7900","7900"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391401","2015-09-07","Department for Education","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans her Department has to review (a) standards of foster care and (b) criteria for becoming a foster carer.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7903","7903"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391402","2015-09-07","Department for Education","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department plans to take to ensure that foster care is of the highest possible standard.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7904","7904"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391403","2015-09-07","Department for Education","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what regulations cover the provision of school nurses in (a) local authority schools, (b) private schools and (c) free schools.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7972","7972"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391404","2015-09-07","Department for Education","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment has been made of the quality of the provision, coverage and monitoring of school nurses in private and free schools.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7973","7973"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391405","2015-09-07","Department for Education","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what training and development is provided to staff in early years settings in (a) the identification of and (b) support for children with speech, language and communication needs.","Biography information for Nick Smith","Nick Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7968","7968"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391406","2015-09-07","Department for Education","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when she expects to approve the redesignation of Hawthorns School in Denton and Reddish constituency as a teaching school.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7969","7969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391407","2015-09-07","Department for Education","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the childhood literacy rate was in (a) Holborn and St Pancras constituency, (b) the London Borough of Camden, (c) London and (d) England in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Keir Starmer","Keir Starmer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7966","7966"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391408","2015-09-07","Department for Education","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many childcare places are available in schools for children eligible for the current 15 hours a week free childcare; and how many such places are registered on the Early Years Register.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7948","7948"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391409","2015-09-07","Department for Education","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many childcare places are available in schools; and how many such places are registered on the Early Years Register.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7949","7949"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391410","2015-09-07","Department for Education","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many childcare places are available in schools for children aged five and under; and how many such places are registered on the Early Years Register.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7947","7947"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391411","2015-09-07","Department for Education","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many special educational needs co-ordinators were employed in each financial year since 2009.","Biography information for Nick Smith","Nick Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7967","7967"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391412","2015-09-07","Department for Education","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what entry-level qualifications are available to students with special educational needs who are educated in a special school setting.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7999","7999"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391413","2015-09-07","Department for Education","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to support plans for development of the site and premises of St Andrew the Apostle Greek Orthodox Free School.","Biography information for Mr David Burrowes","Mr David Burrowes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8049","8049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391414","2015-09-07","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment she has made of the potential effect of the removal of onshore windfarm subsidy on business growth in the wind energy sector over the next five years.","Biography information for Mr Nick Clegg","Mr Nick Clegg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8091","8091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391415","2015-09-07","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what measures she is taking ahead of the COP21 UN Climate Change Summit to ensure successful outcomes.","Biography information for Mr Nick Clegg","Mr Nick Clegg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8062","8062"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391416","2015-09-07","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate she has made of the total cost of smart meters being delivered to (a) 100 per cent of customers and (b) 80 per cent of customers by 2020.","Biography information for Kelly Tolhurst","Kelly Tolhurst","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8075","8075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391417","2015-09-07","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps she is taking to ensure that the smart meter programme will not exceed the projected costs set out in her Department's impact assessment published in January 2014.","Biography information for Kelly Tolhurst","Kelly Tolhurst","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8076","8076"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391418","2015-09-07","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the reason is for the difference between the estimated cost of the Smart Metering Implementation Programme of £10.9 billion included in her Department's Third Annual Report on the roll-out of Smart Meters, December 2014 and the whole life costs of £19.25 billion included in the Major Project Authority's Portfolio data for her Department of June 2015.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8015","8015"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391419","2015-09-07","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if she will take steps to ensure that developers are required to register solar panels with British Gas before they sell their properties.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7981","7981"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391420","2015-09-07","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if she will take steps to ensure that British Gas increases the transparency and efficacy of the process for registering solar panels.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7980","7980"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391421","2015-09-07","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what progress she has made on reducing the time taken for homeowners to switch energy and gas supplier; and what forecast she has made of the effect on switching times of the completion of the smart metering implementation programme.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7974","7974"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391422","2015-09-07","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if she will review the effects to date of the use of smart meters; and if she will estimate how much consumers reduce gas and electricity usage once a smart meter has been installed.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7975","7975"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391423","2015-09-07","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if she will make it her policy to obtain binding commitments from her international counterparts at forthcoming global talks on climate change.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7922","7922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391424","2015-09-07","Department for Transport","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how his Department monitors and enforces International Maritime Organisation regulation on air quality in cities.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7970","7970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391425","2015-09-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment her Department has made of the cleanliness of beaches in (a) Copeland and (b) Cumbria.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7961","7961"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391426","2015-09-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to reduce levels of marine pollution on the Cumbrian coast.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7960","7960"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391427","2015-09-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment her Department has made of the level of marine pollution in (a) Copeland, (b) Cumbria and (c) England.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7959","7959"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391428","2015-09-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will (a) publish separate 25-year plans to restore biodiversity and to grow more, buy more and sell more British food and (b) take steps to ensure that each such plan will contribute to the other's objectives.","Biography information for Albert Owen","Albert Owen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8095","8095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391429","2015-09-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions her Department has with shooting organisations before adding a specific bird or mammal to the protected list.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8034","8034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391430","2015-09-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will (a) publish a 25-year plan to restore biodiversity in the UK and (b) consult with devolved Parliamentary bodies and agencies on that plan.","Biography information for Albert Owen","Albert Owen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8096","8096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391431","2015-09-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will publish a 25-year plan to restore biodiversity in the UK that includes (a) the biodiversity of the UK Overseas Territories and (b) an impact assessment on the effect of UK production and consumption on biodiversity in other countries.","Biography information for Albert Owen","Albert Owen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8097","8097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391432","2015-09-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what percentage rental increases tenants of New Covent Garden Market Authority have been subject to in the last five years; and what such increases that Authority has planned for future years.","Biography information for Chris Heaton-Harris","Chris Heaton-Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8115","8115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391433","2015-09-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that crimes committed against British nationals by family members overseas are investigated and prosecuted.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8100","8100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391434","2015-09-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received of the provision of financial assistance from Saudi Arabian citizens to support ISIS activities in Syria and Iraq; and what discussions he has held with foreign counterparts on tackling such assistance.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8060","8060"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391435","2015-09-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 16 July 2015 to Question 6077, how many (a) meetings and (b) emails his Department has had with the organisation Action on Smoking and Health in drafting these guidelines.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8083","8083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391436","2015-09-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 16 July 2015 to Question 6077, which organisations he consulted when drafting that guidance.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8084","8084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391437","2015-09-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will raise the case of Mr Tsege with the US administration before President Obama's visit to Ethiopia.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8079","8079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391438","2015-09-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Israeli counterpart on the demolition of the village of Susiya in the West Bank.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8009","8009"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391439","2015-09-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received from (a) the Israeli government, (b) the Palestinian government and (c) non-governmental bodies on the demolition of Susiya.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8010","8010"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391440","2015-09-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 16 July 2015 to Question 6077, if he will publish and place in the Library the guidance on engaging with the tobacco industry issued to staff in December 2013.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7910","7910"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391441","2015-09-07","Department of Health","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 25 June 2015 to Question 2842, what the average yearly earnings were of GPs employed directly by the NHS in (a) England and (b) London in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7918","7918"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391442","2015-09-07","Department of Health","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 25 June 2015 to Question 2847, what the total amount of funding was under the (a) global sum and (b) Minimum Practice Income Guarantee received by GP practices in (i) England, (ii) London, (iii) the London Borough of Islington and (iv) Islington South and Finsbury constituency in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7909","7909"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391443","2015-09-07","Department of Health","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will review the potential merits of raising the savings threshold for payment of social care from £23,500 to account for the wide spectrum of medical issues covered by social care.","Biography information for Julian Knight","Julian Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7901","7901"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391444","2015-09-07","Department of Health","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many operations to treat respiratory disease the NHS has undertaken in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7937","7937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391445","2015-09-07","Cabinet Office","2015-07-20","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the numbers of (a) male and (b) female deaths caused by respiratory diseases in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7934","7934"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391446","2015-09-07","Department of Health","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many bed days each year are used by the NHS for treating respiratory diseases.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7935","7935"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391447","2015-09-07","Department of Health","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of working days lost each year due to respiratory diseases.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7933","7933"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391448","2015-09-07","Department of Health","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the implications for his policies of the recommendations of the British Medical Association Report, Food for Thought, published in July 2015.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8016","8016"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391449","2015-09-07","Department of Health","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if his Department will consider the proposal by the British Medical Association to implement a 20 per cent tax on drinks high in sugar.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8017","8017"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391450","2015-09-07","Department of Health","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many and what proportion of GP practices in (a) England, (b) London, (c) the London Borough of Islington and (d) Islington South and Finsbury constituency are covered by (i) general medical services, (ii) personal medical services and (iii) alternative provider medical services contracts.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7998","7998"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391451","2015-09-07","Department of Health","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that patients from the South Asian community are able to benefit fully from new treatments made available through NHS England's hepatitis C commissioning policy.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7997","7997"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391452","2015-09-07","Department of Health","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what provision his Department plans to make under the Healthier Together reforms for patients in the North West of England with severe and complex cardiac disease who need tertiary cardiorespiratory services.","Biography information for Sir Graham Brady","Mr Graham Brady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7986","7986"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391453","2015-09-07","Department of Health","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of the number of people in the South Asian community who are infected with genotype 3 hepatitis C.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7995","7995"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391454","2015-09-07","Department of Health","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps the NHS is taking to improve hepatitis C diagnosis and treatment rates among the South Asian community.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7996","7996"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391455","2015-09-07","Department of Health","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what account was taken of the financial costs and workforce implications of maintaining high-risk general surgery at University Hospital South Manchester to support the provision of tertiary services for the purposes of the Decision Making Business Case under the Healthier Together programme; and whether those factors were included in the financial modelling for options 4.3 and 4.4 of that programme.","Biography information for Sir Graham Brady","Mr Graham Brady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7990","7990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391456","2015-09-07","Department of Health","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if his Department will encourage makers of drinks high in sugar to consider (a) product reformulation, (b) smaller pack sizes and (c) increased promotion of low and no calorie drinks.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7991","7991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391457","2015-09-07","Department of Health","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the average length of stay in hospital for people with dementia in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7983","7983"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391458","2015-09-07","Department of Health","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans his Department has to encourage people to include fruit and vegetables in their diets using (a) subsidisation and (b) other new methods.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7992","7992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391459","2015-09-07","Department of Health","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of hospital beds in England which are occupied by people with dementia.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7984","7984"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391460","2015-09-07","Department of Health","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what targets his Department has set for reducing unnecessary hospital admissions for people with dementia.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7985","7985"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391461","2015-09-07","Department of Health","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the (a) primary, (b) inpatient, (c) hospital day and (d) outpatient care costs are to the NHS of treating respiratory diseases.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7936","7936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391462","2015-09-07","Department of Health","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what analysis his Department and NHS England have carried out to determine what standard of high-risk general surgery a site should be providing in order to be an appropriate site for carrying out (a) complex cardiac surgery and (b) other tertiary services.","Biography information for Sir Graham Brady","Mr Graham Brady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7987","7987"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391463","2015-09-07","Department of Health","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that (a) the London Borough of Enfield and (b) other local authorities receive their target funding allocations for public health.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7977","7977"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391464","2015-09-07","Department of Health","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, for what reasons Quality and Safety was not included as a factor for deciding the fourth specialist hospital site proposed by Healthier Together.","Biography information for Sir Graham Brady","Mr Graham Brady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7988","7988"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391465","2015-09-07","Department of Health","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the hospital mortality rate was for each of the Greater Manchester acute hospital trusts in the most recent year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Sir Graham Brady","Mr Graham Brady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7989","7989"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391466","2015-09-07","Department of Health","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what monitoring his Department undertakes of the implementation of guidance in the document, Immunisation against infectious disease, and the section 7A agreement between his Department and NHS England.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8068","8068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391467","2015-09-07","Department of Health","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Written Statement of 16 July 2015, HCWS114, on NHS Remuneration: Doctors and Dentists, what his definition is of a seven day health service.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8064","8064"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391468","2015-09-07","Department of Health","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Written Statement of 16 July 2015, HCWS114, on NHS Remuneration: Doctors and Dentists, by how much he expects the cost of hospital consultants' pay to increase in each year to 2020.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8063","8063"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391469","2015-09-07","Department of Health","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Written Statement of 16 July 2015, HCWS114, on NHS Remuneration: Doctors and Dentists, what assessment he has made of the effect of proposed changes to the consultant contract on the availability of routine hospital appointments on week days.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8065","8065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391470","2015-09-07","Department of Health","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to support local authorities in providing a full and comprehensive seven day social care service to support patients discharged from hospitals at weekends.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8073","8073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391471","2015-09-07","Department of Health","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the implications for its policies of the Carbohydrates and Health Report 2015, produced by the Scientific Advisory Committee on Nutrition.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8080","8080"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391472","2015-09-07","Department of Health","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his policy is on use of grant funding provided by his Department to third parties to lobby his Department.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8047","8047"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391473","2015-09-07","Department of Health","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment Change4Life and Public Health England made of the effect on public perception of the Change4Life programme of entering into a partnership with Disney when selecting Disney for that partnership.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8045","8045"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391474","2015-09-07","Department of Health","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to his speech at Nelson Medical Practice, London, of 19 June 2015, entitled A New Deal for General Practice, how he plans to increase by 5,000 the number of GPs working in England.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8055","8055"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391475","2015-09-07","Department of Health","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he had with the British Medical Association on proposed changes to the consultant contract prior to his King's Fund speech of 16 July 2015, entitled Making healthcare more human-centred and not system-centred.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8056","8056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391476","2015-09-07","Department of Health","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) letters and (b) emails his Department has received from Action on Smoking and Health in each of the last seven years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8048","8048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391477","2015-09-07","Department of Health","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions he has had with his counterpart in the Northern Ireland Executive on the availability of drugs to treat cancer.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8032","8032"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391478","2015-09-07","Department of Health","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what amount from the Cancer Drugs Fund is available to be spent by the Northern Ireland Executive in (a) 2015-16 and (b) 2016-17.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8033","8033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391479","2015-09-07","Department of Health","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average waiting time is for an assessment of patients with continence problems.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8005","8005"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391480","2015-09-07","Department of Health","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans his Department has to upgrade diagnostic equipment in GP surgeries across England and Wales; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8006","8006"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391481","2015-09-07","Department of Health","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to increase the level of recruitment of GPs across England and Wales; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8027","8027"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391482","2015-09-07","Department of Health","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what preventative treatments are available in the NHS for lymphoedema.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8116","8116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391483","2015-09-07","Department of Health","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people were (a) diagnosed and (b) treated for lymphoedema in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8117","8117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391484","2015-09-07","Department of Health","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of additional (a) consultants, (b) nurses, (c) physiotherapists, (d) pharmacists, (e) pathologists, (f) phlebotomists, (g) radiographers, (h) porters, (i) receptionists, (j) administrators, (k) health care support workers and (l) discharge service staff who will be required to work in NHS hospitals in England in order to extend services to seven days a week.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8074","8074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391485","2015-09-07","Home Office","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what representations she has received from shooting sports organisations on the cost of obtaining shotgun and firearms certificates; and if she will take steps to ensure that the cost of obtaining such certificates does not rise at a rate above inflation.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8031","8031"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391486","2015-09-07","Home Office","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people were held on pre-charge bail for (a) three to 12 months and (b) over 12 months in the last year.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8026","8026"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391487","2015-09-07","Home Office","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) men, (b) women and (c) children came forward as potential victims of human trafficking in each year since 2012; how many such people (i) were returned to their country of origin and (ii) stayed on in the UK; how many of those who stayed in the UK were granted asylum; and what data is collected from each shelter administered by the Salvation Army scheme.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8025","8025"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391488","2015-09-07","Home Office","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what funding the Government is providing to (a) Kirklees Council and (b) West Yorkshire Police under the Prevent Strategy in (i) 2015-16 and (ii) each of the next three financial years.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8041","8041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391489","2015-09-07","Home Office","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans she has to increase support for projects under the Prevent strategy in Dewsbury constituency.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8039","8039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391490","2015-09-07","Home Office","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what consultation her Department has carried out with community organisations in Dewsbury constituency on implementation of the Prevent strategy.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8037","8037"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391491","2015-09-07","Home Office","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans she has to provide additional resources for policing in Dewsbury constituency.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8038","8038"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391492","2015-09-07","Home Office","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will publish an impact assessment of the reduced standard rate of asylum cash support due to take effect from 10 August 2015; and if she will make an assessment of the effects of that reduction on (a) single parents and their children, (b) families with children and (c) other people seeking asylum.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8052","8052"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391493","2015-09-07","Home Office","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what guidelines her Department issues to police forces on requiring lists of goods seized from a company during an investigation to be produced within a specified timescale.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8094","8094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391494","2015-09-07","Home Office","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with which non-governmental organisations and individuals her Department has liaised on setting up the Extremism Analysis Unit.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8086","8086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391495","2015-09-07","Home Office","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people granted temporary asylum as children have been denied permanent asylum upon applying as an adult in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Kirsty Blackman","Kirsty Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8066","8066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391496","2015-09-07","Home Office","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what organisations and programmes based in Dewsbury constituency have received funding or support under the Prevent strategy in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8042","8042"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391497","2015-09-07","Home Office","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many full-time equivalent neighbourhood support officers have been employed by Cumbria Constabulary in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8077","8077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391498","2015-09-07","Home Office","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will publish a list of each organisation and individual in receipt of funding under the Prevent strategy.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7945","7945"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391499","2015-09-07","Home Office","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions she has had with (a) the post office network and (b) educational establishments on the management of biometric residence permits at the start of the academic year 2015-16.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7950","7950"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391500","2015-09-07","Home Office","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what criteria are used by her Department to select the post offices used for the issue of biometric residence permits.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7951","7951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391501","2015-09-07","Home Office","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which UK post offices are approved to issue biometric residence permits.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7952","7952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391502","2015-09-07","Home Office","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the total cost to the public purse was of administering shelters organised by the Salvation Army where potential trafficked victims have been placed; how much such funding goes to individual non-governmental organisations who ran such shelters in 2014; and how much of the overall Government grant for these shelters is spent by the Salvation Army on administration and running costs.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8024","8024"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391503","2015-09-07","Home Office","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what she plans for the organisational structure of the Extremism Analysis Unit to be; how many staff she plans to be employed in that unit; and what estimate she has made of the total annual cost of running that unit.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7940","7940"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391504","2015-09-07","Home Office","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what public consultation she is undertaking on the setting up of the Extremism Analysis Unit.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7941","7941"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391505","2015-09-07","Home Office","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to ensure parliamentary scrutiny of the work of the Extremism Analysis Unit.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7942","7942"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391506","2015-09-07","Home Office","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, under what methodology and criteria the Extremism Analysis Unit will blacklist individuals and organisations.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7943","7943"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391507","2015-09-07","Home Office","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will publish the remit of her Department's Extremism Analysis Unit.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7944","7944"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391508","2015-09-07","Home Office","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will take steps to allow organisations and individuals to appeal against being placed on the Extremism Analysis Unit's blacklist.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7939","7939"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391509","2015-09-07","Home Office","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what guidance her Department has published on the timely notification by police services of notifications of intent to prosecute in incidents of motoring offences.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7929","7929"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391510","2015-09-07","Home Office","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the maximum period of time is that a person can be held on pre-charge bail.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7911","7911"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391511","2015-09-07","Department for Transport","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will introduce licensing conditions for taxi drivers to ensure they will carry guide dogs and other assistance dogs.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7896","7896"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391512","2015-09-07","Home Office","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the explanatory note on the Asylum Support (Amendment No. 3) Regulations 2015, on what basis it was concluded that those Regulations would have no impact on the voluntary sector.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7908","7908"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391513","2015-09-07","House of Commons Commission","2015-07-20","To ask the Rt. Hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington representing the House of Commons Commission, pursuant to the Answer of 22 June 2015 to Question 2662, if he will extend the provision of the induction loop system to ensure people who have hearing loss or who are deaf can follow proceedings in all meeting rooms using a personal loop inducted into that system.","Biography information for Mr David Winnick","Mr David Winnick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7923","7923"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391514","2015-09-07","Ministry of Justice","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to ensure the continuation of legal aid in the form of duty solicitor provision in Ceredigion.","Biography information for Mr Mark Williams","Mr Mark Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8011","8011"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391515","2015-09-07","Ministry of Justice","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to ensure that debt solicitors provided through legal aid provide services bilingually in Wales.","Biography information for Mr Mark Williams","Mr Mark Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8012","8012"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391516","2015-09-07","Ministry of Justice","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many applications for legal aid have been made in (a) Copeland and (b) Cumbria in each of the last 10 years; and how many such applications have been successful.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7963","7963"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391517","2015-09-07","Ministry of Justice","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate has been made of the number of criminal appeals departments in law firms that have closed since the changes to legal aid funding introduced in the Legal Aid, Sentencing and Punishment of Offenders Act 2012 were introduced.","Biography information for John Pugh","John Pugh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8046","8046"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391518","2015-09-07","Ministry of Justice","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when he plans to respond to the email sent by the hon. Member for East Worthing and Shoreham on 13 May regarding the case of a constituent receiving inadequate support and provision on leaving jail, and the follow-up email sent in 17 June.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8114","8114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391519","2015-09-07","Department for Transport","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans he has to improve passenger services through Woodgrange Park rail station.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8104","8104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391520","2015-09-07","Department for Transport","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent estimate he has made of the cost of the proposed New Generation Trolleybus scheme in Leeds.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8057","8057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391521","2015-09-07","Department for Transport","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what progress has been made on the Inquiry Inspector's report following the public inquiry into the New Generation Trolleybus scheme; and when he plans to make a further announcement on that scheme.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8087","8087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391522","2015-09-07","Department for Transport","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 14 July 21015 to Question 7026, what the cost-benefit ratio was for North TransPennine electrification programme on the most recent date for which figures are available; and what the cost-benefit ratio was for North TransPennine electrification programme when combined with track improvements on that date.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8093","8093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391523","2015-09-07","Department for Transport","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 14 July 21015 to Question 6468, when the new round of bidding to the New Station Fund will (a) begin and (b) conclude.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8092","8092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391524","2015-09-07","Department for Transport","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much and what proportion of its expenditure the Mode Shift Revenue Support scheme granted to (a) rail and (b) maritime freight operators in each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8000","8000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391525","2015-09-07","Department for Transport","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions his Department has had with Govia Thameslink Railway on the talks between London-based train operators and Transport for London aimed at sharing pay-as-you-go fares on suburban rail routes.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7979","7979"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391526","2015-09-07","Department for Transport","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many people use each train station in (a) Copeland and (b) Cumbria each year.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7962","7962"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391527","2015-09-07","Department for Transport","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what role his Department has in setting fares on trains operated by Govia Thameslink Railway.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7978","7978"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391528","2015-09-07","Department for Transport","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment has been made of the implications for his Department's policies of the increase in the number of privately owned drones and its effects on safety for civil aviation.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7971","7971"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391529","2015-09-07","Department for Transport","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 8 July 2015 to Question 4820 on railways: performance standards, what permission his Department has granted to Govia Thameslink Railway to (a) vary ticket prices and (b) enter into an agreement with Transport for London to share the same-pay-as-you-go fares on suburban rail routes in London.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7902","7902"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391530","2015-09-07","Department for Transport","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to tackle air pollution from road vehicles; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7938","7938"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391531","2015-09-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, in which post codes in the UK agreed limits for air pollution were breached in the most recent year available.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7932","7932"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391532","2015-09-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many lone parent families in Scotland have been affected by the benefit cap to date; and how many such families have (a) one child, (b) two and (c) three children under five.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7931","7931"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391533","2015-09-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make it his policy to conduct an annual equalities impact assessment of the effect in Scotland of the welfare changes announced in the Summer Budget 2015.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7930","7930"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391534","2015-09-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Oral Question  of the hon. Member for Denton and Reddish of 15 July 2015, Official Report, column 889, on state pensions for women, if he will take steps to provide financial support to those women affected by those changes.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7924","7924"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391535","2015-09-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Oral Question  of the hon. Member for Denton and Reddish of 21 July 2015, Official Report, column 889, on state pensions for women, what recent discussions the Minister of State for Pensions has had with (a) his Ministerial colleagues and (b) campaign groups on the effect of those changes on women born in the 1950s.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7925","7925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391536","2015-09-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to reduce delays in the payments of personal independence payments and universal credit.","Biography information for Angela Crawley","Angela Crawley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7914","7914"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391537","2015-09-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will publish guidance for people with private sector pensions on the effect of decisions to change the basis on which pensions are uprated on those people.","Biography information for Angela Crawley","Angela Crawley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7912","7912"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391538","2015-09-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will adopt the definition of full employment used in the Europe 2020 strategy to define full employment in the UK.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7953","7953"
