"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686082","2017-02-09","Department for Education","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the average funding was for a primary school pupil in (a) England, (b) Surrey, (c) Oxfordshire, (d) London and (e) Haringey in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63490","63490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686083","2017-02-09","Department for Education","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many special needs assessments were undertaken in each school in England in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63538","63538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686084","2017-02-09","Department for Education","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans she has for the funding of a university in Hereford.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63544","63544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686085","2017-02-20","Department for Education","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when she plans to announce funding for the planned New Model in Technology and Engineering University in Hereford.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63550","63550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686086","2017-02-20","Department for Education","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to increase the number of applications from (a) male and (b) female applicants to early years  teacher training programmes.","Biography information for Karl McCartney","Karl McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63521","63521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686087","2017-02-09","Department for Education","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the average funding was for a secondary school pupil in (a) England, (b) Surrey, (c) Oxfordshire, (d) London and (e) Haringey in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63467","63467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686088","2017-02-09","Department for Education","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to increase the number of applications for early years teacher training programmes.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63445","63445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686089","2017-02-09","Department for Education","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she has visited any schools in Haringey since her appointment to her post.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63434","63434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686090","2017-02-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment she has made of the condition of the navigable waterways managed by the Environment Agency in the Anglian region.","Biography information for David Mackintosh","David Mackintosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63480","63480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686091","2017-02-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much the Environment Agency spent on the navigable waterways in the Anglian region in each of the last five years.","Biography information for David Mackintosh","David Mackintosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63481","63481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686092","2017-02-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much the Environment Agency plans to spend on the navigable waterways in the Anglian Region in each of the next three years.","Biography information for David Mackintosh","David Mackintosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63482","63482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686093","2017-02-09","Ministry of Defence","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the debate on the Armed Forces Covenant of 2 February 2017, HC column 1270, when he expects the alcohol working group to publish its findings.","Biography information for Dr Andrew Murrison","Dr Andrew Murrison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63542","63542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686094","2017-02-09","Ministry of Defence","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the debate on the Armed Forces Covenant of 2 February 2017, HC column 1270, whether Operation Banner veterans in receipt of invitations to provide witness accounts will be refunded the cost of legal advice.","Biography information for Dr Andrew Murrison","Dr Andrew Murrison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63543","63543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686096","2017-02-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to reduce the number of premature deaths attributed to particulate air pollution; and what assessment she has made of the implications for her Department's policies of Public Health England's report, Estimating local mortality burdens associated with particulate air pollution.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63494","63494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686097","2017-02-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions her Department's officials had with officials of the devolved institutions on preventing further outbreaks of avian influenza in the last three months.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63448","63448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686098","2017-02-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the badger vaccination programme in Ireland, what plans she has to introduce trials of oral bacillus calmette-guerin badger vaccinations in the UK.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63417","63417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686099","2017-02-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, from what countries dogs were imported into the UK for (a) non-commercial reasons under the Pet Travel Scheme and (b) commercial reasons in 2016.","Biography information for Neil Carmichael","Neil Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63358","63358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686100","2017-02-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what his assessment is of the current state of basic freedoms, the rule of law and democracy in Hong Kong; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63369","63369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686101","2017-02-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will review the effectiveness of the implementation of the Sino-British Joint Declaration.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63370","63370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686102","2017-02-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to fulfil the Government's obligations under the Sino-British Joint Declaration to monitor and speak out for basic freedoms and the rule of law in Hong Kong.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63367","63367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686103","2017-02-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the Hong Kong Government regarding (a) legal challenges against democratically elected legislators Nathan Law, Edward Yiu, Lau Siu-lai and Leung Kwok-hung and (b) rulings regarding Yau Wai-Chung and Sixtus Heung; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63368","63368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686104","2017-02-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the capacity of the Ukrainian Government to finance ongoing military operations in the east of that country; what reports he has received of shortfalls in salary payments to members of the Ukrainian armed forces; and what discussions he has had with his Ukrainian counterpart on those issues.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63384","63384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686105","2017-02-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his counterparts in (a) France, (b) Germany, (c) Ukraine and (d) Russia on progress made in meetings under the Normandy Format; when he expects the roadmap, announced by the group in October 2016, to be published; and what steps he is taking to help facilitate this process.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63392","63392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686106","2017-02-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his EU counterparts on the conflict in Ukraine.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63398","63398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686107","2017-02-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received on alleged human rights abuses committed by (a) armed militias and (b) Ukrainian Government troops in eastern Ukraine.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63389","63389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686108","2017-02-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his US counterpart on the conflict in Ukraine.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63399","63399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686109","2017-02-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to support efforts by the Government of Ukraine to tackle official corruption; and what assessment he has made of the progress of such efforts.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63391","63391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686110","2017-02-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to the Sri Lankan Government on the destruction of a church building in Pahariya in North West Sri Lanka in January 2017.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63449","63449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686111","2017-02-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the Government of Kenya on the incidence of home and farm seizures in that country.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63419","63419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686112","2017-02-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Dutch counterpart on implementation of the EU's Association Agreement with Ukraine; and what assessment he has made of the prospects for ratification of that agreement by the Netherlands.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63386","63386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686113","2017-02-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the EU's Association Agreement with Ukraine on the prospects for economic growth in that country.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63385","63385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686114","2017-02-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the progress of the Governments of (a) Ukraine and (b) Russia in implementing their respective obligations under the Minsk agreements; and when he expects those agreements to be implemented in full.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63393","63393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686115","2017-02-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his Russian counterparts on the conflict in Ukraine.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63400","63400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686116","2017-02-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to the Government of Ukraine on the passage of political and constitutional reforms stipulated by the Minsk agreements.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63390","63390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686117","2017-02-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his Ukrainian counterparts on the conflict in that country.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63401","63401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686118","2017-02-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his Filipino counterpart on extra-judicial killings in that country.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63323","63323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686119","2017-02-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many times (a) he and (b) the Minister for the Middle East and Africa have met representatives of Reprieve to discuss the case of Andargachew Tsege.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63341","63341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686120","2017-02-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make it his policy to make regular oral or written statements to the House on the situation in Libya.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63329","63329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686121","2017-02-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the prospects for a negotiated settlement between Ukraine and Russia on the status of Crimea.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63486","63486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686122","2017-02-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to the Israeli Prime Minister on the building of settlements.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63513","63513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686123","2017-02-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the treatment of Christians in Nepal.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63478","63478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686124","2017-02-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to the Nepal Government on permitting Christian non-governmental organisations to register and carry out humanitarian work unhindered in that country.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63479","63479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686125","2017-02-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has discussed tax (a) avoidance and (b) evasion with his counterpart in the Turks and Caicos Islands since the last Joint Ministerial Council.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63462","63462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686126","2017-02-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether (a) he and (b) the Minister for the Overseas Territories discussed the creation of public registers of beneficial ownership which name the owners of offshore companies with the Deputy Premier of Bermuda in the last six months.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63463","63463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686127","2017-02-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has discussed tax (a) avoidance and (b) evasion with his counterpart in Montserrat since the last Joint Ministerial Council.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63461","63461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686128","2017-02-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has discussed tax (a) avoidance and (b) evasion with his counterpart in the British Virgin Islands since the last Joint Ministerial Council.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63464","63464"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686129","2017-02-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has discussed tax (a) avoidance and (b) evasion with his counterpart in Bermuda since the last Joint Ministerial Council.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63465","63465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686130","2017-02-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has discussed tax (a) avoidance and (b) evasion with his counterpart in Anguilla since the last Joint Ministerial Council.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63466","63466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686131","2017-02-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what contact he has had with Fayez Sharary or his family since his detainment in Israel in September 2016.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63435","63435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686132","2017-02-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Israeli counterpart on the case of Fayez Sharary.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63436","63436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686133","2017-02-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he plans to meet his Israeli counterpart to discuss the retrospective legalisation of settlements in the occupied West Bank.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63431","63431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686134","2017-02-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the progress of the Colombian peace process.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63432","63432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686135","2017-02-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether (a) he or (b) the Minister of State for Europe and the Americas plans to visit Colombia in the near future.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63433","63433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686136","2017-02-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions his Department has had with officials from the OSCE Special Monitoring Mission in Ukraine on the withdrawal of heavy weapons from the Line of Contact; and what steps his Department is taking to deter violations of that requirement.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63427","63427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686137","2017-02-09","Department of Health","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what representations he has made to the Governments of (a) Pakistan and (b) China on the trafficking of human organs from those countries; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63418","63418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686138","2017-02-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the capacity of the OSCE Special Monitoring Mission in Ukraine to fulfil its responsibilities under the Minsk agreements; and what steps he is taking to support that work.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63442","63442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686139","2017-02-09","Department of Health","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent steps the NHS has taken to tackle trends in blood pressure related complaints among people in their 50s.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63424","63424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686140","2017-02-09","Department of Health","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many deaf people have received end of life care in the last five years.","Biography information for Alex Salmond","Alex Salmond","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63504","63504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686141","2017-02-09","Department of Health","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many NHS staff involved in end of life care have received bespoke British sign language and deaf awareness training for their work in the last five years.","Biography information for Alex Salmond","Alex Salmond","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63505","63505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686142","2017-02-20","Department of Health","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to improve the rates of early diagnosis for bowel cancer.","Biography information for Colleen Fletcher","Colleen Fletcher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63453","63453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686143","2017-02-09","Department of Health","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether an assessment has been made of the potential merits of making ketamine available on the NHS to help tackle alcohol dependency.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63422","63422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686144","2017-02-09","Department of Health","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps the NHS is taking to disseminate guidance on the benefits to hygiene of people in hospitals washing their hands.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63423","63423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686145","2017-02-09","Department of Health","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average time is for which applicants to the National Dental Performers' List wait for their application to be processed in (a) NPL1, (b) NPL2 and (c) NPL3 categories.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63437","63437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686146","2017-02-09","Department of Health","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many dentists in (a) NPL1, (b) NPL2 and (c) NPL3 categories are waiting for applications to the National Dental Performers List to be processed.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63438","63438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686147","2017-02-09","Department of Health","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many deaf people who have requested a British sign language interpreter at medical appointments have had their request fulfilled in the last five years.","Biography information for Alex Salmond","Alex Salmond","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63507","63507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686148","2017-02-09","Department of Health","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) staff in social care settings and (b) people providing care in people's own home have received bespoke British sign language and deaf awareness training in the last five years.","Biography information for Alex Salmond","Alex Salmond","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63506","63506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686149","2017-02-09","Department of Health","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the NHS has a standard procedure for booking British sign language interpreters; whether that guidance is publicised to NHS staff; and whether such staff can use it confidentially.","Biography information for Alex Salmond","Alex Salmond","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63509","63509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686150","2017-02-09","Department of Health","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many appointments have had to be postponed due to a British sign language interpreter (a) not being booked and (b) being unavailable in the last five years.","Biography information for Alex Salmond","Alex Salmond","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63508","63508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686151","2017-02-20","Department of Health","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many extractions of multiple teeth for children under the age of 18 in Peterborough and Stamford Hospitals NHS Foundation Trust took place in each year since 2005; what the cost of such extractions was in each such year; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stewart Jackson","Mr Stewart Jackson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63522","63522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686152","2017-02-20","Department of Health","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to assess the effectiveness of 5-aminolevulinic acid treatment for high grade brain tumours; and whether this treatment will be made available nationally.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63514","63514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686153","2017-02-09","Department of Health","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure relapsed and refractory Hodgkin lymphoma patients continue to have access to brentuximab vedotin.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63498","63498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686154","2017-02-09","Department of Health","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to ensure that palbociclib is made available to all eligible breast cancer patients.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63499","63499"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686155","2017-02-09","Department of Health","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to establish the Mental Trauma Service in Northern Ireland proposed in the Stormont House Agreement.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63496","63496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686156","2017-02-09","Department of Health","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what funding the Government provides to care for people affected by the troubles in Northern Ireland living in England.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63534","63534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686158","2017-02-09","Department of Health","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much funding was provided to mental health services in Northamptonshire in 2015-16; and how much is projected to be spent in 2016-17.","Biography information for David Mackintosh","David Mackintosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63396","63396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686159","2017-02-20","Department of Health","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 27 January 2017 to Question 60941, on blood: contamination, how many such applications have been received from bereaved people since 27 January 2017; and how many of those applications have been (a) accepted and (b) rejected.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63452","63452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686160","2017-02-20","Department of Health","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the capacity available in care homes in Coventry for patients who are ready to leave hospital.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63415","63415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686161","2017-02-20","Department of Health","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 29 January 2017 to Question 61554, what information on the availability of dental services his Department routinely collects.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63406","63406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686162","2017-02-20","Department of Health","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 30 January 2017 to Question 61555, how many children were seen in each 12 month period from 2010 to 2016; and what proportion of those patients were seen as an emergency appointment in each such period.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63404","63404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686163","2017-02-20","Department of Health","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 30 January 2017 to Question 61555, how many patients were seen in each 12 month period from 2010 to 2016; and what proportion of those patients were seen as an emergency appointment in each such period.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63405","63405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686164","2017-02-20","Department of Health","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with North Staffordshire Clinical Care Group on lines of responsibility for cancer and end-of-life care services delivered for the Group by private sector organisations.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63357","63357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686165","2017-02-20","Department of Health","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to improve the performance of the North West Ambulance Service; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63382","63382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686166","2017-02-09","Department of Health","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his policy is on clinical trials to genetically modify human embryos by means of mitochondrial transfer techniques with the intention of bringing those human embryos to full term and giving birth to them; and what assessment he has made of the risks to the health of trial subjects.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63363","63363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686167","2017-02-20","Department of Health","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he plans to take in response to the recent report published by the Care Quality Commission into the abuses and safety failures identified at Marie Stopes International clinics throughout the UK; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63378","63378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686168","2017-02-20","Department of Health","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he has taken to respond to the finding of Public Health England in the Public Health Burden of Alcohol and the Effectiveness and Cost-effectiveness of Alcohol Control Policies, published in December 2016, that increasing the price of alcohol products would save over a billion pounds a year over the next 20 years.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63379","63379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686169","2017-02-09","Department of Health","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his policy is on clinical trials involving children in the UK beginning before such trials are proven to be safe.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63364","63364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686170","2017-02-09","Department of Health","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department funds alternative treatments for mitochondrial disorders that (a) can treat those born with mitochondrial disease and (b) do not involve the creation of genetically modified human embryos; and what plans he has to do so in the future.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63365","63365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686171","2017-02-09","Department of Health","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will conduct a more detailed investigation into sex-selective abortions in England which takes into account (a) women born in the UK to parents of a different nationality and (b) the sub-populations within those countries.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63366","63366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686172","2017-02-09","Department of Health","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what response he plans to make to the Public Health England report which found minimum unit pricing to be a targeted intervention having the greatest effect on heavy drinkers while having a minimal effect on moderate drinkers.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63374","63374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686173","2017-02-09","Department of Health","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer to the hon. Member for Shipley of 25 January 2017 to Question 43975, on Action on Smoking and Health: complaints, what information his Department holds on whether it has received any complaints about that organisation since June 2016.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63359","63359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686174","2017-02-09","Department of Health","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 6 February 2017 to Question 62473, on Action on Smoking and Health, for what reason his Department does not hold records of complaints concerning that organisation.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63360","63360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686175","2017-02-09","Department of Health","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of availability of naloxone to treat drug-related disorders in (a) England, (b) the North West and (c) Lancashire.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63353","63353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686176","2017-02-20","Home Office","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many referrals to the National Referral Mechanism under the claim of adult-sexual exploitation resulted in positive conclusive decisions in (a) 2013, (b) 2014 and (c) 2015.","Biography information for Neil Carmichael","Neil Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63356","63356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686177","2017-02-09","Home Office","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment she has made of the adequacy of local authorities' capacity to implement early morning restriction orders on the sale of alcohol.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63375","63375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686178","2017-02-09","Home Office","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many nationals of each of the other 27 EU countries were employed by (a) her Department and (b) UK Visas and Immigration in (i) 2013, (ii) 2014, (iii) 2015 and (iv) 2016.","Biography information for Mike Gapes","Mike Gapes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63403","63403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686179","2017-02-09","Home Office","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 25 October 2015 to Question 48815, how many convictions for slavery and human trafficking there have been under each of the new offences following the passage of the Modern Slavery Act 2015 since the criminal justice provisions in that Act commenced on 31 July 2015.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63394","63394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686180","2017-02-20","Home Office","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what her policy is on the timing of the return of original documents to people applying for (a) citizenship, (b) further leave to remain and (c) indefinite leave to remain.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63409","63409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686181","2017-02-09","Home Office","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have been barred from entering the UK for having engaged in unacceptable behaviour in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63395","63395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686182","2017-02-20","Home Office","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Answer of 15 April 2016 to Question 34251, how many decisions on international protection her Department made from 1 April 2016 to 31 December 2016 with further submissions lodged under rule 353 of the Immigration Rules in respect of (a) grants on protection grounds, (b) grants on non-protection grounds, (c) decisions to treat as a fresh claim and then refused, (d) further submissions refused and (e) further submissions withdrawn before any decision is made.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63330","63330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686183","2017-02-20","Home Office","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps Border Force is taking to reduce the number of dogs being brought into the UK illegally.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63331","63331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686184","2017-02-09","Home Office","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of (a) online and (b) non-cyber harassment and hate crimes resulted in a conviction in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63348","63348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686185","2017-02-09","Home Office","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of police work primarily on cybercrime cases; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63349","63349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686186","2017-02-09","Home Office","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of online fraud and other forms of cybercrime was reported to the police in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63350","63350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686188","2017-02-09","Home Office","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of (a) fraudulent banking transactions and (b) crimes in other categories result in a conviction.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63351","63351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686189","2017-02-09","Home Office","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if the Minister of State for Policing and the Fire Service will meet the All-Party Parliamentary Fire Safety and Rescue Group.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63324","63324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686190","2017-02-09","Home Office","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of Tier 4 visa applications was processed within 15 working days in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63536","63536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686191","2017-02-09","Home Office","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of administrative review appeals for a UK visa was processed within 28 working days in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63537","63537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686192","2017-02-09","Home Office","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many unaccompanied children have come to the UK under the Dubs amendment.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63510","63510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686193","2017-02-09","Home Office","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which (a) individuals and (b) teams in her Department are responsible for bringing unaccompanied children into the UK under the Dubs amendment.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63531","63531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686194","2017-02-09","Home Office","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment the Government has made of its effectiveness in implementing the Dubs amendment.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63532","63532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686195","2017-02-09","Home Office","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many asylum or visa applications from Afghan interpreters formerly employed by the armed forces were refused in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for James Gray","James Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63533","63533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686196","2017-02-09","Home Office","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to improve coastal and marine policing in the East of England.","Biography information for James Cartlidge","James Cartlidge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63500","63500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686197","2017-02-09","Home Office","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many asylum decisions were made in cases of applicants who were detained at the point of decision in each quarter since 1 January 2014.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63501","63501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686198","2017-02-09","Home Office","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of non-settlement visa applications was processed within 15 working days in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63483","63483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686199","2017-02-09","Home Office","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will introduce a knife amnesty in England and Wales.","Biography information for Stephen McPartland","Stephen McPartland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63546","63546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686200","2017-02-09","Home Office","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 6 February 2017 to Question 62601, how many contractors, temporary staff and guests have been given a security pass or unescorted day pass who are (a) an employee of and (b) seconded from a private firm that has been awarded a Home Office contract or lobbied the Department.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63441","63441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686201","2017-02-09","Department for International Development","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 28 November 2016 to Question 53867, who will represent the Government at the 61st session of the UN Commission on the Status of Women in New York in March 2017.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63439","63439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686202","2017-02-20","Department for International Development","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether a Minister of her Department plans to attend the donor conference for Nigeria and Lake Chad in Oslo on 24 February 2017.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63454","63454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686203","2017-02-20","Department for International Development","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether her Department plans to make a funding pledge at the donor conference on the humanitarian crisis in Nigeria and Lake Chad region in Oslo on 24 February 2017.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63455","63455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686204","2017-02-09","Department for International Development","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 31 January 2017 to Question 61410, on developing countries: children, how her Department measures the effectiveness of humanitarian assistance which is not included in her Department's annual targets.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63340","63340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686205","2017-02-09","Department for International Development","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent representations she has made to the Governments of (a) Ukraine and (b) Russia on humanitarian access to eastern Ukraine; what assessment she has made of the effect of recent fighting on civilian infrastructure in that region; and what steps she is taking to assist civilians affected by the ongoing conflict in that region.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63387","63387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686206","2017-02-09","Department for International Development","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent steps her Department has taken in response to the humanitarian situation in the Central African Republic; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63371","63371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686207","2017-02-09","Ministry of Justice","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many victims of domestic violence received awards from the Criminal Injuries Compensation Authority in 2016; what the average length of time was between application and receipt of such an award; and what the average value of such awards was.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63347","63347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686208","2017-02-20","Ministry of Justice","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) prison officers were injured at work in (i) 2014, (ii) 2015 and (iii) 2016 and (b) of those officers (i) returned to work and (ii) are still serving as a prison officer following their injury.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63354","63354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686209","2017-02-20","Ministry of Justice","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prison officers recruited since 2015 have retained their job after a probation period for (a) one year and (b) two years or more.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63355","63355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686210","2017-02-09","Ministry of Justice","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when she plans to reply to the letter from the hon. Member for Hitchin and Harpenden of 2 December 2016 on behalf of his constituent, William Dickinson of Cross Farm, Harpenden, Hertfordshire, on the issue of rural crime.","Biography information for Lord Lilley","Mr Peter Lilley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63402","63402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686211","2017-02-20","HM Treasury","2017-02-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many employers have been convicted of paying staff less than the national living wage since its introduction.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63450","63450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686212","2017-02-09","Home Office","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent progress has been made on implementing the processes required to enforce the Proceeds of Crime Act systems.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63335","63335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686213","2017-02-09","Ministry of Justice","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if she will commence section 67 of the Serious Crime Act 2015.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63468","63468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686214","2017-02-09","Ministry of Justice","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if she will ensure the local provision of Welsh language transcription services in Wales once contracts have been awarded under the Framework and Contracts for the Provision of Transcription Services for Court Reporting and Transcription Services OJEU Prior Information Notice (ref: 2016/S 155-281276) tender.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63473","63473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686215","2017-02-09","Ministry of Justice","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps she has taken to ensure that cost savings to consumers resulting from reforms to personal injury statutes are passed on to consumers by the insurance industry.","Biography information for Tom Elliott","Tom Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63485","63485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686216","2017-02-09","Ministry of Justice","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps she is taking to ensure that (a) transcription of UK court and tribunal hearings will not be undertaken offshore, (b) UK transcription jobs and skills will be safeguarded and (c) safeguards are put in place to eliminate risk to national security following contracts being awarded as a result of the Framework and Contracts for the Provision of Transcription Services for Court Reporting and Transcription Services OJEU Prior Information Notice tender.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63495","63495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686217","2017-02-09","Northern Ireland Office","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what assessment he has made of the implications for Northern Ireland of a visit by President Trump; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63457","63457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686218","2017-02-09","Northern Ireland Office","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what steps he is taking to fund pensions for those victims of terrorism identified by the Northern Ireland Victims' Commissioner as in need of such pensions; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63459","63459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686219","2017-02-09","Department for Transport","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when the Severn Bridges will return to public ownership.","Biography information for Craig Williams","Craig Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63469","63469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686220","2017-02-09","Department for Transport","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the proposed timescale is for installing a free-flow toll system on the Severn Bridges.","Biography information for Craig Williams","Craig Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63470","63470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686221","2017-02-09","Department for Transport","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to improve road safety for children near schools.","Biography information for Derek Thomas","Derek Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63446","63446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686223","2017-02-09","Department for Transport","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate his Department has made of the number of new apprenticeships resulting from the expansion of Heathrow airport; and what assessment he has made of the effect of that expansion on the skill bank of workers in local communities.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63420","63420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686224","2017-02-20","Department for Transport","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he plans to publish the Vehicle Technology and Aviation Bill.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63516","63516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686225","2017-02-20","Department for Transport","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what reports he has received from Volkswagen on (a) its progress on the technical update of vehicles fitted with defeat devices and (b) any change to its timetable for that update; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63515","63515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686226","2017-02-09","Department for Transport","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the cost to the public purse has been of consultants working on High Speed 2.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63535","63535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686227","2017-02-09","Department for Transport","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what his most recent estimate is of the cost to the public purse of High Speed 2.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63545","63545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686228","2017-02-09","Department for Transport","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the implications of his policies of the Public Health England report, The Public Health Burden of Alcohol and the Effectiveness and Cost-Effectiveness of Alcohol Control Policies: An evidence review, published in December 2016, which found that designated driver schemes did not change the prevalence of people drink driving or riding with a drink driver.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63326","63326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686229","2017-02-09","Department for Transport","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the Public Health England report, The Public Health Burden of Alcohol and the Effectiveness and Cost-Effectiveness of Alcohol Control Policies: An evidence review, published in December 2016, which found that graduated driving licences for young drivers were effective; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63327","63327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686230","2017-02-20","Department for Transport","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate his Department has made of the number of additional road vehicle movements per year resulting from the decision to reduce the budget for rail freight mode shift revenue support grants.","Biography information for Pat Glass","Pat Glass","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63333","63333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686232","2017-02-20","Department for Transport","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what salary was paid to the Interim Chief Executive of HS2 Ltd, Ray Hill, during his term of office; and what terms and functions applied to his employment within HS2.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63380","63380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686233","2017-02-20","Department for Transport","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which schools have been contacted by Hopscotch Consulting under its contract to promote HS2.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63381","63381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686234","2017-02-09","Women and Equalities","2017-02-07","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what steps the Government Equalities Office is taking to ensure that schools are safe spaces for children and young people to learn without the threat of (a) sexual bullying, (b) LGBT bullying and (c) harassment.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63383","63383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686235","2017-02-09","Department of Health","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps the Government Equalities Office is taking to ensure that young women's life choices are not limited by unplanned parenthood.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63397","63397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686236","2017-02-09","Women and Equalities","2017-02-07","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, whether she plans to extend the provisions of the Equality Act 2010 (Gender Pay Gap Information) Regulations to the public sector.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63488","63488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686237","2017-02-09","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to tackle discrimination against women who are expecting or have children; and what recent assessment he has made of the effectiveness of legislation on maternity and flexible working pay.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63428","63428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686238","2017-02-09","Women and Equalities","2017-02-07","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, pursuant to the Answer of 20 December 2016 to Question 57766, when she plans to confirm the budget for the Equality and Human Rights Commission for (a) 2017-18, (b) 2018-19 and (c) 2019-20.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63440","63440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686239","2017-02-09","Women and Equalities","2017-02-07","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, pursuant to the Answer of 2 February 2017 to Question 62006, when in 2017 she plans to make an announcement on funding arrangements for the revenge porn helpline.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63444","63444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686240","2017-02-09","Home Office","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what educational programmes the Government makes available to youth bodies to help support young people who are the victims of domestic abuse.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63429","63429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686241","2017-02-09","Women and Equalities","2017-02-07","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what recent discussions she has had with the Home Secretary on the handling of racially motivated attacks.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63430","63430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686242","2017-02-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many universal credit claimants have received support through the Flexible Support Fund following changes to work allowances introduced in March 2016.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63527","63527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686243","2017-02-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether his Department plans to publish an updated impact assessment for plans to replace bereavement benefits with bereavement support payments; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63529","63529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686244","2017-02-09","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what assessment he has made of the effect of the UK leaving the EU on low-income families.","Biography information for Dr Eilidh Whiteford","Dr Eilidh Whiteford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63487","63487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686245","2017-02-20","HM Treasury","2017-02-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many tax credit recipients have been naturally migrated onto universal credit since March 2016.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63528","63528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686246","2017-02-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much money has been spent from the public purse on the personalisation pathfinder initiative in each year since its launch.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63525","63525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686247","2017-02-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, in which locations and on what dates personalisation pathfinders have been commenced; and whether each personalisation pathfinder is still in operation.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63524","63524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686248","2017-02-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment his Department has made of the effectiveness of the personalisation pathfinder initiative; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63523","63523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686249","2017-02-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many appeals were lodged against decisions to refuse incapacity benefit in (a) Blackburn and Darwen, (b) Burnley, (c) Hyndburn, (d) Pendle, (e) Ribble Valley and (f) Rossendale and Chorley in (i) 2011, (ii) 2012, (iii) 2013, (iv) 2014, (v) 2015 and (vi) 2016.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63477","63477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686250","2017-02-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many appeals against decisions to refuse disability living allowance were (a) lodged, (b) upheld and (c) dismissed in respect of children resident in (i) Blackburn and Darwen, (ii) Burnley, (iii) Hyndburn, (iv) Pendle, (v) Ribble Valley and (vi) Rossendale and Chorley in (A) 2011, (B) 2012, (C) 2013, (D) 2014, (E) 2015 and (F) 2016.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63474","63474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686251","2017-02-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many appeals against decisions to refuse incapacity benefit were dismissed in (a) Blackburn and Darwen, (b) Burnley, (c) Hyndburn, (d) Pendle, (e) Ribble Valley and (f) Rossendale and Chorley in (i) 2011, (ii) 2012, (iii) 2013, (iv) 2014, (v) 2015 and (vi) 2016.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63475","63475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686252","2017-02-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many appeals were lodged against decisions to refuse employment and support allowance in (a) Blackburn and Darwen, (b) Burnley, (c) Hyndburn, (d) Pendle, (e) Ribble Valley and (f) Rossendale and Chorley in (i) 2011, (ii) 2012, (iii) 2013, (iv) 2014, (v) 2015 and (vi) 2016.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63476","63476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686253","2017-02-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people have had their eligibility for winter fuel allowance stopped as a result of the introduction of temperature tests.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63530","63530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686254","2017-02-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average rate of unemployment is in those communities in which his Department is proposing to close jobcentres.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63517","63517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686255","2017-02-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many appeals against decisions to refuse (a) disability living allowance, (b) personal independence payments, (c) employment and support allowance and (d) incapacity benefit were (i) upheld and (ii) dismissed in respect of adults resident in (1) Blackburn and Darwen (2) Burnley, (3) Hyndburn, (4) Pendle, (5) Ribble Valley and (6) Rossendale and Chorley in (A) 2011, (B) 2012, (C) 2013, (D) 2014, (E) 2015 and (F) 2016.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63489","63489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686256","2017-02-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much will accrue to the Exchequer from the decision not to increase benefit payments for four years.","Biography information for Dr Eilidh Whiteford","Dr Eilidh Whiteford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63491","63491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686257","2017-02-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he has taken in response to the National Audit Office's December report on the UK's benefit sanctions system; and if he will launch an independent review of the sanctions regime.","Biography information for Alex Salmond","Alex Salmond","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63502","63502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686258","2017-02-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, which companies Jobcentre Plus has been barred from making referrals to.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63541","63541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686259","2017-02-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claimants are served by (a) Tile Hill and (b) Cofa Court jobcentres in Coventry; and how many such claimants are (i) disabled and (ii) women.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63413","63413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686260","2017-02-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make it his Department's policy to (a) collect data on the number of people subject to a benefit sanction who have used food banks at any time over the duration of that sanction and (b) publish that data.","Biography information for Jo Churchill","Jo Churchill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63410","63410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686261","2017-02-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people using Tile Hill Jobcentre Plus in Coventry South have been informed in writing of the closure of that jobcentre.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63414","63414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686262","2017-02-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the transition of child maintenance arrangements from 2017 on children and their parents.","Biography information for Stuart Blair Donaldson","Stuart Blair Donaldson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63344","63344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686263","2017-02-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many complaints his Department has received from people on the termination of their arrangements with the Child Support Agency.","Biography information for Stuart Blair Donaldson","Stuart Blair Donaldson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63345","63345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686264","2017-02-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people who have child maintenance arrangements with the Child Support Agency have received letters on the termination of those arrangements with the Child Support Agency.","Biography information for Stuart Blair Donaldson","Stuart Blair Donaldson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63346","63346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686265","2017-02-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the written statement of 12 December 2016, (HCW 5339), what the planned (a) timetable and (b) content is for the Automatic Enrolment 2017 Review.","Biography information for Graham Evans","Graham Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63328","63328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686266","2017-02-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent assessment his Department has made of the effectiveness of the Consumer Ombudsman regime.","Biography information for Richard Arkless","Richard  Arkless","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63332","63332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686267","2017-02-09","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what discussions he has had with the Post Office on the level of government investment in the Post Office and its profitability.","Biography information for Simon Hoare","Simon Hoare","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63336","63336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686268","2017-02-09","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 31 January 2017 to Question 61718, on energy: conservation, if he will make representations to the energy sector and the construction industry on developing more apprenticeship standards for energy efficiency; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63337","63337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686269","2017-02-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 6 February 2017 to Question 62717, how many UK students in each (a) region and (b) local authority have participated in the Erasmus Scheme in the last 10 years.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63518","63518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686270","2017-02-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will take steps to ensure that the provisions of Directive 89/48/EEC relating to professional qualifications are retained in UK law when the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Chris Elmore","Chris Elmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63512","63512"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686271","2017-02-09","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps the Government is taking to prevent counterfeit electrical goods from entering the UK.","Biography information for Dame Caroline Spelman","Dame Caroline Spelman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63443","63443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686272","2017-02-20","Department for International Development","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will make it her policy to encourage the involvement of church groups and other Christian organisations in the delivery of overseas development projects and programmes.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Mrs Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63519","63519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686273","2017-02-20","Department for International Trade","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what assessment his Department has made of the return on investment of its marketing budget in 2016-17.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63520","63520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686274","2017-02-20","Department for International Trade","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what visits to which countries each of the Government's trade envoys have made on since May 2015.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63549","63549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686277","2017-02-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what research her Department has commissioned on likely trends in the agricultural and environmental sectors' international trade once the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63334","63334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686278","2017-02-09","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, if he will consult British expat communities living in other EU countries on the planned negotiation on the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63342","63342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686279","2017-02-09","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what proportion of his Department's employees are from black and ethnic minority backgrounds.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63343","63343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686280","2017-02-20","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what plans he has to negotiate visa-free travel for British citizens in the EU as a part of negotiations for the UK to exit the EU.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63540","63540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686281","2017-02-20","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what steps he plans to take during negotiations on the UK leaving the EU to ensure that electrical safety in the workplace is protected after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Chris Elmore","Chris Elmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63456","63456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685397","2017-02-08","Attorney General","2017-02-06","To ask the Attorney General, how many security passes into the Law Officers' Departments are issued to people (a) not directly employed by and (b) who are not civil servants who work in the Law Officers' Departments.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63255","63255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685398","2017-02-08","Cabinet Office","2017-02-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many cases accepted for investigation by the Parliamentary and Health Service Ombudsman were classed as open in each month since January 2015.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63235","63235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685399","2017-02-08","Cabinet Office","2017-02-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many security passes into his Department are issued to people (a) not directly employed by and (b) who are not civil servants who work in his Department.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63256","63256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685400","2017-02-09","Cabinet Office","2017-02-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, which contracts the Government has awarded to Capita in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63305","63305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685401","2017-02-08","Cabinet Office","2017-02-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether his Department plans to move any of the operations carried out by the Parliamentary and Health Service Ombudsman outside of London.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63236","63236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685402","2017-02-08","Cabinet Office","2017-02-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether his Department plans to converge services undertaken by the Parliamentary and Health Service Ombudsman with the Local Government Ombudsman.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63237","63237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685403","2017-02-08","Cabinet Office","2017-02-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 3 February 2017 to Question 61923, what assessment he has made of the long-term risks to the financial performance of the Parliamentary Contributory Pensions Fund of that funds' investments in the fossil fuel extractive industry.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63244","63244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685404","2017-02-08","Department for Transport","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the Driver and Vehicle Licensing Agency's news story of 30 January 2017, new vehicle tax rate from 1 April 2017, what steps his Department and Cabinet colleagues are taking to raise awareness of those new vehicle tax rates; and what the cost to the public purse of publicising those new rates will be.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63243","63243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685405","2017-02-08","HM Treasury","2017-02-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the cost of decommissioning North Sea oil infrastructure; for what proportion of those costs the taxpayer will be liable; and what steps he plans to take to reduce those costs.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63179","63179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685406","2017-02-09","HM Treasury","2017-02-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he has received representations on his proposed change to vehicle taxation scheduled for April 2017 on (a) the potential effect on future vehicles, (b) the potential effect on air quality and (c) postponing the introduction of those changes until further consultation is carried out.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63203","63203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685407","2017-02-08","HM Treasury","2017-02-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will estimate the cost to the public purse of abolishing employer National Insurance contributions for care leavers in 2016-17.","Biography information for Michael Gove","Michael Gove","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63172","63172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685408","2017-02-09","HM Treasury","2017-02-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate has he made of the amount of VAT that has been raised in respect of hot takeaway food in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63145","63145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685409","2017-02-09","HM Treasury","2017-02-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many businesses elected to use tonnage tax in (a) 2013-14 and (b) 2014-15.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63147","63147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685410","2017-02-08","HM Treasury","2017-02-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the financial value to fossil fuel producers of tax allowances taken up in financial year 2015-16.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63180","63180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685411","2017-02-08","HM Treasury","2017-02-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the value is of the subsidies provided for the (a) production and (b) consumption of fossil fuels in the current financial year.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63181","63181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685412","2017-02-08","HM Treasury","2017-02-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the cost was of starting payment vouchers for child trust funds between 1 September 2002 and 2 January 2011.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63196","63196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685413","2017-02-08","HM Treasury","2017-02-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many child trust funds exist.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63197","63197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685414","2017-02-08","HM Treasury","2017-02-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the total cost has been of the child trust fund initiative.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63198","63198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685415","2017-02-08","HM Treasury","2017-02-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate his Department has made of annual future tax revenues from the North Sea oil and gas industry up to 2030.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63182","63182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685416","2017-02-08","HM Treasury","2017-02-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many (a) people and (b) businesses received the Landlord's Energy Saving Allowance in (a) 2013-14 and (b) 2014-15.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63120","63120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685417","2017-02-08","HM Treasury","2017-02-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many (a) people and (b) businesses received capital allowance in (i) 2013-14 and (ii) 2014-15.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63121","63121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685418","2017-02-08","HM Treasury","2017-02-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people received income tax exemption of foreign service allowance paid to Crown servants abroad in (a) 2013-14 and (b) 2014-15.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63122","63122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685419","2017-02-08","HM Treasury","2017-02-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people received income tax exemption of premium bond prizes in (a) 2013-14 and (b) 2014-15.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63124","63124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685420","2017-02-08","HM Treasury","2017-02-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many (a) people and (b) businesses received the annual investment allowance for income and corporation tax in (i) 2013-14 and (ii) 2014-15.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63125","63125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685421","2017-02-08","HM Treasury","2017-02-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many businesses received Land Mediation Relief in (a) 2013-14 and (b) 2014-15.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63123","63123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685422","2017-02-08","HM Treasury","2017-02-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many businesses received animation tax relief in (a) 2013-14 and (b) 2014-15.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63126","63126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685423","2017-02-08","HM Treasury","2017-02-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many businesses received video games tax relief in (a) 2013-14 and (b) 2014-15.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63127","63127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685424","2017-02-08","HM Treasury","2017-02-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many businesses received theatre tax relief in (a) 2013-14 and (b) 2014-15.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63128","63128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685425","2017-02-08","HM Treasury","2017-02-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many (a) people and (b) businesses received rollover relief for balancing charges on ships in (i) 2013-14 and (ii) 2014-15.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63129","63129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685426","2017-02-08","HM Treasury","2017-02-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many businesses received the life companies reduced rate of corporation tax on policy holders' fraction of profit in (a) 2013-14 and (b) 2014-15.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63130","63130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685427","2017-02-08","HM Treasury","2017-02-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many (a) people and (b) businesses received foreign tax credits and reliefs under the double taxation agreement for income and corporation tax in (i) 2013-14 and (ii) 2014-15.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63131","63131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685428","2017-02-08","HM Treasury","2017-02-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many (a) people and (b) businesses received community investment tax relief in (i) 2013-14 and (ii) 2014-15.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63134","63134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685429","2017-02-08","HM Treasury","2017-02-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many (a) people and (b) businesses received national insurance contributions relief for Enterprise Management Incentives in (i) 2013-14 and (ii) 2014-15.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63132","63132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685430","2017-02-08","HM Treasury","2017-02-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many (a) people and (b) businesses received the Business Premises Renovation Allowance in (i) 2013-14 and (ii) 2014-15.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63133","63133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685431","2017-02-09","HM Treasury","2017-02-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the top 20 categories as defined by HM Revenue and Customs (HMRC) were according to value of imports of goods imported into the UK in the most recent year for which records are available; and how much HMRC collected in gross customs duties in each of those categories.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63157","63157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685432","2017-02-08","HM Treasury","2017-02-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the Declaration on global economic and political challenges made by the G7 leaders at the Ise-Shima Summit in May 2016, what progress the Government has made on its commitment to ending inefficient fossil fuel subsidies by 2025.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63285","63285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685433","2017-02-08","HM Treasury","2017-02-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the G20 Leaders' Communique made at the Hangzhou Summit in September 2016, whether the Government will participate in the fossil fuel subsidy peer review process.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63284","63284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685434","2017-02-08","HM Treasury","2017-02-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many security passes into his Department are issued to people (a) not directly employed by and (b) who are not civil servants who work in his Department.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63277","63277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685435","2017-02-08","Church Commissioners","2017-02-06","To ask the right hon. Member for Meriden, representing the Church Commissioners, how many security passes into the Church Commissioners are issued to people (a) not directly employed by and (b) who are not civil servants who work in the Church Commissioners.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63257","63257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685436","2017-02-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many security passes into his Department are issued to people (a) not directly employed by and (b) who are not civil servants who work in his Department.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63258","63258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685437","2017-02-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what his Department's policy is on the length of time that district councils in Dorset be allowed to (a) consider and (b) present alternative proposals on the future of local government structures in that area.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63309","63309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685438","2017-02-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what his Department's policy is on the termination of district council partnership working arrangements where the future structure of local government is under consideration; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63310","63310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685439","2017-02-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether it is his Department's policy to accept proposals for unitarisation in the event that there is a disagreement between the councils affected by those proposals.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63311","63311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685440","2017-02-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what guidance his Department has issued to local authorities on requirements for consulting with all councils that have (a) accepted and (b) rejected proposals on unitarisation; and what steps his Department has taken to encourage reconciliation in such cases.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63312","63312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685441","2017-02-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will make an assessment of recent trends in buy-to-let cost rises; and what steps his Department is taking to mitigate against any adverse effect from significant changes in property prices.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63153","63153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685442","2017-02-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will make an assessment of the potential effect of the UK leaving the EU on house-building projections.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63154","63154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685443","2017-02-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what recent assessment he has made of the (a) level and (b) extent of arrears of tenants in the (i) social and (ii) private rented sector.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63188","63188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685444","2017-02-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what discussions his Department has had with small businesses ahead of the introduction of proposed changes to business rate rateable values on the definition of a small business.","Biography information for Craig Tracey","Craig Tracey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63190","63190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685445","2017-02-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if his Department will increase transitional thresholds for business rate relief.","Biography information for Craig Tracey","Craig Tracey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63191","63191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685446","2017-02-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether his Department has made an assessment of the potential merits of Changing Places toilet facilities in public places; and if he will include requirements for such facilities in any future disability strategy.","Biography information for Richard Arkless","Richard  Arkless","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63204","63204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685447","2017-02-08","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps she is taking to ensure that the diverse needs of the creative industries will be supported after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Nigel Adams","Nigel Adams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63239","63239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685448","2017-02-08","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what her policy is on whether the UK will be able to protect the territoriality of copyright after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Nigel Adams","Nigel Adams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63240","63240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685449","2017-02-08","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions her Department has had with the Premier League to ensure that football clubs not meeting disability access criteria make the necessary improvements.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63109","63109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685450","2017-02-08","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps she is taking to help improve disability access at Football League grounds.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63108","63108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685451","2017-02-09","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, who owns the Burghers of Calais sculpture in Victoria Tower Gardens.","Biography information for Sir Edward Leigh","Sir Edward Leigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63158","63158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685452","2017-02-09","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what the level of Government funding for (a) Tech UK and (b) Tech North has been in each year from their establishment to date.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63168","63168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685453","2017-02-08","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent discussions her Department has had with sports governing bodies on improving disability access at sports stadia.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63107","63107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685454","2017-02-08","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many security passes into her Department are issued to people (a) not directly employed by and (b) who are not civil servants who work in her Department.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63259","63259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685455","2017-02-09","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, on what dates Ministers of her Department have met the British Board of Film Classification to discuss the Digital Economy Bill since July 2015.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63301","63301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685456","2017-02-08","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions she has had with representatives from the digital industries on data protection regulations since the UK's decision to leave the EU.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63265","63265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685457","2017-02-08","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how much her Department has spent on promoting media literacy in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63296","63296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685458","2017-02-08","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many officials in her Department work on promoting media literacy.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63297","63297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685459","2017-02-08","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps her Department is taking to promote media literacy.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63298","63298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685460","2017-02-08","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many officials in her Department are working on preparations to implement the General Data Protection Regulation.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63299","63299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685461","2017-02-08","Ministry of Defence","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many security passes into his Department are issued to people (a) not directly employed by and (b) who are not civil servants who work in his Department.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63260","63260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685462","2017-02-08","Ministry of Defence","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 3 February 2017 to Question 62363, whether the current draft of Joint Doctrine Publication 0-30.2, Unmanned Aircraft Systems, discusses the legal framework for the employment of Unmanned Aircraft Systems (a) within and (b) outside areas of armed conflict.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63288","63288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685463","2017-02-08","Ministry of Defence","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what reports his Department has received on the mistreatment of Sunni Arab refugees by Kurdish forces following the offensive of Mosul.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63232","63232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685464","2017-02-08","Ministry of Defence","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent estimate he has made of the proportion of gross domestic product spent on defence by each other NATO member state.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63233","63233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685465","2017-02-08","Ministry of Defence","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what forecast his Department has made of the likely timescale for the full liberation of Mosul.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63229","63229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685466","2017-02-09","Ministry of Defence","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he has made an assessment of the socio-economic effect of the proposed MoD site closures announced in 2016; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63307","63307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685467","2017-02-09","Ministry of Defence","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what discussions he has had with military and civilian personnel on the proposed MoD site closures; and what assistance his Department plans to give to people required to relocate.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63308","63308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685468","2017-02-09","Ministry of Defence","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of adopting the recommendation by the Single Source Regulations Office that programmes and platforms procured through foreign military sales should be brought into the single source procurement regulations regime; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63163","63163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685469","2017-02-09","Ministry of Defence","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he plans to announce the final number of vehicles his Department plans to procure as part of the Mechanised Infantry Vehicle programme.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63162","63162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685470","2017-02-08","Ministry of Defence","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what his plans are for the future of his Department's Saint Athan estate; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63112","63112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685471","2017-02-08","Ministry of Defence","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many UK service personnel are embedded with or seconded to the national armed forces of other countries in the coalition participating in Operation Restoring Hope in Yemen.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63105","63105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685472","2017-02-08","Ministry of Defence","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many UK service personnel have been embedded with or seconded to coalition forces participating in Operation Restoring Hope in Yemen; and what roles those personnel are performing.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63104","63104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685473","2017-02-09","Ministry of Defence","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the threat that underwater drones and distributed netted sensors pose, as part of the risk reduction and demonstration phase for the Dreadnought Class submarines.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63146","63146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685474","2017-02-09","Ministry of Defence","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the role and establishment is of the 16th Regiment Royal Artillery based at Thorney Island.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63156","63156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685475","2017-02-09","Department for Education","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what information her Department holds on how many places there are available in secure residential accommodation for children in (a) England, (b) Scotland and (c) Wales; how many of those places are currently filled; and how many children placed in such accommodation in (i) England were previously resident in (A) Scotland and (B) Wales, (ii) Scotland were previously resident in (A) England and (B) Wales and (iii) Wales were previously resident in (A) England and (B) Scotland.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63206","63206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685476","2017-02-09","Department for Education","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many adopted children (a) were placed with their full or half siblings in the last three years and (b) who were not so placed have not had contact with their full or half siblings detailed in their adoption order in the last three years.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63208","63208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685477","2017-02-09","Department for Education","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many looked-after children who have one or more siblings have (a) been placed and (b) not been placed with their siblings in each of the last three years; and of those children who were not placed with their siblings (i) how many have contact with the siblings they are separated from and (ii) what the frequency is of that contact.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63207","63207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685478","2017-02-09","Department for Education","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to reduce the attainment gaps of five A* to C GCSE grades between secondary schools in the North and the South; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63212","63212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685479","2017-02-08","Department for Education","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what representation she has received on the effect of university and college diversity officers on academic freedom.","Biography information for Michael Gove","Michael Gove","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63173","63173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685480","2017-02-08","Department for Education","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 7 December 2016 to Question 56626, for what reasons information that was held centrally from 2010 to 2014 on which charitable organisations her Department funds is no longer held centrally.","Biography information for Michael Gove","Michael Gove","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63174","63174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685481","2017-02-08","Department for Education","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment her Department has made of the potential effect of the school funding formula on the funding of schools in Tynemouth constituency in real terms in each of the next three years.","Biography information for Sir Alan Campbell","Mr Alan Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63117","63117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685482","2017-02-08","Department for Education","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to increase funding for schools with a high concentration of students with special educational needs in North Tyneside.","Biography information for Sir Alan Campbell","Mr Alan Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63118","63118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685483","2017-02-08","Department for Education","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the total cost was to the public purse of rebuilding schools in North Tyneside in 2016.","Biography information for Sir Alan Campbell","Mr Alan Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63119","63119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685484","2017-02-09","Department for Education","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 30 January 2017 to Question 61766, if she will publish the supportive statements regarding the power to test different ways of working from the 15 organisations and individuals she lists in that Answer.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63314","63314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685485","2017-02-09","Department for Education","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when she plans to publish the early years workforce strategy; and whether it will include steps to increase the number of early years teachers in the private, voluntary and independent childcare sector.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63315","63315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685486","2017-02-09","Department for Education","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many new early years teachers are expected to be recruited in England in the next three years.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63316","63316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685487","2017-02-09","Department for Education","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what funds have been given to the Educational Endowment Foundation in each year since its establishment; what underspends by her Department have been repaid to the Treasury in each of the last 10 years; how much was granted for Academies Conversion; on what it has been spent; and how much has been returned to the Treasury.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63317","63317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685488","2017-02-09","Department for Education","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many Ofsted early years inspectors are employed (a) nationally and (b) in each region.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63306","63306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685489","2017-02-09","Department for Education","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of the amount that Ofsted spent on inspecting early years settings in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63247","63247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685490","2017-02-08","Department for Education","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many security passes into her Department are issued to people (a) not directly employed by and (b) who are not civil servants who work in her Department.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63261","63261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685491","2017-02-09","Department for Education","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children subject to care orders (s31) as defined by the Children Act 1989 are placed with their (a) full and (b) half siblings.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63302","63302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685492","2017-02-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many security passes into her Department are issued to people (a) not directly employed by and (b) who are not civil servants who work in her Department.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63262","63262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685493","2017-02-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what her Department's plans are for the operation of the three crop rule after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63226","63226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685494","2017-02-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to protect breeding habitats for woodcock.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63227","63227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685495","2017-02-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to tackle the spread of the invasive species of demon shrimp, dikerogammarus haemobaphes.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63228","63228"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685496","2017-02-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what research the Government has commissioned in the last six months to inform the development of agricultural and environmental policy once the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63096","63096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685497","2017-02-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to protect the hedgehog population.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63209","63209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685498","2017-02-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent progress has been made in tackling tax (a) avoidance and (b) evasion by companies registered in the Overseas Territories.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63205","63205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685499","2017-02-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has discussed tax (a) avoidance and (b) evasion with his counterpart in the Cayman Islands since the last meeting of the Joint Ministerial Council.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63214","63214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685500","2017-02-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the Government's policy is on the establishment of a UN inquiry into alleged human rights violations committed against the Rohingya by the Burmese Army and security forces.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63178","63178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685501","2017-02-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his Turkish counterpart on the arrests of Kurdish members of the Turkish parliament.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63199","63199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685502","2017-02-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the level of Iranian compliance with the Joint Comprehensive Plan of Action.","Biography information for Michael Gove","Michael Gove","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63170","63170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685503","2017-02-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what his policy is on the basing of the British Embassy in Tel Aviv; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Michael Gove","Michael Gove","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63171","63171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685504","2017-02-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many UK ambassadors are in post; and how many of those ambassadors are (a) women and (b) black, Asian or minority ethnic.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63102","63102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685505","2017-02-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to the Iranian Government condemning the use of the death penalty in that country.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Mrs Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63100","63100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685506","2017-02-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent progress has been made on steps to retake Mosul from Daesh.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63217","63217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685507","2017-02-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received on whether President Putin has endorsed support for Field Marshal Khalifa Haftar to be the future leader of the Libyan state.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63224","63224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685508","2017-02-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the security risks to British citizens living in the countries listed for a potential travel ban to the US.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63225","63225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685509","2017-02-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 1 February 2017 to Question 61335, when he plans to meet the US Secretary of State; and whether he plans to discuss international climate change cooperation at their first meeting.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63282","63282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685510","2017-02-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has received representations from (a) parliamentarians and (b) the public on the appointment of a new chair of the Guyanese Election Commission.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63283","63283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685511","2017-02-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many security passes into his Department are issued to people (a) not directly employed by and (b) who are not civil servants who work in his Department.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63264","63264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685512","2017-02-08","Department of Health","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many security passes into his Department are issued to people (a) not directly employed by and (b) who are not civil servants who work in his Department.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63266","63266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685513","2017-02-09","Department of Health","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the findings of the report by CLIC Sargent, entitled Cancer costs: financial impact of childhood cancer revealed, published in September 2016, whether he plans to review the financial assistance for travel costs for families not on low incomes.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63295","63295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685514","2017-02-09","Department of Health","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of cancer on the emotional health and wellbeing of young cancer patients and their families.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63248","63248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685515","2017-02-09","Department of Health","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what sanctions are available to him to address the performance of Capita in the administration of the National Dental Performers List.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63249","63249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685516","2017-02-09","Department of Health","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect on patients of the performance of Capita in its administration of the National Dental Performers List.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63250","63250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685517","2017-02-09","Home Office","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the Government plans to produce a new alcohol strategy.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63251","63251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685518","2017-02-09","Home Office","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans the Government has to revise its March 2012 alcohol strategy.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63252","63252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685519","2017-02-09","Department of Health","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what mental health support is available for children and young people who have been diagnosed with cancer.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63289","63289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685520","2017-02-09","Department of Health","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many times an ambulance has been called to HM Prison Woodhill for an inmate who has attempted suicide in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63318","63318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685521","2017-02-09","Ministry of Justice","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many self-inflicted deaths there were of prisoners from HM Prison Woodhill within 14 days of their release in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63319","63319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685522","2017-02-09","Ministry of Justice","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many blue code emergencies there were in HM Prison Woodhill in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63320","63320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685523","2017-02-09","Department of Health","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of nationals of other EU countries working in the NHS as clinical psychologists; and what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the UK leaving the EU on (a) the number of such nationals and (b) NHS productivity would be.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63321","63321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685524","2017-02-09","Department of Health","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 2 February 2017 to Question 62392, how many beds for in-patients with eating disorders there were in each month since April 2016.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63322","63322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685525","2017-02-08","Department of Health","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make it his policy to (a) plan no further capital developments using the Private Finance Initiative and (b) place no further NHS contracts with private health firms.","Biography information for Christian Matheson","Christian Matheson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63098","63098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685526","2017-02-08","Department of Health","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what costs have been (a) incurred to date and (b) committed for future periods for the development and management of the sustainability and transformations plan process for North Tyneside.","Biography information for Sir Alan Campbell","Mr Alan Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63116","63116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685528","2017-02-08","Department of Health","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when the updated NICE guidelines on the diagnosis and management of peripheral arterial disease will be published.","Biography information for Derek Thomas","Derek Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63113","63113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685529","2017-02-08","Department of Health","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to increase access to genetic testing for familial hypercholesterolaemia.","Biography information for Derek Thomas","Derek Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63114","63114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685530","2017-02-09","Department of Health","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many and what proportion of properties owned by NHS Property Services are (a) freehold and (b) leasehold.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr   Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63164","63164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685531","2017-02-09","Department of Health","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what financial management structures have been put in place to ensure that NHS Property Services offers value for money.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr   Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63165","63165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685532","2017-02-09","Department of Health","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many properties held by NHS Property Services are not used for clinical purposes.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr   Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63166","63166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685533","2017-02-09","Department of Health","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many properties held by NHS Property Services are vacant.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr   Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63167","63167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685534","2017-02-08","Department of Health","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the findings of the report by the Centre for Mental Health, entitled Immigration Removal Centres in England: A mental heath needs analysis, published on 9 January 2017.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63135","63135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685535","2017-02-09","Department of Health","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to promote nursing degrees to take account of trends in the number of people applying for such degrees.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63155","63155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685536","2017-02-08","Department of Health","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what representations he has received on trends in the number of deaths from illegal drug use; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63186","63186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685537","2017-02-08","Department of Health","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, in how many instances the Care Quality Commission has asked service providers to instigate fit and proper persons requirement (FPPR) investigations for each year since the FPPR came into force; and how many of those FPPR investigations resulted in a director being discharged from duty.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63183","63183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685538","2017-02-08","Department of Health","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to reduce the number of deaths from illegal drug use.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63184","63184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685539","2017-02-08","Department of Health","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, for what reasons the Care Quality Commission closed its fit and proper persons requirement process on Paula Vasco-Knight, then Chief Executive of South Devon NHS Foundation Trust.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63192","63192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685540","2017-02-09","Department of Health","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether an NHS trust which the Care Quality Commission reports as requiring improvement can be awarded a community health services contract under an NHS-led transaction process in the event that it applied for such a contract prior to the rules changing to permit only NHS trusts with a good inspection rating to apply or be awarded such contracts.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63149","63149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685541","2017-02-08","Department of Health","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps the NHS is taking to prevent technological faults in equipment used in heart operations from causing harm or fatality.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63220","63220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685542","2017-02-08","Department of Health","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the timetable is for availability on the NHS of a calcium channel blocker to tackle high blood pressure and sepsis.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63221","63221"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685543","2017-02-08","Department of Health","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people have been diagnosed with blephorospasm in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63222","63222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685544","2017-02-08","Department of Health","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the timetable is for availability on the NHS of new treatments to tackle polymyalgia rheumatica.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63223","63223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685545","2017-02-09","Department of Health","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many ambulances based in (a) Coventry South constituency and (b) the UK have responded outside the Category (i) A and (ii) B response-time target in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63211","63211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685546","2017-02-08","Department of Health","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, by what metrics the effectiveness of Regulation 5: Fit and proper persons: directors is measured; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63175","63175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685547","2017-02-20","Home Office","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what controls on freedom of movement are available to the Government within the EU Treaties.","Biography information for Richard Arkless","Richard  Arkless","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63253","63253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685548","2017-02-08","Home Office","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions her Department has had with the Department for Communities and Local Government to ensure that building regulations fire safety guidance is revised to reflect changes such as new construction techniques, building use and changing response patterns.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63194","63194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685549","2017-02-08","Home Office","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department has taken to ensure that relevant data from the incident reporting system on fires is made publicly available during relevant departmental consultations.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63195","63195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685550","2017-02-08","Home Office","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans she has to reopen Tier 3 of the non-EU immigration system.","Biography information for James Cartlidge","James Cartlidge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63193","63193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685551","2017-02-09","Home Office","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether it is her policy for those admitted to the UK through the Syrian vulnerable persons programme to be able to apply for refugee status in the UK; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63148","63148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685552","2017-02-09","Home Office","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many prosecutions have been brought under the Female Genital Mutilation Act 2003 since the introduction of that legislation.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63143","63143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685553","2017-02-09","Home Office","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make it her policy to delay the UK's participation in the European Investigation Order until after the UK's departure from the EU.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63144","63144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685554","2017-02-08","Home Office","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to reduce the number of deaths from illegal drug use.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63185","63185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685555","2017-02-09","Home Office","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many certificates of sponsorship were issued to Scottish employers for students switching from Tier 4 to Tier 2 visas in each year from 2011 to 2015.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63160","63160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685556","2017-02-09","Home Office","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) certificates of sponsorship and (b) extensions of stay were issued for people working for Scottish employers for Tier 1, Tier 2 and Tier 5 visas, by industry, in each year from 2011 to 2015.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63159","63159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685557","2017-02-09","Home Office","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she plans to respond to the letter from the hon. Member for Wolverhampton South West of 14 October 2016, on deportation of people whose immigration status application has not been finally determined, reference ZA4101.","Biography information for Rob Marris","Rob Marris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63169","63169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685558","2017-02-08","Home Office","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she expects to announce the name of the new Metropolitan Police Commissioner.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63103","63103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685559","2017-02-09","Home Office","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many illegal migrants have been (a) identified, (b) arrested and (c) deported after being detected at Poole Port in each of the last six months for which information is available.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63313","63313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685560","2017-02-08","Home Office","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to reduce the number of forged or illegally-obtained UK passports in the Republic of Ireland.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63218","63218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685561","2017-02-08","Home Office","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she plans to continue the implementation of section 67 of the Immigration Act 2016 for the rest of the current Parliament.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63231","63231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685562","2017-02-08","Home Office","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many security passes into her Department are issued to people (a) not directly employed by and (b) who are not civil servants who work in her Department.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63267","63267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685563","2017-02-08","House of Commons Commission","2017-02-06","To ask the right hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington, representing the House of Commons Commission, how many security passes into the House of Commons Commission are issued to people (a) not directly employed by and (b) who are not civil servants who work in the House of Commons Commission.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63268","63268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685564","2017-02-08","Department for International Development","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many security passes into her Department are issued to people (a) not directly employed by and (b) who are not civil servants who work in her Department.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63269","63269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685565","2017-02-09","Department for International Development","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 14 December 2016 to Question 58565, on overseas aid, what discussions her Department has had with multilateral agencies on the co-ordination of the withdrawal of aid from middle-income countries.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63245","63245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685566","2017-02-08","Department for International Development","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she has taken to improve nutrition outcomes for women and girls through her Department's water and sanitation programmes.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63106","63106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685567","2017-02-08","Ministry of Justice","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent discussions she has had with the Family Justice Board on handling vexatious repeated requests relating to access to children; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63110","63110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685568","2017-02-08","Ministry of Justice","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps she is taking to ensure that people with mental health conditions receive fair treatment in the criminal justice system.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Mrs Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63099","63099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685569","2017-02-08","Ministry of Justice","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps she is taking to protect prison officers from the harmful effects of psychoactive substances used by prisoners.","Biography information for Sir Gary Streeter","Mr Gary Streeter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63242","63242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685570","2017-02-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many prosecutions there have been in respect of non-compliant dogs and puppies entering the UK via Dover or the Eurotunnel in (a) 2012, (b) 2013, (c) 2014, (d) 2015 and (e) 2016.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63213","63213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685571","2017-02-09","Ministry of Justice","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment she has made of the effect of charges levied for a doctor's letter as evidence of domestic violence on the number of domestic violence claims; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63210","63210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685572","2017-02-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps (a) he and (b) the Government has taken to make public its policy against Holocaust denial and anti-Semitism since May 2015.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63230","63230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685573","2017-02-08","Ministry of Justice","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many security passes into her Department are issued to people (a) not directly employed by and (b) who are not civil servants who work in her Department.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63271","63271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685574","2017-02-08","Leader of the House","2017-02-06","To ask the Leader of the House, how many security passes into his Office are issued to people (a) not directly employed by and (b) who are not civil servants who work in his Office.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63272","63272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685575","2017-02-08","Northern Ireland Office","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many security passes into his Department are issued to people (a) not directly employed by and (b) who are not civil servants who work in his Department.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63273","63273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685576","2017-02-08","Prime Minister","2017-02-06","To ask the Prime Minister, how many security passes into 10 Downing Street are issued to people (a) not directly employed by and (b) who are not civil servants who work in 10 Downing Street.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63274","63274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685577","2017-02-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he plans to make representations to the US President on the UK's policy on torture.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63304","63304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685578","2017-02-08","Scotland Office","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how many security passes into his Department are issued to people (a) not directly employed by and (b) who are not civil servants who work in his Department.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63275","63275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685579","2017-02-08","Speaker's Committee for the Independent Parliamentary Standards Authority","2017-02-06","To ask the hon. Member for Broxbourne, representing the Speaker's Committee for the Independent Parliamentary Standards Authority, how many security passes into IPSA are issued to people (a) not directly employed by and (b) who are not civil servants who work in IPSA.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63294","63294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685580","2017-02-08","Speaker's Committee for the Independent Parliamentary Standards Authority","2017-02-06","To ask the hon. Member for Broxbourne, representing the Speaker's Committee for the Independent Parliamentary Standards Authority, what the total pay bill was for (a) male and (b) female employees in IPSA in 2015-16; and what the average per capita spend from that pay bill was for men and women in that year.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63139","63139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685581","2017-02-08","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2017-02-06","To ask the hon. Member for Houghton and Sunderland South, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what the total pay bill was for (a) male and (b) female employees in the Electoral Commission in 2015-16; and what the average per capita spend from that pay bill was for men and women in that year.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63138","63138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685582","2017-02-08","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2017-02-06","To ask the hon. Member for Houghton and Sunderland South, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, how many security passes into the Electoral Commission are issued to people (a) not directly employed by and (b) who are not civil servants who work in the Electoral Commission.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63280","63280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685583","2017-02-08","Department for Transport","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many security passes into his Department are issued to people (a) not directly employed by and (b) who are not civil servants who work in his Department.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63276","63276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685584","2017-02-08","Department for Transport","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 3 February 2017 to Question 62467, on shipping: pollution control, whether any UK registered vessels were detained for infringement of provisions of Annex VI of the International Convention for the Prevention of Pollution from Ships in (a) 2015 and (b) 2016.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63286","63286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685585","2017-02-09","Department for Transport","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much funding has been paid to CH2M by (a) his Department and (b) HS2 Ltd in each financial year since 2009.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63303","63303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685586","2017-02-08","Department for Transport","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that drivers from other EU member states who are charged with traffic offences in the UK are dealt with effectively by their national authorities.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63219","63219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685587","2017-02-09","Department for Transport","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate his Department has made of how many (a) ultra low emission, (b) hydrogen and (c) fully electric vehicles there will be on roads in each of the next five years; and whether his Department is on course to meet targets related to such vehicle numbers.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63246","63246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685588","2017-02-08","Department for Transport","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 3 February 2017 to Question 62467, on shipping: pollution control, how many vessels on routes in the sulphur emission control areas were inspected for compliance with Annex VI of the International Convention for the Prevention of Pollution from Ships in (a) 2015 and (b) 2016.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63287","63287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685589","2017-02-08","Department for Transport","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of quality partnership schemes between 2010 and 2016.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63176","63176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685590","2017-02-08","Department for Transport","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to incentivise the use of electric cars.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63216","63216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685591","2017-02-08","Department for Transport","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the reasons why the number of deaths caused by drink-driving has increased each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63238","63238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685592","2017-02-08","Department for Transport","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 2 February 2017 to Question 62343, for what reasons the technical advice from Chris Gibb has not been made publicly available.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63187","63187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685593","2017-02-08","Department for Transport","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans he has to support the growth of Birmingham Airport in his Department's planned aviation strategy.","Biography information for Ms Gisela Stuart","Ms Gisela Stuart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63140","63140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685594","2017-02-08","Department for Transport","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions he has had with Midlands Connect on ensuring its strategy promotes the importance of Birmingham Airport.","Biography information for Ms Gisela Stuart","Ms Gisela Stuart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63141","63141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685595","2017-02-09","Department for Transport","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the total pay bill was for (a) male and (b) female employees in his Department in 2015-16; and what the average per capita spend from that pay bill was for men and women in that year.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63150","63150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685596","2017-02-08","Wales Office","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what the total pay bill was for (a) male and (b) female employees in his Department in 2015-16; and what the average per capita spend from that pay bill was for men and women in that year.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63136","63136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685597","2017-02-08","Wales Office","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how many security passes into his Department are issued to people (a) not directly employed by and (b) who are not civil servants who work in his Department.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63278","63278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685598","2017-02-08","Women and Equalities","2017-02-06","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, how many security passes into her Department are issued to people (a) not directly employed by and (b) who are not civil servants who work in her Department.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63281","63281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685599","2017-02-09","Women and Equalities","2017-02-06","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what the total pay bill was for (a) male and (b) female employees in her Department in 2015-16; and what the average per capital spend from that pay bill was for men and women in that year.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63152","63152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685600","2017-02-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, for what reasons the New Enterprise Allowance is not available to carers on income support.","Biography information for Alex Chalk","Alex Chalk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63137","63137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685601","2017-02-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, on which date a Minister of his Department last visited a jobcentre in (a) North Tyneside and (b) the North East.","Biography information for Sir Alan Campbell","Mr Alan Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63115","63115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685602","2017-02-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what criteria were used to determine individual need in setting the rate of jobseeker's allowance and the lower rate of employment and support allowance for a single adult at 73.10 per week.","Biography information for Christian Matheson","Christian Matheson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63097","63097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685603","2017-02-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the total pay bill was for (a) male and (b) female employees in his Department in 2015-16; and what the average per capita spend from that pay bill was for men and women in that year.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63151","63151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685604","2017-02-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to page 10 of the Government response to the Work and Pensions Committee report on Benefit Delivery, published on 12 July 2016, HC 522, what evaluation his Department has carried out on changes to guidance for jobcentre staff handling claims from refugees; and when he plans to publish the findings of that evaluation.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63202","63202"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685605","2017-02-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how long the consultation on the closure of Jobcentre Plus offices will last.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63201","63201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685606","2017-02-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of process by which veterans with post-traumatic stress disorder access their personal independence payments.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63200","63200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685607","2017-02-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the level of rent arrears of universal credit recipients who are tenants in temporary accommodation in universal credit pilot areas.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63177","63177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685608","2017-02-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many work coaches his Department has employed in each (a) region and (b) constituent part of the UK in each of the last three years; and how many work coaches his Department plans to employ in each such region and part of the UK in each of the next three years.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63215","63215"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685609","2017-02-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of employees at Eastern Avenue Jobcentre, Sheffield whose mobility rule within their contract will be breached by the decision to close that jobcentre.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63189","63189"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685610","2017-02-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many security passes into his Department are issued to people (a) not directly employed by and (b) who are not civil servants who work in his Department.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63279","63279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685611","2017-02-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when in Spring 2017 he plans to implement the changes to the Renewable Heat Incentive scheme.","Biography information for Richard Arkless","Richard  Arkless","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63292","63292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685612","2017-02-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many security passes into his Department are issued to people (a) not directly employed by and (b) who are not civil servants who work in his Department.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63254","63254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685613","2017-02-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the Government's Response to the Energy and Climate Change Committee's Sixth Special Report of Session 2014-15, HC1105, when his Department plans to publish its techno-economic assessment of the development of small modular reactors in the UK; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63300","63300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685614","2017-02-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when he plans to publish his Department's road map for the development of small modular reactors; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63241","63241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685615","2017-02-08","Department for International Trade","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what export credits the Government granted to fossil fuel projects in 2015-16.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63111","63111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685616","2017-02-09","Department for International Trade","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what assessment he has made of the implications for those elements of the UK's legal and regulatory framework for arms exports derived from EU directives when the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63161","63161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685617","2017-02-09","Department for International Trade","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, pursuant to the Answer of 13 January 2017 to Question 59272, if he will make a request to the Government's business managers to hold a debate on the floor of the House on the Comprehensive Economic and Trade Agreement.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63142","63142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685618","2017-02-09","Department for International Trade","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, which export contracts in which the applicant declared that an agent had provided facilitation services were supported by UK Export Finance classified by (a) type of export support, (b) amount of expert support, (c) country, (d) project, (e) amount or rate of commission, (f) fees payable to the agent and (g) the countries where such fees are payable in each month and year since 2010; and what the name and address of each such agent was.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63290","63290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685619","2017-02-08","Department for International Trade","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many security passes into his Department are issued to people (a) not directly employed by and (b) who are not civil servants who work in his Department.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63270","63270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685620","2017-02-08","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many security passes into his Department are issued to people (a) not directly employed by and (b) who are not civil servants who work in his Department.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63263","63263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685621","2017-02-08","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, pursuant to the Answer of 26 January 2017 to Question 61140, what estimate he has made of his Department's expenditure on consultancy costs in each financial year up to 2017-18.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63234","63234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685622","2017-02-20","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to the Scottish Government's report entitled, Scotland's Place in Europe, published on 20 December 2016, whether he plans to accept any of the proposals of that report within his future negotiating framework.","Biography information for Richard Arkless","Richard  Arkless","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63291","63291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685623","2017-02-08","Cabinet Office","2017-02-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many British citizens live in (a) the EU and (b) each EU country other than the UK.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63101","63101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685624","2017-02-08","Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster","2017-02-06","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster, how many security passes into his Department are issued to people (a) not directly employed by and (b) who are not civil servants who work in his Department.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63293","63293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686275","2017-02-09","Department for International Trade","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what assessment he has made of SME business interest in the great.gov.uk digital platform.","Biography information for Karl McCartney","Karl McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 908696","908696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686276","2017-02-09","Department for International Trade","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what discussions he has had with the Australian Government on preparations for opening trade talks.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Mrs Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 908687","908687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687266","2017-02-09","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions her Department has had with sports governing bodies on tackling homophobia in sport.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 908724","908724"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687267","2017-02-09","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps her Department is taking to encourage the hosting of major sporting and tourism events in the UK.","Biography information for Oliver Colvile","Oliver Colvile","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 908726","908726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687268","2017-02-09","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, when her Department plans to announce its proposed review of fixed odds betting terminals.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 908725","908725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687269","2017-02-09","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps she is taking to secure an adequacy of the protection of data decision from the European Commission.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 908727","908727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687270","2017-02-09","Department for International Trade","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, when he plans to submit schedules to the WTO for approval after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 908693","908693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687271","2017-02-09","Department for International Trade","2017-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what recent discussions he has had with the WTO.","Biography information for Neil Carmichael","Neil Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 908698","908698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/684009","2017-02-07","Attorney General","2017-02-03","To ask the Attorney General, what the total pay bill was for (a) male and (b) female employees in the Law Officers' Departments in 2015-16; and what the per capita spend from that pay bill for each man and woman was in that year.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63063","63063"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/684010","2017-02-07","Cabinet Office","2017-02-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the total pay bill was for (a) male and (b) female employees in his Department in 2015-16; and what the per capita spend from that pay bill for each man and woman was in that year.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63064","63064"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/684011","2017-02-07","HM Treasury","2017-02-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent steps he has taken to support high street banking for local communities.","Biography information for Kelly Tolhurst","Kelly Tolhurst","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63006","63006"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/684012","2017-02-08","HM Treasury","2017-02-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment he has made of the potential effect on tax revenues of proposed reductions in the maximum allowed stake on fixed-odds betting terminals.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63017","63017"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/684013","2017-02-08","HM Treasury","2017-02-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the total pay bill was for (a) male and (b) female employees in his Department in 2015-16; and what the per capita spend from that pay bill for each man and woman was in that year.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63083","63083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/684014","2017-02-07","Church Commissioners","2017-02-03","To ask the right hon. Member for Meriden, representing the Church Commissioners, what the total pay bill was for (a) male and (b) female employees in the Church Commissioners in 2015-16; and what the per capita spend from that pay bill for each man and woman was in that year.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63065","63065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/684015","2017-02-07","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the total pay bill was for (a) male and (b) female employees in his Department in 2015-16; and what the per capita spend from that pay bill for each man and woman was in that year.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63066","63066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/684016","2017-02-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he has taken to reduce the number of homeless rough sleepers in (a) Coventry and (b) England in each of the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63089","63089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/684017","2017-02-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to ensure that the Urban Growth Company takes account of the potential contribution of Birmingham Airport to UK trade.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63039","63039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/684018","2017-02-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many jobs have been created in Ashfield constituency as a result of funding from the European Regional Development Fund since that fund's inception.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63046","63046"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/684019","2017-02-07","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether the Government plans to introduce regulatory proposals for bodies which manage shared accommodation in which vulnerable people are housed.","Biography information for Kwasi  Kwarteng","Kwasi Kwarteng","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62999","62999"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/684020","2017-02-08","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how much funding the Government has awarded to the Foundation for Social Improvement since that charity was founded.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63042","63042"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/684021","2017-02-08","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, on how many separate occasions her Department has awarded (a) grants and (b) contracts to the Foundation for Social Improvement.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63043","63043"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/684022","2017-02-07","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what the total pay bill was for (a) male and (b) female employees in her Department in 2015-16; and what the per capita spend from that pay bill for each man and woman was in that year.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63067","63067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/684023","2017-02-07","Ministry of Defence","2017-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the total pay bill was for (a) male and (b) female employees in his Department in 2015-16; and what the per capita spend from that pay bill for each man and woman was in that year.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63068","63068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/684024","2017-02-08","Ministry of Defence","2017-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the 2016-17 war pension rate is for (a) monthly and (b) weekly claimants.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63021","63021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/684025","2017-02-07","Ministry of Defence","2017-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many civilian personnel are employed at Sennybridge Storage Compound on a (a) permanent and (b) temporary basis.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63024","63024"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/684026","2017-02-07","Ministry of Defence","2017-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) military and (b) civilian personnel are based at MOD St Athan.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63030","63030"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/684027","2017-02-07","Ministry of Defence","2017-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many military personnel are based at Sennybridge Storage Compound on a (a) permanent and (b) temporary basis.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63031","63031"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/684028","2017-02-08","Ministry of Defence","2017-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the potential economic and social effect on the local community and local businesses of the proposed closure of Invicta Park Barracks; and what plans he has for a formal consultation on that proposed closure.","Biography information for Mrs Helen Grant","Mrs Helen Grant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63010","63010"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/684029","2017-02-07","Department for Education","2017-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Written Statement of 9 January 2017, on mental illness, HCWS397, what preventative initiatives will be included in the programme of randomised control trials focusing on mental health in schools; and whether that programme will include school-based counselling in (a) primary schools, (b) secondary schools and (c) colleges and further education establishments.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63007","63007"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/684030","2017-02-08","Department for Education","2017-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children under the age of 16 have been (a) adopted and (b) on the adoption waiting list in (i) Ashfield constituency and (ii) Nottinghamshire in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63014","63014"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/684031","2017-02-07","Department for Education","2017-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Written Statement of 9 January 2017, on mental health, HCWS397, what the proposed timescale is for the programme of randomised control trials focusing on preventative mental health support in schools.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63002","63002"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/684032","2017-02-08","Department for Education","2017-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the average unit cost was to a (a) school and (b) local authority of employing a (i) teacher and (ii) classroom assistant in the most recent year for which figures are available; and what estimate she has made of such costs in (A) 2016-17, (B) 2017-18, (C) 2018-19 and (D) 2019-20.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63019","63019"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/684033","2017-02-07","Department for Education","2017-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Written Statement of 9 January 2017, on mental health, HCWS397, whether the programme of randomised control trials of preventative mental health support in schools will be tested in (a) primary schools, (b) secondary schools and (c) colleges and further education establishments.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63003","63003"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/684034","2017-02-07","Department for Education","2017-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children aged under 16 have been placed in long-term foster care placements in (a) Ashfield constituency and (b) Nottinghamshire in each year since 2010; and how many children have been on the waiting list for such a placement in each of those years.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63049","63049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/684035","2017-02-07","Department for Education","2017-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the total pay bill was for (a) male and (b) female employees in her Department in 2015-16; and what the per capita spend from that pay bill for each man and woman was in that year.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63069","63069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/684036","2017-02-08","Department for Education","2017-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment her Department has made of the link between post-natal depression and children being taken into social care; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63059","63059"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/684037","2017-02-08","Department for Education","2017-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 1 February 2017 to Question 61973, for what reasons there has been a decrease in the number of citizenship trainees since 2010; and what steps her Department is taking to increase the number of trained citizenship teachers.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63054","63054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/684038","2017-02-08","Department for Education","2017-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 1 February 2017 to Question 61973, what assessment her Department has made of the effect of the change in the number of citizenship trainees since 2010 on the quality of citizenship education provided in schools.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63055","63055"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/684039","2017-02-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the total pay bill was for (a) male and (b) female employees in her Department in 2015-16; and what the per capita spend from that pay bill for each man and woman was in that year.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63070","63070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/684040","2017-02-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the Producer Support Estimate is for beef, lamb and dairy products in the UK.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63027","63027"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/684041","2017-02-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what progress his Department is making on supporting religious leaders to promote community cohesion and reconciliation through its Conflict, Security and Stability Fund; in which countries religious leaders are being supported by that fund; and which religious communities those leaders represent.","Biography information for Dame Caroline Spelman","Dame Caroline Spelman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63036","63036"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/684042","2017-02-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the total pay bill was for (a) male and (b) female employees in his Department in 2015-16; and what the per capita spend from that pay bill for each man and woman was in that year.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63079","63079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/684043","2017-02-08","Department of Health","2017-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the oral contribution of the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Health of 13 December 2016, Official Report, column 257WH, on the accelerated access review, what progress has been made on taking forward negotiations on Orkambi with Vertex.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63093","63093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/684044","2017-02-08","Department of Health","2017-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of instances when the Red Cross has provided care to people at home after their discharge from hospital in each of the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63090","63090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/684045","2017-02-08","Department of Health","2017-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many school-aged children have been diagnosed with an eating disorder in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63058","63058"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/684046","2017-02-07","Department of Health","2017-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to reduce the number of bed days lost owing to delayed transfers of care in NHS trusts; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63084","63084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/684047","2017-02-07","Department of Health","2017-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of mental health service provision in (a) Coventry and (b) England; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63085","63085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/684048","2017-02-08","Department of Health","2017-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will list (a) the community-based eating disorder services for children and young people which (i) currently and (ii) plan in 2017-18 to accept non-GP referrals, including self-referral, (b) those services which are not currently accepting such referrals and (c) those services which have no plan to do so in 2017-18.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63094","63094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/684049","2017-02-07","Department of Health","2017-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the total pay bill was for (a) male and (b) female employees in his Department in 2015-16; and what the per capita spend from that pay bill for each man and woman was in that year.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63072","63072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/684050","2017-02-08","Department of Health","2017-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the report, Preventing suicide in England: A cross-government outcomes strategy to save lives, published on 9 January 2017, whether his Department has evidence of an increase in the number of vulnerable individuals in prisons in the last five years.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63009","63009"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/684051","2017-02-07","Department of Health","2017-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether clinical commissioning group restrictions on access to joint surgery for obese patients and smokers are compatible with NICE guidance on osteoarthritis: care and management, that patient-specific factors, including age, sex, smoking, obesity and co-morbidities, should not be barriers to referral for joint surgery.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63000","63000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/684052","2017-02-08","Department of Health","2017-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will hold discussions with technology companies on the implications for his policies on suicide prevention of the publication of detailed information on suicide methods online.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63012","63012"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/684053","2017-02-07","Department of Health","2017-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that the guidance on the use of face-down restraint in the NHS set out in the Positive and Safe initiative is properly implemented.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63004","63004"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/684054","2017-02-07","Department of Health","2017-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress has been made on implementing the recommendations and guidance of the Positive and Safe initiative.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63005","63005"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/684055","2017-02-08","Department of Health","2017-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans there are to include community-based eating disorder services for children and young people in the in-depth thematic review of children and young people's mental health services, announced by the Prime Minister on 9 January 2017.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63011","63011"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/684056","2017-02-07","Department of Health","2017-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to reduce unplanned admission rates for heart failure.","Biography information for Sir Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63037","63037"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/684057","2017-02-07","Department of Health","2017-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of the prevalence of heart failure (a) nationally and (b) in The Cotswolds constituency.","Biography information for Sir Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63038","63038"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/684058","2017-02-07","Department of Health","2017-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of recent UCAS statistics showing a 23 per cent reduction in applications to nursing courses; and what steps he is taking to increase the number of nursing graduates.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63028","63028"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/684059","2017-02-08","Department of Health","2017-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 2 November 2016 to Question 50911, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that the funding referred to is spent in full on child and adolescent eating disorder services.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63044","63044"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/684060","2017-02-08","Department of Health","2017-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress has been made on implementing access and waiting time standards for eating disorder services for children and young people; and what his timetable is for NHS England to begin regular publication of waiting times for those services.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63015","63015"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/684061","2017-02-08","Department of Health","2017-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of using cystic fibrosis treatments to pilot the recommendations of the Accelerated Access Review.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63018","63018"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/684062","2017-02-08","Department of Health","2017-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when Health Education England plans to publish its five-year mental health workforce strategy.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63032","63032"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/684063","2017-02-08","Department of Health","2017-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 2 February 2017 to Question 62390, how many people were admitted to adult in-patient mental health wards in each month of 2016 by age at admission.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63033","63033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/684064","2017-02-08","Department of Health","2017-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 27 January 2017 to Question 61518, what the recorded causes of death were of the 11 children who died in in-patient mental health units since 2013.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63034","63034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/684065","2017-02-07","Department of Health","2017-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Answer of 3 May 2016 to Question 35295, whether the routinely collected data on clinical commissioning group expenditure on  children and young people's mental health services will be publicly available.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63035","63035"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/684066","2017-02-08","Department of Health","2017-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether an impact assessment of the Memorandum of Understanding (MOU) between his Department, NHS Digital and the Home Office on sharing patient information has been undertaken; what consultation process his Department carried out on that MOU; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63026","63026"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/684067","2017-02-07","Department of Health","2017-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of the effect of changes to local authority social care budgets on the demand for health services.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63025","63025"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/684068","2017-02-08","Department of Health","2017-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to page seven of the NHS England report, Implementing the Five Year Forward View for Mental Health, published in February 2016, when NHS England plans to publish the expected trajectory for localities' progress towards meeting new standards for children and young people's eating disorder services.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63022","63022"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/684069","2017-02-08","Home Office","2017-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the number of UK citizens who have applied for dual Irish-UK nationality since 23 June 2016.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63020","63020"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/684070","2017-02-07","Home Office","2017-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what her Department's policy is on bringing forward legislative proposals that will further regulate and limit animal testing after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63001","63001"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/684071","2017-02-07","Home Office","2017-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many Irish citizens have applied for UK citizenship since 23 June 2016.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63029","63029"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/684072","2017-02-08","Home Office","2017-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the total pay bill was for (a) male and (b) female employees in her Department in 2015-16; and what the per capita spend from that pay bill for each man and woman was in that year.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63081","63081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/684073","2017-02-08","Home Office","2017-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many reported instances of domestic violence there have been in (a) the London Borough of Newham, (b) Greater London and (c) the UK in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63057","63057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/684074","2017-02-08","Home Office","2017-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the oral contribution of the Minister for Immigration of 23 January 2017, Official Report, column 15, what her Department's policy is on the number of international students who will be given leave to study at UK universities in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63091","63091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/684075","2017-02-07","House of Commons Commission","2017-02-03","To ask the right hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington, representing the House of Commons Commission, what the total pay bill was for (a) male and (b) female employees in the House of Commons Commission in 2015-16; and what the per capita spend from that pay bill for each man and woman was in that year.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63073","63073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/684076","2017-02-07","Department for International Development","2017-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what the total pay bill was for (a) male and (b) female employees in her Department in 2015-16; and what the per capita spend from that pay bill for each man and woman was in that year.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63074","63074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/684077","2017-02-08","Department for International Development","2017-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what discussions she had with the Foreign Secretary on the case of Andy Tsege prior to her recent visit to Ethiopia.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63095","63095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/684078","2017-02-07","Department for International Development","2017-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to support the key principles outlined in its guidance note, Shifting social norms to tackle violence against women and girls, published on 20 January 2016; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63086","63086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/684079","2017-02-07","Ministry of Justice","2017-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the total pay bill was for (a) male and (b) female employees in her Department in 2015-16; and what the per capita spend from that pay bill for each man and woman was in that year.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63076","63076"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/684080","2017-02-07","Ministry of Justice","2017-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many cases of breaches or failings of the Victims' Code have been received by her Department since 1 January 2017 by (a) text, (b) tweet, (c) e-mail and (d) letter.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63050","63050"
