"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627310","2016-11-07","Department for Education","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many independent reviewing officers (a) are currently employed and (b) were employed in 2010 in each local authority as headcount and full-time equivalents.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51611","51611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627311","2016-11-07","Department for Education","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will rank (a) selective, (b) partially selective and (c) comprehensive local authority areas in England by correlating guaranteed per pupil funding against the proportion of pupils attaining five or more grade A* to C GCSEs including English and mathematics in the last year for which data is available.","Biography information for Sir Graham Brady","Mr Graham Brady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51709","51709"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627313","2016-11-07","Department for Education","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of children in care attend fee-paying boarding schools.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51679","51679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627314","2016-11-07","Department for Education","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 13 September 2016 to Question 44997, in what ways the Government is (a) encouraging a wider range of young people into apprenticeships and (b) increasing the proportion of BAME apprenticeship starts by 20 per cent by 2020.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51574","51574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627315","2016-11-07","Department for Education","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans she has to provide extra funds to higher education institutions after the UK leaves the EU in the event of a reduction in income from tuition fees paid by students from other EU countries.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51575","51575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627316","2016-11-07","Department for Education","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate her Department has made of the tuition fees expected to be paid to UK universities by overseas (a) EU and (b) non-EU students in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51578","51578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627317","2016-11-04","Department for Education","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much her Department has spent on agency workers in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51616","51616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627318","2016-11-07","Department for Education","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of the extent of the reduction in the number of children being adopted; and what steps she is taking to address that reduction.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51608","51608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627319","2016-11-07","Department for Education","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what research her Department has carried out into the number of disrupted adoptive placements in each of the last 10 years; and if she will publish the number of such placements.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51609","51609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627320","2016-11-07","Department for Education","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many adoptive families have applied to the Adoption Support Fund in the last 12 months; how much has been paid from that Fund during that time period; and how much has been paid out below the amount claimed in that time period.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51610","51610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627321","2016-11-04","Department for Education","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many foster carers there are in the UK by (a) region or constituent nation, (b) local authority area and (c) type and level of foster carers.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51599","51599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627322","2016-11-04","Department for Education","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many registered foster carers there have been in the UK in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51598","51598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627323","2016-11-07","Department for Education","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will take steps to limit increases in the cost of student accommodation.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51531","51531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627324","2016-11-07","Department for Education","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many free schools were delayed in opening in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51533","51533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627325","2016-11-07","Department for Education","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what free school project applications have been withdrawn or cancelled since 2010; and what costs were incurred by the applicant on (a) property and planning, (b) technical advice and consultancy and (c) legal fees before withdrawal or cancellation.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51534","51534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627331","2016-11-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much her Department has spent on agency workers in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51617","51617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627332","2016-11-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of whether the requirement of the ferry company DFDS to require companion animals such as dogs and cats to remain inside vehicles and unattended during ferry crossings is compliant with her Department's pet travel policies.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51554","51554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627333","2016-11-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to policy 62 of the Calderdale Flood Action Plan, published in October 2016, for what reasons the Environment Agency will progressively review existing burning consents with regard to moorland in Calderdale.","Biography information for Holly Lynch","Holly Lynch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51681","51681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627334","2016-11-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, which Minister from her Department plans to attend the 13th Conference of the Parties to the Convention on Biological Diversity in December 2016.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51657","51657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627335","2016-11-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions she has had with the Environment Agency on the implications for its remit of the draft Transatlantic Trade and Investment Partnership.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51647","51647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627336","2016-11-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what analysis the Environment Agency has conducted on the condition of blanket bog on moorland currently managed for grouse shooting; and the condition it believes to be optimal for slowing water flows.","Biography information for Holly Lynch","Holly Lynch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51612","51612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627337","2016-11-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether she has consulted the Office of Water Services on the implications for its remit of the draft Transatlantic Trade and Investment Partnership.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51642","51642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627338","2016-11-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether she has consulted the Food Standards Agency on the implications for its remit of the draft Transatlantic Trade and Investment Partnership.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51638","51638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627339","2016-11-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will make it her policy to seek access to the EU market under existing terms for Scottish agricultural firms after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51651","51651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627340","2016-11-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will make it her policy to allow individual ports to ban live animal exports after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51663","51663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627341","2016-11-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 1 November 2016 to Question 50488 and the Answer of 13 October 2016 to Question 47024, whether her Department has made an assessment of the potential effect of the total ban on domestic ivory sales on the number of elephants poached for ivory.","Biography information for Julian Knight","Julian Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51733","51733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627343","2016-11-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment the Government has made of whether the ongoing election process in Somalia is free and fair; and if he will take steps to encourage the government of Somalia to increase the number of Somalian people able to vote in that election.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51742","51742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627344","2016-11-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to address the recent arbitrary arrests and the media shut down in Ethiopia.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51743","51743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627345","2016-11-07","Department for International Trade","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, when the Government plans to appoint a new trade envoy to South Africa.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51744","51744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627346","2016-11-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government is taking in response to President Kabila of Democratic Republic of Congo delaying elections in that county with an explanation that one of the reasons is a lack of EU funding for those elections.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51746","51746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627347","2016-11-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions his Department has had with other EU member states on demolition of EU-funded buildings in the Occupied Palestinian Territories and compensation for those buildings.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51713","51713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627348","2016-11-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many meetings there have been in the last 12 months between human rights organisations operating in the Occupied Palestinian Territories and (a) the British Consulate-General in Jerusalem and (b) the British Embassy in Tel Aviv.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51715","51715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627350","2016-11-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how much his Department has spent on agency workers in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51619","51619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627351","2016-11-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the budget was for projects in (a) Israel and (b) the Palestinian territories within the Conflict, Security and Stability Fund in the 2015-16.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51682","51682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627352","2016-11-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with (a) the Gulf Cooperation Council and (b) governments of other countries on plans to improve security in the Middle East.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51710","51710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627353","2016-11-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what proportion of women are employed by his Department on an inner London pay structure in the following pay grades (a) Administrative Assistant, (b) Administrative Officer, (c) Executive Officer, (d) Higher Executive Officer, (e) Fast Streamer, (f) Senior Executive Officer, (g) Grade Seven, (h) Grade Six, (i) Senior Civil Service Band 1, (j) Senior Civil Service Band 1A, (k) Senior Civil Service Band 2 and (l) Senior Civil Service Band 3.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51555","51555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627354","2016-11-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the implications of the ongoing glorification sanctioned by the Palestinian Authority of people who have killed Israelis for the viability of a lasting two-state solution.","Biography information for Bob Blackman","Bob Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51552","51552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627355","2016-11-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 28 October 2016 to Question 50165, if he will raise with the Israeli government the issue of access to essential medical treatment for people living in Palestinian territories.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51606","51606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627357","2016-11-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the government of Honduras on human rights activists and the right to peaceful protest in that country.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51593","51593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627358","2016-11-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has had any discussions with representatives of the firm Mossack Fonseca since April 2016.","Biography information for Stewart Malcolm McDonald","Stewart Malcolm McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51590","51590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627360","2016-11-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how much funding the Government is providing to each (a) Israeli and (b) Palestinian non-governmental organisation through the (i) Conflict, Security and Stability Fund and (ii) bilateral programme budget in 2016-17.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51536","51536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627361","2016-11-07","Department of Health","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department has made an assessment of the potential level of cost pressures on learning disability service provider wage budgets arising from the application of the national living wage to sleep-in shifts.","Biography information for Peter Aldous","Peter Aldous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51566","51566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627364","2016-11-04","Department of Health","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the age profile of midwives working in the NHS in England was in (a) the most recent year for which figures are available, (b) 2010 and (c) 2005.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51597","51597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627365","2016-11-04","Department of Health","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the evidential basis is for his Department's proposal on a smaller number of large volume pharmacies reducing costs or improving NHS services.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Mr David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51603","51603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627366","2016-11-04","Department of Health","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the potential savings which community pharmacies can make to clinical commissioning group budgets.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Mr David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51604","51604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627367","2016-11-08","Department of Health","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which Ministers of his Department have met with NHS Improvement and the Care Quality Commission in which weeks since 11 July 2016; and at which of those meetings specific accident and emergency department closures were discussed.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51550","51550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627368","2016-11-04","Department of Health","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of women are employed by his Department on an inner London pay structure in the following pay grades (a) Administrative Assistant, (b) Administrative Officer, (c) Executive Officer, (d) Higher Executive Officer, (e) Fast Streamer, (f) Senior Executive Officer, (g) Grade Seven, (h) Grade Six, (i) Senior Civil Service Band 1, (j) Senior Civil Service Band 1A, (k) Senior Civil Service Band 2 and (l) Senior Civil Service Band 3.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51556","51556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627369","2016-11-04","Department of Health","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the letter of 17 December 2015 from the Director General, Innovation, Growth and Technology, and the Chief Pharmaceutical Officer supporting NHS England, to the Chief Executive of the Pharmaceutical Services Negotiating Committee, in which parts of the country there are more pharmacies than are necessary to maintain good access.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Mr David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51662","51662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627370","2016-11-07","Department of Health","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of accident and emergency admissions in October, November, December and January in each year since 2010 resulted from fireworks-related injuries.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51672","51672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627371","2016-11-04","Department of Health","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 12 October 2016 to Question 47425, how many GPs require assistance.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51648","51648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627372","2016-11-04","Department of Health","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 12 October 2016 to Question 47425, how much public money it is planned that each GP on the resilience programme will receive.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51649","51649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627373","2016-11-04","Department of Health","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether clinical commissioning groups' medicine management teams are held accountable by NHS England where they choose not to follow NICE guidelines.","Biography information for Nicky Morgan","Nicky Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51652","51652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627374","2016-11-04","Department of Health","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 12 October 2016 to Question 47425, what steps he took to encourage clinical commissioning groups to identify vulnerable practices by talking directly to the practices and local medical committees.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51650","51650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627375","2016-11-04","Department of Health","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information his Department holds on the average travel distance for treatment for child mental health inpatients.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51716","51716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627376","2016-11-04","Department of Health","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of the availability of mental health inpatient treatment for (a) children and (b) adults in (i) Birmingham Northfield constituency, (ii) Birmingham and (iii) England.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51714","51714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627378","2016-11-04","Department of Health","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that mental health inpatients under the age of 12 are able to receive treatment as close to their family home as possible.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51717","51717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627379","2016-11-07","Department of Health","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many psychological therapists were employed in Improving Access to Psychological Therapies Step 4 services in (a) Liverpool, Wavertree constituency, (b) Liverpool, (c) the Liverpool City Region and (d) each clinical commissioning group area in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51701","51701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627380","2016-11-07","Department of Health","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many repeat referrals there were to Improving Access to Psychological Therapies services in (a) Liverpool, Wavertree constituency, (b) Liverpool, (c) the Liverpool City Region and (d) each clinical commissioning group area in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51702","51702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627381","2016-11-07","Department of Health","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many clients with common mental health conditions were seen by an Improving Access to Psychological Therapies Step 4 service in (a) Liverpool, Wavertree constituency, (b) Liverpool, (c) the Liverpool City Region and (d) each clinical commissioning group area in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51704","51704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627382","2016-11-07","Department of Health","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make it his policy to publish recovery rates for Improving Access to Psychological Therapies Step 4 services.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51703","51703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627383","2016-11-07","Department of Health","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to his Department's publication, Future in Mind, published in March 2015, if he will take steps to implement the recommendations in that publication that young people who have been sexually abused or exploited receive a comprehensive specialist initial assessment and referral to the services they need.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51748","51748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627384","2016-11-04","Department of Health","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much his Department has spent on agency workers in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51722","51722"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627385","2016-11-04","Home Office","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that reviews under the Victims' Right to Review process are concluded swiftly.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51726","51726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627387","2016-11-04","Home Office","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 24 October 2016 to Question 49457, on children: refugees, when she expects a full answer to be provided to that Question.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51734","51734"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627388","2016-11-04","Home Office","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what other types of complaint can be made by someone who has requested a review under the Victims' Right to Review process while that process is ongoing.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51727","51727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627389","2016-11-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 13 October 2016 to Question 47261, on housing benefit: hostels, whether the new funding model will ensure that the social sector continues to be funded at current levels in real terms.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51735","51735"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627390","2016-11-04","Home Office","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of victims of human trafficking rescued in the UK during 2016 have been allowed to remain in the UK; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51667","51667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627392","2016-11-04","Home Office","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of the Security Industry Authority's online application processing of licences; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51666","51666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627393","2016-11-04","Home Office","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, for what reasons the Security Industry Authority has been unable to process promptly online applications for its licences; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51665","51665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627394","2016-11-04","Home Office","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how long on average the Victims' Right to Review process took to reach a conclusion in (a) England, (b) each region and (c) each police area in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51725","51725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627396","2016-11-07","Home Office","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 10 October 2016 to Question 46261, on asylum: EU law, how long she expects it will take her Department to prepare the information requested.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51736","51736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627397","2016-11-04","Home Office","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of victims of human trafficking rescued in the UK in the last five years are (a) EU nationals and (b) non-EU nationals; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51668","51668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627398","2016-11-07","Home Office","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which files and documents she reviewed before making her decision not to proceed with an inquiry into the events at Orgreave in 1984.","Biography information for Andy Burnham","Andy Burnham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51705","51705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627399","2016-11-04","Home Office","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make it her policy to ensure that freedom of movement to and from the UK for Irish citizens is pursued during negotiations between the UK and the EU on the UK's departure from the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51655","51655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627400","2016-11-04","Home Office","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much her Department has spent on agency workers in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51620","51620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627401","2016-11-07","Home Office","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of incidents attended by the Fire and Rescue Service have been related to fireworks in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51669","51669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627402","2016-11-07","Home Office","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many recorded crimes have related to fireworks in each year since 2010 in (a) the UK, (b) Wales, (c) Newport and (d) Newport East constituency.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51670","51670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627403","2016-11-04","Department for Education","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to provide assistance with the adoption process to  British nationals who adopt foreign-born children.","Biography information for Mary Robinson","Mary Robinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51695","51695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627404","2016-11-07","Home Office","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the Government plans to review its policy on the inclusion of students within the immigration cap.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51675","51675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627405","2016-11-04","Home Office","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of women are employed by her Department on an inner London pay structure in the following pay grades (a) Administrative Assistant, (b) Administrative Officer, (c) Executive Officer, (d) Higher Executive Officer, (e) Fast Streamer, (f) Senior Executive Officer, (g) Grade Seven, (h) Grade Six, (i) Senior Civil Service Band 1, (j) Senior Civil Service Band 1A, (k) Senior Civil Service Band 2 and (l) Senior Civil Service Band 3.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51557","51557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627406","2016-11-07","Home Office","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many named day written questions have not been answered with a substantive reply (a) on the day in question and (b) up to 4 days later than that day in the last six months.","Biography information for Mr David Winnick","Mr David Winnick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51571","51571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627407","2016-11-04","Home Office","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what sentences are handed down to people who commit a crime against animals that work with police officers.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51542","51542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627408","2016-11-04","Home Office","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what meetings her predecessor had with Ministerial colleagues to discuss the Troubled Families Programme between 12 May 2010 and 13 July 2016.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51538","51538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627409","2016-11-07","Home Office","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department was consulted by staff working for the Independent Inquiry into Child Sexual Abuse on that Inquiry's decision to procure the services of an external facilitator to assist in addressing tensions between Dame Lowell Goddard and other inquiry officials.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51587","51587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627410","2016-11-07","Home Office","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what her Department's policy is on Chief Constables replying to letters from Members of Parliament.","Biography information for Crispin Blunt","Crispin Blunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51588","51588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627411","2016-11-07","Home Office","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department has made an assessment of the potential effect of the revised funding formula on the Cumbria constabulary.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51532","51532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627412","2016-11-07","House of Commons Commission","2016-11-02","To ask the Rt. hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington representing the House of Commons Commission, how many hours have been spent by the staff of the House on the certification process necessitated by the English Votes for English Laws Standing Orders of the House of Commons since those orders were implemented; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51700","51700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627413","2016-11-07","Department for International Development","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what progress the Government has made on work with the US and the UN to respond to the request from the President of Botswana on behalf of SADC for funding to deal with the drought in Southern Africa.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51745","51745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627414","2016-11-07","Department for International Development","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what the percentage change there was in spending by her Department on programmes coded under HIV treatment, prevention and care in each year since 2012-13; and what the percentage change in such spending is projected to be between 2015-16 and 2016-17.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51673","51673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627416","2016-11-07","Department for International Development","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many of her Department's programmes that contribute to HIV prevention, treatment and care are planned to close in 2016-17; and what the value of those projects is.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51674","51674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627417","2016-11-04","Department for International Development","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much her Department has spent on agency workers in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51621","51621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627418","2016-11-07","Department for International Development","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what proportion of her Department's budget for Israel and the Occupied Palestinian Territories is spent on coexistence projects.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51535","51535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627419","2016-11-07","Department for International Development","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what proportion of the financial assistance provided to (a) projects through the Conflict, Stability and Security Fund and (b) bilateral programme budgets funds projects which promote coexistence between Israelis and Palestinians.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51548","51548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627420","2016-11-04","Department for International Development","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what proportion of women are employed by her Department on an inner London pay structure in the following pay grades (a) Administrative Assistant, (b) Administrative Officer, (c) Executive Officer, (d) Higher Executive Officer, (e) Fast Streamer, (f) Senior Executive Officer, (g) Grade Seven, (h) Grade Six, (i) Senior Civil Service Band 1, (j) Senior Civil Service Band 1A, (k) Senior Civil Service Band 2 and (l) Senior Civil Service Band 3.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51558","51558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627421","2016-11-04","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of women are employed by her Department on an inner London pay structure in the following pay grades (a) Administrative Assistant, (b) Administrative Officer, (c) Executive Officer, (d) Higher Executive Officer, (e) Fast Streamer, (f) Senior Executive Officer, (g) Grade Seven, (h) Grade Six, (i) Senior Civil Service Band 1, (j) Senior Civil Service Band 1A, (k) Senior Civil Service Band 2 and (l) Senior Civil Service Band 3.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51560","51560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627422","2016-11-04","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what discussions she has had with leaders of Crown Dependencies on publicly accessible central registers of beneficial ownership.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51541","51541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627423","2016-11-07","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps are being taken to ensure appropriate sentencing for people convicted of attacks and assaults on police and all front line emergency officers.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51573","51573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627424","2016-11-04","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps she is taking to limit the potential re-traumatisation of vulnerable 16 and 17 year old victims of sexual abuse or exploitation in the criminal justice system.","Biography information for Mrs Pauline Latham","Pauline Latham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51605","51605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627425","2016-11-04","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much her Department has spent on agency workers in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51623","51623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627426","2016-11-04","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the oral contribution of the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Justice of 1 November 2016, Official Report, column 777, when she plans to publish the review into the care and management of transgender offenders.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51656","51656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627427","2016-11-04","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, for what reasons her Department removed the requirement to have a panel member with direct experience of disability from the personal independence payments appeals process.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51740","51740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627429","2016-11-04","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps she is taking to ensure that people who appeal unsuccessful personal independence payments applications are adequately represented during the appeals process.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51741","51741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627430","2016-11-04","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 1 November 2016 to Question 49987, how many offenders who absconded from approved premises in each financial year since 2010-11 have (a) been re-arrested and (b) not yet been caught.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51723","51723"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627431","2016-11-04","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 1 November 2016 to Question 49987, what class order of offences were committed by people who absconded in each financial year since 2010-11.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51724","51724"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627432","2016-11-07","Leader of the House","2016-11-02","To ask the Leader of the House, what estimate he has made of the cost of implementation of the English Votes for English Laws Standing Orders of the House of Commons; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51699","51699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627433","2016-11-04","Northern Ireland Office","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how much his Department has spent on agency workers in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51624","51624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627434","2016-11-07","Northern Ireland Office","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, if he will hold discussions with the Northern Ireland Executive and business leaders on the promotion in the Irish Republic of retailing opportunities in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51530","51530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627435","2016-11-04","Northern Ireland Office","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what proportion of women are employed by his Department on an inner London pay structure in the following pay grades (a) Administrative Assistant, (b) Administrative Officer, (c) Executive Officer, (d) Higher Executive Officer, (e) Fast Streamer, (f) Senior Executive Officer, (g) Grade Seven, (h) Grade Six, (i) Senior Civil Service Band 1, (j) Senior Civil Service Band 1A, (k) Senior Civil Service Band 2 and (l) Senior Civil Service Band 3.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51561","51561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627436","2016-11-07","Prime Minister","2016-11-02","To ask the Prime Minister, if she will take steps to ensure that named day written questions for the Home Office are replied to with substantive replies on the day in question or when that is not possible not later than four days after that day in question.","Biography information for Mr David Winnick","Mr David Winnick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51572","51572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627437","2016-11-04","Prime Minister","2016-11-02","To ask the Prime Minister, what plans she has to change the official guidelines for recording meetings that take place with the newspaper press.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51537","51537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627438","2016-11-04","Home Office","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, for what reasons the Government plans not to reinstate police widow pensions for widowers who have had their pensions revoked due to remarriage or co-habiting under the Police Pension Regulations 1987; and if she will bring forward new proposals to ensure that all police widows are treated equally for the provision of such pensions.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51600","51600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627439","2016-11-04","Prime Minister","2016-11-02","To ask the Prime Minister, pursuant to the Answer of 28 October 2016 to Question 50210, for what reasons the Government does not include minutes of meetings with external agencies and members of the press in its quarterly releases.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51591","51591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627440","2016-11-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to the briefing given by his official spokesperson on 18 October 2016, when he plans to review available evidence on the Troubled Families Programme.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51696","51696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627441","2016-11-04","Scotland Office","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how much his Department has spent on agency workers in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51625","51625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627442","2016-11-04","Scotland Office","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what proportion of women are employed by his Department on an inner London pay structure in the following pay grades (a) Administrative Assistant, (b) Administrative Officer, (c) Executive Officer, (d) Higher Executive Officer, (e) Fast Streamer, (f) Senior Executive Officer, (g) Grade Seven, (h) Grade Six, (i) Senior Civil Service Band 1, (j) Senior Civil Service Band 1A, (k) Senior Civil Service Band 2 and (l) Senior Civil Service Band 3.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51562","51562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627443","2016-11-04","Department for Transport","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what proportion of women are employed by his Department on an inner London pay structure in the following pay grades (a) Administrative Assistant, (b) Administrative Officer, (c) Executive Officer, (d) Higher Executive Officer, (e) Fast Streamer, (f) Senior Executive Officer, (g) Grade Seven, (h) Grade Six, (i) Senior Civil Service Band 1, (j) Senior Civil Service Band 1A, (k) Senior Civil Service Band 2 and (l) Senior Civil Service Band 3.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51563","51563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627444","2016-11-04","Department for Transport","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans he has to (a) consult on and (b) publish new guidance for the Civil Aviation Authority on Environmental Objectives Relating to the Exercise of its Air Navigation Functions.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51601","51601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627445","2016-11-04","Department for Transport","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much his Department has spent on agency workers in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51626","51626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627446","2016-11-04","Department for Transport","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he has consulted the Office of Rail and Road on the implications for its remit of the draft Transatlantic Trade and Investment Partnership.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51640","51640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627447","2016-11-04","Department for Transport","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with the Civil Aviation Authority on the implications for its remit of the draft Transatlantic Trade and Investment Partnership.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51643","51643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627449","2016-11-07","Department for Transport","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what powers local authorities possess to effectively regulate private hire vehicles that operate outside of their primary licensing area.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51678","51678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627450","2016-11-04","Wales Office","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how much his Department has spent on agency workers in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51628","51628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627451","2016-11-04","Wales Office","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what proportion of women are employed by his Department on an inner London pay structure in the following pay grades (a) Administrative Assistant, (b) Administrative Officer, (c) Executive Officer, (d) Higher Executive Officer, (e) Fast Streamer, (f) Senior Executive Officer, (g) Grade Seven, (h) Grade Six, (i) Senior Civil Service Band 1, (j) Senior Civil Service Band 1A, (k) Senior Civil Service Band 2 and (l) Senior Civil Service Band 3.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51564","51564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627453","2016-11-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, which local authorities plan to roll-out the lower benefit cap for newly-affected claimants from the week commencing (a) 7 November 2016, (b) 14 November 2016, (c) 21 November 2016, (d) 28 November 2016, (e) 5 December 2016, (f) 12 December 2016, (g) 19 December 2016, (h) 26 December 2016, (i) 2 January 2017, (j) 9 January 2017, (k) 16 January 2017 and (l) 23 January 2017.","Biography information for Ms Karen Buck","Ms Karen Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51568","51568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627454","2016-11-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of claimants affected by the lower benefit cap in (a) Westminster City Council and (b) the Royal Borough of Kensington and Chelsea are in receipt of (i) jobseeker's allowance, (ii) employment and support allowance and (iii) income support.","Biography information for Ms Karen Buck","Ms Karen Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51569","51569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627455","2016-11-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of women are employed by his Department on an inner London pay structure in the following pay grades (a) Administrative Assistant, (b) Administrative Officer, (c) Executive Officer, (d) Higher Executive Officer, (e) Fast Streamer, (f) Senior Executive Officer, (g) Grade Seven, (h) Grade Six, (i) Senior Civil Service Band 1, (j) Senior Civil Service Band 1A, (k) Senior Civil Service Band 2 and (l) Senior Civil Service Band 3.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51565","51565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627456","2016-11-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many notices of finalised Child Support Agency (CSA) arrears have been sent to parents with care whose CSA liability has ended in each month since March 2016.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51583","51583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627457","2016-11-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many Child Support Agency cases have been referred for arrears cleansing in each month since March 2016.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51584","51584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627458","2016-11-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what amount of former Child Support Agency arrears has been written off at the parent with care's request since the end of March 2016.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51585","51585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627459","2016-11-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, by what amount the total of Child Support Agency (CSA) maintenance arrears held on CSA IT systems has been reduced since January 2015 as a result of cases selected on a proactive or reactive basis for case closure.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51586","51586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627460","2016-11-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many applications were made for short-term benefit advance and hardship payments in the last 12 months; and what proportion of such applications were successful.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51544","51544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627461","2016-11-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of new claims for (a) jobseeker's allowance and (b) employment and support allowance were processed within (i) five, (ii) 10 and (iii) 16 days in the most recent 12 months for which data is available.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51545","51545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627462","2016-11-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of new claims for universal credit were processed and paid within 42 days in the most recent 12 month period for which data is available.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51546","51546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627463","2016-11-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many households in (a) East Ham constituency and (b) the London Borough of Newham will be affected by the extension of the benefit cap to 23,000; and in each such case what the average reduction in benefits will be.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51576","51576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627464","2016-11-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in East Ham constituency (a) are entitled to claim child maintenance and (b) have experienced payment arrears due to non-resident parents not paying full or any child maintenance within the last 12 months; and what the total value is of these unpaid arrears.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51577","51577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627465","2016-11-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much his Department has spent on agency workers in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51629","51629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627466","2016-11-04","Department for Education","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to paragraph 3.85 of the Government's publication, Keep on Caring, published in July 2016, what progress is being made by her Department on exploring the extension of the exemption from the shared accommodation rate of housing benefit to age 25.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51694","51694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627467","2016-11-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many full-time equivalent staff have worked in the Child Poverty Unit in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51676","51676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627468","2016-11-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he plans to make an announcement on the timetable for the future roll-out of universal credit.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51677","51677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627470","2016-11-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate his Department has made of the potential effect of the extension of the benefit cap to 23,000 per year in London and 20,000 per year outside London on the level of spending by local authorities  on (a) emergency, (b) temporary and (c) bed and breakfast accommodation for people at risk of homelessness.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51693","51693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627471","2016-11-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate his Department has made of the potential effect of the extension of the benefit cap to 23,000 per year in London and 20,000 per year outside London on the levels of homelessness.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51684","51684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627472","2016-11-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate his Department has made of the potential effect of the extension of the benefit cap to 23,000 per year in London and 20,000 per year outside London on the number of (a) people and (b) children who use food banks.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51685","51685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627473","2016-11-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate his Department has made of the number of (a) households and (b) children who will be affected by the extension of the benefit cap to 23,000 per year in London and 20,000 per year outside London in (i) Tottenham constituency, (ii) Borough of Haringey, (iii) London and (iv) the UK.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51686","51686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627474","2016-11-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate his Department has made of the potential effect of the extension of the benefit cap to 23,000 per year in London and 20,000 per year outside London on the number of (a) people and (b) children living in households in (i) relative poverty and (ii) absolute poverty.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51687","51687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627475","2016-11-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate his Department has made of the number of households living in emergency housing who will be affected by the extension of the benefit cap to 23,000 per year in London and 20,000 per year outside London.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51688","51688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627476","2016-11-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate his Department has made of the  potential effect of the extension of the benefit cap to 23,000 per year in London and 20,000 per year outside London on the number of households applying for discretionary housing payments.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51689","51689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627477","2016-11-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate his Department has made of the number of (a) households and (b) children who have been affected by the benefit cap since it was introduced in 2013.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51692","51692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627478","2016-11-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 1 November 2016 to Question 49935, what arrangements he has put in place to assess the effect on the children concerned of the revised provisions in the 2012 scheme for varying child support payments following changes in income of the paying parent.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51732","51732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627479","2016-11-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people from Garston and Halewood constituency have had their personal independence payment claim rejected since April 2013.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51738","51738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627481","2016-11-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people from Garston and Halewood constituency have had their eligibility for the motability scheme revoked since April 2013.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51739","51739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627482","2016-11-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many people are deemed to live in fuel poverty; and how this figure has changed over the last three years.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51747","51747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627483","2016-11-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department is taking to promote innovation in (a) south east England and (b) nationally.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51661","51661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627484","2016-11-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what discussions he had with his counterparts at the Department for Transport prior to Nissan's announcement of 27 October 2016 on the production of the next Qashqai and X-Trail models in the UK.","Biography information for Stewart Malcolm McDonald","Stewart Malcolm McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51712","51712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627485","2016-11-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department plans to take to help ensure that medical research between British and Israeli scientists who receive funding from EU institutions continue to have access to similar levels of funding after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51660","51660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627486","2016-11-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate he has made of the level of public sales of fireworks in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51671","51671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627487","2016-11-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how much his Department has spent on agency workers in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51613","51613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627488","2016-11-04","Department for International Trade","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether he has consulted the Office of Gas and Electricity Markets on the implications for its remit of the draft Transatlantic Trade and Investment Partnership.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51639","51639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627489","2016-11-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether it is his policy that the UK will remain part of the European Community Urgent Radiological Information Exchange after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for George Kerevan","George Kerevan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51654","51654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627490","2016-11-04","Department for International Trade","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether he has consulted the Competition and Markets Authority on the implications for its remit of the draft Transatlantic Trade and Investment Partnership.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51637","51637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627491","2016-11-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate he has made of the effect of delays to the DCC go-live date.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51579","51579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627492","2016-11-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the effect of increased volumes of SMETS1 smart meters being installed on customers' ability to switch energy supplier.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51580","51580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627493","2016-11-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the implications are for UK membership of the European Atomic Energy Community of the UK's decision to leave the EU.","Biography information for George Kerevan","George Kerevan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51592","51592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627494","2016-11-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what his Department's timetable is for publication of its plans for the next Contract for Difference allocation round for less established technologies.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51594","51594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627495","2016-11-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the reasons are for the time taken to prepare the readiness of the Data and Communications Company after Capita plc was awarded the operating licence in October 2013; and what the timetable is for that company to become ready.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51595","51595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627496","2016-11-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate he has made of the number of recruitment agencies which require clients to register as a business before finding them employment.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51602","51602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627497","2016-11-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment the Government has made of whether UK companies will need to register future trademarks and patents in both the UK and the EU to ensure protection after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51553","51553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627498","2016-11-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate his Department has made of the potential economic benefits of the remote Scottish islands onshore wind projects for (a) the regional economies of those islands and (b) the wider UK supply chain.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51581","51581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627499","2016-11-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when he plans to publish an updated impact assessment for the smart meter programme.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51582","51582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627501","2016-11-04","Department for International Trade","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what proportion of women are employed by his Department on an inner London pay structure in the following pay grades (a) Administrative Assistant, (b) Administrative Officer, (c) Executive Officer, (d) Higher Executive Officer, (e) Fast Streamer, (f) Senior Executive Officer, (g) Grade Seven, (h) Grade Six, (i) Senior Civil Service Band 1, (j) Senior Civil Service Band 1A, (k) Senior Civil Service Band 2 and (l) Senior Civil Service Band 3.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51559","51559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627502","2016-11-04","Department for International Trade","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, if he will make it his Department's policy to refuse future trade deals between the UK and countries that criminalise consensual same-sex conduct.","Biography information for Stewart Malcolm McDonald","Stewart Malcolm McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51589","51589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627503","2016-11-04","Department for International Trade","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how much his Department has spent on agency workers in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51622","51622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627504","2016-11-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if his Department will introduce a ban on the import of carbon monoxide alarms which do not comply with the BS EN 50291 safety standard after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51659","51659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627505","2016-11-04","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how much his Department has spent on agency workers in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51618","51618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627506","2016-11-04","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, which repatriated powers will become the responsibility of the devolved administrations when the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Tom Elliott","Tom Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51539","51539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/628097","2016-11-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment the Government has made of the level of business growth since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Ranil Jayawardena","Mr Ranil Jayawardena","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 907137","907137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/628181","2016-11-08","Department for Transport","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on business of airport expansion in the South East.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 907129","907129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/631269","2016-11-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department is taking to maximise the potential benefits of the UK leaving the EU for businesses.","Biography information for Oliver Colvile","Oliver Colvile","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 907133","907133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/631334","2016-11-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps the Government has taken to set out its industrial strategy; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris White","Chris White","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 907132","907132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/631335","2016-11-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the (a) job security and (b) employment rights of on-demand workers.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 907134","907134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/631336","2016-11-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent discussions he has had with the Chancellor of the Exchequer on support for the North Sea oil and gas sector.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 907135","907135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626501","2016-11-03","Attorney General","2016-11-01","To ask the Attorney General, what proportion of women are employed by the Law Officers' Departments on an inner London pay structure in the following pay grades (a) Administrative Assistant, (b) Administrative Officer, (c) Executive Officer, (d) Higher Executive Officer, (e) Fast Streamer, (f) Senior Executive Officer, (g) Grade Seven, (h) Grade Six, (i) Senior Civil Service Band 1, (j) Senior Civil Service Band 1A, (k) Senior Civil Service Band 2 and (l) Senior Civil Service Band 3.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51385","51385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626502","2016-11-04","Cabinet Office","2016-11-01","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what guidance his Department has given to other government departments on answering Written Parliamentary Questions using a reference to the gov.uk website without referring hon. Members to a specific page where the information sought can be found.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51397","51397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626503","2016-11-03","Cabinet Office","2016-11-01","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what proportion of women are employed by his Department on an inner London pay structure in the following pay grades (a) Administrative Assistant, (b) Administrative Officer, (c) Executive Officer, (d) Higher Executive Officer, (e) Fast Streamer, (f) Senior Executive Officer, (g) Grade Seven, (h) Grade Six, (i) Senior Civil Service Band 1, (j) Senior Civil Service Band 1A, (k) Senior Civil Service Band 2 and (l) Senior Civil Service Band 3.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51386","51386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626504","2016-11-03","Cabinet Office","2016-11-01","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what plans the Government has to strengthen the security of voter identification to prevent electoral fraud.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51374","51374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626505","2016-11-03","Cabinet Office","2016-11-01","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether the Cabinet Office plans to alter official guidelines for (a) Ministers and (b) special advisers to Ministers relating to meetings with members of the press.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51376","51376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626506","2016-11-04","Cabinet Office","2016-11-01","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 1 November 2016 to Question 49982, which Minister will exercise the prerogative to trigger Article 50 of the Treaty on the Functions of the EU on behalf of the sovereign.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51394","51394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626507","2016-11-04","Cabinet Office","2016-11-01","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, which government departments allow professional drivers making deliveries to departmental premises to use employee toilet facilities.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51435","51435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626508","2016-11-03","HM Treasury","2016-11-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what proportion of women are employed by his Department on an inner London pay structure in the following pay grades (a) Administrative Assistant, (b) Administrative Officer, (c) Executive Officer, (d) Higher Executive Officer, (e) Fast Streamer, (f) Senior Executive Officer, (g) Grade Seven, (h) Grade Six, (i) Senior Civil Service Band 1, (j) Senior Civil Service Band 1A, (k) Senior Civil Service Band 2 and (l) Senior Civil Service Band 3. Band 3.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51393","51393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626509","2016-11-04","HM Treasury","2016-11-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much (a) further education colleges and (b) sixth form colleges paid in VAT in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51488","51488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626510","2016-11-04","HM Treasury","2016-11-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people in (a) Warrington and (b) Warrington North constituency have (i) been wrongly accused by Concentrix of falsely claiming tax credits and (ii) had tax credits wrongly withdrawn.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51504","51504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626511","2016-11-03","HM Treasury","2016-11-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what guidance his Department makes available to help prepare for the consequences of inheritance tax and other death-related costs.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51295","51295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626512","2016-11-04","HM Treasury","2016-11-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the (a) average waiting time was for a call to be answered, (b) average length of each answered call and (c) longest waiting time was to the HM Revenue and Customs' publicised helplines in each of the last 12 months for which figures are available.","Biography information for Kirsty Blackman","Kirsty Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51310","51310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626513","2016-11-04","HM Treasury","2016-11-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people are eligible for marriage tax allowance; and of those people, how many have taken it up.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51521","51521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626514","2016-11-03","HM Treasury","2016-11-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people in Tottenham constituency have had a tax credit claim stopped by Concentrix.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51463","51463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626516","2016-11-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he expects to approve the Birmingham local plan.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51305","51305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626517","2016-11-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when and how he plans to publish the work programme of the ministerial group on homelessness; and how voluntary and community organisations are represented on that group.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51313","51313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626518","2016-11-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to improve the supply of shared equity affordable housing in (a) Peterborough and (b) England; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stewart Jackson","Mr Stewart Jackson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51309","51309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626519","2016-11-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, for what reasons his Department has called in the Birmingham local plan for review.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51304","51304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626520","2016-11-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what progress has been made on drawing up a register of rogue landlords.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51372","51372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626521","2016-11-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the effect on the personal, social and economic well-being of older people of moving into accommodation designed to meet their needs.","Biography information for David Mackintosh","David Mackintosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51353","51353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626522","2016-11-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to encourage developers to offer optional eco-friendly extras in new-build properties.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51354","51354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626523","2016-11-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what information his Department holds on the number of street homeless people with a (a) disability or (b) mental health condition.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51498","51498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626524","2016-11-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will amend the Town and Country Planning (Use Classes) Order 1987 and the Town and Country Planning (General Permitted Development) (England) Order 2016 to remove public houses from the A4 Use Class and place them in a class of their own.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51413","51413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626525","2016-11-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what proportion of women are employed by his Department on an inner London pay structure in the following pay grades (a) Administrative Assistant, (b) Administrative Officer, (c) Executive Officer, (d) Higher Executive Officer, (e) Fast Streamer, (f) Senior Executive Officer, (g) Grade Seven, (h) Grade Six, (i) Senior Civil Service Band 1, (j) Senior Civil Service Band 1A, (k) Senior Civil Service Band 2 and (l) Senior Civil Service Band 3.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51387","51387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626526","2016-11-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will make it his policy to strengthen the protections afforded to private rent tenants under section 4 of the Defective Premises Act 1972.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51405","51405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626527","2016-11-03","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what proportion of women are employed by her Department on an inner London pay structure in the following pay grades (a) Administrative Assistant, (b) Administrative Officer, (c) Executive Officer, (d) Higher Executive Officer, (e) Fast Streamer, (f) Senior Executive Officer, (g) Grade Seven, (h) Grade Six, (i) Senior Civil Service Band 1, (j) Senior Civil Service Band 1A, (k) Senior Civil Service Band 2 and (l) Senior Civil Service Band 3.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51388","51388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626528","2016-11-04","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if she will make urgent representations to FIFA to ensure that football teams representing the constituent parts of the UK can display a poppy on their shirts during forthcoming international fixtures if they so choose.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51511","51511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626529","2016-11-04","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment her Department has made of the benefits of the forthcoming release of 2.3GHz and 3.4GHz for the availability of high-speed mobile broadband in rural areas.","Biography information for Richard Arkless","Richard  Arkless","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51515","51515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626530","2016-11-04","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment her Department has made of the effect of mobile spectrum distribution on the data capacity of the UK's mobile networks.","Biography information for Richard Arkless","Richard  Arkless","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51518","51518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626531","2016-11-04","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether her Department will make an assessment of the benefits to the UK mobile market of imposing a cap on the total amount of mobile spectrum that individual operators can hold.","Biography information for Richard Arkless","Richard  Arkless","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51519","51519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626532","2016-11-03","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Answer of 29 March 2016 to Question 32105, what progress has been made on securing the release of the MQ-9 Reaper User Group terms of reference.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51332","51332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626533","2016-11-03","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to support armed forces veterans who are disabled or have a long-term health condition.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51334","51334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626534","2016-11-03","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, on what dates he met (a) Ministers and (b) officials of the Department for Education to discuss academic support for children of military personnel.","Biography information for Dr Andrew Murrison","Dr Andrew Murrison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51306","51306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626535","2016-11-03","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that retired Gurkhas and their families settled in the UK have access to adequate welfare support and advice.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51296","51296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626536","2016-11-03","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the estimated cost is of refurbishment at MOD Lyneham for accommodating consolidated Army, Royal Navy and RAF training.","Biography information for Dr Andrew Murrison","Dr Andrew Murrison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51317","51317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626537","2016-11-03","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many personnel are being trained at MOD Lyneham.","Biography information for Dr Andrew Murrison","Dr Andrew Murrison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51318","51318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626538","2016-11-03","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 31 October 2016 to Question 49921, if he will place in the Library a copy of the forward purchase programme for foreign currency as at 1 November 2016.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51418","51418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626539","2016-11-04","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many of the allegations of bribery and corruption his Department referred to law enforcement agencies resulted in a company being found guilty.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51500","51500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626540","2016-11-03","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many personnel from the (a) Royal Navy and (b) Royal Air Force are seconded to work on US Navy Aircraft Carriers.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51470","51470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626541","2016-11-03","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans he has to test the suitability of the Northrop Grumman X-47B Unmanned Ariel Vehicle for operation aboard Queen Elizabeth Class ships.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51471","51471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626542","2016-11-03","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Royal Marine personnel are currently seconded to HMS Queen Elizabeth.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51472","51472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626543","2016-11-03","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the principal technical faults are that have led to the delay of the transfer of the RFA Tidespring to the UK for customisation and capability assessment trials until 2017.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51473","51473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626544","2016-11-03","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what proportion of women are employed by his Department on an inner London pay structure in the following pay grades (a) Administrative Assistant, (b) Administrative Officer, (c) Executive Officer, (d) Higher Executive Officer, (e) Fast Streamer, (f) Senior Executive Officer, (g) Grade Seven, (h) Grade Six, (i) Senior Civil Service Band 1, (j) Senior Civil Service Band 1A, (k) Senior Civil Service Band 2 and (l) Senior Civil Service Band 3.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51389","51389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626545","2016-11-04","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which submarine will undergo Initial Dismantling at Rosyth.","Biography information for Steven Paterson","Steven Paterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51434","51434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626546","2016-11-04","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 25 October 2016 to Question 49700, how many of the allegations of bribery and corruption referred by his Department to law enforcement agencies involved (a) UK companies and (b) foreign companies; and if he will release the names of those companies and the results of any investigations.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51487","51487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626547","2016-11-04","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much his Department has spent on maintenance and checks for the nuclear-powered submarines in laid-up storage at (a) Her Majesty's Naval Base Devonport and (b) Rosyth Dockyard.","Biography information for Steven Paterson","Steven Paterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51442","51442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626548","2016-11-03","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 17 October 2016 to Question 47824, what provisions his Department has made to service all six Type 45 Destroyers when they are alongside together at HMNB Portsmouth.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51416","51416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626549","2016-11-03","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 15 February 2016 to Question 26634, what progress he has made on the establishment of UK Defence Staffs in the Asia Pacific, Middle East and Africa.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51417","51417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626550","2016-11-04","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 25 October 2016 to Question 49700, how many of the allegations of bribery and corruption referred by his Department to law enforcement agencies involved the bribery of foreign public officials; and how many of those referrals resulted in law enforcement action being taken.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51486","51486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626551","2016-11-04","Department for Education","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans she has to consult with employers on the appointment of a new permanent chief executive of the Institute for Apprenticeships.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51490","51490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626552","2016-11-04","Department for Education","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many students enrolled in each of the further education colleges in Greater Manchester for each level of NVQ in the last three years for which information is available.","Biography information for Ann Coffey","Ann Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51436","51436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626553","2016-11-04","Department for Education","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many students progressed from level 2 NVQ to further training and education in each of the further education colleges in Greater Manchester in the last five years for which information is available.","Biography information for Ann Coffey","Ann Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51437","51437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626555","2016-11-04","Department for Education","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many students enrolled in (a) GCSE and (b) A Level courses in each of the further education colleges in Greater Manchester in the last five years for which information is available.","Biography information for Ann Coffey","Ann Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51438","51438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626556","2016-11-03","Department for Education","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of women are employed by her Department on an inner London pay structure in the following pay grades (a) Administrative Assistant, (b) Administrative Officer, (c) Executive Officer, (d) Higher Executive Officer, (e) Fast Streamer, (f) Senior Executive Officer, (g) Grade Seven, (h) Grade Six, (i) Senior Civil Service Band 1, (j) Senior Civil Service Band 1A, (k) Senior Civil Service Band 2 and (l) Senior Civil Service Band 3.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51390","51390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626557","2016-11-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the legal protections in place for workers engaged with online platforms in the gig economy.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51367","51367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626558","2016-11-03","Department for Education","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many special guardianship orders were made in respect of children who were (a) under one year old, (b) one to four years old, (c) five to nine years old, (d) 10 to 15 years old and (e) 16 years old and above on 31 March 2016.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51356","51356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626559","2016-11-04","Women and Equalities","2016-11-01","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, which civil society stakeholders have been consulted on the proposed restructuring of the Equality and Human Rights Commission.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51366","51366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626560","2016-11-04","Department for Education","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent estimate she has made of the number of (a) EU and (b) non-EU students in UK universities in each of the next five years; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51501","51501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626561","2016-11-04","Department for Education","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many people in Warrington North constituency have undertaken an apprenticeship in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51502","51502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626562","2016-11-04","Department for Education","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many 16 to 18 year olds have undertaken an apprenticeship in each of the last five years; and how many of those apprentices were (a) male, (b) female and (c) from an ethnic minority.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51489","51489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626563","2016-11-04","Department for Education","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her Department's policy is on the respective roles of the Apprenticeship Delivery Board and the Institute for Apprenticeships after the departure of the hon. Member for Stratford-upon-Avon from the position of Apprenticeship Tsar.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51491","51491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626564","2016-11-04","Department for Education","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the written statement of 27 October 2016, HCWS223, on technical and further education, what additional staffing and resources she plans to allocate to the Institute for Apprenticeships.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51492","51492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626565","2016-11-04","Department for Education","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of the number of staff who will be employed by the Institute for Apprenticeships by (a) January 2017, (b) May 2017 and (c) January 2018.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51493","51493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626566","2016-11-03","Department for Education","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which 10 local authority areas had the largest decline in GCSE take-up for (a) art and design, (b) design and technology, (c) drama and (d) music in the last five years; and what proportion of students qualified for free school meals in each of those areas.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51458","51458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626567","2016-11-03","Department for Education","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will increase the fair access limit of 5,000 per child from the Adoption Support Fund from March 2017; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51457","51457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626568","2016-11-03","Department for Education","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many applications for support of a value equal to or above 5,000 from the Adoption Support Fund have been made since that fund was established.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51455","51455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626569","2016-11-03","Department for Education","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the value is of the average application for support from the Adoption Support Fund.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51453","51453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626570","2016-11-03","Department for Education","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of total applications for support from the Adoption Support Fund are of a sum equal to or above 5,000.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51454","51454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626571","2016-11-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate he has made of the funding to UK-based consortia from the EU Horizon 2020 programme in each of the next four years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51506","51506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626572","2016-11-03","Department for Education","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many instances of financial malpractice and irregularity in (a) free schools and academies and (b) community schools have occurred in each of the last three years; and what proportion of each type of school they have occurred in.","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51423","51423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626573","2016-11-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will match EU funding for universities and other research institutions for (a) the Erasmus plus programme and (b) any other sources of non-Horizon 2020 funding after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51507","51507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626574","2016-11-03","Department for Education","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate her Department has made of the proportion of adopted children requesting support that costs over the 5,000 fair access limit who live in the top 20 per cent most deprived local authority areas.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51449","51449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626575","2016-11-04","Department for Education","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many new (a) school sixth forms and (b) 16 to 19 free schools have opened in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51508","51508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626576","2016-11-04","Department for Education","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to implement the recommendations of the Report of the Independent Panel on Technical Education.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51509","51509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626577","2016-11-03","Department for Education","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate her Department has made of the effect of local authority funding on (a) the willingness of local authorities to approve support that costs more than the 5,000 fair access limit and (b) the ability of local authorities to pay their share of support that exceeds the 5,000 fair access limit.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51450","51450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626578","2016-11-04","Department for Education","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many grammar schools (a) sponsor academy schools, (b) sponsor free schools or (c) run multi-academy trusts; and what the Ofsted grades are for each school sponsored by a (i) university or (ii) multi-academy trust run by a university.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51314","51314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626579","2016-11-04","Department for Education","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many universities sponsor (a) academy schools, (b) free schools or (c) run multi-academy trusts; and what the Ofsted grades are for each school sponsored by a (i) university or (ii) multi-academy trust run by a university.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51315","51315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626580","2016-11-03","Department for Education","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when her Department plans to make available fairer funding to families in Worcestershire.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51302","51302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626581","2016-11-04","Department for Education","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 17 October 2016 to Question 48450, which local authorities have teaching schools.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51337","51337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626582","2016-11-04","Department for Education","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when her Department plans to Answer Questions 49159, 49160, 49203 and 49204.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51343","51343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626583","2016-11-04","Women and Equalities","2016-11-01","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what recent assessment she has made of the effect on engagement with civil society organisations of the reduction made in the 2015 Comprehensive Spending Review to the budget of the Equality and Human Rights Commission.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51365","51365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626584","2016-11-04","Women and Equalities","2016-11-01","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what the Equality and Human Rights Commission budget will be for each of the next three years.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51364","51364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626585","2016-11-04","Department for Education","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to ensure that UK universities remain globally competitive after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51362","51362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626587","2016-11-03","Department for Education","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans her Department has to address the change in the uptake of arts and humanities subjects at GCSE (a) among disadvantaged students and (b) generally.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51460","51460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626588","2016-11-03","Department for Education","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many applications for support from the Adoption Support Fund have been made in each month since it was established.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51456","51456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626589","2016-11-03","Department for Education","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate her Department has made of the change in the uptake of arts and humanities subjects at GCSE as a result of the English Bacclaureate.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51459","51459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626590","2016-11-03","Department for Education","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will increase funding to local authorities to support adopted children who require therapy and support of a value above the 5,000 Adoption Support Fund fair access cap.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51461","51461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626591","2016-11-03","Department for Education","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment her Department has made of the effect of the Adoption Support Fund fair access limit on (a) children with significant and complex needs and (b) adoptive families.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51462","51462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626592","2016-11-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what her policy is on maintaining the standards set out in EU food standards directives after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51361","51361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626593","2016-11-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the oral contribution by the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, of 18 October 2016, Official Report, column 300WH, on environmental protection, for what reasons judgments can be made by (a) judicial review, (b) the European Court of Justice and (c) the European Commission; what the scope is of such judgments; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51345","51345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626594","2016-11-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the oral contribution by the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, of 18 October 2016, Official Report, column 300WH, on Environmental protection, what information the Government holds on the average costs to the litigant of (a) a judicial review, (b) a case being considered by the European Court of Justice and (c) the European Commission; what the scope is of such judgments; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51346","51346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626595","2016-11-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of harmonising with the Council of Europe's Emerald Network of Areas of Special Conservation Interest; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51347","51347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626596","2016-11-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to assess the potential threat to chestnut trees from moth-borne diseases.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51294","51294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626597","2016-11-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when she plans to publish her Department's review into animal establishments licensing in England.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51311","51311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626598","2016-11-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, on what dates she has met representatives from the milk industry to discuss raising dairy prices.","Biography information for Dr Andrew Murrison","Dr Andrew Murrison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51319","51319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626599","2016-11-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will bring forward legislative proposals to (a) end third-party sales of puppies and (b) regulate adverts relating to the private sale of puppies.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51512","51512"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626600","2016-11-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what proportion of women are employed by her Department on an inner London pay structure in the following pay grades (a) Administrative Assistant, (b) Administrative Officer, (c) Executive Officer, (d) Higher Executive Officer, (e) Fast Streamer, (f) Senior Executive Officer, (g) Grade Seven, (h) Grade Six, (i) Senior Civil Service Band 1, (j) Senior Civil Service Band 1A, (k) Senior Civil Service Band 2 and (l) Senior Civil Service Band 3.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51391","51391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626601","2016-11-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many vehicles the Animal and Plant Agency has inspected (a) during the loading of live animals and (b) at ports from which live animals have been exported in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Mr Mark Williams","Mr Mark Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51396","51396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626602","2016-11-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the contribution that monitoring settlement expansion in the West Bank makes to the prospects for (a) coexistence of Israelis and Palestinians and (b) the creation of a viable and independent Palestinian state alongside Israel.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51476","51476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626603","2016-11-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to the Palestinian Authority on its commitments to the Quartet Principles.","Biography information for John Howell","John Howell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51375","51375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626604","2016-11-03","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Government's Response to the Joint Committee on Human Rights Second Report of Session 2015-16, what recent discussions his Department has had with their (a) US and (b) European counterparts on international law on the use of force and the law of armed conflict.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51426","51426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626605","2016-11-03","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Government's Response to the Joint Committee on Human Rights Second Report of Session 2015-16, what recent assessment his Department has made of the legal principles of (a) international and (b) domestic law that apply to the use of lethal force outside the scope of armed conflict.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51425","51425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626606","2016-11-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his Department has received representations from the BBC on providing a Korean-language service for North Korea.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51444","51444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626607","2016-11-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the contribution that Israelis working alongside Palestinians make to promoting equality and respect for human rights for both peoples.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51478","51478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626609","2016-11-03","Department of Health","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he plans to take to ensure that all people with diabetes have access to a multidisciplinary footcare team at their local hospital.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51278","51278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626610","2016-11-03","Department of Health","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will introduce a target for trusts on the proportion of people with diabetes receiving a foot risk assessment on admission to hospital.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51279","51279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626611","2016-11-03","Department of Health","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 26 October 2016 to Question 49514, when the decision on whether to adopt the ethnicity values from the 2011 census within the NHS is expected.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51280","51280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626612","2016-11-03","Department of Health","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to improve the process of patient data transfer when moving from one GP to another.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51281","51281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626613","2016-11-03","Department of Health","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to increase the number of neurologists.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51282","51282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626614","2016-11-03","Department of Health","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to increase the number of specially trained epilepsy nurses.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51283","51283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626616","2016-11-03","Department of Health","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimates he has made of the total number of specially trained epilepsy nurses (a) currently working in the UK and (b) that NHS trusts require.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51284","51284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626617","2016-11-03","Department of Health","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the total number of people from black and minority ethnic backgrounds suffering from epilepsy in (a) the UK, (b) London and (c) the London North West Healthcare NHS Trust.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51285","51285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626618","2016-11-03","Department of Health","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the total number of children and young people suffering from epilepsy in (a) the UK, (b) London and (c) the London North West Healthcare NHS Trust.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51286","51286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626619","2016-11-03","Department of Health","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of people suffering from epilepsy in (a) the UK, (b) London and (c) the London North West Healthcare NHS Trust.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51287","51287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626620","2016-11-03","Department of Health","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to financially support people with coeliac disease.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51288","51288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626621","2016-11-03","Department of Health","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions his Department has had with clinical bodies on the potential link between dizziness and dementia.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51289","51289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626622","2016-11-03","Department of Health","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of standardising the charge levied by GPs on patients for the provision of sick notes for benefit queries and other purposes.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51290","51290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626623","2016-11-03","Department of Health","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many women have had polycystic ovary syndrome in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51291","51291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626624","2016-11-03","Department of Health","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidance is made available to women participating in IVF treatments on avoidance of artificial sweetners.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51292","51292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626625","2016-11-03","Department of Health","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions his Department has had with clinical bodies on the potential link between headaches and depression.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51293","51293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626626","2016-11-03","Department of Health","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure the safety of the HPV vaccination.","Biography information for Sir Graham Brady","Mr Graham Brady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51320","51320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626627","2016-11-03","Department of Health","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether HC2 certificates provided to asylum seekers being supported under section 95 of the Immigration and Asylum Act 1999 are automatically renewed.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51321","51321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626629","2016-11-04","Department of Health","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 21 October 2016 to Question 48541, when and where the refreshed local transformation plans will be published; and what steps his Department will take to monitor how effectively those plans support the delivery of mental health services to children and young people.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51327","51327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626630","2016-11-03","Department of Health","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent steps his Department has taken to ensure patients attend (a) GP and (b) acute services appointments.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51300","51300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626631","2016-11-04","Department of Health","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people are on NHS waiting lists for cornea transplants.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51341","51341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626632","2016-11-04","Department of Health","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people are on NHS waiting lists for lung transplants.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51338","51338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626633","2016-11-04","Department of Health","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people are on NHS waiting lists for pancreas transplants.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51339","51339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626634","2016-11-04","Department of Health","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people are on NHS waiting lists for small bowel transplants.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51340","51340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626635","2016-11-04","Department of Health","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people are on NHS waiting lists for tissue transplants.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51342","51342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626636","2016-11-03","Department of Health","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness and suitability of psychological interventions offered as autism treatments.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51349","51349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626637","2016-11-04","Department of Health","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 27 June 2014 to Question 40281, on what date he expects NICE to publish the results of the consultation on the guidance on the use of nivolumab for the treatment of lung cancer.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51363","51363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626638","2016-11-04","Department of Health","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much of the funds allocated in the 2015 Budget to child and adolescent mental health services has been spent in Warrington.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51503","51503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626639","2016-11-03","Department of Health","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the correction of 1 November 2016 to the Answer of 26 October 2016 to Question 49779, for what reasons the High Weald Lewes Havens Clinical Commissioning Group did not immediately instruct Copeforma to cease using Docklands Medical Services Limited as a subcontractor when it identified that the Care Quality Commission registration in question related to Docklands Medical Services (London) rather than Docklands Medical Services Ltd; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51445","51445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626640","2016-11-03","Department of Health","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will initiate an investigation under section 48 of the Health and Social Care Act 2008 into the provision of Patient Transport Services in East Surrey and Sussex.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51420","51420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626641","2016-11-03","Department of Health","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many applications to join the National Dental Performers List there were in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51421","51421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626642","2016-11-04","Department of Health","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, who was consulted during the development of NHS sustainability and transformation plans for (a) Haringey, (b) Enfield, (c) Barnet, (d) Camden, (e) Islington and (f) Hackney.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51494","51494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626643","2016-11-04","Department of Health","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans his Department has to publish the draft sustainability and transformation plans for (a) Haringey, (b) Enfield, (c) Barnet, (d) Camden, (e) Islington and (f) Hackney.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51495","51495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626644","2016-11-03","Department of Health","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the correction of 1 November 2016 to the Answer of 26 October 2016 to Question 49779, what the terms of reference were of the NHS England investigation into the provision of patient transport services during July, August and September 2016; by what date he asked for that investigation to be completed; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51446","51446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626645","2016-11-03","Department of Health","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of applications to join the National Dental Performers List were determined within (a) one, (b) two, (c) three and (d) four or more months in the last three years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51422","51422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626646","2016-11-04","Department of Health","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of the financial situation of NHS trusts in England; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51505","51505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626647","2016-11-03","Department of Health","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the correction of 1 November 2016 to the Answer of 26 October 2016 to Question 49779, on what date the High Weald Lewes Haven Clinical Commissioning Group contacted Copeforma asking them to confirm the relevant Care Quality Commission registration status and on what date Copeforma responded; what the content of Copeforma's response to that request was; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51447","51447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626648","2016-11-03","Department of Health","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make it his policy to review the private contracting of patient transport services; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51381","51381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626649","2016-11-03","Department of Health","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to reduce atrial fibrillation related strokes.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51379","51379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626650","2016-11-03","Department of Health","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average time taken is for issuing HC2 forms to asylum seekers; and how many such forms are currently awaiting processing.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51406","51406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626651","2016-11-04","Department of Health","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 1 November 2016 to Question 50285, in relation to which diseases and other long-term conditions his Department has made an assessment of the future cost of treatment to NHS services.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51407","51407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626652","2016-11-03","Department of Health","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the effectiveness of Capita plc in managing the process of applications to the National Dental Performers List.","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51400","51400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626653","2016-11-03","Department of Health","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many strokes relating to prior atrial fibrillation occurred in (a) 2005, (b) 2010 and (c) 2015; and what forecast his Department has made of the number of such strokes in 2020.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51380","51380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626654","2016-11-03","Department of Health","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 1 November 2016 to Question 50156, if he will write to the High Weald Havens Clinical Commissioning Group to ask them to inform him of the value of invoices they have received from each trust which has incurred private ambulance costs arising from performance problems with Patient Transport Services provided by Coperforma and arms length driver operatives; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51429","51429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626655","2016-11-03","Department of Health","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people are undergoing cancer treatment in (a) Barts Health NHS and (b) each hospital trust in London.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51409","51409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626656","2016-11-03","Department of Health","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many appointments for a first cancer referral were cancelled in the Barts Health NHS Trust in (a) the last six months and (b) 2013 to 2015.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51410","51410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626657","2016-11-03","Department of Health","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average waiting times are for a cancer referral in (a) Barts Health NHS Trust, (b) each hospital trust in London and (c) each hospital trust in England.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51411","51411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626658","2016-11-03","Department of Health","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 1 November 2016 to Question 50284, of which diseases and other long-term conditions he has made long-term assessments of future prevalence in the population of the UK; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51408","51408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626659","2016-11-04","Department of Health","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Mental Health Five Year Forward View Dashboard, when he plans to publish data relating to the indicator on individual placement and support (IPS) reach and number of people getting access to IPS.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51430","51430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626660","2016-11-04","Department of Health","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Mental Health Five Year Forward View Dashboard, when he plans to publish data relating to the indicator on outcome measures for integrated IAPT services.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51431","51431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626661","2016-11-04","Department of Health","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Mental Health Five Year Forward View Dashboard, when he plans to publish data relating to the indicator on net movement of people off benefits or into employment from IAPT.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51432","51432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626662","2016-11-04","Department of Health","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Mental Health Five Year Forward View Dashboard, when he plans to publish data relating to the indicator on average waiting time measure for children and young people's mental health.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51433","51433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626663","2016-11-04","Department of Health","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Mental Health Five Year Forward View Dashboard, when his Department plans to publish data relating to the indicator on IPS Programme spend.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51522","51522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626664","2016-11-04","Home Office","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will release all Cabinet papers relating to events at Orgreave in 1984.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51523","51523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626665","2016-11-04","Home Office","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to her Answer of 31 October 2016, Official Report, columns 645-6, when the operational order of the day will be released.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51440","51440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626666","2016-11-03","Home Office","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to monitor and improve the performance of UK Visas and Immigration's implementation of decisions made by the First Tier Tribunal (Immigration and Asylum).","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51383","51383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626667","2016-11-03","Cabinet Office","2016-11-01","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the (a) total cost and (b) cost in each principal category of expenditure was of the police and crime commissioner elections in 2016; and in which months of 2016 costs for each of the principal items were incurred.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51402","51402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626669","2016-11-03","Cabinet Office","2016-11-01","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many fraud offences involving online shopping have been recorded by each UK law enforcement agency in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51403","51403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626670","2016-11-03","Home Office","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average police helicopter response times have been for each police force in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51404","51404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626671","2016-11-04","Home Office","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when her Department was first notified by the Independent Inquiry into Child Sexual Abuse that an allegation of sexual assault had been made against Ben Emmerson QC.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51399","51399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626672","2016-11-03","Home Office","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what immigration status children transferred to the UK under section 67 of the Immigration Act 2016 will be given on arrival in the UK.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51377","51377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626673","2016-11-03","Home Office","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether children arriving in the UK under section 67 of the Immigration Act 2016 will be referred to the Refugee Council's Children's Panel Advice Service.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51378","51378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626674","2016-11-04","Home Office","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent progress she has made in implementing the recommendations of the Bradley Report on liaison and diversion of people with mental vulnerability in the criminal justice system.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51510","51510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626675","2016-11-04","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 11 October 2016 to Question 46111, if she will say where on the gov.uk website there are details of the number of people convicted for offences under section 127 of the Communications Act 2003 in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51520","51520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626676","2016-11-03","Home Office","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many asylum seekers were granted permission to work in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51465","51465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626677","2016-11-03","Home Office","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what value of criminal assets has been recovered from overseas confiscation orders in each of the last seven years.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51371","51371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626678","2016-11-03","Home Office","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many police officers were dismissed under The (a) Police (Conduct) Regulations 2012, (b) Police (Performance) Regulations 2012 and (c) the Police (Attendance Management) Regulations in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for James Berry","James Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51370","51370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626679","2016-11-04","Home Office","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what representations she has received on extending the proposed limit for initial bail periods contained in the Policing and Crime Bill; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51344","51344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626680","2016-11-03","Department for International Development","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what account her Department's Strategic Vision on Women and Girls takes of the mortality rate among women of a reproductive age in Sub Saharan Africa from AIDs.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51480","51480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626681","2016-11-03","Department for International Development","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what account her Department's Youth Strategy takes of the mortality rate among adolescents and young people of AIDs.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51479","51479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626682","2016-11-03","Department for International Development","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will conduct a review of her Department's HIV and AIDS programmes to ensure her Department is meeting its international commitments to ending AIDS, as a public health threat by 2030.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51482","51482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626683","2016-11-03","Department for International Development","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will undertake a stocktake review of her Department's bilateral HIV programmes to assess gaps and shortcomings of her Department's response compared to its international commitments.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51481","51481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626684","2016-11-03","Department for International Development","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of monitoring restrictions on access of goods and people into and out of (a) Gaza and (b) the West Bank for the (i) economic and social development of those territories and (ii) successful future coexistence between Israelis and Palestinians.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51477","51477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626685","2016-11-03","Department for International Development","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, on what principles her Department invests in HIV/AIDS programmes.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51412","51412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626686","2016-11-03","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when she plans to start the national roll-out of pre-recorded cross-examination for young vulnerable witnesses following the pilot of section 28 of the Youth and Criminal Evidence Act 1999.","Biography information for Mrs Pauline Latham","Pauline Latham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51414","51414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626687","2016-11-03","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 19 October 2016 to Question 48793, whether her Department requires foreign jurisdictions to meet human rights standards set out in the European Convention on Human Rights before considering the provision of prison and security-related services to them.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51415","51415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626688","2016-11-08","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when she plans to ratify the Istanbul Convention.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51526","51526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626689","2016-11-03","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if she will make it her policy to create a central database of lasting powers of attorney.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51355","51355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626690","2016-11-03","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if she will report on the progress of the prison reform programme.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51357","51357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626691","2016-11-03","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment her Department has made of the causes of the increase in the number of women recalled to prison from licence since December 2014.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51467","51467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626692","2016-11-03","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what discussions she has had with leaders of the Crown Dependencies on publicly accessible central registers of beneficial ownership.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51448","51448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626693","2016-11-04","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps she is taking to support the police and prison services in informing and reassuring the public in a timely manner during escape incidents.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51368","51368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626694","2016-11-03","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the Answer of 13 February 2014 to Question 184186, how many (a) active and (b) inactive registered intermediaries there were in each year since 2013.","Biography information for Ann Coffey","Ann Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51352","51352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626695","2016-11-03","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the Answer of 13 February 2014 to Question 184190, how many sexual offences were prosecuted which involved a person aged under 18 years old where that person was (a) matched and (b) unmatched with a registered intermediary since 2013.","Biography information for Ann Coffey","Ann Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51351","51351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626696","2016-11-03","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the Answer of 13 February 2014 to Question 184189, how many (a) matched and (b) unmatched registered intermediaries there were for each age group of vulnerable witnesses in each year since 2013.","Biography information for Ann Coffey","Ann Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51350","51350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626697","2016-11-03","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what improvements have been made to overall conditions at HMP Pentonville since July 2015; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51348","51348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626698","2016-11-04","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the Answers of 26 February 2014 to Questions 184188 and 184187, how many requests were made for each age group of vulnerable witnesses for registered intermediaries by (a) the police, (b) the Crown Prosecution Service, (c) courts, (d) solicitors and (e) other groups in each year since 2013.","Biography information for Ann Coffey","Ann Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51360","51360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626699","2016-11-03","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what her policy is on remaining a (a) signatory to the European Court of Human Rights and (b) fully participant in the court structure of that Convention.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51299","51299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626700","2016-11-04","Northern Ireland Office","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, with reference to his Department's press release of 20 October 2016, entitled Appointment of new members to Equality Commission, what steps he is taking to ensure that the makeup of that Commission is representative of the communities it serves.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51484","51484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626701","2016-11-04","Prime Minister","2016-11-01","To ask the Prime Minister, when she has met leaders of the Overseas Territories.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51497","51497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626702","2016-11-04","Scotland Office","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what progress has been made on the development of a long-term decommissioning strategy for the North Sea oil and gas industry to (a) ensure the development of that industry and (b) maintain the role of that industry in the Scottish economy.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51369","51369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626703","2016-11-03","Department for Transport","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 26 October 2016 to Question 49208, for what reasons statistics on supported bus service mileage by local authorities are not available for periods earlier than 2013-14.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51333","51333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626704","2016-11-04","Department for Transport","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the proportion of potential capacity at Heathrow Airport which will be unfilled when a new third runway is operational.","Biography information for Dr Tania Mathias","Dr Tania Mathias","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51359","51359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626705","2016-11-04","Department for Transport","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 6 September 2016 to Question 45235, what progress his Department has made on reviewing compensation options for Southern Rail passengers following the recent disruption to the regular timetable.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51329","51329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626706","2016-11-04","Department for Transport","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what progress his Department has made on introducing (a) flexible ticketing and (b) rail season tickets tailored towards part-time workers on the Govia Thameslink Railway franchise.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51330","51330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626707","2016-11-04","Department for Transport","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the runway capacity was for each UK airport in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51322","51322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626709","2016-11-04","Department for Transport","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 31 October 2016 to Question 49985, how many passengers travelled by (a) road and (b) train to (i) Manchester and (ii) Liverpool Airport in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51316","51316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626710","2016-11-04","Department for Transport","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the PwC report prepared for the Airports Commission entitled 2. Economy: Wider impact assessment, published in November 2014, whether he has had discussions with PwC on the modelling methodology used in that report.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51441","51441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626711","2016-11-03","Department for Transport","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps the Government is taking to encourage the take-up of electric and low emission vehicles by airport staff on airport-owned land.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51466","51466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626712","2016-11-03","Department for Transport","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what (a) Highways Agency and (b) Highways England funding has been allocated to the Driver Education Budget in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51428","51428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626713","2016-11-03","Department for Transport","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he has the power to enforce landing slot requirements at Heathrow Airport to ensure (a) access for domestic flights and (b) the use of cleaner aircraft by airlines in the event of a third runway being built at that airport.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51427","51427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626714","2016-11-04","Department for Transport","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with the Civil Aviation Authority on working together with owners and managers at Heathrow Airport to develop a plan for landing slots until 2030.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51443","51443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626715","2016-11-03","Women and Equalities","2016-11-01","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what proportion of women are employed by the Government Equalities Office on an inner London pay structure in the following pay grades (a) Administrative Assistant, (b) Administrative Office, (c) Executive Office, (d) Higher Executive Office, (e) Fast Streamer, (f) Senior Executive Officer, (g) Grade Seven, (h) Grade Six, (i) Senior Civil Service Band 1, (j) Senior Civil Service Band 1A, (k) Senior Civil Service Band 2 and (l) Senior Civil Service Band 3.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51373","51373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626716","2016-11-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department has taken to make sure that British Sign Language users are made aware that the two-ticks scheme is being transferred to Disability Confident.","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51335","51335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626717","2016-11-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department has taken to ensure that employers based within the construction industry are engaged with the Disability Confident scheme.","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51336","51336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626718","2016-11-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the total monthly receipts to the public purse were from (a) the fee charged for applications to the Child Maintenance Service (CMS), (b) the collection fee for paying parents using the CMS collect and pay service, (c) the collection fee for receiving payments using the CMS collect and pay service and (d) enforcement fees levied on paying parents in each month since June 2014.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51323","51323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626719","2016-11-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the projected monthly income is from charges in the Child Maintenance Service (CMS) once all cases have transferred from the legacy schemes to the CMS.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51324","51324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626720","2016-11-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much the Government has received in total to date in charges from the Child Maintenance Service since charging was introduced in June 2014.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51325","51325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626721","2016-11-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether it remains Government policy to continue the triple-lock guarantee on the basic state pension throughout the lifetime of the current Parliament.","Biography information for Natalie McGarry","Natalie McGarry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51328","51328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626722","2016-11-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many families in Peterborough constituency are subject to the most recent changes in the welfare benefit cap; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stewart Jackson","Mr Stewart Jackson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51312","51312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626723","2016-11-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the cost of a real terms increase of (a) 1.5 and (b) 2.5 per cent in the basic state pension in each year to 2025.","Biography information for Dr Andrew Murrison","Dr Andrew Murrison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51307","51307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626724","2016-11-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the estimated projected cost is of (a) the basic state pension and (b) additional pensioner benefits by benefit for (i) the lifetime of the current Parliament and (ii) 2020 to 2025.","Biography information for Dr Andrew Murrison","Dr Andrew Murrison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51308","51308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626725","2016-11-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department has taken to ensure that employers who engage with the Disability Confident scheme are provided with the information they need to be able to employ people with hearing loss.","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51382","51382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626726","2016-11-04","HM Treasury","2016-11-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions his Department has had with the (a) Wales Office and (b) Welsh Government on the devolution of income tax powers and the effect of such devolution on people receiving overseas civil service pensions who are currently exempt from double taxation.","Biography information for Simon Hart","Simon Hart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51395","51395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626727","2016-11-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many households in (a) Tottenham constituency and (b) the London Borough of Harringey will be affected by the extension of the benefit cap to 23,000; and what the average cut in benefits will be.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51452","51452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626728","2016-11-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many disability employment advisers were employed in his Department in each year since 2009.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51513","51513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626729","2016-11-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many non-payroll staff are employed in his Department; and what estimate he has made of the cost of such staff in the financial year to date.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51514","51514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626730","2016-11-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he expects that the goal of halving the disability employment gap will be achieved.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51516","51516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626731","2016-11-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what change in the disability employment gap he expects between 2015 and 2020.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51517","51517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626732","2016-11-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many of his Department's digital and IT projects are (a) under review and (b) at risk of cancellation.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51424","51424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626733","2016-11-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in Tottenham constituency (a) are entitled to claim child benefit and (b) have experienced payment arrears due to non-resident parents not paying full or any child maintenance within the last 12 months; and what the total value of these unpaid arrears is.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51451","51451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626734","2016-11-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he plans to publish his Department's response to the British Steel Pension Scheme Consultation.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51468","51468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626735","2016-11-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 19 October 2016 to Question 47959, whether his Department plans to regulate the way public money is spent by private companies who are contracted by the Government with respect to members of staff being paid financial bonuses in addition to a salary.","Biography information for Philip Boswell","Phil Boswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51419","51419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626736","2016-11-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to ensure that all claimants suffering from any progressive and incurable condition will be exempt from employment and support allowance medical re-assessment.","Biography information for Tommy Sheppard","Tommy Sheppard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51496","51496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626737","2016-11-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many contractors employed by his Department to work on DWP Digital projects have left the employment of his Department in the 2016-17 financial year to date.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51525","51525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626738","2016-11-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much his Department has spent on DWP Digital for each target set in the 2016-17 financial year to date.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51524","51524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626740","2016-11-03","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department has taken to develop a long-term strategy for business growth after the UK's decision to leave the EU.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51469","51469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626741","2016-11-03","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what plans he has to implement the recommendations of the Independent Review of Consumer Protection Measures concerning online secondary ticketing facilities.","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51464","51464"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626742","2016-11-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether he has met (a) Sir Philip Green or (b) any employees of British Home Stores about that company's move into administration.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51499","51499"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626743","2016-11-03","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what proportion of women are employed by his Department on an inner London pay structure in the following pay grades (a) Administrative Assistant, (b) Administrative Officer, (c) Executive Officer, (d) Higher Executive Officer, (e) Fast Streamer, (f) Senior Executive Officer, (g) Grade Seven, (h) Grade Six, (i) Senior Civil Service Band 1, (j) Senior Civil Service Band 1A, (k) Senior Civil Service Band 2 and (l) Senior Civil Service Band 3.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51384","51384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626744","2016-11-03","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to encourage businesses to offer flexible working conditions to (a) improve productivity and (b) reduce transport congestion.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51401","51401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626745","2016-11-04","HM Treasury","2016-11-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of fraudulent self-employment on the UK economy.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51398","51398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626746","2016-11-03","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the effect of the UK's decision to leave the EU on the UK manufacturing sector.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51474","51474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626747","2016-11-03","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what discussions he has had with the Chancellor of the Exchequer on support for the North Sea oil and gas sector.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51475","51475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626748","2016-11-03","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how (a) Midlands devolution and (b) the West Midlands growth engine plan will apply to Redditch constituency.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51303","51303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626749","2016-11-03","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how his Department plans to ensure that the interests of manufacturers are enhanced by the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51301","51301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626751","2016-11-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent assessment he has made of future funding requirements for the Post Office.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51358","51358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626752","2016-11-04","Department for International Trade","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether the Government plans to provide a mechanism for (a) British citizens, (b) the voluntary sector and non-governmental organisations, (c) local authorities, (d) the devolved administrations and (e) Parliament to have an input on the terms and priorities of the bilateral trade deals the UK will negotiate when it leaves the EU.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51485","51485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626753","2016-11-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what his Department's policy is on using the flexibility provided by the Trade Related Aspects of Intellectual Property Rights under World Trade Organisation rules for compulsory license for the Kadcyla form of trastuzumab emtansine for UK patients.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51439","51439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626754","2016-11-03","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what proportion of women are employed by his Department on an inner London pay structure in the following pay grades (a) Administrative Assistant, (b) Administrative Officer, (c) Executive Officer, (d) Higher Executive Officer, (e) Fast Streamer, (f) Senior Executive Officer, (g) Grade Seven, (h) Grade Six, (i) Senior Civil Service Band 1, (j) Senior Civil Service Band 2, (k) Senior Civil Service Band 1A, (l) Senior Civil Service Band 2 and (m) Senior Civil Service Band 3.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51392","51392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626755","2016-11-03","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether he plans to give domestic effect to Postal Workers Directive 96/71/EC through the forthcoming Repeal Bill.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51298","51298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626756","2016-11-03","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether he plans to give domestic effect to the Pregnant Workers Directive 92/85/EEC through the forthcoming Repeal Bill.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51297","51297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626757","2016-11-04","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many staff are employed in his Department's Communications Directorate.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51326","51326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627287","2016-11-07","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he plans for construction of the Type 26 frigates to begin.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 907106","907106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627288","2016-11-07","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the potential implications of Russia's military manoeuvres in Eastern Europe and through the English Channel for (a) UK and (b) NATO security policy.","Biography information for Craig Tracey","Craig Tracey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 907094","907094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/630907","2016-11-07","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what progress the Government has made on protecting the armed forces from persistent legal claims.","Biography information for Stuart Andrew","Stuart Andrew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 907110","907110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/630908","2016-11-07","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the Government plans to maintain its NATO commitment to spend 2 per cent of GDP on defence.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 907099","907099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/630909","2016-11-07","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent progress has been made on the order for Type 26 frigates.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 907105","907105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625855","2016-11-02","Attorney General","2016-10-31","To ask the Attorney General, how many people have been convicted of tampering with electric or gas meters in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51073","51073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625856","2016-11-02","Cabinet Office","2016-10-31","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what progress he has made in reducing the cost of stationery across all government departments; and if he will take steps to promote the use of the same paper from the same supplier to reduce those costs.","Biography information for Mike Freer","Mike Freer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51032","51032"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625857","2016-11-02","Cabinet Office","2016-10-31","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many citizens of non-UK EU countries work in his Department, its agencies and non-departmental public bodies.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51002","51002"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625858","2016-11-02","HM Treasury","2016-10-31","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many citizens of non-UK EU countries work in his Department, its agencies and non-departmental public bodies.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51004","51004"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625859","2016-11-02","HM Treasury","2016-10-31","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether his Department plans to make additional funding available to HM Revenue and Customs to resolve tax credit claims.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51035","51035"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625860","2016-11-02","HM Treasury","2016-10-31","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what arrangements his Department has put in place to ensure that financial recompense and support is provided for tax credit claimants erroneously investigated by Concentrix.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51051","51051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625861","2016-11-02","HM Treasury","2016-10-31","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what information his Department holds on what proportion of tax credit claimants erroneously investigated by Concentrix were women.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51052","51052"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625862","2016-11-02","HM Treasury","2016-10-31","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the evidential basis is for HM Revenue and Customs communications to Concentrix that another adult may be living at the house of a tax claimant; and in what form such information is being conveyed to Concentrix.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51053","51053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625863","2016-11-02","HM Treasury","2016-10-31","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if (a) his Department, (b) HM Revenue and Customs and (c) Concentrix will issue a formal apology for each erroneous accusation made by Concentrix against legitimate tax credit recipients; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51089","51089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625864","2016-11-02","HM Treasury","2016-10-31","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many officials of his Department have opted out of the EU Working Time Directive.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51138","51138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625865","2016-11-03","HM Treasury","2016-10-31","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what information his Department holds on the number of financial services firms registered with the Financial Conduct Authority which have been identified by the US Department of Homeland Security as being elements of transnational criminal organisations.","Biography information for Roger Mullin","Roger Mullin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51159","51159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625866","2016-11-03","HM Treasury","2016-10-31","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what measures (a) the Government, (b) law enforcement agencies and (c) financial regulators have put in place to ensure that unregulated payments are not being used for money laundering.","Biography information for Roger Mullin","Roger Mullin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51160","51160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625867","2016-11-03","HM Treasury","2016-10-31","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the Government's policy is on oversight of globally operating electronic payment systems using virtual UK places of business.","Biography information for Roger Mullin","Roger Mullin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51161","51161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625868","2016-11-03","HM Treasury","2016-10-31","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how (a) the Government, (b) law enforcement agencies and (c) financial regulators prevent the use of unregulated payments systems for the purpose of UK tax evasion.","Biography information for Roger Mullin","Roger Mullin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51162","51162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625869","2016-11-03","HM Treasury","2016-10-31","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if his Department will make an assessment of the potential effect on the economy of reductions in the rate of VAT.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51163","51163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625870","2016-11-03","HM Treasury","2016-10-31","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if his Department will make an assessment of the effect on the economy of potential reductions in the rate of corporation tax.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51164","51164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625871","2016-11-02","HM Treasury","2016-10-31","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the contracts relating to the provision of (a) Trident and (b) Hinkley Point are denominated in pounds, euros or dollars.","Biography information for Patricia Gibson","Patricia Gibson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51152","51152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625872","2016-11-02","HM Treasury","2016-10-31","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the effect on the cost to the public purse of the (a) Trident renewal programme and (b) Hinkley Point contracts of the change in the value of the pound since the EU referendum.","Biography information for Patricia Gibson","Patricia Gibson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51153","51153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625873","2016-11-02","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what estimate his Department has made of the potential effect of the UK leaving the EU on (a) the number of EU and EEA nationals working in the UK and (b) the level of national insurance contribution receipts; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Rupa Huq","Dr Rupa Huq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51194","51194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625874","2016-11-02","HM Treasury","2016-10-31","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether his Department has made an assessment of the effect of the UK leaving the EU on UK food prices.","Biography information for Nick Smith","Nick Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51268","51268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625875","2016-11-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to ensure the adequate provision of housing for older people across all housing types and tenures.","Biography information for David Mackintosh","David Mackintosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51240","51240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625876","2016-11-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 13 October 2016 to Question 46626, on home ownership incentive schemes, what the value was of the equity loans included in the 4,090,595,000 figure given in that Answer.","Biography information for James Cartlidge","James Cartlidge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51234","51234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625877","2016-11-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 13 October 2016 to Question 46626, on home ownership incentive schemes, if he will estimate the amount of accumulated interest and other costs due to the Government included within the 4,090,595,000 figure given in that Answer.","Biography information for James Cartlidge","James Cartlidge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51235","51235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625878","2016-11-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many officials of his Department have opted out of the EU Working Time Directive.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51126","51126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625879","2016-11-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what plans the Government has to replace EU funding currently received by local authorities when the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51098","51098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625880","2016-11-03","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps her Department is taking to increase participation in sport among school-aged children.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51059","51059"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625881","2016-11-03","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent steps her Department has taken to improve diversity in employment in the creative industries.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51060","51060"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625882","2016-11-03","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps her Department is taking to improve sports provision in local communities for disabled children.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51061","51061"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625883","2016-11-02","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many citizens of non-UK EU countries work in her Department, its agencies and non-departmental public bodies.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51008","51008"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625884","2016-11-02","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many officials of her Department have opted out of the EU Working Time Directive.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51127","51127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625885","2016-11-03","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 28 October 2016 to Question 50181, what the cost, inclusive of operating costs of the National Citizen Service Trust and payments to delivery organisations, has been to the public purse of each young person undertaking the National Citizen Service programme in each financial year since that programme's inception.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51166","51166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625886","2016-11-02","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 17 October 2016 to Question 47357, what proportion of households in Fermanagh and South Tyrone constituency have access to superfast broadband.","Biography information for Tom Elliott","Tom Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51200","51200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625887","2016-11-02","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to prevent cases of mental ill-health among combat veterans.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51211","51211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625888","2016-11-02","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many officials of his Department have opted out of the EU Working Time Directive.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51128","51128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625889","2016-11-03","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 27 October 2016 to Question 50014, if he will make an assessment of the effect on householders of his Department's policy not to allow residents to have water meters installed so that those residents are charged only for the water consumed.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51119","51119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625890","2016-11-02","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many ex-servicemen and women are currently participating in the Veterans and Reserves Mental Health programme in Worcestershire.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51193","51193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625891","2016-11-02","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much funding has been allocated to the East Europe and Central Asia Conflict, Stability and Security Fund budget-funded teams delivering training to build the capability and resilience of the Ukrainian armed forces since the launch of that fund.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51144","51144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625892","2016-11-02","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many citizens of non-UK EU countries work in his Department, its agencies and non-departmental public bodies.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51006","51006"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625893","2016-11-03","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the precautionary safety notice concerning use of the high-explosive L31 artillery round currently in use with the L118 light gun has been lifted.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51010","51010"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625894","2016-11-03","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many times his Department has had to suspend the use of the high-explosive L31 artillery round in use with the L118 light gun since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51012","51012"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625895","2016-11-03","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much funding his Department has allocated for Defence Internal Audit in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51016","51016"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625896","2016-11-02","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much of the Cyber Security Operations Centre budget his Department plans to spend in Scotland.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51025","51025"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625897","2016-11-02","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much of the Maritime Mine Counter Measures programme budget his Department plans to spend in Scotland.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51026","51026"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625898","2016-11-02","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many people are directly employed by his Department in the Emerging Technology and Innovation Analysis Cell.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50973","50973"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625899","2016-11-02","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans he has to improve the (a) quality and (b) affordability of accommodation for service personnel based at Leuchars.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50982","50982"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625900","2016-11-02","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans he has to invest in family accommodation for service personnel at (a) Leuchars and (b) elsewhere in North East Fife.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50983","50983"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625901","2016-11-02","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, to which budget the revenue received from civil aviation visits to Leuchars in 2016-17 has been allocated.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50984","50984"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625902","2016-11-02","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many pupils attended service children's education schools in Cyprus in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50992","50992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625903","2016-11-02","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many pupils attended service children's education schools in Germany in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50993","50993"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625904","2016-11-02","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many trained regular Commonwealth nations armed forces personnel joined the (a) Army, (b) Royal Air Force and (c) Royal Navy in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50994","50994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625905","2016-11-02","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the estimated annual budget is of his Department's Emerging Technology and Innovation Analysis Cell.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50995","50995"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625906","2016-11-02","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many trained regular armed forces personnel were based in Germany in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50990","50990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625907","2016-11-02","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many trained regular armed forces personnel were based in Cyprus in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50991","50991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625908","2016-11-02","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many civilian staff within Defence Intelligence are (a) men, (b) women and (c) from black and minority ethnic groups.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50996","50996"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625909","2016-11-02","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department plans to implement the Future Accommodation Model at Leuchars.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50997","50997"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625910","2016-11-02","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to help veterans into employment.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51042","51042"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625911","2016-11-02","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many UK Regular Officers completing the Commissioning Course at the Royal Military Academy, Sandhurst had previously served as regular soldiers in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51047","51047"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625912","2016-11-02","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to help ensure families maintain networks of support when other family members are away on active service.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51048","51048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625913","2016-11-02","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many entrants completed the Late Entry Officers Course at the Royal Military Academy, Sandhurst in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51045","51045"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625914","2016-11-02","Department for Education","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many unaccompanied asylum-seeking children were being looked after under a (a) section 20 voluntary accommodation arrangement and (b) care order (interim or final) on 31 March 2016.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51114","51114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625915","2016-11-02","Department for Education","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many foster-for-adoption placements occurred from (a) 25 July 2014 to 31 March 2015, (b) 1 April 2015 to 31 March 2016 and (c) 1 April 2016 to 31 August 2016; and how many of those cases involved placement of more than one child.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51115","51115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625916","2016-11-02","Department for Education","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children on special guardianship orders as of 31 March 2016 were looked after immediately prior to the special guardianship order.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51041","51041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625917","2016-11-02","Department for Education","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many care leavers in England as of 31 March 2016 were (a) mothers and (b) fathers; how many such care leavers were aged (i) 17, (ii) 18, (iii) 19, (iv) 20 and (v) 21; and how many such care leavers (A) had more than one child and (B) have at least one child who is or has been subject to (1) a child protection inquiry, (2) a child protection plan and (3) an interim or final care order or is voluntary accommodated.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51116","51116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625918","2016-11-02","Department for Education","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of children obtained five or more GCSEs including mathematics and English at Grade A* to C at (a) non-selective schools in selective areas and (b) comprehensive schools in the latest year for which data is available.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51100","51100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625919","2016-11-02","Department for Education","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of pupils at grammar schools obtained five or more GCSEs including mathematics and English at Grade A* to C at in the latest year for which data is available.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51101","51101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625920","2016-11-03","Department for Education","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 24 October 2016 to Question 48981, what the staff numbers for the Institute for Apprenticeships will be in (a) 2017-18, (b) 2018-19 and (c) 2019-20.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51066","51066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625921","2016-11-02","Department for Education","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, of those children who were subject of a special guardianship order as at 31 March 2016 but were not looked after immediately prior to the special guardianship order being made, how many (a) have been on a child protection plan and (b) were looked after at some point in their childhood.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51030","51030"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625922","2016-11-02","Department for Education","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many care leavers in England on 31 March 2016 were (a) mothers and (b) fathers.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51021","51021"
