"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453046","2016-02-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 11 February 2016 to Question 25611, on employment: telephone services, if he will commission an assessment of the outcome for workers of the transfer of the functions of the Pay and Work Rights Helpline to Acas from 1 April 2015.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27210","27210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453047","2016-02-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the number of apprentices at each of the apprenticeship educational levels 2 to 6 whom the Government plans to be part of its target of three million apprentices by 2020.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27238","27238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453048","2016-02-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the security of supply of (a) the rare earths neodymium and dysprosium and (b) tellurium.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27339","27339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453049","2016-02-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change on the effect of the Government's policy on biomass on the availability of UK-produced wood supplies to UK industries.","Biography information for Susan Elan Jones","Susan Elan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27352","27352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453050","2016-02-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what discussions he has had with local enterprise partnerships on supporting social enterprises.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27378","27378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453051","2016-02-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to improve access to parental leave for self-employed people.","Biography information for Susan Elan Jones","Susan Elan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27413","27413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453052","2016-02-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, for what reasons the process for including Citizens Advice as the statutory consumer watchdog differs for changes to Crown post offices outside compared with those within the Crown Transformation Programme.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27410","27410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453053","2016-02-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what discussions he (a) has had and (b) plans to have with Rio Tinto on that company's strategic review of its smelter operations in Lochaber.","Biography information for Ian Blackford","Ian Blackford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27411","27411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453054","2016-02-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what discussions he has had with social enterprises and other small and medium-sized enterprises about the potential effect of the closure of the Growth Accelerator Programme.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27418","27418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453055","2016-02-24","Cabinet Office","2016-02-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when the Government plans to respond to the Law Commission's recommendations for change to UK electoral law published on 4 February 2016.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27583","27583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453056","2016-02-23","Cabinet Office","2016-02-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the rate of pay is for cleaners in his Department.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27550","27550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453057","2016-02-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether she has made an assessment of the potential effect on UK GDP of the National Grid issuing Notification of Inadequate System Margin notices; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27566","27566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453058","2016-02-23","HM Treasury","2016-02-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will place in the library a copy of the impact assessment of the carbon price floor mechanism.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27559","27559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453059","2016-02-24","HM Treasury","2016-02-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 10 February 2016 to Question 26025, for what reason Thea Rogers' salary increased from £69,250 in 2014 to £98,000 in 2015.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27582","27582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453060","2016-02-23","HM Treasury","2016-02-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many migrants residing in the UK claim benefits on behalf of children living abroad; and what the value is of such claims by country of residence of the child.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27574","27574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453061","2016-02-24","HM Treasury","2016-02-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to ensure that there is full market participation in real-time data-sharing in the short-term credit market.","Biography information for Meg Hillier","Meg Hillier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27579","27579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453062","2016-02-23","HM Treasury","2016-02-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he plans to take to ensure that all UK-registered companies are subject to the same tax provisions as their UK competitors providing the same services to the same customer base regardless of the official locations of the European subsidiaries of such companies.","Biography information for Tom Elliott","Tom Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27529","27529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453063","2016-02-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether she has made an assessment of the potential effect on UK GDP of the National Grid using its demand side balancing reserve powers; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27564","27564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453064","2016-02-23","HM Treasury","2016-02-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the implications for the effectiveness of the ring-fence between retail and investment banking of the Prudential Regulation Authority's proposal to allow ring-fenced bodies to pay dividends to other entities in the parent group.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27453","27453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453065","2016-02-23","HM Treasury","2016-02-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what meetings (a) Ministers and (b) officials of his Department have had on the implementation of the ring-fence between retail and investment banking since May 2015.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27454","27454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453066","2016-02-23","HM Treasury","2016-02-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the implications for financial system resilience of the Prudential Regulation Authority's proposed rules on ringfencing; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27449","27449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453067","2016-02-23","HM Treasury","2016-02-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment he has made of the likely effectiveness of the ring-fence between retail and investment banking in reducing the interconnectedness of the UK financial system; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27450","27450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453068","2016-02-23","HM Treasury","2016-02-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment he has made of the potential effectiveness of the ring-fence between retail and investment banking in reducing funding risk in the UK financial system; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27451","27451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453069","2016-02-23","HM Treasury","2016-02-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the implications for the effectiveness of the ring-fence between retail and investment banking of the Prudential Regulation Authority's proposal to allow cross-selling and cross-lending between ring-fenced bodies and other entities in the parent group in some circumstances.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27452","27452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453070","2016-02-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how he plans to respond to the recent request from the Leader of Redcar and Cleveland Council for a transitional sum of £1 million in lieu of raising the adult social care precept.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27478","27478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453071","2016-02-24","HM Treasury","2016-02-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether his Department plans to renegotiate tax treaties with developing countries.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27248","27248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453072","2016-02-23","HM Treasury","2016-02-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 15 February 2016 to Question 26319 on the national minimum wage, what assessment he has made of the reasons for the increase in the arrears identified between April 2015 and November 2015; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27319","27319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453073","2016-02-23","HM Treasury","2016-02-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, for how long HM Revenue and Customs is required to keep records on individual tax credit cases.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27416","27416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453074","2016-02-26","HM Treasury","2016-02-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps the Government is taking to support self-employed people who want to buy their own home.","Biography information for Susan Elan Jones","Susan Elan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27414","27414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453075","2016-02-26","HM Treasury","2016-02-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps the Government is taking to improve access to mortgages for self-employed people.","Biography information for Susan Elan Jones","Susan Elan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27415","27415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453076","2016-02-23","HM Treasury","2016-02-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the Oral Contribution of the Economic Secretary to the Treasury of 1 February 2016, Official Report, column 748, what further progress has been made on investigations into the Connaught Income Fund, series 1.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27426","27426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453077","2016-02-24","HM Treasury","2016-02-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 12 February 2016 to Question 26203, if he will provide the number of publicly-funded jobs related directly to the Northern Powerhouse located in (a) Cumbria, (b) Northern England, (c) London and (d) other parts of England.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27475","27475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453078","2016-02-23","HM Treasury","2016-02-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of the fall in China's foreign currency reserves on the UK economy.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27377","27377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453079","2016-02-23","HM Treasury","2016-02-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what proportion of tax credit investigations carried out by Concentrix under its contract with his Department have resulted in findings of (a) fraud and (b) error in the claim.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27382","27382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453080","2016-02-23","HM Treasury","2016-02-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many tax credit investigations carried out by Concentrix under its contract with his Department have resulted in (a) no change in and (b) withdrawal of the tax credit award; and how many decisions to withdraw such awards were appealed successfully.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27383","27383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453081","2016-02-23","HM Treasury","2016-02-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much has accrued to the public purse from the taxation of coal in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27406","27406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453082","2016-02-23","HM Treasury","2016-02-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with which financial institutions on the energy exposure of such institutions in response to the falling price of oil.","Biography information for Philip Boswell","Phil Boswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27297","27297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453083","2016-02-23","HM Treasury","2016-02-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what mechanisms the Government has in place to ensure that banks with high energy exposure remain stable.","Biography information for Philip Boswell","Phil Boswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27298","27298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453084","2016-02-23","HM Treasury","2016-02-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions his Department has had with the Prudential Regulation Authority on the level of risk at (a) financial institutions with high energy market exposure and (b) such institutions which have issued loans to the North Sea oil industry.","Biography information for Philip Boswell","Phil Boswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27299","27299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453085","2016-02-23","HM Treasury","2016-02-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of (a) the effects on financial institutions with high energy exposure of the falling price of oil and (b) the effect of that falling price on businesses in the North Sea.","Biography information for Philip Boswell","Phil Boswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27300","27300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453086","2016-02-23","Church Commissioners","2016-02-19","To ask the right hon. Member for Meriden, representing the Church Commissioners, what plans the Church of England has to mark the 90th birthday of Her Majesty the Queen.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27423","27423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453087","2016-02-23","Church Commissioners","2016-02-19","To ask the right hon. Member for Meriden, representing the Church Commissioners, what the average hourly earnings for their (a) female and (b) male (i) full-time and (ii) part-time employees was in each of the last five years.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27425","27425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453088","2016-02-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many people were employed as occupational therapists in each of the last five years; what information his Department holds on unfilled vacancies in occupational therapy in the last 12 months; and what steps he is taking to increase the number of people trained as occupational therapists.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27407","27407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453089","2016-02-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the deliverable five-year housing allocation is for each local authority in (a) Derbyshire, (b) South Yorkshire and (c) Nottinghamshire.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27360","27360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453090","2016-02-23","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2016-02-19","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, when he expects the Local Government Boundary Commission for England to next review the (a) ward and (b) councillor arrangements in metropolitan districts in West Yorkshire.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27396","27396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453091","2016-02-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of proposals to impose mandatory rent reductions on social landlords of one per cent each year for four years on housing co-operatives which have had a policy of maintaining low levels of rent.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27371","27371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453092","2016-02-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what guidance his Department has issued on the applicability of Florrie's law, capping council housing repair bills, to works which were commissioned but not implemented before that law was introduced in August 2014.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27372","27372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453093","2016-02-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to support Help to Buy applicants whose new build completion has been delayed.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27332","27332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453094","2016-02-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many official visits he has made to local authorities since May 2015 where the primary purpose of the visit was in connection with the Northern Powerhouse policy.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27333","27333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453095","2016-02-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many and what proportion of full-time members of staff in his Department work on the Northern Powerhouse initiative.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27334","27334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453096","2016-02-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that the statistics it produces on homelessness and rough sleeping comply with the Code of Practice for Official Statistics in relation to each of the requirements identified by the UK Statistics Authority in its report, Assessment of compliance with the Code of Practice for Official Statistics: Statistics on Homelessness and Rough Sleeping in England, published in December 2015.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27313","27313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453097","2016-02-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the formal consultation process will be for the review of the Homes and Communities Agency.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27314","27314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453098","2016-02-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what range of options will be considered for the status of the Homes and Communities Agency as part of the review of that Agency.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27315","27315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453099","2016-02-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the timetable is for the review of the Homes and Communities Agency.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27316","27316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453100","2016-02-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the cost to the public purse has been of his Department reimbursing local authorities for payments to (a) households and (b) businesses in flood protection grants.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27227","27227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453101","2016-02-23","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what discussions his Department has had with burial authorities and other stakeholders on the reuse of graves.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27219","27219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453102","2016-02-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, by what date he expects all local authorities to be fully reimbursed for flood protection grants they have paid to (a) households and (b) businesses.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27228","27228"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453103","2016-02-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, by what date he expects all local authorities to be fully reimbursed for flood compensation payments they have made to households.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27229","27229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453104","2016-02-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the cost to the public purse has been of his Department reimbursing local authorities for payments to households in flood compensation payments.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27230","27230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453105","2016-02-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate his Department has made of the amount paid out by local authorities to households in flood compensation payments.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27222","27222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453106","2016-02-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many £5,000 flood protection grants have been paid to (a) households and (b) businesses by local authorities.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27224","27224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453107","2016-02-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many applications have been made to local authorities for £5,000 flood protection grants.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27225","27225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453108","2016-02-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 27 January 2016 to Question 23605, whether he plans to publish the thresholds for council homes to be taken into account when calculating the levy on councils contained in Part 4 of the Housing and Planning Bill before the relevant part of that Bill is debated at Committee Stage in the House of Lords.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27217","27217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453109","2016-02-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much has been paid out by local authorities to households in flood compensation payments that remains to be reimbursed to those authorities by his Department.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27226","27226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453110","2016-02-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if his Department will review planning permissions granted to developments that are yet to be started on floodplains that have been affected by recent flooding.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27519","27519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453111","2016-02-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if his Department will undertake a reassessment of the adequacy of flood alleviation measures proposed in planning permissions that have been granted to developments on floodplains affected by recent flooding.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27520","27520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453112","2016-02-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the potential benefit to the local economies of North, East, South and West Yorkshire of a devolution deal.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27506","27506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453113","2016-02-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many Syrian nationals have resettled in each region under the Vulnerable Persons Relocation Scheme since March 2014.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27501","27501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453114","2016-02-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what proportion of Syrian nationals resettled under the Vulnerable Persons Relocation Scheme since March 2014 were housed under the COMPASS accommodation contract agreements.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27503","27503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453115","2016-02-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether his Department has spent any money on advertising the Northern Powerhouse policy since May 2015.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27554","27554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453116","2016-02-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will place in the Library all correspondence between the Government and EU Commission on the application of EU Directive 41/2003 Institutional Retirement Provision to the Local Government Pension Scheme.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27565","27565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453117","2016-02-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make an assessment of the potential effect on the availability of women's refuge services of the local rate of local housing allowance being applied to tenants in supported housing.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27514","27514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453118","2016-02-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what discussions he has had with the Secretaries of State for Work and Pensions and Health on transferring responsibility for attendance allowance to local authorities.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27537","27537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453119","2016-02-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the (a) budget and (b) total spend was on the disabled facilities grants scheme in each year from 2009-10 to 2014-15.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27551","27551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453120","2016-02-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many times the Ministerial Committee for Syrian Refugees has met.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27575","27575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453121","2016-02-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, (a) how many people applied for disabled facilities grants, (b) how many such applications were successful and (c) what the average grant award was in each year from 2009-10 to 2014-15.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27552","27552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453122","2016-02-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 25 November 2015 to Question 16106, when he expects his Department's review of compliance with the Local Government Transparency Code 2015 to be completed.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27580","27580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453123","2016-02-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assistance is available to people undertaking flood protection measures who cannot afford to pay for the works before claiming a flood protection grant.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27553","27553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453124","2016-02-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 5 January 2016 to Question 20554, when he plans to carry out a post-implementation review of the Localism Act 2011.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27581","27581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453125","2016-02-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the rate of pay is for cleaners in his Department.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27549","27549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453126","2016-02-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the average waiting time was to be assessed by an occupational therapist for disabled facilities grants in each year from 2009-10 to 2014-15.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27558","27558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453127","2016-02-23","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, when he plans to answer Question 23160 tabled on 19 January 2016, on the Code for America programme.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27320","27320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453128","2016-02-24","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many new athletics tracks have been built since August 2012.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27359","27359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453129","2016-02-23","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many new community cricket grounds have been opened in the last five years.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27362","27362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453130","2016-02-23","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department is taking to encourage tourism in Calder Valley since the recent flooding and severe weather in that area.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27394","27394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453131","2016-02-23","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will estimate the cost to the tourist industry in Calder Valley of recent flooding and severe weather in that area.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27395","27395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453132","2016-02-23","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, where he expects the two-star headquarters of the Ultra Rapid Reaction Corps to be located.","Biography information for James Gray","James Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27379","27379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453133","2016-02-23","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many UK armed forces personnel cultural advisers are currently deployed on overseas operations.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27295","27295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453134","2016-02-23","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many UK armed forces personnel have received region-specific culture training at the Defence Centre for Languages and Culture in each year since 2013; and to which regions such training related.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27296","27296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453135","2016-02-24","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans his Department has to commemorate the Battle of Jutland.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27351","27351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453136","2016-02-23","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will place a copy of the UK Joint Targeting and Battle Damage Assessment Policy paper, dated 2005, in the Library.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27212","27212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453137","2016-02-23","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many people were recruited to the (a) Army, (b) Royal Air Force, (c) Royal Navy and (d) reserve forces in Scotland in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27213","27213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453138","2016-02-23","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the Government has sought from or been given permission by the Italian government for use of the Sigonella air station in Sicily.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27211","27211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453139","2016-02-23","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what information his Department holds on the number of war widows who remarried between 6 April 2005 and 1 April 2015.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27234","27234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453140","2016-02-24","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what information his Department holds on the number of women who become war widows before 6 April 2005 and remarried between 6 April 2005 and 1 April 2015.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27253","27253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453141","2016-02-23","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 10 February 2016 to Question 25312, whether he has been consulted about proposals for a US drone operation centre at RAF Lakenheath; and whether he has received a Host Nation Notification from the US in respect of RAF Lakenheath in the last year.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27237","27237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453142","2016-02-23","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to his Written Statement of 17 December 2015, HCWS 431, to which deployed coalitions the UK is party.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27205","27205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453143","2016-02-24","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many UK armed forces personnel in (a) the Army, (b) the RAF and (c) the Royal Navy are classed as level 3 or higher linguists in (i) Arabic, (ii) Polish, (iii) Russian, (iv) Ukrainian, (v) Estonian, (vi) German, (vii) French, (viii) Pashto, (ix) Dari, (x) Farsi and (xi) Spanish.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27331","27331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453144","2016-02-24","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the US Department of Defense's decision to delay the acceleration of orders of the F-35 until 2021.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27329","27329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453145","2016-02-24","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment his Department has made of whether the Project Centurion configuration for the Typhoon will be completed by the end of 2018.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27330","27330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453146","2016-02-23","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he has been informed of any defects relating to the reliability of the Rolls-Royce MT-30 marine gas turbine engines for the Queen Elizabeth Class aircraft carriers.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27515","27515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453147","2016-02-23","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department has taken to improve security at the Akrotiri and Dhekelia RAF Sovereign Base Areas; and how much his Department has spent on securing those areas in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27508","27508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453148","2016-02-24","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what his Department's policy is and what guidance it issues to civil servants on the acceptance and declaration of corporate gifts.","Biography information for Kate Hollern","Kate Hollern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27492","27492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453149","2016-02-24","Department for Education","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to ensure that local authorities, free schools and academies uphold the Armed Forces Covenant in relation to school admissions.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27482","27482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453150","2016-02-24","Department for Education","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many four year olds in Ashfield constituency have received the 15 hours free childcare allowance (a) in private, voluntary or independent sector nurseries, (b) in nursery schools or nursery units in infant or primary schools and (c) from childminders registered to provide early years education in each academic year since that allowance was introduced.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27479","27479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453151","2016-02-24","Department for Education","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent estimate she has made of the number of pupils currently in receipt of the service pupil premium.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27483","27483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453152","2016-02-24","Department for Education","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many two year olds in Ashfield constituency have received the 15 hours free childcare allowance (a) in private, voluntary or independent sector nurseries and (b) from childminders registered to provide early years education in each academic year since that allowance was introduced.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27480","27480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453153","2016-02-24","Department for Education","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that those pupils who are eligible to receive the service pupil premium are receiving that premium.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27484","27484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453154","2016-02-24","Department for Education","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she plans to increase the service pupil premium from its current rate.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27485","27485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453155","2016-02-24","Department for Education","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many three year olds in Ashfield constituency have received the 15 hours free childcare allowance (a) in private, voluntary or independent sector nurseries, (b) in nursery schools or nursery units in infant or primary schools and (c) from childminders registered to provide early years education in each academic year since that allowance was introduced.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27481","27481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453156","2016-02-23","Department for Education","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the implications for her policies of the recommendation in the Chief Schools Adjudicator for England's Annual Report, published in December 2015, that her Department should clarify what is expected in guidance produced by relevant religious authorities for schools which give priority on the grounds of religion in their admission arrangements.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27468","27468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453157","2016-02-23","Department for Education","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of students are taught in schools rated by Ofsted as good or outstanding in (a) Calder Valley constituency and (b) West Yorkshire.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27507","27507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453158","2016-02-24","Department for Education","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what representations she received from religious organisations on steps to prevent civil society organisations from objecting to school admission arrangements prior to her announcing proposals to limit such objections to local parents and councils.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27535","27535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453159","2016-02-24","Department for Education","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to ensure that charities or other civil society organisations who wish to object to the admission arrangements of a school can do so on behalf of parents local to that school.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27536","27536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453160","2016-02-23","Department for Education","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether school funding for (a) inner London boroughs and (b) outer London boroughs will decrease in the next financial year.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27530","27530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453161","2016-02-24","Department for Education","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the average number of days was for a determination to be made by the Office of the Schools Adjudicator after an objection to a school's admission arrangements was submitted in each the last four years.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27542","27542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453162","2016-02-24","Department for Education","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many cases the Schools Adjudicator has investigated in connection with the provisions of the Armed Forces Covenant since 2011.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27540","27540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453163","2016-02-23","Department for Education","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment she has made of the effectiveness of the Prevent training programme in schools; what benchmarks her Department uses to assess and train staff who provide Prevent training; and what representations she has received from schools on that training.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27567","27567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453164","2016-02-23","Department for Education","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will undertake a national review of the operation of admissions procedures and the School Admissions Code.","Biography information for Holly Lynch","Holly Lynch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27274","27274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453165","2016-02-23","Department for Education","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what procedures are in place to ensure that headteachers follow the School Admissions Code.","Biography information for Holly Lynch","Holly Lynch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27275","27275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453166","2016-02-23","Department for Education","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what criteria are used to define challenging behaviour as used in the 2012 School Admissions Code.","Biography information for Holly Lynch","Holly Lynch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27276","27276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453167","2016-02-24","Department for Education","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether her Department has received representations on requests by schools to parents and carers that children with autism spectrum disorder not attend school during Ofsted inspections in the last five years.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27239","27239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453168","2016-02-24","Department for Education","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that the number of pupils taking creative subjects does not fall as a result of the introduction of the English Baccalaureate.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27241","27241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453169","2016-02-24","Department for Education","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 20 January 2016 to Question 22095, whether her new proposals on special guardianship orders will include revisions to the child maintenance system.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27244","27244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453170","2016-02-24","Department for Education","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment she has made of the access to therapeutic services for children who enter the care system.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27343","27343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453171","2016-02-24","Department for Education","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what procedures schools are required to follow in order to withdraw from an academy trust.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27245","27245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453172","2016-02-24","Department for Education","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of the strengths and difficulties questionnaire in assessing the wellbeing of children and young people when they enter the care system.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27344","27344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453173","2016-02-23","Department for Education","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will make an assessment of the implications for her policy on school admissions of the finding of the report, An Unholy Mess, published by the Fair Admissions Campaign in October 2015, relating to information made available on requirements for religious observance as part of the admissions process for certain religiously selective schools.","Biography information for Jeff Smith","Jeff Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27200","27200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453174","2016-02-23","Department for Education","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 11 February 2016 to Question 25621, if her Department will publish that part of the small schools taskforce report which is not already in the public domain.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27231","27231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453175","2016-02-23","Department for Education","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will make an assessment of the implications for her policy on school admissions of the finding of the report, An Unholy Mess, published by the Fair Admissions Campaign in October 2015, on the use of supplementary information forms which assume that parents are of the opposite sex; and if she will take steps to ensure that such forms are not used by schools in future.","Biography information for Jeff Smith","Jeff Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27214","27214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453176","2016-02-23","Department for Education","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many vexatious complaints there have been against faith schools from secularist campaign groups in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Jeff Smith","Jeff Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27201","27201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453177","2016-02-24","Department for Education","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will estimate the change in that part of her Department's budget which is allocated to free school meals that will result from discontinuation of universal infant free school meals; and whether such a change would trigger a consequential change in the payment to devolved administrations under the Barnett formula.","Biography information for Carol Monaghan","Carol Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27349","27349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453178","2016-02-24","Department for Education","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will make an assessment of the potential effect of the new grading system for GCSEs on students of Latin and Greek; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27350","27350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453179","2016-02-23","Department for Education","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment her Department has made of the effect of fair access protocols on pupil referral units.","Biography information for Holly Lynch","Holly Lynch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27278","27278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453180","2016-02-23","Department for Education","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment her Department has made of the effect of (a) the school a pupil attends and (b) access to transport on participation in after-school sport.","Biography information for Holly Lynch","Holly Lynch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27279","27279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453181","2016-02-23","Department for Education","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 16 February 2016 to Question 26162 on free schools: Luton, whether she plans to publish details of the repayments made by Luton Girl's Academy or people associated with its application, by date, in March 2016.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Mr Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27321","27321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453182","2016-02-23","Department for Education","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of children and young people entering care complete the strengths and difficulties questionnaire to assess their wellbeing in (a) England and (b) Birmingham.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27312","27312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453183","2016-02-23","Department for Education","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of identified violations of the Schools Admissions Code since 2014 related to failure to properly prioritise looked-after and previously looked-after children.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27309","27309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453184","2016-02-23","Department for Education","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will establish a regulatory body to enforce the School Admissions Code.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27310","27310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453185","2016-02-23","Department for Education","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of the objections received by the Office of the Schools Adjudicator in relation to the School Admissions Code by (a) all parties, (b) civil society organisations and (c) individuals in a school's local area have not been upheld in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27311","27311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453186","2016-02-23","Department for Education","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what measures are in place to ensure that no school is asked to admit a disproportionate number of children who have been excluded from other schools.","Biography information for Holly Lynch","Holly Lynch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27277","27277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453187","2016-02-23","Department for Education","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment her Department has made of the effect of the built environment on learning progress in schools.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27397","27397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453188","2016-02-23","Department for Education","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the implications for her Department's policies on the design of new schools of the study entitled, The impact of classroom design on pupils' learning, by Professor Barrett of Salford University, published in July 2015.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27398","27398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453189","2016-02-23","Department for Education","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will estimate the number of children from families from Eastern European countries that have entered the care system in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Margaret Beckett","Margaret Beckett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27387","27387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453190","2016-02-23","Department for Education","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether her Department has taken steps to disseminate the findings of the study, The impact of classroom design on pupils' learning, by Professor Barrett of Salford University, published in July 2015, to (a) primary schools, (b) secondary schools and (c) sixth form colleges.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27399","27399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453191","2016-02-23","Department for Education","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment her Department has made of the potential benefits of using adjustable furniture in schools to improve the classroom learning environment.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27400","27400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453192","2016-02-23","Department for Education","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the findings in the Chief Schools Adjudicator for England's Annual Report, published in December 2015, that there is a lack of transparency in the school admission system, what steps she plans to take to monitor and enforce compliance with the School Admissions Code.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27467","27467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453193","2016-02-23","Department for Education","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the implications for her policies of the finding in the Chief Schools Adjudicator for England's Annual Report, published in December 2015, that parents are often unable to understand the complicated admissions criteria employed by religiously selective schools.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27469","27469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453194","2016-02-23","Department for Education","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the key findings in the Chief Schools Adjudicator for England's Annual Report, published in December 2015, whether she plans to publish guidance for schools on how best to comply with the school admissions code.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27470","27470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453195","2016-02-23","Department for Education","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the potential effect of preventing civil society organisations from submitting complaints about school admission arrangements on the transparency and accountability of the admissions system.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27435","27435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453196","2016-02-23","Department for Education","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if her Department will hold a consultation on changing the School Admissions Code to require religiously selective schools to prioritise all looked-after children and previously looked-after children in their admission arrangements in addition to such children of the same denomination of such schools.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27466","27466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453197","2016-02-23","Department for Education","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much her Department has spent on horticultural training in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27421","27421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453198","2016-02-23","Department for Education","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many maintained nurseries there are in (a) Burnley, (b) Lancashire and (c) the North West.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27428","27428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453199","2016-02-23","Department for Education","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many people are employed in maintained nurseries in (a) Burnley, (b) Lancashire and (c) the North West.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27429","27429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453200","2016-02-24","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the additional cost to the public purse will be of storage of additional spent fuel arising from the lifetime extension of nuclear reactors.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27472","27472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453201","2016-02-24","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether new storage facilities will be required at Sellafield to accommodate additional spent fuel arising from the life extension of nuclear reactors.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27473","27473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453202","2016-02-24","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what volume of additional spent fuel will be produced as a consequence of the life extension of nuclear reactors.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27474","27474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453203","2016-02-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if she will place in the Library copies of the impact assessments produced related to the moratorium on gas fired power stations between 1998 and 2000.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27405","27405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453204","2016-02-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what charges the Government plans to levy for connection to the National Grid on the proposed interconnector cable from Iceland.","Biography information for Corri Wilson","Corri Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27325","27325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453205","2016-02-24","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if she will undertake an assessment of the effect on the availability of UK-sourced wood supplies of (a) 50MW and under and (b) over 50MW wood-burning biomass plants.","Biography information for Susan Elan Jones","Susan Elan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27354","27354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453206","2016-02-24","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what plans she has to review the UK Bioenergy Strategy.","Biography information for Susan Elan Jones","Susan Elan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27353","27353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453207","2016-02-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what plans she has to promote a global goal on adaptation to climate change.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27563","27563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453208","2016-02-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the objectives are of the Sellafield workforce reform initiative; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27461","27461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453209","2016-02-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment her Department has made of the potential effect of the Sellafield workforce reform initiative on workforce salary expenditure by Sellafield Ltd in (a) Copeland, (b) Allerdale, (c) Barrow-in-Furness and (d) Cumbria.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27458","27458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453210","2016-02-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment her Department has made of the potential effect of the Sellafield workforce reform initiative on the economy of (a) Copeland, (b) Allerdale, (c) Barrow-in-Furness and (d) Cumbria.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27459","27459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453211","2016-02-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate her Department has made of the cost to the public purse of the Sellafield workforce reform initiative.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27455","27455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453212","2016-02-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if she will meet Sellafield workforce representatives to discuss how better to achieve (a) safer, (b) quicker and (c) more efficient decommissioning of the Sellafield site.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27460","27460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453213","2016-02-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many gas fired power stations have been built in the UK since July 1998.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27447","27447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453214","2016-02-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment her Department has made of how the Sellafield workforce reform initiative will ensure (a) safer, (b) quicker and (c) more efficient delivery of decommissioning at Sellafield.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27456","27456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453215","2016-02-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether her Department has made an assessment of the potential savings to the public purse arising from the Sellafield workforce reform initiative.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27457","27457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453216","2016-02-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether she has made an estimate of the difference in value between coal produced in the UK and coal imported from overseas for each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27448","27448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453217","2016-02-24","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if she has made an assessment of the potential effect on carbon dioxide emissions of the life extension of nuclear reactors compared with the use of (a) coal and (b) gas-powered electricity plants producing the same amount of electricity over the same period.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27476","27476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453218","2016-02-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what (a) timetable and (b) process his Department plans for its forthcoming review of the remit of the Groceries Code Adjudicator.","Biography information for Corri Wilson","Corri Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27561","27561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453219","2016-02-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions have taken place with the European Commissioner for Agriculture and Rural Development on the situation in the dairy industry since the early support payments were made in November 2015.","Biography information for Corri Wilson","Corri Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27562","27562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453220","2016-02-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what progress has been made on introducing a Europe-wide groceries adjudicator.","Biography information for Corri Wilson","Corri Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27560","27560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453221","2016-02-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she plans to take to improve the standard of hazardous waste management in response to the recommendations contained in the assessment of member states' performance published by the European Commission in January 2016; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27518","27518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453222","2016-02-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether the Government uses the Food Insecurity Experience Scale survey to monitor UK households' vulnerability to hunger.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27543","27543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453223","2016-02-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department plans to take to improve biosecurity on farms.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27218","27218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453224","2016-02-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment her Department has made of the sensitivity of the single intradermal comparative cervical tuberculin test for Bovine TB; and what steps her Department is taking to improve testing for TB.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27220","27220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453225","2016-02-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the cost of the badger cull was in 2015; how much of that cost was for policing that cull; and what proportion of that cost was spent in (a) Somerset, (b) Gloucestershire and (c) Dorset.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27249","27249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453226","2016-02-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many cases of Bovine TB there have been in Somerset in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27250","27250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453227","2016-02-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans her Department has to monitor the disease status of badgers within cull areas.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27251","27251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453228","2016-02-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, further to her Written Ministerial Statement of 17 December 2015, HCWS 409, to which areas her Department plans to extend the badger cull in 2016; and what the evidential basis is for selecting those areas.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27252","27252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453229","2016-02-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to her Written Ministerial Statement of 17 December 2015, Bovine TB, HC 45409, when her Department plans to introduce statutory post-movement TB testing for cattle entering the low-risk area.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27246","27246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453230","2016-02-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to encourage more young people to go into farming.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27324","27324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453231","2016-02-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many dairy farmers have gone out of business in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27338","27338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453232","2016-02-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what her Department's policy is on the installation of mandatory, independently-monitored CCTV in slaughterhouses and abattoirs.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27422","27422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453233","2016-02-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many homes she estimates will benefit from Flood Re in (a) the North West, (b) Lancashire and (c) Pendle.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27420","27420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453234","2016-02-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect of the UK leaving the EU on the rights of British citizens living in (a) other EU countries and (b) non-EU countries.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27412","27412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453235","2016-02-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what contribution his Department has made to the UN Special Rapporteur on Freedom of Religion or Belief's report on Bangladesh which will be published in March 2016.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27381","27381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453236","2016-02-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 17 December 2015 to Question 19830, when he plans to report on his review of the UK National Action Plan on Business and Human Rights.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27322","27322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453237","2016-02-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received of deployment by China of surface-to-air missiles on the Paracels Islands in the South China Sea.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27326","27326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453238","2016-02-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has (a) received and (b) made on the cancellation of the UK delegation to Israel and the Occupied Territories to follow up the report published by a delegation of British lawyers, entitled Children in Military Custody, in June 2012; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27341","27341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453239","2016-02-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to reduce the intensity of conflict in urban areas in Yemen.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27269","27269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453240","2016-02-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to support Saudi Arabia's internal inquiry into war crimes in Yemen.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27267","27267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453241","2016-02-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the UK is taking to prevent a refugee crisis in Yemen.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27261","27261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453242","2016-02-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what evidence the Government holds of terrorists linked to Daesh or Al Qaeda crossing the Mediterranean Sea from Libya.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27262","27262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453243","2016-02-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to his Belarusian counterpart on recent death penalty sentences handed down by Belarusian courts and the position of the Belarusian government on the abolition of the death penalty.","Biography information for Mark Pritchard","Mark Pritchard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27318","27318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453244","2016-02-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent steps the Government has taken to (a) monitor and (b) counter the activities of Al Qaeda and Daesh in Yemen.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27258","27258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453245","2016-02-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what estimate he has made of the number of Daesh fighters in Yemen.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27259","27259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453246","2016-02-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many foreign consulates or diplomatic offices have closed in Scotland since 2010.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27233","27233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453247","2016-03-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his Egyptian counterpart on freedom of expression in Egypt.","Biography information for Dr Rupa Huq","Dr Rupa Huq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27327","27327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453248","2016-03-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his Egyptian counterpart on alleged human rights abuses in that country.","Biography information for Dr Rupa Huq","Dr Rupa Huq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27328","27328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453249","2016-02-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the implications for the Government's policies of the recognition of acts constituting genocide in the European Parliament's Resolution, Systematic mass murder of religious minorities by ISIS, agreed on 4 February 2016.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27223","27223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453250","2016-02-24","HM Treasury","2016-02-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what amount of funding the European Court of Auditors has recorded as having been misspent in the last 12 months for which figures are available.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27541","27541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453251","2016-02-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his Department has made an assessment of the situation on the line of contact between the armed forces of Nagorno-Karabakh and Azerbaijan.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27538","27538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453252","2016-02-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent diplomatic steps the Government has taken to support the reopening of peace talks in Yemen and the establishment of a ceasefire.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27556","27556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453253","2016-02-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the human rights situation in Bangladesh.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27513","27513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453254","2016-02-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has received from the Austrian government on a person suspected of rape in Linz, Austria, who is now resident in the UK.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27524","27524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453255","2016-02-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports his Department has received on the frequency of rocket attacks from the West Bank into Israel in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27547","27547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453256","2016-02-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to his Colombian counterpart to request that he (a) take steps to protect trade unionists who have received death threats in the Valle del Cauca region and (b) establish who is responsible for those threats.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27584","27584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453257","2016-02-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has received on the detainment of Mohammed al-Qeeq in Israel.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27442","27442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453258","2016-02-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with the Saudi Arabian government on tackling the spread of Daesh in the Middle East.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27419","27419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453259","2016-02-24","Department of Health","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will provide additional funding to South Tees Hospitals NHS Foundation Trust and South Tees Clinical Commissioning Group for improvements and new facilities at Guisborough Primary Care Hospital.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27477","27477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453260","2016-02-23","Department of Health","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he plans to take to implement the recommendations of the Mental Health Taskforce's report, The Five Year Forward View for Mental Health, published in February 2016.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27471","27471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453261","2016-02-24","Department of Health","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions he has had with NHS England and NICE on the cancer drugs fund consultation.","Biography information for Mark Durkan","Mark Durkan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27487","27487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453262","2016-02-24","Department of Health","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions his Department has had with NHS England on its decision not to renew the position of National Clinical Director for Adult Neurology from March 2016.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27532","27532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453263","2016-02-24","Department of Health","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how the Accelerated Access Review will ensure that people with epilepsy will have access to drugs found by whole genome sequencing to be effective in treating the cause of their individual epilepsy.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27533","27533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453264","2016-02-24","Department of Health","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people with epilepsy have been offered a personalised care plan since 2013 in accordance with the Department of Health's mandate to NHS England; and what steps he is taking to increase the number of such people.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27531","27531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453265","2016-02-24","Department of Health","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions his Department has had with (a) NICE and (b) NHS England on the availability of Erbitux for metastatic colorectal cancer patients.","Biography information for Mark Durkan","Mark Durkan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27585","27585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453266","2016-02-23","Department of Health","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of adults in (a) Calder Valley, (b) West Yorkshire and (c) England have been diagnosed with dementia in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27573","27573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453267","2016-02-24","Department of Health","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will ensure continued Government funding for the Neurology Intelligence Network through NHS England and Public Health England.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27534","27534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453268","2016-02-23","Department of Health","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many Health and Wellbeing boards have identified in their strategic plans loneliness as an issue needing to be tackled.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27221","27221"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453269","2016-02-24","Department of Health","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with (a) East Lancashire and (b) Blackburn and Darwen clinical commissioning groups on the cost of outsourced mental health services.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27345","27345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453270","2016-02-24","Department of Health","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he plans to reply to the letter to his Department from the hon. Member for Ashfield of 4 January 2016 on the GP surgery in Underwood.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27340","27340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453271","2016-02-24","Department of Health","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many full-time equivalent GPs were employed in general practices in Ashfield in the financial years (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12, (c) 2012-13 and (d) 2014-15.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27254","27254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453272","2016-02-23","Department of Health","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what rules govern the movement of senior NHS staff to private sector organisations.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27263","27263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453273","2016-02-23","Department of Health","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many NHS trust chief executives have become private sector consultants after leaving that post.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27264","27264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453274","2016-02-23","Department of Health","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of public health budgets are allocated to services related to diabetes in 2015-16.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27256","27256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453275","2016-02-23","Department of Health","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the salaries are of the directors of each clinical commissioning group in Leicestershire.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27265","27265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453276","2016-02-23","Department of Health","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to reduce ambulance waiting times in (a) the East Midlands and (b) England.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27257","27257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453277","2016-02-24","Department of Health","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of the provision of mental health care services for children in the care system.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27342","27342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453278","2016-02-24","Department of Health","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the total cost to the NHS has been of outsourced mental health services in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27346","27346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453279","2016-02-24","Department of Health","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with NHS England on the cost of outsourced mental health services.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27347","27347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453280","2016-02-23","Department of Health","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he plans to respond to the letter to his Department from the hon. Member for Wolverhampton South West of 23 December 2015, on reform of UK surrogacy law, reference ZA2272.","Biography information for Rob Marris","Rob Marris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27289","27289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453281","2016-02-23","Department of Health","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 12 February 2016 to Question 25934, for what reasons information about how many three year olds received a free NHS dental check is not collected centrally.","Biography information for Mr Graham Allen","Mr Graham Allen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27291","27291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453282","2016-02-23","Department of Health","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many young people aged 17 or under received dental treatment band 1 in (a) Nottingham North constituency, (b) Nottingham and (c) England in 2015.","Biography information for Mr Graham Allen","Mr Graham Allen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27292","27292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453283","2016-02-23","Department of Health","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many NHS dentists there are in (a) Nottingham North constituency, (b) Nottingham and (c) England.","Biography information for Mr Graham Allen","Mr Graham Allen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27293","27293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453284","2016-02-23","Department of Health","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the cost to the public purse was of urgent dental treatment for children in (a) Nottingham North constituency, (b) Nottingham and (c) England in 2015.","Biography information for Mr Graham Allen","Mr Graham Allen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27294","27294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453285","2016-02-24","Department of Health","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he expects that a paperless NHS will be achieved.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27337","27337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453286","2016-02-23","Department of Health","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the conclusions of the report by the Carers Trust, A charge on caring, published in September 2015, that an increasing number of local councils are considering charging carers for the support that they receive to help them in their caring role.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27323","27323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453287","2016-02-23","Department of Health","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of children in England received the meningitis B vaccine in 2015-16; and what steps he is taking to maximise take-up rates.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27288","27288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453288","2016-02-23","Department of Health","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether NHS England's workplan for 2016-17 will include developing a policy for the effective delivery of care for people with tuberous sclerosis complex.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27374","27374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453289","2016-02-23","Department of Health","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will commission a review into the effectiveness of NHS England in discharging its duties in implementing the Rare Diseases Strategy.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27373","27373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453290","2016-02-23","Department of Health","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he last issued guidance to NHS providers on systems for recharging to other countries the cost of NHS treatment of foreign nationals.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27363","27363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453291","2016-02-23","Department of Health","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much was paid to which countries for overseas health treatment of UK nationals in 2015.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27364","27364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453292","2016-02-23","Department of Health","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much was recharged to (a) other EU countries and (b) non-EU countries for health treatment by the NHS in 2015.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27365","27365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453293","2016-02-23","Department of Health","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 22 January 2016 to Question 22461, on blood: contamination, how many cases of liability have been established for people with haemophilia infected with HIV and/or hepatitis C through NHS-supplied contaminated blood or blood products.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27301","27301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453294","2016-02-23","Department of Health","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the oral contribution of the Parliamentary Under Secretary of State for Quality of 20 July 2015, Official Report, column 1227, for what reasons dependent children are not included in the consultation seeking views on proposed reforms to the schemes supporting those infected with, or affected by, HIV and/or hepatitis C through NHS-supplied blood products.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27302","27302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453295","2016-02-23","Department of Health","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average cost to the NHS has been of supporting a patient on dialysis in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27376","27376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453296","2016-02-23","Department of Health","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what contingency plans are in place to alleviate the increased demands on neighbouring GP practices when a practice closes.","Biography information for Mr Nick Clegg","Mr Nick Clegg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27430","27430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453297","2016-02-23","Department of Health","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what obligations NHS England has to provide patients access to a GP practice.","Biography information for Mr Nick Clegg","Mr Nick Clegg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27431","27431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453298","2016-02-23","Department of Health","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what measures NHS England uses to assess GP service provision to an area.","Biography information for Mr Nick Clegg","Mr Nick Clegg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27432","27432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453299","2016-02-23","Department of Health","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidelines have been issued to GP practices on the safe ratio of patients to doctors in GP practices.","Biography information for Mr Nick Clegg","Mr Nick Clegg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27433","27433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453300","2016-02-23","Department of Health","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many GP surgeries have closed in (a) Sheffield, (b) Yorkshire and the Humber and (c) England in the last three years.","Biography information for Mr Nick Clegg","Mr Nick Clegg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27434","27434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453301","2016-02-23","Home Office","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people were victims of online fraud in (a) Burnley, (b) Lancashire and (c) the North West in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27427","27427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453302","2016-02-23","Home Office","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many unaccompanied asylum seekers claiming to be under the age of 18 arrived in the UK for each of the last three years for which figures are available.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27417","27417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453303","2016-02-23","Home Office","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 4 February 2016 to Question 22830, whether the Warnings Index Checks system has been affected by high-priority incidents in the last five years.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27424","27424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453304","2016-02-23","Home Office","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the risk of radicalisation of asylum claimants whose asylum claim has been refused but who cannot legally be deported because their destination country is deemed unsafe.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27392","27392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453305","2016-02-23","Home Office","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to reduce the number of cases in which asylum claims are refused on the basis that the claimant is not judged to have a sufficient case but the claimant cannot be deported because their home country is deemed to be unsafe.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27393","27393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453306","2016-02-23","Home Office","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make an assessment of the implications for her Department's policy on the factors influencing migration to the UK of the findings of the Overseas Development Institute in its report, Journeys to Europe: the role of policy in migrant decision-making, published in February 2016.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27384","27384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453307","2016-02-23","Home Office","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of how the EU Refugee Facility for Turkey will reduce migration from Turkey.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27385","27385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453308","2016-02-23","Home Office","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she has had discussions with the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs on the possibility of establishing third party agreements to enable the deportation of foreign nationals who refuse or who cannot safely be returned to their country of origin to return to a neighbouring country.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27388","27388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453309","2016-02-23","Home Office","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate her Department has made of the number of asylum claimants whose asylum claim has been refused, but who cannot be legally deported because their destination country is deemed unsafe (a) in each of the last five years and (b) in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27389","27389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453310","2016-02-23","Home Office","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what receipts were received by each police force from the proceeds of crime in 2015.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27361","27361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453311","2016-02-23","Home Office","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when her Department plans to respond to the letter from the hon. Member for Wolverhampton South West of 14 December 2015 on the International Sikh Youth Federation, case reference ZA2442.","Biography information for Rob Marris","Rob Marris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27290","27290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453312","2016-02-23","Home Office","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she plans to issue a response to the Migration Advisory Committee review of Tier 2 visas.","Biography information for Ruth Smeeth","Ruth Smeeth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27308","27308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453313","2016-02-23","Home Office","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the number of UK citizens previously granted refugee status who have been refused permission for family members to join them on account of the minimum income threshold in Appendix FM of the Immigration Rules.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27235","27235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453314","2016-02-23","Home Office","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what safeguards her Department has put in place to ensure that out-of-country entry clearance applications are rigorously checked and processed.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27525","27525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453315","2016-02-23","Home Office","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to protect the public from fraudulent organisations presenting themselves as Disclosure and Barring Service umbrella body companies seeking personal data.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27528","27528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453316","2016-02-23","Home Office","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many unaccompanied children from each country of embarkation arrived at UK airports without being eligible for entry clearance in 2015.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27572","27572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453317","2016-02-23","Home Office","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which providers are expected to provide accommodation for the estimated 20,000 Syrian nationals to be resettled under the Vulnerable Persons Relocation Scheme by 2020.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27502","27502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453318","2016-02-23","Home Office","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many asylum seekers were being accommodated by G4S in the (a) North East, Yorkshire and the Humber and (b) Midlands and East of England regions on the latest date for which figures are available.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27504","27504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453319","2016-02-23","Home Office","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many asylum seekers were being accommodated by Serco in the North West region on the latest date for which figures are available.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27505","27505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453320","2016-02-23","Home Office","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many asylum seekers who claim to be under the age of 18 have undergone independent testing to determine their age in each of the last three years.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27500","27500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453321","2016-02-23","Home Office","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many asylum seekers were suspected of making fraudulent claims to be under the age of 18 in the last 12 months.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27499","27499"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453322","2016-02-24","Home Office","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many unaccompanied children arriving at UK airports from which countries were not eligible for entry clearance in 2015.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27491","27491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453323","2016-02-23","Department for International Development","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the implications for her policies of the Clean Clothes Campaign memorandum, published on 28 January 2016; and if she will raise the matters discussed in that memorandum with the Bangladeshi government.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27521","27521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453324","2016-02-23","Department for International Development","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what representations her Department has (a) made to and (b) received from Saferworld, Unicef, Save the Children and Oxfam on UK arms sales to Saudi Arabia in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27545","27545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453325","2016-02-23","Department for International Development","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what discussions her Department has had with (a) other government departments and (b) external organisations on the effects of UK arms sales to Saudi Arabia on the delivery of development aid.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27546","27546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453326","2016-02-23","Department for International Development","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps the Government has taken to (a) alleviate the blockade of Yemen and (b) address the shortage of essential medicines in that country.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27557","27557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453327","2016-02-23","Department for International Development","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the contributions of the Minister of State for International Development at the International Development Committee, 27 January 2016, Question 28, and on 3 February 2016, Official Report, column 908, what the evidential basis is for the statements that export of arms by the UK to Saudi Arabia is not undermining her Department's humanitarian work in Yemen.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27544","27544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453328","2016-02-24","Department for International Development","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what discussions her Department is having with HM Treasury on renegotiation of tax treaties between the UK and developing countries.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27247","27247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453329","2016-02-23","Department for International Development","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps the Government has taken to reduce fuel insecurity in  Yemen.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27270","27270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453330","2016-02-23","Department for International Development","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what estimate she has made of the number of people who have left Yemen as refugees since March 2015.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27268","27268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453331","2016-02-23","Department for International Development","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps the UK is taking to assist in the repair of hospitals damaged by air strikes in Yemen.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27266","27266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453332","2016-02-23","Department for International Development","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what funding the Government has allocated specifically to child protection in Yemen.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27255","27255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453333","2016-02-23","Department for International Development","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps the Government is taking to encourage increased international donor support for Yemen.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27272","27272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453334","2016-02-23","Department for International Development","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps the Government has taken to relieve food insecurity in (a) Taiz and (b) elsewhere in Yemen.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27271","27271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453335","2016-02-23","Department for International Development","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps are being taken to address and prevent the spread of the H1N1 virus in Yemen.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27260","27260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453336","2016-02-23","Department for International Development","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will take steps to ensure that HIV prevention is fully integrated into her Department's work on sexual and reproductive health and rights; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27367","27367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453337","2016-02-23","Department for International Development","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department has taken or plans to take to build the capacity of communities to (a) engage with the Global Fund to Fight AIDS, Tuberculosis and Malaria and (b) hold their governments to account for engagement on that issue.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27366","27366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453338","2016-02-23","Department for International Development","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps the Government is taking to assist vulnerable Syrian minorities register with the UNHCR who have not done so due to fear of persecution.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27409","27409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453339","2016-02-23","Home Office","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many asylum claimants whose asylum claim had been refused but who could not be legally deported because their destination country was deemed unsafe were admitted to prison in each year between 2006-07 and 2009-10.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27390","27390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453340","2016-02-23","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will estimate the number of care proceedings involving children and families from countries in Eastern Europe in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Margaret Beckett","Margaret Beckett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27386","27386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453341","2016-02-23","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will make an assessment of the comparative effect of changes to civil service pensions on prison officers who joined that scheme under Classic but have been switched to the Alpha scheme and colleagues with the same length of service who have not been switched.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27380","27380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453342","2016-02-23","Home Office","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many asylum claimants whose asylum claim has been refused but who cannot be legally deported because their destination country is deemed unsafe have been admitted to prison in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27391","27391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453343","2016-02-23","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department plans to take to ensure that proposed revisions to the sentencing guideline for guilty plea reductions do not lead to a culture of plea bargaining.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27375","27375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453344","2016-02-23","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment his Department has conducted of the potential effect of the closure of 86 courts and tribunals in England and Wales on access to justice by people in low-income households.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27287","27287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453345","2016-02-23","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what progress his Department has made on ensuring that all judges and family court sittings in private family proceedings cases where there is evidence of domestic abuse adhere to Practice Direction 12J:  Child Arrangements and Contact Order: Domestic Violence and Harm.","Biography information for Caroline Nokes","Caroline Nokes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27284","27284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453346","2016-02-23","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many family courts have designated safe waiting rooms for vulnerable victims and witnesses.","Biography information for Caroline Nokes","Caroline Nokes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27285","27285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453347","2016-02-24","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what plans his Department has for consultation with (a) civil society groups, (b) the devolved administrations and (c) Northern Ireland to inform its report for the third cycle of the Human Rights Council Universal Periodic Review.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27335","27335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453348","2016-02-23","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that all victims of domestic abuse attending the family courts have access to special measures similar to those available in the criminal courts.","Biography information for Caroline Nokes","Caroline Nokes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27286","27286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453349","2016-02-23","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment his Department has made of the potential psychological effect on victims of domestic abuse who are representing themselves as litigants in person in the family court of being cross-examined by their alleged abuser.","Biography information for Caroline Nokes","Caroline Nokes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27282","27282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453350","2016-02-24","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much the Government spent on The Queen on the application of Rights of Women v The Lord Chancellor and Anr. Appeal of Claimant from the order of Mrs Justice Lang, dated 22 January 2015, filed 12 February 2015.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27336","27336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453351","2016-02-23","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment his Department has made of the potential psychological effect on victims of domestic abuse who are representing themselves as litigants in person in the family court of having to cross-examine their alleged abuser.","Biography information for Caroline Nokes","Caroline Nokes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27283","27283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453352","2016-02-23","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much he estimates will have been spent by April 2016 on implementing digitalisation requirements at Calderdale Magistrates' Court and Halifax County Court and Family Court.","Biography information for Holly Lynch","Holly Lynch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27273","27273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453353","2016-02-24","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the safety of the family court estate for victims of domestic abuse during cases involving child contact.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27240","27240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453354","2016-02-23","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, (a) how many and (b) what proportion of prison governors have received (i) diversity training since 1 January 2012 and (ii) no such training; and what proportion of such training included transgender issues.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27215","27215"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453355","2016-02-23","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, (a) how many and (b) what proportion of judges have received (i) diversity training since 1 January 2012 and (ii) no such training; and what proportion of such training included transgender issues.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27216","27216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453356","2016-02-23","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many applications for (a) non-molestation orders and (b) ex parte non-molestation orders were (i) made and (ii) declined in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Andrew Bridgen","Andrew Bridgen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27512","27512"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453357","2016-02-23","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many applications for compensation from the Criminal Injuries Compensation Authority have been made in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Graham Stuart","Graham Stuart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27571","27571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453358","2016-02-23","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average length of time of cases in employment tribunals was in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27463","27463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453359","2016-02-24","Northern Ireland Office","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what plans she has to encourage foreign direct investment in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27498","27498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453360","2016-02-24","Northern Ireland Office","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what discussions she has had with the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills on job losses at Bombardier in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27496","27496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453361","2016-02-24","Northern Ireland Office","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what discussions she plans to have with Chancellor of the Exchequer on job losses at Bombardier in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27497","27497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453362","2016-02-24","Northern Ireland Office","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what discussions she plans to have with Ministers of the Northern Ireland Executive on job losses at Bombardier.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27495","27495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453363","2016-02-25","Northern Ireland Office","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of the early release of Stormont House legacy funding to support legacy inquests.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27348","27348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453364","2016-02-23","Department of Health","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Prime Minister's oral statement of 26 March 2015, Official Report, column 1423, on the Penrose Report on contaminated blood, when the Government plans to respond to the findings of that report.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27523","27523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453365","2016-02-23","Department for Transport","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 3 February 2016 to Question 24236, whether Transport for London's financial contribution to the British Transport Police budget for 2016-17 has been confirmed.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27206","27206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453366","2016-02-23","Department for Transport","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many British Transport Police officers will be deployed in 2016-17.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27207","27207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453367","2016-02-23","Department for Transport","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with Volkswagen on the provision of additional staffing in the UK during its repair programme.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27236","27236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453368","2016-02-23","Department for Transport","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many people used the subsidised part of the Number 14 bus service to Peel Park in each of the last 24 months.","Biography information for Paul Maynard","Paul Maynard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27203","27203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453369","2016-02-23","Department for Transport","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 11 January 2016 to Question 21012 on roads: floods, what recent assessment his Department has made of (a) the extent of damage caused by the winter floods, (b) the estimated cost of such damage, (c) the timetable for repairs and (d) relevant projects which have been identified as national priorities.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27202","27202"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453370","2016-02-23","Department for Transport","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many projects under the Road Investment Strategy are (a) completed, (b) ongoing and (c) still to be launched, by region; how many of those projects which are ongoing are (i) on schedule and (ii) on budget, by region; and how many of those projects which have been completed were on or under budget, by region.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27232","27232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453371","2016-02-23","Department for Transport","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent representations his Department has received on laser pens being pointed at aircraft in flight.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27317","27317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453372","2016-02-23","Department for Transport","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answers of 9 February 2016 to Question 25766 and 11 January 2016 to Question 20570 on British Transport Police: finance, if he will provide a breakdown of the budget by areas of expenditure for (a) 2015-16 and (b) 2016-17.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27209","27209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453373","2016-02-23","Department for Transport","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answers of 3 February 2016 to Question 24232 and 11 January 2016 to Question 20570 on British Transport Police: finance, how much income from (a) Transport for London, (b) train operating companies, (c) Network Rail and (d) other funding sources is included in the budget for 2016-17; and how much income by funding source (i) is in the budget for and (ii) has been received in 2015-16.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27208","27208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453374","2016-02-23","Department for Transport","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many railway stations are (a) staffed and (b) unstaffed.","Biography information for Teresa Pearce","Teresa Pearce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27401","27401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453375","2016-02-23","Department for Transport","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many railway station ticket offices have (a) been closed and (b) had their opening hours reduced since 2010.","Biography information for Teresa Pearce","Teresa Pearce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27402","27402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453376","2016-02-23","Department for Transport","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate his Department has made of the proportion of railway station ticket offices that will be closed by (a) 2020 and (b) 2025.","Biography information for Teresa Pearce","Teresa Pearce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27403","27403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453377","2016-02-23","Department for Transport","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate his Department has made of the proportion of railway stations that will be unstaffed in (a) 2020 and (b) 2025.","Biography information for Teresa Pearce","Teresa Pearce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27404","27404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453378","2016-02-23","Department for Transport","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what proportion of funding to the new northern rail franchise will be provided by (a) subsidies to Northern Rail, (b) investment by Network Rail, (c) passenger revenue and (d) investment by Arriva.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27408","27408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453379","2016-02-23","Department for Transport","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 10 February 2016 to Question 25769, on aviation: emergencies, whether he has received recent reports of further developments relating to the unplanned emergency landing of American Airlines flight AA109 at Heathrow.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27443","27443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453380","2016-02-23","Department for Transport","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with Midland Expressway on the proposed sale of the M6 Toll road.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27444","27444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453381","2016-02-23","Department for Transport","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the number of bus routes that have been (a) added and (b) removed since 2010.","Biography information for Ruth Smeeth","Ruth Smeeth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27305","27305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453382","2016-02-23","Department for Transport","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the potential benefits for bus passengers of municipal ownership of bus companies.","Biography information for Ruth Smeeth","Ruth Smeeth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27306","27306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453383","2016-02-23","Department for Transport","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had on devolving responsibility for rail services to the Midlands.","Biography information for Ruth Smeeth","Ruth Smeeth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27307","27307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453384","2016-02-24","Department for Transport","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment Highways England has made of the effectiveness of the response to the incident on the M6 Motorway between junctions 5 and 6 on Thursday 4 February 2016.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27356","27356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453385","2016-02-24","Department for Transport","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the (a) adequacy and (b) effectiveness of the level of co-operation between local authorities, the emergency services and Highways England in connection with the incident on the M6 Motorway between junctions 5 and 6 on Thursday 4 February 2016.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27355","27355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453386","2016-02-23","Department for Transport","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he will issue the draft environmental statement on Phase 2 of High Speed Two (Fradley to Crewe).","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27303","27303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453387","2016-02-23","Department for Transport","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what arrangements are being made for public consultation on the draft environmental statement for Phase Two of High Speed 2 (Fradley to Crewe).","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27304","27304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453388","2016-02-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department has taken to ensure the (a) maintenance of and (b) appropriate location for public weighbridges.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27446","27446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453389","2016-02-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the number of operational public weighbridges was by region in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27445","27445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453390","2016-02-23","Department for Transport","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what reports he has received of an emergency landing in Abuja by British Airways flight BA59 from Heathrow to Cape Town on 29 January 2016.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27441","27441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453391","2016-02-23","Department for Transport","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 15 February 2016 to Question 26148, on roads: investment, which two projects are not progressing on or ahead of schedule; and when those projects are now expected to be completed.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27569","27569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453392","2016-02-23","Department for Transport","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 15 February 2016 to Question 26202, how many items of correspondence his Department has received from the public on the extension of the plug-in grant for motor cycles.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27570","27570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453393","2016-02-23","Department for Transport","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of staffing of railway stations on (a) passenger safety, (b) passenger assurance, (c) safety of women passengers, (d) disabled passengers, (e) revenue protection and (f) passenger assistance.","Biography information for Teresa Pearce","Teresa Pearce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27577","27577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453394","2016-02-23","Department for Transport","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect on passenger safety of removing guards and introducing driver-controlled operation on Northern Rail services.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27578","27578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453395","2016-02-23","Department for Transport","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when each allocated route under the Regional Air Connectivity Fund will be launched.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27555","27555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453396","2016-02-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps the Government is taking to increase the number of BME young people in university education.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27509","27509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453397","2016-02-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many cases were being dealt with by his Department's Child Maintenance Group's Financial Investigation Unit in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27464","27464"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453398","2016-02-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many full-time equivalent staff are employed within his Department's Child Maintenance Group's Financial Investigation Unit.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27465","27465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453399","2016-02-23","HM Treasury","2016-02-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much was paid in (a) child tax credits and (b) child benefit for children within the European Economic Area outside the UK in the most recent period for which figures are available; and what assessment he has made of the effect on the level of such payments of proposed reforms to the payment of those benefits to such children under the terms of the renegotiation proposed by the European Council.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27522","27522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453400","2016-02-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many children live in households affected by the under-occupancy penalty in (a) Merseyside and (b) the UK; and what the average reduction in housing benefit award was for each such household.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27488","27488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453401","2016-02-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of new claims for universal credit were paid within 42 days of a claim being made in the most recent 12 months for which data is available.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27489","27489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453402","2016-02-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of new claims for (a) jobseeker's allowance and (b) employment and support allowance were paid within 10 days of a claim being made in the most recent 12 months for which data is available.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27490","27490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453403","2016-02-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people have been placed in (a) the support group and (b) the work-related activity group with a prognosis statement of (i) three months, (ii) six months, (iii) 12 months, (iv) 18 months, (v) two years and (iv) longer than two years since the introduction of employment and support allowance.","Biography information for Mark Durkan","Mark Durkan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27486","27486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453404","2016-02-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what (a) proportion of vacancies listed on Universal Jobmatch that are within 20 miles of Birkenhead are unfilled and (b) wage levels those vacancies are listed at; and for how long those vacancies have been unfilled.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27539","27539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453405","2016-02-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he plans to reply to the letters from the hon. Member for Birkenhead (a) of 20 November 2015 on school holiday provision and (b) of 16 December 2015 on the All-Party Parliamentary Group on Hunger and Food Poverty's report of December 2014.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27526","27526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453406","2016-02-23","HM Treasury","2016-02-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many foreign nationals living in the UK have been prosecuted for a fraudulent child benefit claim for a child living in the EU.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27517","27517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453407","2016-02-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many applications for a variation from the standard formula have been made under the 2012 statutory child maintenance scheme by (a) non-resident parents and (b) parents with care since the introduction of that scheme.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27370","27370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453408","2016-02-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment he has made of the (a) effectiveness and (b) level of use by single parents of the Jobcentre Plus Flexible Support Fund.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27357","27357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453409","2016-02-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much and what proportion of the Flexible Support Fund was spent on female jobseekers in 2014-15.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27358","27358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453410","2016-02-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of non-resident parents within the live caseload of the (a) Child Support Agency and (b) Child Maintenance Service are self-employed.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27368","27368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453411","2016-02-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many requests were made by his Department's Child Maintenance Group to HM Revenue and Customs for information relating to a non-resident parent's unearned income in each year since the commencement of the 2012 statutory child maintenance scheme.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27369","27369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453412","2016-02-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 16 February 2016 to Question 26169, on social security benefits: disqualification, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that safeguards to prevent the accrual of sanctions are effective.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27280","27280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453413","2016-02-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 16 February 2016 to Question 26169, on social security benefits: disqualification, what the established safeguards are which are in place to prevent the accrual of sanctions.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27281","27281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453414","2016-02-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 29 January 2016 to Question 24142, how much is owed in child maintenance arrears by non-resident parents whose CSA liability has ended as a result of the proactive or reactive CSA case closure process.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27439","27439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453415","2016-02-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 29 January 2016 to Question 24142, how many current CSA cases where there are existing child maintenance arrears have been subject to proactive or reactive case closure.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27440","27440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453416","2016-02-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 29 January 2016 to Question 24142, what the average length of time per case has been that his Department has taken to complete the child maintenance arrears cleansing or validation process following the ending of liability on a CSA case in the current year.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27437","27437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453417","2016-02-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 29 January 2016 to Question 24142, how many closed CSA cases with child maintenance arrears have been referred for arrears cleansing or validation in each month since 1 April 2015.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27438","27438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453418","2016-02-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 29 January 2016 to Question 24142, how many former CSA clients whose liability ended as part of the Department's CSA case closure process arrears have been sent a notice setting out the validated child maintenance arrears balance on their former CSA case in each month since 1 April 2015.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27436","27436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453419","2016-02-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effect of the European Social Fund on levels of unemployment in the UK.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27243","27243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453420","2016-02-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the number of people helped into work through funding provided under the European Social Fund.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27242","27242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453421","2016-02-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, for what reason his Department decided not to renew funding of the extension of the Number 14 bus service to Peel Park.","Biography information for Paul Maynard","Paul Maynard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27204","27204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452326","2016-02-22","Attorney General","2016-02-11","To ask the Attorney General, if he will estimate the costs attributed to the Department for Education by the Government Legal Department in the 2014-15 financial year.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27074","27074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452327","2016-02-22","Attorney General","2016-02-11","To ask the Attorney General, if he will estimate the costs attributed to the Department for Education for cases relating to the Freedom of Information Act 2000 by the Government Legal Department in the 2014-15 financial year.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27075","27075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452328","2016-02-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will make an assessment of the implications for his arms export policy to Saudi Arabia of the legal advice on that matter commissioned by Amnesty International and Saferworld, published in December 2015.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27077","27077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452329","2016-02-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate his Department has made of the potential effect on levels of employment in convenience stores of proposals to devolve Sunday trading restrictions; and what the evidential basis for that estimate was.","Biography information for Derek Thomas","Derek Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27069","27069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452330","2016-02-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect on the profit of convenience stores of proposals to devolve Sunday trading restrictions; and what the evidential basis for that estimate was.","Biography information for Derek Thomas","Derek Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27070","27070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452331","2016-02-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to paragraph 2.9 of Devolving Sunday Trading Rules: government response, published in February 2016, from which organised campaigns the six petitions were received.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27071","27071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452332","2016-02-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what representations were received from (a) USDAW, (b) other trade unions, (c) ACS and (d) other trade and workers' associations in response to the government's consultation, Devolving Sunday trading rules, published on 5 August 2015; and what (i) number and (ii) proportion of those respondents answered (A) yes, (B) no and (C) otherwise to Question 1 in that consultation.","Biography information for Derek Thomas","Derek Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27030","27030"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452333","2016-02-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on levels of exports of changes in the budget of UK Trade and Investment between 2015 and 2020.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27039","27039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452334","2016-02-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, further to the oral contribution of the Minister for Skills of 2 February 2016, Official Report, column 776, whether his Department intends to bring forward amendments relating to check-off and facilities time before the Trade Union Bill reaches Report Stage in the House of Lords.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26990","26990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452335","2016-02-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on UK productivity of the planned introduction of research and development grants.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26996","26996"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452336","2016-02-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of amending trade defence instruments to add a further exemption to the lesser duty rules in cases of social and environmental dumping.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27111","27111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452337","2016-02-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to the publication, entitled The Department for Education review, published in November 2012, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Education on the potential benefits of departmental regional office bases to the delivery of his Department's policies.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27112","27112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452338","2016-02-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will publish the cost-benefit analysis related to his Department's decision to close its Sheffield office.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27113","27113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452339","2016-02-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the benefits to his Department of conducting policy work outside of London.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27114","27114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452340","2016-02-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many people he estimates will (a) relocate to London and (b) leave his Department following the announcement to close his Department's Sheffield office.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27115","27115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452341","2016-02-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, when he expects all final decisions on his Department's estate relating to the implementation of the BIS 2020 strategy to be concluded.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27116","27116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452342","2016-02-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment the Government has made of the effect of the 2012 temporary liberalisation of Sunday trading regulations on its proposals for the devolution of such regulations to local authorities.","Biography information for Derek Thomas","Derek Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27080","27080"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452343","2016-02-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what investment his Department has made in video-conferencing facilities in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27096","27096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452344","2016-02-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent assessment he has made of the extent of anti-competitive practices in the newspaper wholesale market.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27103","27103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452345","2016-02-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of investing in video-conferencing facilities to facilitate split-site working by staff in his Department.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27097","27097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452346","2016-02-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many staff in his Department have relocated (a) out of London and (b) into London in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27101","27101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452347","2016-02-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the effect of the closure of his Department's Sheffield office on the delivery of his Department's policies.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27098","27098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452348","2016-02-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the effect on his Department's policy expertise and experience in the development of (a) higher and (b) further education of the closure of his Department's Sheffield office.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27099","27099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452349","2016-02-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, which offices outside London he does not plan to close under the BIS 2020 strategy.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27100","27100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452350","2016-02-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the apprenticeship levy on the charity and voluntary sectors.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27184","27184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452351","2016-02-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of transferring staff from the UK Commission for Employment and Skills to the Institute for Apprentices to allow continuity of collected labour market information when government funding for that commission ceases in 2016-17.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27185","27185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452352","2016-02-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will put mechanisms in place to ensure that the Institute for Apprentices responds to labour market information when setting funding cap levels for apprenticeships.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27186","27186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452353","2016-02-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 20 October 2015 to Question 12101, for what reasons the Family Test assessment on Sunday trading has not yet been published; when he expects that assessment to be published; and if he will ensure that that assessment is published before consideration of new clauses in the Enterprise Bill [Lords].","Biography information for Mr David Burrowes","Mr David Burrowes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27189","27189"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452354","2016-02-22","HM Treasury","2016-02-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether his Department has conducted an impact assessment on proposals to require small businesses and self-employed people to complete quarterly digital tax returns by 2020.","Biography information for Julian Knight","Julian Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27148","27148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452355","2016-02-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, for what reasons changes to Crown branches take place outside the scope of formal Crown transformation programmes.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27153","27153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452356","2016-02-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the apprenticeship levy on universities.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27181","27181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452357","2016-02-22","Department for International Development","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to encourage UK companies to improve (a) working conditions, (b) safety standards and (c) pay in clothes factories in Bangladesh in their supply chains.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27154","27154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452358","2016-02-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, for what reasons he has decided to withdraw funding from the UK Commission for Employment and Skills; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27196","27196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452359","2016-02-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether he consulted the board of the UK Commission for Employment and Skills prior to his decision to withdraw its funding.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27197","27197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452360","2016-02-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what representations he has received form the governments of Scotland, Wales and Northern Ireland on his decision to withdraw funding from the UK Commission for Employment and Skills.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27198","27198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452361","2016-02-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he plans to take to collect data on trends in the UK labour market after funding is withdrawn from the UK Commission for Employment and Skills.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27199","27199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452362","2016-02-22","Cabinet Office","2016-02-11","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, which charities have used government grants to pay for campaigns in (a) 2014-15 and (b) 2015-16 to date; what the nature of each such campaign was; what estimate he has made of the amount of government funding used for each such campaign; and which such charities have been asked to repay part of their grant on the grounds that such expenditure was outwith the terms and conditions of that grant.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27174","27174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452363","2016-02-22","Cabinet Office","2016-02-11","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 11 February 2016 to Question 26056, when the Data Steering Group last met; who attended that meeting; and if he will publish the (a) minutes of that meeting and (b) programme of work of that group.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27120","27120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452364","2016-02-22","Cabinet Office","2016-02-11","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the average hourly earnings of (a) female, (b) male, (c) full-time and (d) part-time employees of 10 Downing Street were in each of the last five years.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27010","27010"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452365","2016-02-22","HM Treasury","2016-02-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will exempt people from the extra three per cent stamp duty charge on second properties who have moved home because of flooding and are unable to sell their primary home within the 18 month eligibility period for a refund.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26995","26995"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452366","2016-02-22","HM Treasury","2016-02-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the oral evidence by the Chief Secretary to the Treasury to the Scottish Affairs Committee on 3 February 2016, Question 173, what steps he is taking to ensure that proposals for the revised fiscal framework with Scotland will be subject to parliamentary scrutiny.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27035","27035"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452367","2016-02-22","HM Treasury","2016-02-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the implications are for the Government's policy on balanced budgets of the decision of the Scottish Government not to enhance the powers of the Scottish Fiscal Commission; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27036","27036"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452368","2016-02-22","HM Treasury","2016-02-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he has made an assessment of the effect on the public purse of the transfer of licence fee rates tax receipts to devolved city region authorities.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27012","27012"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452369","2016-02-22","HM Treasury","2016-02-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many Financial Conduct Authority staff are (a) seconded to his Department and (b) work in the private office of each Minister of his Department.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27047","27047"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452370","2016-02-22","HM Treasury","2016-02-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the average annual change in tax relief for a person employed via an employment intermediary as a result of the Government's proposed changes to income tax relief for travel and subsistence.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27059","27059"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452371","2016-02-22","HM Treasury","2016-02-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the HM Revenue and Customs policy paper, Income tax: changes to dividend taxation, published in December 2015, if he will publish the data and calculations used as the basis for the statement that 95 per cent of all taxpayers will either gain or be unaffected by changes to dividend taxes.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27151","27151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452372","2016-02-22","HM Treasury","2016-02-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many Seed Enterprise Investment Schemes HM Revenue and Customs have (a) registered and (b) approved in each financial year since 6 April 2012.","Biography information for Craig Mackinlay","Craig Mackinlay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27159","27159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452373","2016-02-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment he has made of the level of compliance with regulations on electrical safety in care homes in England.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27176","27176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452374","2016-02-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how the Transitional Grant in the local government spending review is funded.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27177","27177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452375","2016-02-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether it is his policy that his Department's changes to security of tenure for council tenants will apply to (a) the tenancies of existing tenants and (b) existing tenants when they transfer to a new local authority property; and when he plans that those changes will come into effect.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27128","27128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452376","2016-02-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the deadline is for making an application to the EU Solidarity Fund in relation to the Cumbria floods.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27055","27055"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452377","2016-02-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what discussions he has had with housing associations on flexibility on the mandatory 20 per cent discount for the section 106 starter homes.","Biography information for Paul Scully","Paul Scully","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27041","27041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452378","2016-02-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what discussions he has had with housing associations on reducing or removing Government control over rent setting.","Biography information for Paul Scully","Paul Scully","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27042","27042"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452379","2016-02-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what account his Department has taken of (a) new nuclear developments and (b) tidal lagoon projects in West Cumbria in devolving its Northern Powerhouse agenda.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27048","27048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452380","2016-02-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what discussions he has had with housing associations on flexibility in the time allowed to spend capital receipts from Right to Buy.","Biography information for Paul Scully","Paul Scully","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27040","27040"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452381","2016-02-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the effect of the increase in council tax on living standards in each income decile.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27011","27011"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452382","2016-02-22","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, when he intends to answer the letter to him dated 5 January 2016 with regard to Mr Julian Chapman.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26984","26984"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452383","2016-02-22","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many staff have been seconded to his Department to analyse responses to the BBC Charter Review consultation.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27064","27064"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452384","2016-02-22","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many public libraries have (a) closed and (b) opened in England since May 2010; and how many libraries which were previously run by professionally-qualified staff are now run by volunteers.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27175","27175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452385","2016-02-22","Department for Education","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent discussions her Department has had with social media providers on steps to combat cyber bullying.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27105","27105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452386","2016-02-22","Department for Education","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much her Department has spent on steps to tackle cyber bullying in each of the last three years.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27106","27106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452387","2016-02-22","Department for Education","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of criminalising cyber bullying.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27104","27104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452388","2016-02-22","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what property and land assets his Department holds in Greater Manchester.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27082","27082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452389","2016-02-22","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to ensure that military assistance, support and training provided by the UK to the Kurdistan regional government does not directly or indirectly contribute to or facilitate the commission of violations of international human rights or humanitarian law.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27145","27145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452390","2016-02-22","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the (a) physical state, (b) mass quantity and (c) total radiological quantity in Becquerels was of Defence Nuclear Materials transported or carried by fixed wing aircraft or helicopter in the last five years.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27164","27164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452391","2016-02-22","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many flights were undertaken in fixed wing aircraft or helicopters to transport or carry Defence Nuclear Materials in the last five years.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27165","27165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452392","2016-02-22","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether land at the rear of number 243, Thames Side, Chertsey, or land within a two mile radius of it, has been used by his Department in the last 30 years.","Biography information for Kwasi  Kwarteng","Kwasi Kwarteng","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27168","27168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452393","2016-02-22","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the flight path of any flight in a fixed wing aircraft or helicopter of Defence Nuclear Materials has involved travel over the airspace of Scotland and its territorial seas in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27160","27160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452394","2016-02-22","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the country of origin was of the fixed wing aircraft or helicopter in each flight transporting or carrying Defence Nuclear Materials in the last five years.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27158","27158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452395","2016-02-22","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the country of (a) origin and (b) destination was of each flight in a fixed wing aircraft or helicopter carrying or transporting Defence Nuclear Materials in the last five years.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27157","27157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452396","2016-02-22","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will hold discussions with the Defence Police Federation on the (a) level of morale and (b) terms and conditions of service within the Ministry of Defence Police; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27065","27065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452397","2016-02-22","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he plans to inform the hon. Member for East Worthing and Shoreham of progress made on matters relating to the future of the Victory 1744 discussed in that hon. Member's meeting with the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Defence in September 2015.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27079","27079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452398","2016-02-22","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many properties have been purchased through the Forces Help to Buy Scheme in each month since its inception.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27037","27037"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452399","2016-02-22","Department for Education","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many specialist contractors hired by her Department to advise regional school commissioners there are; and how much her Department spent on such contractors in the last financial year.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27017","27017"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452400","2016-02-22","Department for Education","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what training is provided to specialist contractors hired by her Department to advise regional school commissioners on their responsibilities related to the Civil Service Code.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27018","27018"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452401","2016-02-22","Department for Education","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the daily rate of pay is for specialist contractors hired by her Department to advise regional school commissioners.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27019","27019"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452402","2016-02-22","Department for Education","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which specialist contractors her Department has hired to advise regional school commissioners.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27020","27020"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452403","2016-02-22","Department for Education","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether the specialist contractors hired by her Department to advise regional school commissioners are required to declare any interests relevant to their employment by her Department.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27021","27021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452404","2016-02-22","Department for Education","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many staff in the office of each regional schools commissioners are employed under a contract of employment to another third party.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27024","27024"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452405","2016-02-22","Department for Education","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the implications for her Department's policies on training teachers of the findings of the National Audit Office report, Training new teachers, published in February 2016.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27027","27027"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452406","2016-02-22","Department for Education","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans she has to improve links between schools and elite sports organisations.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27028","27028"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452407","2016-02-22","Department for Education","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of (a) maintained primary schools, (b) maintained secondary schools, (c) primary academies and (d) secondary academies provide at least two hours of physical education per week.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27029","27029"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452408","2016-02-22","Department for Education","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department plans to take to publish performance data for academy chains.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26994","26994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452409","2016-02-22","Department for Education","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what functions are delegated to each specialist contractor hired by her Department to advise regional school commissioners.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27022","27022"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452410","2016-02-22","Department for Education","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will publish the terms and conditions of the contracts of the specialist contractors hired by her Department to advise regional school commissioners.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27023","27023"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452411","2016-02-22","Department for Education","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what duties are placed on regional school commissioners to consult with local authorities on school place planning.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27025","27025"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452412","2016-02-22","Department for Education","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the staffing complement is of the office of each regional schools commissioner; and what the staff grade is of each post in each such office.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27026","27026"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452413","2016-02-22","Department for Education","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate her Department has made of the number of schools which have restricted the school trips which children with autism spectrum disorder can attend in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27052","27052"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452414","2016-02-22","Department for Education","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of pupils who were (a) permanently and (b) temporarily excluded from school were recorded as having mental health conditions in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27053","27053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452415","2016-02-22","Department for Education","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of pupils in Years 10 and 11 were (a) permanently and (b) temporarily excluded from school had autism spectrum disorder in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27054","27054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452416","2016-02-22","Department for Education","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of implications for her policies of the finding in the Fair Admissions Campaign's report, An unholy mess, published in October 2015, that schools which are their own admission authorities are consistently failing to comply with the School Admissions Code.","Biography information for Jeff Smith","Jeff Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27169","27169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452417","2016-02-22","Department for Education","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to her Department's press release, Parents to get greater say in the school admissions process of 25 January 2016, when her Department plans to launch its consultation on proposed revisions to the School Admissions Code.","Biography information for Jeff Smith","Jeff Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27147","27147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452418","2016-02-22","Department for Education","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 11 February 2016 to Question 25804, what the two sites are that are being considered for disposal within the Greater Manchester Combined Authority area.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27178","27178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452419","2016-02-22","Department for Education","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the cost has been of provision of free school meals by region in each of the last three years.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27163","27163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452420","2016-02-22","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, with reference to the Which? 2016 energy satisfaction survey, what steps she is taking to ensure the big six energy companies improve their customer service as well as reduce their prices.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27094","27094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452421","2016-02-22","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what support her Department is providing for the development of (a) technologies for the improved storage of electricity and (b) locally-based smart grids.","Biography information for Alex Chalk","Alex Chalk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27081","27081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452422","2016-02-22","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 21 January 2016 to Question 22354, whether her Department plans to publish the updated detailed projections of the LCF overspend before the Easter recess.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27058","27058"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452423","2016-02-22","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what plans she has to support solar thermal systems in the domestic and non-domestic Renewable Heat Incentive.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27051","27051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452424","2016-02-22","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many jobs are expected to be created in (a) the supply chain and (b) other areas as an indirect result of (i) new nuclear builds in Moorside and (ii) Solway Firth Tidal Lagoon project, West Cumbria.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27050","27050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452425","2016-02-22","HM Treasury","2016-02-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much the climate change levy raised from non-domestic users in London in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26998","26998"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452426","2016-02-22","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many meetings her Department has had with representatives of Tidal Power Ltd on the proposed Solway Firth Tidal Lagoon project.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27049","27049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452427","2016-02-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will take steps to ensure the resilience of agriculture businesses in (a) Copeland and (b) Allerdale to respond to the effects of (i) Storm Desmond and (ii) future severe weather events.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27038","27038"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452428","2016-02-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will publish the names of all insurers which have Flood Re-compatible products available to consumers on the day of launch of the Flood Re-scheme before that day.","Biography information for Nigel Adams","Nigel Adams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27046","27046"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452429","2016-02-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what powers she intends to extend to farmers in relation to the dredging of watercourses on their land.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27063","27063"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452430","2016-02-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to her comments at the Oxford Farming Conference on 6 January 2016 on additional powers to internal drainage boards, what plans she has to give local authorities a role in the maintenance of local watercourses.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27067","27067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452431","2016-02-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to her comments at the Oxford Farming conference on 6 January 2016 on decentralising decision-making, what steps she plans to take to ensure funding to tackle flooding and the maintenance of flood defences is allocated fairly and transparently to local groups.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27066","27066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452432","2016-02-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many licenses issued under the Welfare of Wild Animals in Travelling Circuses (England) Regulations 2012 are currently in force; and how many applications for such licenses for what reasons have been (a) granted, (b) refused, (c) suspended and (d) revoked in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27093","27093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452433","2016-02-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 11 February 2016 to Question 26276, on recycling in Christchurch, if she will place in the Library a copy of the assessment including the cost-benefit analysis.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27122","27122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452434","2016-02-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking in cooperation with his international counterparts to pursue criminal responsibility of the leadership of the Democratic People's Republic of Korea.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27078","27078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452435","2016-02-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the application of the rule of law in the Maldives.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27091","27091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452436","2016-02-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to provide financial support to Jordan to tackle the humanitarian crisis in the Middle East.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27092","27092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452437","2016-02-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what diplomatic progress has been made by the international community in delivering peace in Syria.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27083","27083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452438","2016-02-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effect of the UK's relationship with Saudi Arabia on human rights in that country.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27084","27084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452439","2016-02-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what evidence from independent bodies he has seen that Saudi Arabia is complying with international humanitarian law in the Yemen conflict.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27085","27085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452440","2016-02-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what diplomatic progress he has made in delivering a peaceful transition in Libya.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27086","27086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452441","2016-02-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of whether Daesh are committing genocide in Syria.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27087","27087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452442","2016-02-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he supports the aims of the Arms Trade Treaty.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27088","27088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452443","2016-02-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to support the global abolition of the death penalty.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27089","27089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452444","2016-02-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what diplomatic steps he is taking to tackle the refugee crisis on the Turkish-Syrian border.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27090","27090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452445","2016-02-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 11 February 2016 to Question 26339, what representations he is making to the Egyptian government on an independent inquiry being carried out into the death of Giulio Regeni.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27188","27188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452446","2016-02-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the government of North Korea on the arrest of Mr Otto Frederick Warmbier, and the detention of Hyeon Soo Lim and Kim Dong Chul.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27110","27110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452447","2016-02-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the political situation in Moldova on stability and security in that region.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27109","27109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452448","2016-02-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the extent of funding from Iran for (a) Hezbollah and (b) Hamas; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Mrs Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27183","27183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452449","2016-02-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions the Government has had with the Indonesian government on the situation of Ahmadis in Bangka, Indonesia.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27152","27152"
