"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/971511","2018-09-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-09-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what information his Department holds on the socio-economic background of people appointed to senior positions in his Department in the last five years.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 172620","172620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/971512","2018-09-12","Ministry of Defence","2018-09-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what information his Department holds on the socio-economic background of people appointed to senior positions in his Department in the last five years.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 172621","172621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/971513","2018-09-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information his Department holds on the socio-economic background of people appointed to senior positions in his Department in the last five years.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 172622","172622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/971514","2018-09-12","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-09-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what information his Department holds on the socio-economic background of people appointed to senior positions in his Department.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 172623","172623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/971515","2018-09-12","Home Office","2018-09-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what information his Department holds on the socio-economic background of people appointed to senior positions in his Department in the last five years.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 172624","172624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/971516","2018-09-12","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-09-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what information his Department holds on the socio-economic background of people appointed to senior positions in his Department in the last five years.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 172625","172625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/971517","2018-09-13","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many patients were affected by the failure of the Lorenzo software system at East and North Herts Hospital NHS Trust; and whether his Department is aware of any harm caused to patients by that failure.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 172626","172626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/971518","2018-09-13","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, which NHS England trusts use the Lorenzo software system.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 172627","172627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/971519","2018-09-13","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what his policy is for informing Parliament of serious incidents in the NHS.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 172628","172628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/971520","2018-09-13","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the cost to the NHS of problems with the Lorenzo software system at East and North Herts Hospital NHS Trust.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 172629","172629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/971521","2018-09-12","Treasury","2018-09-10","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many staff are employed by HMRC in East Kilbride.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 172630","172630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/971522","2018-09-12","Treasury","2018-09-10","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many staff HMRC plans to employ in East Kilbride when the opening of phase one of its Glasgow regional centre is complete.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 172631","172631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/971523","2018-09-12","Treasury","2018-09-10","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many staff HMRC plans to employ in its Glasgow regional centre when it withdraws from East Kilbride in 2026.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 172632","172632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/971524","2018-09-12","Treasury","2018-09-10","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many additional EU-related posts HMRC will require by March 2019 in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 172633","172633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/971525","2018-09-12","Treasury","2018-09-10","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many of the additional EU-related posts that HMRC will require by March 2019 in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal will be located in Scotland.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 172634","172634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/971526","2018-09-12","Treasury","2018-09-10","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the average cost per call is of opening HMRC contact centres (a) Monday to Friday and (b) on a (i) Saturday and (ii) Sunday.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 172635","172635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/971527","2018-09-12","Treasury","2018-09-10","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many HMRC workers are aged (a) under 25, (b) 25 to 39, (c) 40 to 49 and (d) 50 and over.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 172636","172636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/971528","2018-09-12","Treasury","2018-09-10","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the overall (a) cost and (b) projected staffing numbers of the HMRC Building Our Future programme changed following the decision to retain the Ipswich office of HMRC as a permanent specialist location after 2026.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 172637","172637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972274","2018-09-13","Home Office","2018-09-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what representations his Department received before 2018 on the eligibility for UK passports of Caribbean-born UK residents.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 906876","906876"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969434","2018-09-11","Ministry of Defence","2018-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will carry out a review of whether there is sufficient and quality accommodation available to service personnel on the defence estates.","Biography information for Kirstene Hair","Kirstene Hair","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171738","171738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969435","2018-09-12","Department for Education","2018-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what curriculum requirements there are in (a) primary and (b) secondary schools to teach mental health.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171648","171648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969436","2018-09-12","Department for Education","2018-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children are home-schooled in (a) Coventry South constituency, (b) Coventry, (c) the West Midlands and (d) England.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171649","171649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969437","2018-09-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate she has made of the number of vacancies filled as a result of the Find a Job website since May 2018.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171650","171650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969438","2018-09-12","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions he has held with (a) representatives of the Football Association and (b) Cabinet colleagues on an (i) English or (ii) British bid to host the 2030 World Cup.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171651","171651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969439","2018-09-11","Department for Education","2018-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many students in (a) Coventry South constituency, (b) the West Midlands and (c) England attend single-sex secondary schools.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171652","171652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969440","2018-09-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the research conducted by the Health Service Journal, published on 8 May 2018, if he will make an estimate on the number of patients at risk of developing a venous thromboembolism as a result of the decline in assessments being undertaken.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171670","171670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969441","2018-09-12","Ministry of Justice","2018-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate his Department has made of the reduction in the number of magistrates in (a) England and Wales and (b) Northumbria in the last three years.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171671","171671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969442","2018-09-11","Department for International Development","2018-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department has taken to support the Indian Government in its response to the flooding in Kerala state.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171653","171653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969443","2018-09-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with (a) Cabinet colleagues and (b) his Indian counterpart on the flooding in Kerala state.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171654","171654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969444","2018-09-11","Department for Education","2018-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the accuracy of examination marking for (a) GCSEs, (b) BTECs and (c) A-Levels in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171655","171655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969445","2018-09-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Education on the number of people (a) applying for and (b) taking up a place on the Step Up to Social Work programme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171656","171656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969446","2018-09-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to support universities to recruit students to Social Work programmes; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171657","171657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969447","2018-09-12","Home Office","2018-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the document Crime in England and Wales: Police Force Area Data Tables, published by the Office for National Statistics on 19 July 2018, what assessment his Department has made of the reason for the increase in the level of reported crime in Northumbria between April 2017 and March 2018; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171672","171672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969448","2018-09-12","Home Office","2018-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, for what reason his Department has informed applicants for priority visas that the 30-day processing time would be extended to up to 12 weeks.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171665","171665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969449","2018-09-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will make it his policy to introduce an exemption for charities from authorised supply capacity charges relating to smart meters.","Biography information for Bill Grant","Bill Grant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171723","171723"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969450","2018-09-11","Ministry of Defence","2018-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the operations of International Military Services Ltd are fully subject to Parliamentary scrutiny.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171705","171705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969451","2018-09-11","Ministry of Defence","2018-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, for what reasons the audited accounts for the Government-owned International Military Services Ltd are not laid before Parliament.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171706","171706"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969452","2018-09-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the document, Stepping forward to 2020/21: The mental health workforce plan for England, published by the NHS in July 2017, how many of the additional 19,000 mental health staff to be recruited by 2020 were employed by July 2018.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171694","171694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969453","2018-09-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many (a) posts and (b) vacancies were there in mental health NHS trusts in England in the most recent month for which data is available.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171695","171695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969454","2018-09-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the number of mental health staff that have left the NHS since June 2017.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171696","171696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969455","2018-09-12","Department for Education","2018-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many (a) nursing associates and (b) apprentice nurses are in training.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171673","171673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969456","2018-09-12","Department for Education","2018-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 2 May 2018 to Question 138485, on Education Fellowship Trustm, whether (a) Pembroke Park Primary in Wiltshire and (b) Wrenn Academy in Northamptonshire have been re-brokered.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171674","171674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969457","2018-09-11","Ministry of Justice","2018-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, on what dates (a) he and (b) Ministers of his Department have visited HMP Berwyn since February 2017.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171707","171707"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969458","2018-09-11","Ministry of Justice","2018-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether he made an assessment of the potential merits of the recommendations of the Report of the Zahid Mubarek inquiry, published in June 2006, when designing HMP Berwyn.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171708","171708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969459","2018-09-11","Ministry of Justice","2018-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether his Department has plans to implement the recommendations of the Report of the Zahid Mubarek inquiry, published in June 2006.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171709","171709"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969460","2018-09-11","Ministry of Justice","2018-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether his Department has plans to implement the recommendations of the Report of the Zahid Mubarek inquiry, published in June 2006, in the design of new prisons.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171710","171710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969461","2018-09-11","Ministry of Justice","2018-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what representations his Department has received from The Honourable Mr Justice Keith on the recommendations of the Report of the Zahid Mubarek inquiry, published in June 2006.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171711","171711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969462","2018-09-11","Ministry of Justice","2018-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the timeframe is for HMP Berwyn to operate at full capacity.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171712","171712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969463","2018-09-11","Ministry of Justice","2018-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department is taken to ensure that HMP Berwyn operates at full capacity.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171713","171713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969464","2018-09-11","Ministry of Justice","2018-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what contingency plans his Department has made in the event that HMP Berwyn does not operate at full capacity.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171714","171714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969465","2018-09-11","Ministry of Justice","2018-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of converting HMP Berwyn to a single-occupancy cell prison in the event that the prison not reach full capacity.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171715","171715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969466","2018-09-11","Ministry of Justice","2018-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) double cells and (b) single cells were occupied at HMP Berwyn at 31 July 2018.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171716","171716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969467","2018-09-11","Ministry of Justice","2018-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many unoccupied single cells there were HMP Berwyn at 31 July 2018.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171717","171717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969468","2018-09-11","Ministry of Justice","2018-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether it is the policy of HMP Berwyn to require inmates to share cells only in the event that a single cell is unavailable.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171718","171718"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969469","2018-09-11","Ministry of Justice","2018-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what purposeful activities have been made available to inmates at HMP Berwyn since February 2017.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171719","171719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969470","2018-09-11","Ministry of Justice","2018-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will publish the number of staff employed at each pay band at HMP Berwyn since February 2017.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171720","171720"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969471","2018-09-11","Department for Transport","2018-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions he has had with Network Rail on the use of glyphosate along tracks after tree felling.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171725","171725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969472","2018-09-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 4 January 2018 to Question 147424 on Radiotherapy, when the postcode-level dataset which will enable the calculation of travel times to radiotherapy centres will be published.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171667","171667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969473","2018-09-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when he plans to publish the Government response to the consultation on allocating funds to radiotherapy services which closed on 24 January 2018.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171668","171668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969474","2018-09-11","Ministry of Defence","2018-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent assessment he has made of the security situation in Idlib, and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171721","171721"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969475","2018-09-11","Ministry of Defence","2018-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent discussions he has had with (a) the US envoy for Syria and (b) his American counterpart on whether there is evidence that Syrian Government forces are preparing a chemical weapons attack.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171722","171722"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969476","2018-09-11","Ministry of Defence","2018-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many civil servants there are at each grade in his Department.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171666","171666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969477","2018-09-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the oral contribution of the Parliamentary Under Secretary of State for Health and Social Care of 10 January 2018, Official Report, column 146WH, when he plans to (a) publish the findings of the consultation on making radiotherapy services more accessible and (b) assess data on travel times for such therapy.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171669","171669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969478","2018-09-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, for what reasons the Government extended its deadline for announcing whether to launch an independent judge-led inquiry into UK involvement in torture and rendition.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171733","171733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969479","2018-09-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when the Government plans to announce whether to launch an independent judge-led inquiry into UK involvement in torture and rendition.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171734","171734"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969480","2018-09-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, who will take the final decision on launching an independent judge-led inquiry into UK involvement in torture and rendition.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171735","171735"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969481","2018-09-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what factors the Government will take into account in its decision on whether to launch an independent judge-led inquiry into UK involvement in torture and rendition.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171736","171736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969482","2018-09-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions (a) he and (b) Ministers of his Department have had with international counterparts on whether to launch an independent judge-led inquiry into UK involvement in torture and rendition.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171737","171737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969483","2018-09-11","Department for International Development","2018-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much funding her Department plans to provide for the Global Financing Facility (GFF) for Every Woman Every Child initiative at the GFF replenishment conference in Autumn 2018.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171703","171703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969484","2018-09-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 30 July 2018 to Question 166515, what estimate she has made of the proportion of universal credit claims closed and not paid that relate to claimants with disabilities or long-term health conditions.","Biography information for Marsha De Cordova","Marsha De Cordova","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171739","171739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969485","2018-09-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 30 July 2018 to Question 166515, what steps she is taking to reduce the proportion of claims closed and not paid when managed migration commences.","Biography information for Marsha De Cordova","Marsha De Cordova","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171740","171740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969486","2018-09-12","Home Office","2018-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what criteria will be used to determine destitution in the renewed asylum accommodation contract.","Biography information for Mr Paul Sweeney","Mr Paul Sweeney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171726","171726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969487","2018-09-12","Home Office","2018-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps his Department is taking to (a) monitor and (b) enforce the provisions in the asylum accommodation contract that people who would otherwise be destitute will continue to be housed.","Biography information for Mr Paul Sweeney","Mr Paul Sweeney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171727","171727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969488","2018-09-12","Cabinet Office","2018-09-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 6 September 2018 to Question 169500 on Electoral Register, whether the Government plans to collate the information from local Electoral Registration Officers at the local authority level to evaluate the potential effect of the legislative changes on the level of anonymous voter registration.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171697","171697"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969489","2018-09-12","Home Office","2018-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many asylum seekers have had their housing provision removed before their asylum process was fully completed including the appeals process since 2012.","Biography information for Mr Paul Sweeney","Mr Paul Sweeney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171728","171728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969490","2018-09-12","Department for Transport","2018-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he plans to publish the responses to the public consultation, Proposals for the creation of a Major Road Network, published in December 2017.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171659","171659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969491","2018-09-12","Department for Transport","2018-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he has plans to include the A68 in the major roads network.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171660","171660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969492","2018-09-11","Treasury","2018-09-07","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the consultation, Cash and digital payments in the new economy, published in December 2017, whether his Department has made an assessment of the effect of the increase in cashless and electronic payments on homeless people.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171701","171701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969493","2018-09-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the effect on small businesses of proposed mandatory calorie counts on all restaurant and takeaway menus.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171702","171702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969494","2018-09-12","Department for Transport","2018-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he has plans to change the criteria for road improvement funding.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171661","171661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969495","2018-09-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much his Department paid the company Odgers Berndtson for recruitment services in each of the last eight years.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171662","171662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969496","2018-09-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many people have been (a) prosecuted and (b) convicted for offences related to the non-disclosure of Person of Significant Control of UK companies; and what the total amount of fines imposed was for such offences for the most recent period for which data is available.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171645","171645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969497","2018-09-11","Home Office","2018-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many unexplained wealth orders are in force; and what the total value of the assets covered by those orders is.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171646","171646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969498","2018-09-11","Home Office","2018-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will publish a list of the people, companies or other entities on whom unexplained wealth orders have been served; and if he will list the assets concerned for each of those orders.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171647","171647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969499","2018-09-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the application process is for the role of Chair of a Sustainability and Transformation Partnership.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171663","171663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969500","2018-09-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the remuneration is for the Chair of Humber, Coast and Vale Sustainability and Transformation Partnership.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171664","171664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969501","2018-09-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to ensure that the UK has more control of its fishing waters after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Bill Grant","Bill Grant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171724","171724"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969502","2018-09-11","Treasury","2018-09-07","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what fiscal steps he is taking to help people move on from their first property and move up the housing ladder.","Biography information for Mr Ranil Jayawardena","Mr Ranil Jayawardena","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171698","171698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969503","2018-09-11","Treasury","2018-09-07","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make it his policy to increase the marriage allowance.","Biography information for Mr Ranil Jayawardena","Mr Ranil Jayawardena","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171699","171699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969504","2018-09-11","Department for International Trade","2018-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Transport on the potential benefits for future UK trade of improved integration between road and rail infrastructure.","Biography information for Mr Ranil Jayawardena","Mr Ranil Jayawardena","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171700","171700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969505","2018-09-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the complaints procedures are for clinical commissioning groups (CCGs); how CCGs are held accountable; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171658","171658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969506","2018-09-12","Treasury","2018-09-07","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many time to pay arrangements have been agreed between HMRC and (a) businesses and (b) individuals in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171729","171729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969507","2018-09-11","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on professional football of the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171675","171675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969508","2018-09-11","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what recent discussions he has had and with whom on the proposed sale of Wembley Stadium.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171676","171676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969509","2018-09-11","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of grass roots football facilities in (a) England and (b) Ellesmere Port and Neston constituency.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171677","171677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969510","2018-09-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will estimate how much water was lost due to leaks in each of the last ten years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171678","171678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969511","2018-09-11","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what his policy is on devolution in the Cheshire West and Chester local authority area.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171679","171679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969512","2018-09-11","Department for Transport","2018-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many road traffic accidents there were on the M56 between junctions 12 and 14 in the last three years; and what steps his Department is taking to reduce accidents on that stretch of road.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171680","171680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969513","2018-09-11","Department for Education","2018-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many complaints have been made to the Education Funding Agency relating to (a) academies and (b) free schools in the last three years; and what proportion of such complaints have been upheld.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171681","171681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969514","2018-09-11","Department for Education","2018-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the value is of the total assets held by (a) academies and (b) free schools; and what proportion of such assets were formerly held by public bodies.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171682","171682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969515","2018-09-11","House of Commons Commission","2018-09-07","To ask the right hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington, representing the House of Commons Commission, how many personal injury claims were made relating to incidents on the parliamentary estate in each of the last ten years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171683","171683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969516","2018-09-11","Cabinet Office","2018-09-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many personal injury claims were made relating to incidents in Government-owned buildings in each of the last ten years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171684","171684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969517","2018-09-11","Department for Transport","2018-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many vehicles have been procured for the Government Car Service since 2015; and what the country of origin is of each such vehicle.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171685","171685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969518","2018-09-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many members of staff aged under 18 have been employed by NHS 111 in each of the last 12 months for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171686","171686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969519","2018-09-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what proportion of NHS 111 staff are clinically trained.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171687","171687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969520","2018-09-11","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what recent representations he has made to Premier League football clubs on the level of ticket prices and the availability of concessionary ticket rates for young people.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171688","171688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969521","2018-09-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many cases of sepsis there were in each region of England in each of the last ten years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171689","171689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969522","2018-09-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to reduce rates of hospital-acquired infections.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171690","171690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969523","2018-09-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department plans to take to help ensure that opportunities for diagnosis and intervention in sepsis are detected early.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171691","171691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969524","2018-09-11","Prime Minister","2018-09-07","To ask the Prime Minister, what recent steps she has taken to reduce the number of peers.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171692","171692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969525","2018-09-11","Department for Transport","2018-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the number of reported personal injury road accidents in each category of severity on the M56 between junctions 12 and 14 in each month of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171693","171693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969526","2018-09-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what comparative assessment he has made of the rates of recovery from heroin addiction through methadone in the UK and other countries.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171730","171730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969527","2018-09-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the rate of methadone usage in the last three years.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171731","171731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969528","2018-09-12","Home Office","2018-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether his Department has paid damages under its hostile environment immigration policy on condition that the recipient did not publicise that payment since October 2010.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171732","171732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969529","2018-09-12","Department for International Development","2018-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 13 September 2017 to Question 8642, for what reasons her Department concluded that the IMPACT-SE report on the Palestinian Elementary School Curriculum 2016-17 was not objective in its findings.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171640","171640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969530","2018-09-12","Department for International Development","2018-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the Palestinian Authority's school curriculum compliance with the Memorandum of Understanding signed between her Department and the Palestinian Authority.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171641","171641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969531","2018-09-11","Department for International Development","2018-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether the methodologies of the review of the Palestinian Authority's curriculum will include compliance with (a) Articles 1, 4.2 and 5 of the Declaration of principles on tolerance proclaimed and signed by the member states of UNESCO on 16 November 1995, (b) Principles 1, 2, 3, 4 and 5 of the UN Declaration on the promotion among youth of the ideals of peace, mutual respect and understanding between peoples, signed in 1965, and (c) Articles 9 and 18 of the integrated framework for action on education for peace, human rights and democracy, approved by the general conference of UNESCO at the 28th session in Paris in November 1995.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171642","171642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969532","2018-09-11","Department for International Development","2018-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether the review of the Palestinian Authority's curriculum has been commissioned.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171643","171643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969533","2018-09-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the effect of geo-blocking on (a) UK businesses and (b) digital subscribers and consumers in the event of the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171644","171644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969534","2018-09-11","Department for International Development","2018-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, when she plans to launch the UK-aid food trade and resilience programme.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171704","171704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968430","2018-09-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps she is taking to improve the safety standard of inflatables at funfairs.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170953","170953"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968956","2018-09-06","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-09-06","What recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of the level of funding in relation to programming for the nations of the UK.","Biography information for Carol Monaghan","Carol Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 906663","906663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968957","2018-09-06","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-09-06","What steps his Department is taking to tackle gambling-related harm.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 906665","906665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968958","2018-09-06","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-09-06","What plans he has to discuss the establishment of a youth full-time social action pilot programme with delivery organisations.","Biography information for Michael Tomlinson","Michael Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 906667","906667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968959","2018-09-06","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-09-06","Whether he plans to visit Wakefield in the next 12 months; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 906668","906668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968960","2018-09-06","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-09-06","What steps his Department is taking to encourage the public sector to commission goods and services from social enterprises.","Biography information for Gareth Snell","Gareth Snell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 906669","906669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969023","2018-09-10","Home Office","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether evidence provided to substantiate immigration applications in the UK is (a) digitally stored and (b) automatically allocated to the correct application and caseworker.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171376","171376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969024","2018-09-10","Department for International Development","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, with reference to the press release, New UK aid package will stop dirty money in its tracks and recover millions of pounds for developing countries, published by the Government on 30 August 2018,  whether the programme will include tackling tax havens.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171377","171377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969025","2018-09-10","Department for International Development","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of access to Saada by humanitarian relief organisations after the military operations in that area in August 2018.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171378","171378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969026","2018-09-10","Department for International Development","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, with reference to the press release, New UK aid package to meet immediate needs of Palestinians through UN Relief and Works Agency, published on 4 September 2018, whether she plans to allocate additional funding for Palestinian refugees as a result of the US administration's decision to cut its funding to the UNRWA.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171379","171379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969027","2018-09-10","Department for Transport","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 7 June 2018 to Question 149570 on Thameslink Industry Readiness Board, whether anybody not associated with the parties represented at the Thameslink Industry Readiness Board has attended any meetings of that Board.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171380","171380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969028","2018-09-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people flowed off Employment and Support Allowance whose date of death was at the same time, and who had a Work Capability Assessment decision of fit for work between March 2014 and February 2017.","Biography information for Marsha De Cordova","Marsha De Cordova","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171381","171381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969029","2018-09-10","Treasury","2018-09-06","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether an assessment has been made of the potential effect on family incomes of the closure to new entrants of the childcare voucher scheme.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171382","171382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969030","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent steps the Government has taken to ensure that (a) negotiations between Vertex Pharmaceuticals and NHS England on access to Orkambi for people with cystic fibrosis proceed without further delay and (b) an agreement is reached between the two parties.","Biography information for Luke Hall","Luke Hall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171383","171383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969031","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the oral contribution of the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Health and Social Care of 17 July 2018, Official Report, column 384, what progress the Government has made on access to Orkambi in England since Vertex Pharmaceuticals was called on to accept NHS Englands proposal to make that drug available to people with cystic fibrosis.","Biography information for Luke Hall","Luke Hall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171384","171384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969032","2018-09-10","Department for Education","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 4 September 2018 to Question 168014 on Academies, whether academy schools that are in deficiency can be considered for education authority oversight.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171337","171337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969033","2018-09-11","Prime Minister","2018-09-06","To ask the Prime Minister, when she plans to respond to the letter sent by the Hon. Member for Wrexham on 21 February 2018 reference ZA21109 on modern slavery.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171319","171319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969034","2018-09-11","Department for Transport","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much funding his Department has allocated from the public purse to roads and highways in (a) Merseyside and (b) Surrey in each of the last seven years.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171295","171295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969035","2018-09-11","Home Office","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps his Department is taking to ensure the adequacy of (a) financial and (b) other support to Merseyside Fire Service.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171296","171296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969036","2018-09-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the take-up rate for cervical screening  was in (a) the North West and (b) Wallasey constituency in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171297","171297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969037","2018-09-11","Home Office","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the provision of (a) tampons and (b) sanitary towels for women in custody at each police station in each constabulary in theNorth West.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171298","171298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969038","2018-09-11","Department for Education","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of secondary schools in (a) Merseyside and (b) London were rated (a) good or (b) outstanding in the last three years.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171299","171299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969039","2018-09-10","Department for Education","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate his Department has made of the number of school places in the London Borough of Barnet.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171363","171363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969040","2018-09-10","Women and Equalities","2018-09-06","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what progress the Government has made on the implementation of section 36 of the Equality Act 2010.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171364","171364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969041","2018-09-10","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that public service broadcasters remain impartial in the coverage of politics.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171365","171365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969042","2018-09-10","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he plans to take in response to the high court ruling that judged Northamptonshire's bid to close 21 libraries as unlawful.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171366","171366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969043","2018-09-10","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what guidance his Department has issued to local authorities on the criteria for a comprehensive and efficient library service.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171367","171367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969044","2018-09-10","Home Office","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps he is taking to ensure that police forces enforce speed limits consistently in all areas of the UK.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171368","171368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969045","2018-09-10","Home Office","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment his Department has made of trends in the level of crime in London in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171369","171369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969046","2018-09-10","Department for Transport","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of increasing the speed limit to 80 miles per hour on the motorway network.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171370","171370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969047","2018-09-10","Treasury","2018-09-06","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what progress has been made on the review of business rates.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171371","171371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969048","2018-09-10","Treasury","2018-09-06","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of the level of coverage of free to use automated transaction machines throughout the UK.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171372","171372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969049","2018-09-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will take steps to replace the living wage and national minimum wage with one minimum wage.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171373","171373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969050","2018-09-10","Treasury","2018-09-06","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will take steps to use the Consumer Prices Index in preference to RPI as a measurement in all government transactions, negotiations and agreements.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171374","171374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969051","2018-09-10","Treasury","2018-09-06","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of a cash-less economy on taxation revenues.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171375","171375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969052","2018-09-10","Home Office","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the timescale and expected completion date are for his Departments work to introduce statutory guidance under section 55A of the Firearms Act 1968.","Biography information for Victoria Prentis","Victoria Prentis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171385","171385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969053","2018-09-10","Home Office","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether his Department plans for its guidance relating to firearms licensing medical procedures to be made statutory under section 55A of the Firearms Act 1968.","Biography information for Victoria Prentis","Victoria Prentis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171386","171386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969054","2018-09-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the timeframe is for the publication of the independent review of the Financial Reporting Council.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171387","171387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969055","2018-09-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, who will be representing the UK at the eighth Conference of the Parties to the World Health Organisation Framework Convention on tobacco control in October 2018.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171320","171320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969056","2018-09-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of the UK's representation at the eighth conference of the parties to the World Health Organisation framework convention on tobacco control in October 2018.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171321","171321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969057","2018-09-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many young people (a) have received support through the Youth Obligation and (b) are currently participating in that programme.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171272","171272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969058","2018-09-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the strategic objectives of his departmental delegation will be at the eighth conference of the parties to the World Health Organisation framework convention on tobacco control in October 2018.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171322","171322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969059","2018-09-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether she plans to publish data on the outcomes for those receiving support through the Youth Obligation; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171273","171273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969060","2018-09-10","Treasury","2018-09-06","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many households in each Welsh constituency are eligible for tax-free childcare; how many such households have (a) applied and (b) been accepted on to that scheme since its introduction; and how many such households have received tax-free childcare in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171388","171388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969061","2018-09-11","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether he plans to ensure that all investigations into deaths of homeless people involve an assessment of whether the death could have been prevented.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171389","171389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969062","2018-09-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what progress his Department has made in tendering for the grant scheme relating to external stakeholder support for the tobacco control plan.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171323","171323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969063","2018-09-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many young people who have received support through the Youth Obligation have subsequently gone on to an apprenticeship.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171274","171274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969064","2018-09-11","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps the Government plans to take to support legacy giving to raise more funds for good causes.","Biography information for Susan Elan Jones","Susan Elan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171335","171335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969065","2018-09-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps she is taking to ensure that claimants do not lose their financial support if they are unable to make a claim for Universal Credit in time during managed migration.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171275","171275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969066","2018-09-11","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to his August 2018 Civil Society Strategy, what plans the Government has to support legacy giving.","Biography information for Susan Elan Jones","Susan Elan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171336","171336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969067","2018-09-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will exempt people with Alzheimers and dementia from charges for the replacement of lost hearing aids.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171338","171338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969068","2018-09-11","Northern Ireland Office","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what steps she is taking to ensure that in the absence of the Northern Ireland Executive NHS staff in Northern Ireland receive pay awards equivalent to those of NHS staff in other constituent parts of the UK; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171316","171316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969069","2018-09-11","Northern Ireland Office","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, for what reasons the salaries of MLAs have not been reduced; and what the timescale is for reducing those salaries.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171317","171317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969070","2018-09-10","Treasury","2018-09-06","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people earned (a) less than 5,000 and (b) between (i) 5,000 and 10,000, (ii) 10,000 and 15,000, (iii) 15,000 and 20,000, (iv) 20,000 and 25,000, (v) 25,000 and 30,000, (vi) 30,000 and 35,000, (vii) 35,000 and 40,000, (viii) 40,000 and 45,000, (ix) 45,000 and 50,000, (x) 50,000 and 55,000 and (xi) 55,000 and 60,000 in each of the last 10 years; and how much in (A) income tax; and (B) national insurance contributions individuals in each of those earnings bands paid in each of those years.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171390","171390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969071","2018-09-10","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, if he will hold discussions with the National Farmers' Union on the supply of agricultural workers during the implementation period.","Biography information for Mark Pritchard","Mark Pritchard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171325","171325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969072","2018-09-10","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, if he will hold discussions with car manufacturers in the West Midlands on frictionless car manufacturing supply chains.","Biography information for Mark Pritchard","Mark Pritchard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171326","171326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969073","2018-09-10","Ministry of Defence","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what records his Department makes of mental health conditions experienced by (a) serving armed forces personnel and (b) veterans.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171391","171391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969074","2018-09-10","Ministry of Defence","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the number of (a) serving armed forces personnel and (b) veterans who are currently experiencing mental health problems.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171392","171392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969075","2018-09-10","Department for Transport","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make an assessment of the effectiveness of the Highways England road maintenance plan for the M54.","Biography information for Mark Pritchard","Mark Pritchard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171327","171327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969076","2018-09-10","Department for Transport","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will hold discussions with Arriva buses to ensure that its statutory obligations relating to access to public transport in rural areas are upheld.","Biography information for Mark Pritchard","Mark Pritchard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171328","171328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969077","2018-09-10","Ministry of Defence","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what his plans are for the future of the RAF Cosford Airshow; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mark Pritchard","Mark Pritchard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171329","171329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969078","2018-09-10","Ministry of Defence","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what (a) number and (b) proportion of service personnel who leave the armed forces secure new employment (i) within one month, (ii) between one month and two months, (iii) between two months and three months, (iv) between three months and six months, (v) between six months and one year and (vi) one year after leaving the armed forces.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171393","171393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969079","2018-09-10","Ministry of Defence","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what his plans are for the future of RAF Cosford.","Biography information for Mark Pritchard","Mark Pritchard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171330","171330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969080","2018-09-10","Ministry of Defence","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the number of Ministry of Defence personnel deployed in Yemen; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mark Pritchard","Mark Pritchard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171331","171331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969081","2018-09-10","Ministry of Defence","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the (a) number and (b) proportion of service personnel who leave the armed forces each year who (i) set up their own business and (ii) become self-employed.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171394","171394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969082","2018-09-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how much each of the Big Six energy companies allocated to the Energy Company Obligation in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171280","171280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969083","2018-09-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the effect of levels of funding on the ability of the NHS to increase access to radiotherapy.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171339","171339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969084","2018-09-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how his Department plans to allocate the two million pounds for assessing options for horizontal spaceports in the UK.","Biography information for Bill Grant","Bill Grant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171395","171395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969085","2018-09-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will list the energy companies that have contributed to the Energy Company Obligation (ECO) in each of the last five years; and how much has been allocated to the ECO by each of those companies.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171281","171281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969086","2018-09-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how NHS England monitors clinical commissionng groups' cancer treatment performance in respect of access to advanced radiotherapy; and what steps NHS England takes to address instances of poor performance.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171340","171340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969087","2018-09-11","Ministry of Justice","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the prison officer to prisoner ratio is for prisons outsourced to the private sector.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171341","171341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969088","2018-09-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether her Department has carried out an impact assessment on the effect of the change to the state pension age for women born in the 1950s on their families and dependents.","Biography information for Bill Grant","Bill Grant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171396","171396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969089","2018-09-10","Ministry of Justice","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps is he taking to improve access to the civil courts for people with limited financial means.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171342","171342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969090","2018-09-10","Ministry of Justice","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will assess the potential merits of alternative dispute resolution mechanisms in relation to inheritance estate dispute cases in the civil court.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171343","171343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969091","2018-09-10","Ministry of Justice","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of (a) six month and (b) 12 month prison sentences on reducing reoffending.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171344","171344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969092","2018-09-10","Ministry of Justice","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the reoffending rate for people receiving a prison sentence of less than 12 months in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171345","171345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969093","2018-09-10","Department for Transport","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he plans to meet representatives of Heathrow Airport to discuss the provision of additional flights to Scotland.","Biography information for Bill Grant","Bill Grant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171397","171397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969094","2018-09-10","Department for Transport","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will bring forward proposals for the electricification of the Durham Coast Line to facilitate the future expansion of Tyne and Wear metro services into the Easington constituency.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171346","171346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969095","2018-09-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the report, Rolling out Universal Credit, published by the National Audit Office on 15 June 2018, how much her Department has paid in compensation to local authorities for additional costs incurred in relation to the implementation and wider impact of universal credit.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171398","171398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969096","2018-09-10","Department for Transport","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what his Department's policy is on pavement parking.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171347","171347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969097","2018-09-10","Department for Transport","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the timeframe is for the planned introduction of additional flights between Heathrow and Scottish airports after the construction of a third runway at Heathrow.","Biography information for Bill Grant","Bill Grant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171399","171399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969098","2018-09-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of trends in the level of the disability employment gap; and what information her Department holds on the disability employment gap by (a) condition and (b) type of disability.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171400","171400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969099","2018-09-10","Department for Transport","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he plans to publish the Government's review of pavement parking following the withdrawal of the Pavement Parking (Protection of Vulnerable Pedestrians) Bill 2015-16.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171348","171348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969100","2018-09-11","Cabinet Office","2018-09-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the number of unemployed people registered as disabled that are capable of employment.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171401","171401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969101","2018-09-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the report, Rolling out Universal Credit, published by the National Audit Office on 15 June 2018, what data her Department collects on the additional cost incurred by local authorities in relation to the implementation of universal credit.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171402","171402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969102","2018-09-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps she is taking to encourage (a) large employers and (b) SME employers to recruit disabled employees.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171403","171403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969103","2018-09-11","Northern Ireland Office","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many legacy cases from the Troubles in Northern Ireland are (a) currently being and (b) are due to be brought to court in the next 12 months; and how many of those cases involve the prosecution of present or former (i) service personnel, (ii) police or other security forces, (iii) republican terrorists and (iv) loyalist terrorists.","Biography information for Dr Julian Lewis","Dr Julian Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171267","171267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969104","2018-09-10","Department for Transport","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what proportion of buses in (a) England and (b) the North East have next stop announcements.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171349","171349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969105","2018-09-11","Ministry of Defence","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when his Department plans to respond to the Defence Committee's 6th Report of Session 2017-19 entitled The Government's Proposals for Future Security Partnership with the European Union, which was published on 8 June 2018.","Biography information for Dr Julian Lewis","Dr Julian Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171268","171268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969106","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the annual cost to the NHS is of providing a prescription delivery service.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171350","171350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969107","2018-09-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what measures is he taking to reduce the amount of water leakage by water companies; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Desmond Swayne","Sir Desmond Swayne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171269","171269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969108","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what guidance his Department has issued on patient eligibility for NHS prescription delivery services.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171351","171351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969109","2018-09-13","Ministry of Justice","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he has plans to remove the same roof rule from the criminal injuries compensations scheme.","Biography information for Sir Desmond Swayne","Sir Desmond Swayne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171270","171270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969110","2018-09-10","Treasury","2018-09-06","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much money has been raised for the public purse from VAT on sanitary products in each of the last three years; and how much funding has been distributed to charities through the Tampon Tax Fund by region.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171352","171352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969111","2018-09-13","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps (a) Government Departments and (b) agencies of his Department have taken to restrict internet access to the Vkontakte website.","Biography information for Sir Desmond Swayne","Sir Desmond Swayne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171271","171271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969112","2018-09-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the criteria is for placing a person in the Universal Credit Limited Capability for Work category without attending a work capability assessment.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171353","171353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969113","2018-09-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what discussions his Department has held with the Ministry of Justice on waiting times for social security tribunal hearings.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171354","171354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969114","2018-09-10","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether the framework for the future relationship with the European Union within the Withdrawal Agreement is planned to include details on the future association to the Ninth EU Framework Programme.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171404","171404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969115","2018-09-10","Treasury","2018-09-06","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what progress the Government has made on reducing taxes for working families.","Biography information for Jack Lopresti","Jack Lopresti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171362","171362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969116","2018-09-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will lower the 40 per cent debt recovery level for people in receipt of universal credit that have children.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171355","171355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969117","2018-09-11","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how much has been spent from the public purse on (a) advertising and (b) promoting the right to buy scheme in each year since 2010; and how much he plans to spend on (i) advertising and (ii) promoting that scheme in each year to 2020.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171291","171291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969118","2018-09-10","Treasury","2018-09-06","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether his Department uses Office for National Statistics estimates of personal well-being when formulating policy; and what policies his Department has introduced to improve national well-being in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171300","171300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969119","2018-09-10","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to the document, Framework for the UK-EU Partnership: Science, research and innovation, published in May 2018, what progress (a) he and (b) officials of his Department have made on a Science and Innovation Pact with the EU.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171405","171405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969120","2018-09-10","Home Office","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether his Department uses Office for National Statistics estimates of personal well-being when formulating policy; and what policies his Department has introduced to improve national well-being in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171301","171301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969121","2018-09-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether his Department uses Office for National Statistics estimates of personal well-being when formulating policy; and what policies his Department has introduced to improve national well-being in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171302","171302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969122","2018-09-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether his Department uses Office for National Statistics estimates of personal well-being when formulating policy; and what policies his Department has introduced to improve national well-being in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171303","171303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969123","2018-09-10","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether his Department uses Office for National Statistics estimates of personal well-being when formulating policy; and what policies his Department has introduced to improve national well-being in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171304","171304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969124","2018-09-10","Department for Education","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether his Department uses Office for National Statistics estimates of personal well-being when formulating policy; and what policies his Department has introduced to improve national well-being in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171305","171305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969125","2018-09-11","Home Office","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have been invited to participate in the pilot of the application process for the EU Settlement Scheme.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171406","171406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969126","2018-09-11","Home Office","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will place in the House of Commons Library a copy of the letter sent to EU citizens inviting them to participate in the pilot of the application process for the EU Settlement Scheme.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171407","171407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969127","2018-09-11","Home Office","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what projection she has made of the number and proportion of people invited to participate in the pilot of the application process for the EU Settlement Scheme who will do so.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171408","171408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969128","2018-09-10","Department for Transport","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department uses Office for National Statistics estimates of personal well-being when formulating policy; and what policies his Department has introduced to improve national well-being in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171306","171306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969129","2018-09-11","Home Office","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people who have been invited to participate in the pilot of the application process for the EU Settlement Scheme had done so as of 5 September 2018.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171409","171409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969130","2018-09-11","Home Office","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether people participating in the pilot of the application process for the EU Settlement Scheme will have to pay an application fee.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171410","171410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969131","2018-09-10","Home Office","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many and what proportion of the people who have been invited in the pilot of the application process for the EU Settlement Scheme are in employment or in full-time education.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171411","171411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969132","2018-09-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether her Department uses Office for National Statistics estimates of personal well-being when formulating policy; and what policies her Department has introduced to improve national well-being in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171307","171307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969133","2018-09-10","Ministry of Defence","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department uses Office for National Statistics estimates of personal well-being when formulating policy; and what policies his Department has introduced to improve national well-being in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171308","171308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969134","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department uses Office for National Statistics estimates of personal well-being when formulating policy; and what policies his Department has introduced to improve national well-being in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171309","171309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969135","2018-09-11","Home Office","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps the Government is taking to protect the rights relating to (a) working and (b) living conditions of workers who come to the UK as part of the new seasonal workers scheme.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171412","171412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969136","2018-09-11","Department for Education","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 5 September 2018 to Question 168037 on Teachers: Pay, which specific forecasts have been scrutinised to allow the Department to centrally meet the cost Teachers Pay Grant; what those forecasts and assumptions originally were; and how those forecasts and assumptions have changed.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171413","171413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969137","2018-09-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make an estimate of the level of labour shortages in the farming sector.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171414","171414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969138","2018-09-11","Ministry of Justice","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether it is his policy that (a) HMCTS and (b) any employee or agent of HMCTS collect information from legal representatives attending court on their client's nationality.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171415","171415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969139","2018-09-11","Home Office","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 5 July 2018 to Question 159721 on Immigration, for what reason the Government does not publicly release information on the (a) numbers and (b) outcomes of administrative reviews.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171416","171416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969140","2018-09-10","Home Office","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people who were arrested for the offence of illegal working were subsequently transferred to an immigration removal center in each of the last twelve months.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171417","171417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969141","2018-09-10","Home Office","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether there is a dedicated case-work team in the National Referral Mechanism hub that makes decisions on referrals made on behalf of potential victims of trafficking who are in detention.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171418","171418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969142","2018-09-10","Home Office","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether decisions on National Referral Mechanism referrals on behalf of potential victims of trafficking in detention are allocated to a specific team within the UK Competent Authorities.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171419","171419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969143","2018-09-10","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department is taking to support women's football in (a) Kent and (b) England.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171356","171356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969144","2018-09-10","Department for Transport","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment he has made of the merits of increasing his Department's funding to Bikeability.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171279","171279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969145","2018-09-11","Department for International Development","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what discussions she has had with her French counterpart on sharing best practice on poverty reduction in Africa.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171420","171420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969146","2018-09-11","Department for International Development","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department has taken to support local think tanks in countries in which it operates.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171421","171421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969147","2018-09-11","Department for International Development","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment her Department has made of the role of Regional Economic Communities of Africa in contributing to poverty reduction.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171422","171422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969148","2018-09-10","Home Office","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much revenue has been raised for the public purse by speed cameras in (a) the West Midlands (b) England and (c) the UK in each year for which information is available.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171423","171423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969149","2018-09-10","Treasury","2018-09-06","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with (a) representatives of local authorities and (b) Metro Mayors about the retention of speed camera revenue by those authorities.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171424","171424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969150","2018-09-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of the 2012 Child Maintenance Scheme computer system to process in a timely manner service requests for (a) a new child maintenance scheme claim, (b) a change of circumstances, (c) a variation request, (d) chasing arrears, and (e) enforcement action.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171425","171425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969151","2018-09-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many Service Requests for (a) a new child maintenance scheme claim, (b) a change of circumstances, (c) a variation request, (d) chasing arrears, and (e) undertaking enforcement action remain outstanding in the 2012 Child Maintenance Scheme computer system.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171426","171426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969152","2018-09-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many hours the Child Maintenance System has been (a) unavailable to staff and (b) working with reduced performance in the last six months.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171427","171427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969153","2018-09-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many processing hours for Child Maintenance service requests were lost as a result of (a) technical and (b) IT faults in the last six months.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171428","171428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969154","2018-09-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether her Department has plans to undertake an assessment of the effectiveness of the Child Maintenance Scheme computer system; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171429","171429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969155","2018-09-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of staffing levels working on the Child Maintenance system.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171430","171430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969156","2018-09-11","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many non-disclosure agreements the Government has signed with companies in relations to contingency plan for the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171292","171292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969157","2018-09-11","Treasury","2018-09-06","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to Operation Yellowhammer, what assessment he has made of the effect of raising no deal contingency planning costs through internal reprioritisation on the ability of Departments to fulfil existing (a) policy and (b) other commitments.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171310","171310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969158","2018-09-11","Treasury","2018-09-06","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of replicating the ring-fenced funding in EU structural funds in the UK Shared Prosperity Fund.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171311","171311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969159","2018-09-11","Treasury","2018-09-06","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the number of lost Child Trust Fund accounts in each (a) nation and (b) region of the UK.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171312","171312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969160","2018-09-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to safeguard persecuted communities in Syria, including Syrian Christians during the offensive in the Idlib area of Syria.","Biography information for Stephen Kerr","Stephen Kerr","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171431","171431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969161","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, which Care Commissioning Groups make provide access to drug Mylotarg.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171285","171285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969162","2018-09-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when he plans to bring forward legislative proposals to increase the maximum sentence for animal cruelty sentences from six months to five years imprisonment.","Biography information for Mark Tami","Mark Tami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171315","171315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969163","2018-09-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of trends in the level of GPs experiencing mental health illness in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171313","171313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969164","2018-09-11","Treasury","2018-09-06","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the Government plans to allocate additional resources to the Gangmasters and Labour Abuse Authority to monitor the new seasonal workers scheme and help protect migrant workers from (a) modern slavery and (b) other abuses.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171432","171432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969165","2018-09-11","Department for Education","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of university students have been diagnosed with a mental health condition.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171314","171314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969166","2018-09-10","Home Office","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether it is the Government's policy that migrant workers on the new seasonal workers scheme will be able to change employer during that scheme.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171433","171433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969167","2018-09-10","Department for International Development","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether she plans to attend the Global Financing Facility in support of Every Woman Every Child Conference in Oslo in November 2018.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171276","171276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969168","2018-09-10","Department for International Development","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of the UKs past investment in the Global Financing Facility in support of Every Woman Every Child in Nigeria.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171277","171277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969169","2018-09-10","Department for International Development","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if the Government will make it its policy to continue their contribution to the Global Financing Facility for Every Woman and Child (GFF) at the GFF replenishment conference in November.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171278","171278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969170","2018-09-11","Department for Transport","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made in trends in the number of people killed in road accidents in the UK since 2010.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171434","171434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969171","2018-09-11","Treasury","2018-09-06","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, which Department will have budgetary responsibility for replacing (a) European Regional Development Fund and (b) European Structural Fund funding for projects in Wales in the event that no deal is reached with the EU on funding for 2019-2020.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171435","171435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969172","2018-09-11","Wales Office","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what discussion he has had with the Welsh Government on contingency planning for traffic controls at (a) Holyhead and(b)  Pembroke Docks in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171436","171436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969173","2018-09-11","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps the Government took to actively encourage young people to apply to be a board member for the National Citizen Service Trust; and how many of those positions will be reserved for young people.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171437","171437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969174","2018-09-11","Treasury","2018-09-06","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate his Department has made of the amount of money that will need to be made available to replace all EU funding in Wales for 2019-2021 in the event that no withdrawal agreement is reached with the EU or funding is not covered in that deal.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171438","171438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969175","2018-09-11","Wales Office","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what estimate his Department has made of the proportion of Welsh fish catch that is landed from Irish waters.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171439","171439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969176","2018-09-11","Department for Education","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what his Department's target is for apprenticeship starts by 2020.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171440","171440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969177","2018-09-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate he has made of the effect of the UK leaving the EU on the number of skilled workers in the UK manufacturing sector.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171441","171441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969178","2018-09-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate the Government has made of the proportion of the manufacturing workforce in (a) the UK and (b) the North East which is made up of non-UK EU nationals.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171442","171442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969179","2018-09-10","Home Office","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when his Department plans to respond to the letter of the right hon. Member for Warley of 31 May 2018 to UK Visas and Immigration on Mr Samra.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171284","171284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969180","2018-09-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether there are any plans to increase the level of available training for NHS staff on Foetal Alcohol Spectrum Disorder.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171443","171443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969181","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people have (a) been referred to and (b) joined the NHS diabetes prevention programme.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171286","171286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969182","2018-09-11","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to reduce the number of people who reach the point of rough sleeping.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171444","171444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969183","2018-09-11","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that board members of the National Citizen Service Trust are actively involved in the recommissioning process of delivery partners for NCS in 2020 and beyond.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171445","171445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969184","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps are being taken to improve the clarification of calorific food labelling in order to achieve his Department's 2024 calorie reduction targets.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171287","171287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969185","2018-09-11","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how much the Government has spent on independent evaluations of the National Citizen Service programme since the launch of that programme.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171446","171446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969186","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to provide specialist bariatric weight assessment and management clinics for patients (a) with diabetes and (b) that are classified as obese.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171288","171288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969187","2018-09-10","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what information his Department holds on the number of complaints the Advertising Standards Authority has received on broadband companies miss-selling download speeds in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171447","171447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969188","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many bariatric operations were performed in (a) 2015, (b) 2016, (c) 2017 and (d) 2018 to date.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171289","171289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969189","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the average cost is of a bariatric operation.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171290","171290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969190","2018-09-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much funding was allocated to community pharmacies through the Pharmacy Access Scheme in 2017-18 by local authority area.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171448","171448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969191","2018-09-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the amount of time pharmacists in the community spend on providing direct clinical services excluding the dispensing of medicines.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171449","171449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969192","2018-09-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the projected costs are for the Pharmacy Access Scheme in each quarter up to March 2019.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171450","171450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969193","2018-09-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the total number of (a) internet and (b) high street community pharmacies has been in each year since 2007-08 in (i) total and (ii) each local authority area.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171451","171451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969194","2018-09-11","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 19 July 2018 to Question 163143 on National Citizen Service Trust, how many workshops were delivered to young people during Summer 2018 in collaboration with the Parliament Education Service; where those workshops were held; how many people attended those workshops; and whether there are plans for similar workshops in the future.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171452","171452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969195","2018-09-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much funding has been allocated for the delivery of the next Adult Dental Health Survey.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171453","171453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969196","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many children had a delayed discharge from in-patient eating disorder treatment; and how many days of delayed discharge there were in each (a) NHS region and (b) mental health trust provider in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171454","171454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969197","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many children were (a) referred to a CAMHS service and (b) accepted by a CAMHS services for each (i) clinical commissioning group area and (ii) trust in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171455","171455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969198","2018-09-10","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 19 July 2018 to Question 163143 on National Citizen Service Trust, what the timescale is for launching the NCS Trust Royal Charter body.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171456","171456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969199","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many children undertook treatment for an eating disorder in each (a) Clinical Commissioning Group area and (b) NHS Trust in each of the last 36 months.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171457","171457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969200","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information he holds on the number of online-ordered tests for sexually transmitted infections which the NHS plans to provide in London in (a) 2018 and (b) each of the next five years.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171458","171458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969201","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many times ambulance technicians (a) accompanied (i) paramedics and (ii) emergency care assistants on an ambulance call-out and (b) attended an ambulance call-out without a paramedic or emergency care assistant in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171459","171459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969202","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much his Department (a) has spent in (i) 2018-19 and (ii) each of the last five financial years and (b) plans to spend in 2019-20, on NHS-provided mental health services.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171460","171460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969203","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the average cost to the NHS was of a (a) hip replacement, (b) knee replacement, (c) cataract operation and (d) hernia operation in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171461","171461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969204","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many and what proportion of assessments for the funding of continuing health care took place outside a hospital setting in (a) March 2017 and (b) October 2017.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171462","171462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969205","2018-09-10","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what the total BDUK allocations of funding to date are for (a) Scotland, (b) Wales, (c) Northern Ireland and (d) England for the roll-out of broadband services.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171463","171463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969206","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many NHS patients participated in a clinical trial in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171464","171464"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969207","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many and what proportion of the NHS budget has been spent (a) in the private sector and (b) on contracts awarded to the private sector since May 2010.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171465","171465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969208","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people visited an NHS walk-in centre in each year since 2004-05.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171466","171466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969209","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the projected real-terms change in mental health expenditure is for the next four financial years.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171467","171467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969210","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many GPs closed their surgeries to new patients in each of the last six years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171468","171468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969211","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department holds information on the longest period of time a child or young person has waited for mental health treatment in the NHS for each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171469","171469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969212","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much his Department spent on NHS staff redundancies in each year since 2011-12.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171470","171470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969213","2018-09-10","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what proportion of funding for the National Citizen Service was spent on frontline delivery in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171471","171471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969214","2018-09-10","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what proportion of superfast broadband coverage in (a) Scotland, (b) Wales, (c) Northern Ireland and (d) England has been provided by private sector funding.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171472","171472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969215","2018-09-11","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what proportion of funding for the National Citizen Service will be ring fenced for a dedicated Inclusion Fund.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171473","171473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969216","2018-09-10","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 19 July 2018 to Question 163141 on National Citizen Service Trust, whether the contracts with National Citizen Service providers included a provision for the repayment of funding by the provider in the event of unfilled places.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171474","171474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969217","2018-09-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether (a) Ministers and (b) officials of his Department have met officials from the World Trade Organisation since the EU referendum in June 2016; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171332","171332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969218","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether (a) Ministers and (b) officials in his Department have met officials from the World Trade Organisation since the EU referendum in June 2016; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171333","171333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969219","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether officials from the Food Standards Agency have met officials from the World Trade Organisation since the EU referendum in June 2016; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171334","171334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969220","2018-09-10","Ministry of Defence","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, for what reasons International Military Services Ltd financially reports under UK Generally Accepted Accounting Principles for small companies rather than the reporting standard for public bodies of International Financial Reporting Standards.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171475","171475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969221","2018-09-10","Ministry of Defence","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will publish a list of government to government contracts through International Military Services Ltd that remain unresolved.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171476","171476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969222","2018-09-10","Ministry of Defence","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will (a) publish the value of contingent liabilities relating to the ongoing dispute on the International Military Services Ltd debt to Iran and (b) identify the portion of that liability that relates to government to government contracts.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171477","171477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969223","2018-09-10","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how many civil servants in his Department work on youth policy; and what specific policy areas they focus on.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171478","171478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969224","2018-09-10","Home Office","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps his Department plans to take to (a) disseminate information and (b) raise awareness among migrants arriving on the new seasonal workers scheme of (i) their labour rights and (ii) channels to lodge complaints.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171479","171479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969225","2018-09-10","Home Office","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, who the Government consulted before proposing the new seasonal workers scheme; and whether the Government consulted with any trade unions on that scheme.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171480","171480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969226","2018-09-10","Home Office","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps he plans to take to ensure that the new seasonal workers scheme does not facilitate modern slavery; and what role the (a) modern slavery taskforce and (b) anti-slavery commissioner will have in oversight over that scheme.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171481","171481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969227","2018-09-10","Treasury","2018-09-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, in which companies the Government has a more than 50 per cent ownership stake; whether he (a) receives a copy of the audited accounts of Government-owned companies in each financial year and (b) keeps a record of the (i) auditors of such companies and (ii) reporting frameworks that those companies use to produce their accounts where they differ from the public sector IFRS standard; and which Government-owned companies lay their accounts before Parliament and share a copy with the Comptroller and Auditor General.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171482","171482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969228","2018-09-10","Treasury","2018-09-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many companies in each Government Department of which the Government owns more than 50 per cent do not lay their accounts before Parliament.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171483","171483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969229","2018-09-10","Treasury","2018-09-06","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the (a) assets and (b) liabilities of International Military Services Ltd are exempt from consolidation in the whole of Government accounts.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171484","171484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969230","2018-09-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many complaints the NHS blood and transplant unit received in the last 12 months on not being able to give blood as a result of (a) a lack of appointment slots and (b) the cancellation of of a session.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171485","171485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969231","2018-09-10","Treasury","2018-09-06","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will publish the number of Government controlled companies that report as small companies under the Generally Accepted Accounting Practice.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171486","171486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969232","2018-09-10","Treasury","2018-09-06","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what his policy is on Government controlled companies being exempt from laying their accounts before Parliament.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171487","171487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969233","2018-09-10","Treasury","2018-09-06","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will publish the Government controlled companies in each Department that do not have their assets and liabilities consolidated into the Whole of Government Accounts.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171488","171488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969234","2018-09-10","Treasury","2018-09-06","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make it his policy to keep the childcare voucher scheme open after 4 October 2018.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171294","171294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969235","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people have (a) used and (b) been refused Passenger Transport Services in each local authority area in the South West in each month in each of the last two years.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171282","171282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969236","2018-09-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of Monday 16 July 2018 to Question 162604 on Department of Health & Social Care: Living Wage, what the lowest hourly wage was paid to staff and agency workers in his Department's offices in (a) London and (b) the UK.","Biography information for Wera Hobhouse","Wera Hobhouse","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171489","171489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969237","2018-09-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many under 18 year olds had an operation for an amputation as a result of diabetes in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171318","171318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969238","2018-09-10","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department is taking to promote women's football in (a) Kent and (b) England.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171357","171357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969239","2018-09-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans Public Health England has have to improve the (a) commissioning guidance  and (b) support for the speech, language and communication elements in the Healthy Child Programme.","Biography information for Matt Western","Matt Western","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171490","171490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969240","2018-09-11","Department for Education","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions he has had with Secretary of State for Health and Social Care on funding a programme of training for people jointly commissioning services for children and young people with speech, language and communication needs.","Biography information for Matt Western","Matt Western","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171491","171491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969241","2018-09-11","Department for Education","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans he has to address delayed language through the use of evidence-based intervention and training programmes.","Biography information for Matt Western","Matt Western","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171492","171492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969242","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans he has to improve access to NHS dental services in (a) Medway and (b) Kent.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171358","171358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969243","2018-09-11","Scotland Office","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what recent discussions he has had with Cabinet colleagues on the merits of the Scottish Parliament being able to bring forward legislative proposals on financial services and pensions regulation with the consent of the Scottish Secretary; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171493","171493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969244","2018-09-11","Scotland Office","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what recent discussions he has had with Cabinet colleagues on the merits of the Scottish Parliament being able to bring forward legislative proposals on broadcasting with the consent of the Scottish Secretary; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171494","171494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969245","2018-09-10","Department for International Development","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much her Department is allocating to the global effort to tackle tuberculosis in the current Parliament.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171359","171359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969246","2018-09-11","Scotland Office","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what recent discussions he has had with Cabinet colleagues on the merits of the Scottish Parliament being able to bring forward legislative proposals on telecommunications and postage with the consent of the Scottish Secretary; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171495","171495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969247","2018-09-11","Scotland Office","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what recent discussions he has had with Cabinet colleagues on the merits of the Scottish Parliament being able to bring forward legislative proposals on import and export controls with the consent of the Scottish Secretary; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171496","171496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969248","2018-09-11","Scotland Office","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what recent discussions he has had with Cabinet colleagues on the merits of the Scottish Parliament being able to bring forward legislative proposals on financial services and pensions regulation with the consent of the Scottish Secretary; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171497","171497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969249","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much funding was allocated from the public purse to neuroblastoma research in 2016-17.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171360","171360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969250","2018-09-10","Home Office","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps his Department is taking to tackle anti-social behaviour.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171361","171361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969251","2018-09-10","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he is taking to help ensure impartiality in news reporting by publicly-funded news stations.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171498","171498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969252","2018-09-10","Department for Transport","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many roadside checks his Department carried out on commercial vehicles in (a) 2015, (b) 2016 and (c) 2017.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171293","171293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969253","2018-09-11","Department for Education","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what criteria his Department used to allocate funding from of the Strategic Schools Investment Fund in the (a) current funding round and (b) previous funding rounds; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171499","171499"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969254","2018-09-11","Treasury","2018-09-06","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he has made and estimate of the cost to the public purse of companies that are permitted to be dissolved without going through a formal insolvency procedure.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171500","171500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969255","2018-09-11","Treasury","2018-09-06","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, in how many cases HMRC has objected to a company being allowed to be struck off by Companies House for non-filing of accounts; and whether he has made an assessment of the cost to the public purse of companies that have been struck-off and not been subject to formal insolvency procedure in the last five years.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171501","171501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969256","2018-09-11","Treasury","2018-09-06","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect on the effectiveness of HMRC of the removal of its status as a preferential creditor in insolvency under the Enterprise Act 2002.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171502","171502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969257","2018-09-11","Treasury","2018-09-06","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he has made an assessment of the level of additional funds to be raised by HMRC as a result of the treating directors loan accounts as income in the hands of the director.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171503","171503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969258","2018-09-11","Treasury","2018-09-06","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the number of complaints made to the Financial Ombudsman Service on packaged bank accounts.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171324","171324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969259","2018-09-11","Department for Education","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of the staff employed in each group of the Higher and Further Education Directorate within his Department are apprentices.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171504","171504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969260","2018-09-10","Cabinet Office","2018-09-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will publish a list of the mobile phone applications developed by his Department and its agencies in the last three years; and what the cost to the public purse was of developing of each of those applications.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171505","171505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969261","2018-09-10","Treasury","2018-09-06","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will publish a list of the mobile phone applications developed by his Department and its agencies in the last three years; and what the cost to the public purse was of developing of each of those applications.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171506","171506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969262","2018-09-10","Home Office","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will publish a list of the mobile phone applications developed by his Department and its agencies in the last three years; and what the cost to the public purse was of developing of each of those applications.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171507","171507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969263","2018-09-11","Department for Education","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of the staff employed in (a) the Permanent Secretary's Office and (b) ministerial private offices within his Department are apprentices.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171508","171508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969264","2018-09-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will publish a list of the mobile phone applications developed by his Department and its agencies in the last three years; and what the cost to the public purse was of developing of each of those applications.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171509","171509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969265","2018-09-10","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, if he will publish a list of the mobile phone applications developed by his Department and its agencies in the last three years; and what the cost to the public purse was of developing of each of those applications.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171510","171510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969266","2018-09-10","Attorney General","2018-09-06","To ask the Attorney General, what steps he is taking with regional police forces to help secure convictions.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171511","171511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969267","2018-09-10","Ministry of Defence","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will publish a list of the mobile phone applications developed by his Department and its agencies in the last three years; and what the cost to the public purse was of developing of each of those applications.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171512","171512"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969268","2018-09-10","Ministry of Justice","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will publish a list of the mobile phone applications developed by his Department and its agencies in the last three years; and what the cost to the public purse was of developing of each of those applications.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171513","171513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969269","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will publish a list of the mobile phone applications developed by his Department and its agencies in the last three years; and what the cost to the public purse was of developing of each of those applications.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171514","171514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969270","2018-09-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will publish a list of the mobile phone applications developed by his Department and its agencies in the last three years; and what the cost to the public purse was of developing of each of those applications.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171515","171515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969271","2018-09-10","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will publish a list of the mobile phone applications developed by his Department and its agencies in the last three years; and what the cost to the public purse was of developing of each of those applications.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171516","171516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969272","2018-09-10","Department for International Trade","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, if he will publish a list of the mobile phone applications developed by his Department and its agencies in the last three years; and what the cost to the public purse was of developing of each of those applications.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171517","171517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969273","2018-09-10","Department for Education","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will publish a list of the mobile phone applications developed by his Department and its agencies in the last three years; and what the cost to the public purse was of developing of each of those applications.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171518","171518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969274","2018-09-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will publish a list of the mobile phone applications developed by his Department and its agencies in the last three years; and what the cost to the public purse was of developing of each of those applications.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171519","171519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969275","2018-09-10","Department for Transport","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will publish a list of the mobile phone applications developed by his Department and its agencies in the last three years; and what the cost to the public purse was of developing of each of those applications.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171520","171520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969276","2018-09-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will publish a list of the mobile phone applications developed by her Department and its agencies in the last three years; and what the cost to the public purse was of developing of each of those applications.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171521","171521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969277","2018-09-10","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, if he will publish a list of the mobile phone applications developed by his Department and its agencies in the last three years; and what the cost to the public purse was of developing of each of those applications.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171522","171522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969278","2018-09-10","Department for International Development","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will publish a list of the mobile phone applications developed by her Department and its agencies in the last three years; and what the cost to the public purse was of developing of each of those applications.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171523","171523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969279","2018-09-10","Scotland Office","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, if he will publish a list of the mobile phone applications developed by his Department and its agencies in the last three years; and what the cost to the public purse was of developing of each of those applications.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171524","171524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969280","2018-09-10","Northern Ireland Office","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, if she will publish a list of the mobile phone applications developed by her Department and its agencies in the last three years; and what the cost to the public purse was of developing of each of those applications.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171525","171525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969281","2018-09-11","Department for Education","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 4 September 2018 to Question 168003, if he will publish the number of academy schools awaiting rebrokering by the academy trust from which they are being transferred.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171526","171526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969282","2018-09-10","Department for Transport","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether all bids received for the East Midlands rail franchise have been compliant with the specifications of the tendering process set out by his Department.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171527","171527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969283","2018-09-10","Department for Transport","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether all bids received for the Southeastern rail franchise are compliant with the specifications of the tendering process set out by his Department.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171528","171528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969284","2018-09-10","Department for Transport","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions took place between his Department and Network Rail in (a) 2015, (b) 2016, (c) 2017 and (d) 2018 to determine the (i) readiness and (ii) specification of the upgraded signalling system to be used on the East Coast mainline ahead of the introduction of the Intercity Express Programme trains.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171529","171529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969285","2018-09-10","Department for Transport","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he took to ensure that the new signalling system on the East Coast mainline was at the correct specification to accommodate the new Intercity Express Programme trains.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171530","171530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969286","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether (a) NHS England and (b) his Department have received requests from clinical commissioning groups for new or more detailed guidance on non-emergency passenger transport eligibility requirements since 2010.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171283","171283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969287","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 6 September 2018 to Question 169507 on Energy Drinks: Public Consultation, whether his Department plans to consult (a) children, (b) young people, (c) school councils, (d) youth councils and (e) other youth groups on its plans to make it illegal to sell energy drinks to children under 16 or under 18.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171531","171531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969288","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answers of 6 September 2018 to Questions 169508 and 169507, what steps he took to consult young people on his plans to make it illegal to sell energy drinks to children under 16 or under 18 before launching the consultation on those proposals.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171532","171532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/971610","2018-09-13","Cabinet Office","2018-09-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he publish the terms of reference of Operation Yellowhammer.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 173517","173517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967965","2018-09-10","Department for Education","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to improve social mobility.","Biography information for Peter Aldous","Peter Aldous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 906754","906754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967972","2018-09-05","Northern Ireland Office","2018-09-05","What recent assessment she has made of the security situation in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Kevin Foster","Kevin Foster","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 906648","906648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967973","2018-09-05","Northern Ireland Office","2018-09-05","What steps she is taking with all communities in Northern Ireland to resolve legacy issues in the absence of a Northern Ireland Executive.","Biography information for Jack Lopresti","Jack Lopresti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 906650","906650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967974","2018-09-05","Northern Ireland Office","2018-09-05","What steps she is taking to support armed forces veterans and police officers who have served in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 906654","906654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968016","2018-09-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the implications for his policies of the approach taken by the devolved administrations in supporting farmers and food producers during the dry weather in summer 2018.","Biography information for Rosie Duffield","Rosie Duffield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170548","170548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968017","2018-09-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effect of the Irish Governments fodder transport scheme on the (a) price and (b) supply of fodder in the UK.","Biography information for Rosie Duffield","Rosie Duffield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170556","170556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968089","2018-09-10","Treasury","2018-09-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to prevent owners of second homes registering their home as a holiday let in order to register for small business rate relief when the home is not available for let for the required number of days per year.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170758","170758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968091","2018-09-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will take steps to ensure that the Deliberate Release Directive continues to be enacted after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170760","170760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968093","2018-09-10","Department for International Trade","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps his Department is taking to achieve future trade liberalisation between Israel and the UK after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170762","170762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968095","2018-09-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the level of youth unemployment was in (a) 2010 and (b) 2018 to date.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170763","170763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968096","2018-09-10","Cabinet Office","2018-09-05","To ask the Minister of Cabinet Office, how many disabled people entered the workforce in (a) 2010 and (b) 2018.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170764","170764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968097","2018-09-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much was paid in disability payments in (a) 2010 and (b) 2018.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170765","170765"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968098","2018-09-10","Home Office","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will take steps to end severe suffering as a research category for all research animals after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170766","170766"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968099","2018-09-10","Home Office","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will ensure that applications for Government-funded research require that animal research conducted in third countries is conducted at standards permitted in the UK.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170767","170767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968100","2018-09-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will prohibit the importation of products, such as foie gras developed in ways which would not be permitted in the UK after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170768","170768"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968102","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussion he has had with the Chancellor of the Exchequer on the funding of treatment for alcohol addiction services in (a) West Midlands and (b) Coventry.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170685","170685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968103","2018-09-10","Department for Education","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment has he made of the quality of teacher training provision in (a) Coventry, (b) the West Midlands and (c) England.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170686","170686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968104","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to reduce the number of children requiring treatment for urgent mental health conditions at A&E in (a) the West Midlands and (b) Coventry; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170687","170687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968105","2018-09-10","Department for Education","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent discussions he has held with (a) the Minister for the Cabinet Office and (b) the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union on the effect of the UK leaving the EU on the recruitment and retention of modern foreign language teachers.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170688","170688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968106","2018-09-10","Department for Education","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs on the nutritional content of free school meals.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170689","170689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968107","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what his policy is on the adoption of the NICE recommendations for all doctors' surgeries to declare the number of patients diagnosed with Lyme Disease.","Biography information for Rosie Duffield","Rosie Duffield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170769","170769"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968108","2018-09-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 23 July 2018 to Question 165149, on Social Security Benefits: Scotland, how many claimants have outstanding benefit overpayment debts that are to be devolved to Scotland which are attributable to (a) overpayment and (b) fraud debts.","Biography information for Martin Whitfield","Martin Whitfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170770","170770"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968109","2018-09-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that utility companies pass on decreases in wholesale energy prices to consumers.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170771","170771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968111","2018-09-10","Department for International Trade","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, pursuant to his oral contribution of 16 July 2018, Official Report columns 41-52, if he will consult rights organisations in countries with which the UK seeks new trade agreements.","Biography information for Rosie Duffield","Rosie Duffield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170772","170772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968112","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether local authorities in England are continuing to receive the former Independent Living Fund recipient grant announced in May 2016; and how the spending of this grant is being monitored.","Biography information for Marsha De Cordova","Marsha De Cordova","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170773","170773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968113","2018-09-10","Home Office","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications for leave to remain on human rights grounds are (a) waiting to be processed and (b) under consideration.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170774","170774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968114","2018-09-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department takes to help public sector organisations ensure that their projects are not resourced with high proportions of under-qualified, unqualified or self-designated electrical workers.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170732","170732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968115","2018-09-10","Treasury","2018-09-05","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to ensure that people receive prompt responses from HMRC caseworkers on (a) inheritance tax payments and (b) other matters.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170733","170733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968116","2018-09-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether his Department has made an assessment of the potential merits of using an alternative weather station to the Mona weather station when determining eligibility for cold weather payments for postcode areas LL33 and LL54-LL61.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170716","170716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968117","2018-09-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Parliamentary Under Secretary of State's evidence to the House of Lords EU Energy and Environment Sub-Committee on 18 July 2018, whether it is the policy of the Government to remain a member of the European Chemicals Agency and subject to REACH after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170775","170775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968119","2018-09-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether his Department has made an assessment of the effect on the economy of the steam railway in Doon Valley; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Bill Grant","Bill Grant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170776","170776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968120","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the (a) number of patients the NHS saw in summer 2018 because of heat-related illnesses and (b) total cost to the NHS of the extreme weather in summer 2018.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170777","170777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968121","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will estimate the annual cost to the NHS of alcohol addiction in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170778","170778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968122","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department has made an assessment of the potential merits of commissioning a national anti-stigma campaign focused on addiction and mental health.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170779","170779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968123","2018-09-10","Department for Transport","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the remit of the Rail Delivery Group includes industrial relations in the rail industry.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170780","170780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968124","2018-09-10","Department for Transport","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if it his policy to maintain European Railway Agency rules in respect of specifications (a) on common track width and (b) uniform platform heights after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170781","170781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968125","2018-09-10","Department for Transport","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the conclusions of the report, UK Aviation Consumer Survey published by the Civil Aviation Authority 18 August 2018, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the reduction in airline passenger satisfaction rates between 2016 and 2018.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170782","170782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968126","2018-09-10","Department for International Trade","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, which EU anti-dumping regulations the Government plans to maintain after the UK leaves the EU are subject to an ongoing expiry review.","Biography information for Gareth Snell","Gareth Snell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170783","170783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968128","2018-09-10","Department for International Trade","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what recent progress he has made on UK-third country free trade agreements.","Biography information for Gareth Snell","Gareth Snell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170784","170784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968129","2018-09-10","Ministry of Defence","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the number of veterans in (a) the UK, (b) the North East and (c) Easington constituency.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170785","170785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968132","2018-09-10","Department for Education","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to limit the amount schools charge for school uniforms.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170787","170787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968133","2018-09-10","Department for Education","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will make it his policy to introduce a scheme to support (a) low income families and (b) families with multiple school-age children with the cost of (i) compulsory uniforms, (ii) school equipment and (iii) school-based activities.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170788","170788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968135","2018-09-10","Department for Education","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions he has had with Cabinet colleagues on the effect of the public sector pay cap on the recruitment and retention of staff in schools.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170790","170790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968136","2018-09-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many people have been (a) charged and (b) prosecuted for fox hunting on National Trust land in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170791","170791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968137","2018-09-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many people have been (a) charged and (b) prosecuted for fox hunting in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170792","170792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968138","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will introduce a notification on the medical files of military veterans to help increase awareness in the NHS of that service's responsibilities under the Military Covenant.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170793","170793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968139","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the number of days supply of epipen available to the NHS.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170794","170794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968140","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the cost to the NHS was to (a) administer and (b) collect prescription fines in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170795","170795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968141","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many prescription fines were issued in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170796","170796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968143","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many prescription fineshave been successfully appealed in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170797","170797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968144","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many staff are employed by the NHS to (a) administer and (b) collect prescription fines.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170798","170798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968145","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much money the NHS has collected in prescription fines in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170799","170799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968146","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the performance of Clinical Commissioning Groups to improve access to advanced radiotherapy.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170800","170800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968147","2018-09-10","Home Office","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much his Department has charged applicants for administering the oath of British Citizenship in overseas consulates in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170801","170801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968148","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to improve data access and sharing arrangements between the Health and Social Care Information Centre and NHS England.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170802","170802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968149","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many and what proportion of cancer patients received treatment within the 62-day target after an urgent GP referral in each region in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170803","170803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968150","2018-09-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how much his Department has received in charges for providing emergency travel documents to UK citizens in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170804","170804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968152","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make an assessment of the cost to the public purse of the establishment of freephone numbers for patients to contact GP surgeries.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170805","170805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968154","2018-09-10","Ministry of Defence","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the cost to the public purse was of training an assistance provided by the armed forces to the Myanmar military in the last five years.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170807","170807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968155","2018-09-10","Treasury","2018-09-05","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assurances he has received from the Chief Executive of HMRC on a resolution to the dispute with the Roadchef Employees Benefit Trust.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170756","170756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968156","2018-09-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 16 July 2018 to Question 163122, what steps he is taking to ensure the continuation of food and plant import data recorded and shared using the EU TRACES system in the event of (a) a UK-EU trade deal and (b) the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170808","170808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968157","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to improve the (a) standard and (b) capacity of NHS crisis and inpatient services.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170698","170698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968158","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to improve access to child and adolescent mental health services for schools and families.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170699","170699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968159","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to improve access to face-to-face talking therapies for people with mental health problems.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170700","170700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968160","2018-09-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans he has for regulations concerning the EU TRACES data recording and sharing system to form part of the common rule book envisaged in the White Paper, The future relationship between the United Kingdom and the European Union, published in July 2018, Cm 9593.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170809","170809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968162","2018-09-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answers of 24 July 2018 to Questions 166203 and 166207, when he plans to publish the terms of reference, chair, membership and timetable for the comprehensive review of the services provided by the Defra group.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170810","170810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968163","2018-09-10","Prime Minister","2018-09-05","To ask the Prime Minister, when she plans to respond to the letter dated 5 June 2018, from northern newspapers on the One North campaign.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170731","170731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968164","2018-09-10","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate his Department has made of the cost to the public purse of delivering the National Citizen Service in (a) the UK and (b) London in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170811","170811"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968165","2018-09-10","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate his Department has made of the number of young people who took part in the National Citizen Service programme in (a) the UK and (b) London in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170812","170812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968166","2018-09-10","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what information his Department holds on the age profile of the young people who have taken part in the National Citizen Service programme in (a) the UK and (b) London in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170813","170813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968167","2018-09-10","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what information his Department holds on the gender profile of the young people who have taken part in the National Citizen Service programme in (a) the UK and (b) London in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170814","170814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968168","2018-09-10","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what information his Department holds on the socio-economic profile of the young people who have taken part in the National Citizen Service programme in (a) the UK and (b) London in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170815","170815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968169","2018-09-10","Department for Education","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what (a) careers advice and (b) information is provided by (i) his Department and (ii) schools to students considering careers in the creative arts.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170816","170816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968170","2018-09-10","Home Office","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many licence applications for medicinal cannabis have been received by the expert panel; and what the status is of those applications.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170718","170718"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968171","2018-09-10","Home Office","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many inquiries the medicinal cannabis licensing panel has received from potential applicants.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170719","170719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968172","2018-09-10","Cabinet Office","2018-09-05","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when he plans to publish the final Boundary Commission proposals; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170817","170817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968174","2018-09-10","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what support his Department provides for deaf athletes.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170702","170702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968175","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 30 April 2018 to Question 137050, on health: children, when the Social Care Policy Research Programme review of the effectiveness of interventions for children and young people aged 3-18 years who have experienced adverse childhood experiences will report.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170818","170818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968176","2018-09-10","Department for Transport","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to his oral evidence to the Transport Committee on 24 July 2018, Q341-345, HC 891, when he plans to publish the minutes of the Thameslink 2018 Industry Readiness Board.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170819","170819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968177","2018-09-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether it is Departmental practice not to use the term ritual slaughter when discussing shechita and halal slaughtering process.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170820","170820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968178","2018-09-10","Ministry of Justice","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to redefine live animals in divorce cases so they are not regarded as property.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170821","170821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968179","2018-09-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what processes her Department uses to (a) notify people of their state pension entitlement and (b) advise them of the number of additional qualifying years of national insurance contributions required to obtain the full state pension; and whether that information is provided via a single communication.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170650","170650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968180","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what courses are run by the NHS Leadership Academy.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170653","170653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968181","2018-09-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many families have claimed the (a) higher and (b) lower rate of bereavement support since 6 April 2017 in (i) England, (ii) the North West, (iii) Merseyside and (iv) Wallasey constituency.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170703","170703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968182","2018-09-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people  have (a) made additional payments to increase the number of qualifying years of National Insurance contributions they require to claim the full state pension and (b) by making such payments have (i) exceeded the 35 years required to claim that pension and (ii) been refunded for making overpayments.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170651","170651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968184","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what funding his Department allocates to the NHS Leadership Academy.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170654","170654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968185","2018-09-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what information her Department holds on the socio-economic background of people appointed to senior positions in her Department in the last five years.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170822","170822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968186","2018-09-10","Ministry of Justice","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the training requirements are for new prison officers; and (a) how and (b) where is that training delivered.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170655","170655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968187","2018-09-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether the requirement to have 35 qualifying years of national insurance contributions to be eligible for a full state pension is set out in correspondence sent to people in relation to (a) their national insurance record and (b) their state pension.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170652","170652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968188","2018-09-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his Department holds information on the socio-economic background of people appointed to senior positions in his Department in the last five years.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170823","170823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968189","2018-09-10","Northern Ireland Office","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, whether her Department holds information on the socio-economic background of people appointed to senior positions in her Department in the last five years.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170824","170824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968190","2018-09-10","Department for Education","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether his Department holds information on the socio-economic background of people appointed to senior positions in his Department in the last five years.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170825","170825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968191","2018-09-10","Treasury","2018-09-05","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether his Department holds information on the socio-economic background of people appointed to senior positions in his Department in the last five years.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170826","170826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968192","2018-09-10","Cabinet Office","2018-09-05","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether his Department holds information on the socio-economic background of people appointed to senior positions in his Department in the last five years.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170827","170827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968194","2018-09-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what guidance ambassadors receive about engaging in political activities.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170828","170828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968195","2018-09-10","Department for International Trade","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether his Department holds information on the socio-economic background of people appointed to senior positions in his Department.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170829","170829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968196","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate his Department has made of the number of medical students who plan to practise overseas after they have completed their training in the UK.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170830","170830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968197","2018-09-10","Women and Equalities","2018-09-05","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what information her office holds on the socio-economic background of people appointed to senior roles in the Government Equalitiies Office in the last five years.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170831","170831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968198","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate his Department has made of the (a) number and (b) proportion of GPs who work part-time.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170832","170832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968199","2018-09-10","Ministry of Justice","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what information his Department holds on the socio-economic background of people appointed to senior positions in his Department in the last five years.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170833","170833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968200","2018-09-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to introduce a national register of publicly available defibrillators.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170834","170834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968201","2018-09-10","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will undertake an assessment of the provision of public toilets throughout England and Wales.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170835","170835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968202","2018-09-10","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many new-build dwellings have been completed in the Hendon constituency since September 2017.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170836","170836"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968204","2018-09-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many universal credit conditionality easements have been applied to claimants suffering a bereavement following the death of a partner, child or qualifying young person since April 2017.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170704","170704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968205","2018-09-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps the Environment Agency is taking to reduce the number of incidents of outflow from sewage overflows in England and Wales.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170837","170837"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968206","2018-09-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what guidance his Department has published for local authorities on requiring the removal of ragwort from public land.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170838","170838"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968207","2018-09-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to reduce the amount of sewage and waste water entering rivers and streams from misconnected water and sewage pipes.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170839","170839"
