"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40802","2014-03-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make it his policy to allow homeowners to pool Government funding provided for flood resilience measures in order to enable communities to take collective action against flood risk.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190101","190101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40803","2014-03-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what flood prevention measures have been undertaken in (a) Cannock Chase constituency and (b) Staffordshire in the last three years; and how many staff of (i) his Department and (ii) the Environment Agency have been employed on those measures.","Biography information for Mr Aidan Burley","Mr Aidan Burley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190083","190083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40804","2014-03-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what advice he has received on distinguishing between infected and uninfected badgers; and what account his Department took of this advice in conducting the badger cull pilots.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190091","190091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40805","2014-03-04","Department of Health","2014-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions officials in his Department have had with his Department's arm's length bodies since 1 January 2014 on raising new purchase orders in the current financial year; what the content of those discussions was; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190063","190063"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40806","2014-03-04","Department of Health","2014-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he plans to make a statement on the outcome of the new congenital heart disease review.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190090","190090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40807","2014-03-04","Department of Health","2014-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people are on (a) invasive and (b) non-invasive ventilation; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190071","190071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40808","2014-03-04","Department of Health","2014-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much the campaign to inform people they can opt out of the Summary Care Record cost; and how much paper was used in that campaign.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190126","190126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40809","2014-03-04","Department of Health","2014-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of the effectiveness of (a) anti-depressants and (b) mindfulness-based treatment in (i) curing and (ii) suppressing depression.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190097","190097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40810","2014-03-05","Department of Health","2014-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what training is currently provided for midwives in the diagnosis of tongue-tie in infants.","Biography information for Teresa Pearce","Teresa Pearce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190119","190119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40811","2014-03-05","Department of Health","2014-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when the one-year cancer survival rate data contained within the Clinical Commissioning Group Outcomes Indicator Set will be released; and what the reasons are for the time taken for their release.","Biography information for Mr John Baron","Mr John Baron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190100","190100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40812","2014-03-05","Department of Health","2014-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the provision of service to diagnose and treat tongue-tie in infants.","Biography information for Teresa Pearce","Teresa Pearce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190118","190118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40813","2014-03-04","Home Office","2014-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what non-statutory discretionary powers she has relating to accepting (a) wider family members and (b) siblings under family reunion applications by refugees and asylum seekers in the UK.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190099","190099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40814","2014-03-04","Department for International Development","2014-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what the Government's objectives are for the UN Commission on the Status of Women; and if she will make it her policy to (a) prioritise women's social and political participation in fragile states and (b) support a gender goal in the post-2015 framework with special reference to fragile states and conflict-affected areas.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190070","190070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40815","2014-03-05","Department for International Development","2014-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will publish any assessment she has made of the value for money of her Department's spending on consultants and interim staff.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190072","190072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40816","2014-03-05","Department for International Development","2014-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what resources her Department has made available in Jordan to assist with the relief effort for Syrian refugees.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190076","190076"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40817","2014-03-05","Department for International Development","2014-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what resources her Department has in Lebanon to assist with the relief effort for Syrian refugees.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190077","190077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40818","2014-03-05","Department for International Development","2014-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what resources her Department currently has in Afghanistan.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190078","190078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40819","2014-03-05","Department for International Development","2014-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many discussions have taken place between Ministers in her Department and the International Labour Organisation in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190079","190079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40820","2014-03-04","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether any prisoners serving a sentence for murder are still unlawfully at large following an escape or abscond since 1 April 2004.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190098","190098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40821","2014-03-05","Northern Ireland Office","2014-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, which (a) prime ministers, (b) deputy prime ministers; (c) Northern Ireland secretaries of state, (d) ministers of state for Northern Ireland, (e) attorney generals and (f) secretaries of state for Defence had knowledge of the existence of administrative letters granting immunity from prosecution for on-the-runs; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190110","190110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40822","2014-03-04","Northern Ireland Office","2014-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, whether Richard Haass was aware of the administrative letter scheme granting immunity from prosecution to on-the-run suspects (a) before, (b) during and (c) after his recent negotiations with the main political parties in Northern Ireland; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190108","190108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40823","2014-03-05","Northern Ireland Office","2014-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, when the last administrative letter granting immunity from prosecution to an on-the-run suspect was issued and by whom; whether she had knowledge of it at the time of its sending; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190111","190111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40824","2014-03-05","Northern Ireland Office","2014-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many administrative letters granting immunity from prosecution to on-the-runs are under consideration at present; what the current status of such draft letters is; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190112","190112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40825","2014-03-05","Northern Ireland Office","2014-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, when the first administrative letters granting immunity from prosecution to on-the-runs were issued; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190113","190113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40826","2014-03-05","Northern Ireland Office","2014-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, when she first became aware of the operation of an administrative letter scheme granting immunity from prosecution to the on-the-runs; how many such letters she sanctioned; to whom those letters were addressed; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190114","190114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40827","2014-03-05","Department for Transport","2014-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many Maritime and Coastguard Agency (MCA) officials were appointed to the Steering Group which considered the recommendations of the Maitland Review of the regulatory regime in the offshore oil and gas industry; how many MCA officials have worked on that Steering Group to date; and for how long in each case.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190073","190073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40828","2014-03-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many Health and Safety Executive (HSE) officials were appointed to the Steering Group which considered the recommendations of the Maitland Review of the regulatory regime in the offshore oil and gas industry; how many HSE officials have worked on that Steering Group to date; and for how long in each such case.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190074","190074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40829","2014-03-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many inspectors have been recruited to the Health and Safety Executive's Energy Division since October 2013.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190075","190075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40830","2014-03-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to ensure that older workers have access to training to improve their skills and employability.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190094","190094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40831","2014-03-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to promote Remploy's Access to Work Mental Health Support Service to small and medium-sized enterprises.","Biography information for Mr Mike Thornton","Mr Michael Thornton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190109","190109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40832","2014-03-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he publish data by age range on new claims for personal independence payment made between 8 April and 31 December 2013.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190104","190104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40833","2014-03-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many 16 to 24 year olds have been reassessed for personal independence payments to date.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190105","190105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40834","2014-03-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will take steps to ensure that the support available on Saturdays for people appealing against the refusal of employment and support allowance is equivalent to that available on other days.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190133","190133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40835","2014-03-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 18 November 2013, Official Report, column 669W, on employment and support allowance, what medical conditions have been diagnosed in each person transferred from incapacity benefit to jobseeker's allowance after having been seen by an assessor; and how many such people have been diagnosed with each such condition.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190127","190127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40836","2014-03-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 18 November 2013, Official Report, column 669W, on employment and support allowance, how many people in the work-related activity group who have not been seen by an assessor have been in contact with the Work Programme to date.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190128","190128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40837","2014-03-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will review the method used by the Valuation Office Agency to calculate the shared accommodation rate so that those with a specific need receive the help to which they are entitled.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190132","190132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40545","2014-03-03","Attorney General","2014-02-27","To ask the Attorney General, how many people were prosecuted for food crime offences in the UK in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189843","189843"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40546","2014-03-03","Attorney General","2014-02-27","To ask the Attorney General, whether any successful prosecutions have been made in the last five years against those accused of exporting horses and ponies for slaughter; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189861","189861"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40547","2014-03-04","Northern Ireland Office","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, for what reason letters of comfort were issued to on-the-runs despite the absence of a police force intending to arrest or question them.","Biography information for Mr John Baron","Mr John Baron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189996","189996"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40548","2014-03-04","Northern Ireland Office","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, which Minister is currently responsible for oversight of the letters of comfort issued to on-the-runs.","Biography information for Mr John Baron","Mr John Baron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189997","189997"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40549","2014-03-04","Northern Ireland Office","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, who first authorised the issue of letters of comfort to on-the-runs.","Biography information for Mr John Baron","Mr John Baron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189998","189998"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40550","2014-03-04","Northern Ireland Office","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what evidence she has identified on whether John Downey's letter was issued in error; and what assessment she has made of whether other such letters have not similarly been issued in error.","Biography information for Mr John Baron","Mr John Baron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189995","189995"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40551","2014-03-04","Northern Ireland Office","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, under what statutory provision letters of comfort have continued to be issued to on-the-runs following the withdrawal of the Northern Ireland (Offences) Bill in 2006.","Biography information for Mr John Baron","Mr John Baron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189999","189999"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40552","2014-03-04","Attorney General","2014-02-27","To ask the Attorney General, how many pagers have been provided to staff by the Law Officers' Departments since May 2010; and what the cost to the Law Officers' Departments was of providing those pagers.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190043","190043"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40553","2014-03-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many pagers have been provided to staff by his Department since May 2010; and what the cost to the Department was of providing those pagers.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190042","190042"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40554","2014-03-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what advice and guidance his Department issues to UK Trade and Investment locations abroad on sourcing ceramic-based promotional material (a) generally and (b) on the Britain is Great promotional campaign.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189992","189992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40555","2014-03-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will publish the most recent UK skills shortage by occupation list.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189989","189989"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40556","2014-03-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the recommendation of the British Chambers of Commerce Skills and Employment Manifesto that Accredited Chambers of Commerce or other organisations trusted by business should be used to provide objective advice to employers about how they can use apprenticeships to grow their businesses.","Biography information for Mr David Ward","Mr David Ward","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189974","189974"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40557","2014-03-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will implement the recommendations of the British Chambers of Commerce Skills and Employment Manifesto that schools should work with local businesses to ensure all young people benefit from quality contact with employers.","Biography information for Caroline Dinenage","Caroline Dinenage","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189872","189872"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40558","2014-03-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the recommendations of the British Chambers of Commerce Skills and Employment Manifesto, if he will support small and medium-sized enterprises to invest in apprenticeships and workplace training.","Biography information for Caroline Dinenage","Caroline Dinenage","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189873","189873"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40559","2014-03-03","Cabinet Office","2014-02-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many deaths of (a) infants, (b) children, (c) adults and (d) elderly people from MRSA ST398 there were in the UK in each year since 2000.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189916","189916"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40560","2014-03-03","Cabinet Office","2014-02-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many deaths of (a) infants, (b) children, (c) adults and (d) elderly people from monophasic salmonella typhimurium there were in the UK in each year since 2000.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189917","189917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40561","2014-03-03","Cabinet Office","2014-02-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many deaths of (a) infants, (b) children, (c) adults and (d) elderly people from new type MRSA which has a mecC rather than a mecA gene there were in the UK in each year since 2000.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189918","189918"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40562","2014-03-03","Cabinet Office","2014-02-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many deaths of (a) infants, (b) children, (c) adults and (d) elderly people from antibiotic-resistant foodborne campylobacter infection there were in the UK in each year since 1990.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189919","189919"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40563","2014-03-03","Cabinet Office","2014-02-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many deaths of (a) infants, (b) children, (c) adults and (d) elderly people from antibiotic-resistant foodborne salmonella infection there were in the UK in each year since 1990.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189920","189920"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40564","2014-03-03","Cabinet Office","2014-02-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many deaths of (a) infants, (b) children, (c) adults and (d) elderly people from antibiotic-resistant pneumonia infection where bacteria were confirmed as cause there were in the UK in each year since 1990.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189922","189922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40565","2014-03-03","Cabinet Office","2014-02-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many deaths of (a) infants, (b) children, (c) adults and (d) elderly people from antibiotic-resistant osteomyelitis infection there were in the UK in each year since 1990.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189921","189921"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40566","2014-03-03","Cabinet Office","2014-02-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many deaths of infants up to the age of one year have been caused by multi-drug resistant bacterial infection; and from which infections such infants have died in each year since 1990.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189912","189912"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40567","2014-03-03","Cabinet Office","2014-02-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many deaths of people aged 70 or over were caused by multi-drug resistant bacterial infection; and from which infections such people have died in each year since 1990.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189913","189913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40568","2014-03-03","Cabinet Office","2014-02-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many deaths of children aged (a) between one and 10 years and (b) 10 and 16 years were caused by multi-drug resistant bacterial infection; and from which infections each such person died in each year since 1990.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189914","189914"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40569","2014-03-03","Cabinet Office","2014-02-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many treatment failures due to multi-drug resistant bacterial infection leading to death have occurred in each year since 1990; and from which infections each such person has died.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189915","189915"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40570","2014-03-03","Cabinet Office","2014-02-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 24 February 2014, Official Report, column 200W, on IT: education, with which groups and organisations his Department has engaged to support the Year of the Code; and what support his Department has so provided.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190022","190022"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40571","2014-03-04","Cabinet Office","2014-02-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many pagers have been provided to staff by his Department since May 2010; and what the cost to the Department was of providing those pagers.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190044","190044"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40572","2014-03-03","HM Treasury","2014-02-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many pagers have been provided to staff by his Department since May 2010; and what the cost to the Department was of providing those pagers.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190060","190060"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40573","2014-03-03","HM Treasury","2014-02-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will take steps to ensure that Bermuda receives public recognition and credit for its open and honest compliance with his Department's request for taxation transparency and reform.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189951","189951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40574","2014-03-03","HM Treasury","2014-02-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what enforcement steps he is taking to ensure that EU migrants living and working in the UK are compliant with British tax laws.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189952","189952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40575","2014-03-03","HM Treasury","2014-02-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 15 January 2014, Official Report, column 599W, on taxation: bingo, if he will undertake a specific review of the bingo duty rate.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189973","189973"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40576","2014-03-03","HM Treasury","2014-02-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what his policy is on extending the Seed Enterprise Investment Scheme beyond UK Ltd companies.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190015","190015"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40577","2014-03-03","HM Treasury","2014-02-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent discussions he has had with campaigners for a financial transaction tax; how many times he has met such campaigners since May 2010; and how many times he has met with representatives from the financial sector to discuss this issue in that time.","Biography information for John Robertson","John Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190016","190016"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40578","2014-03-03","HM Treasury","2014-02-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent discussions he has had with his counterparts in other European countries on the introduction of a financial transaction tax.","Biography information for John Robertson","John Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190017","190017"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40579","2014-03-03","HM Treasury","2014-02-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the costs that would be incurred by renaming national insurance as earnings tax.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189863","189863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40580","2014-03-04","HM Treasury","2014-02-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment he has made of the potential benefits of providing tax relief to the video games sector.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189890","189890"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40581","2014-03-04","HM Treasury","2014-02-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department is taking to prevent money from Ukraine derived from illegal sources entering the British financial system.","Biography information for Anas Sarwar","Anas Sarwar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189886","189886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40582","2014-03-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many local development orders have been issued by local authorities in each constituent part of the UK in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Alun Cairns","Alun Cairns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189929","189929"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40583","2014-03-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 11 February 2014, Official Report, column 560W, on property development: floods, whether information on the decisions taken by him on recovered planning appeals is held; and whether records are kept of any decisions taken by him that are contrary to (a) the local authority's decision and (b) Environment Agency advice.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190026","190026"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40584","2014-03-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many UK constituencies do not have a fire station.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189907","189907"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40585","2014-03-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many pagers have been provided to staff by his Department since May 2010; and what the cost to the Department was of providing those pagers.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190045","190045"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40586","2014-03-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 11 February 2014, Official Report, column 560W, on property development: floods, how many times he has used his powers of recovering a planning application to permit development of any sort on a flood plain or in an area of flood risk in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190027","190027"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40587","2014-03-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he plans to respond to Parliamentary Questions 185480, 185481 and 185482, tabled on 28 January 2014.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190000","190000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40588","2014-03-04","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many pagers have been provided to staff by her Department since May 2010; and what the cost to the Department was of providing those pagers.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190046","190046"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40589","2014-03-03","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment criteria was used by Sport England in determining which (a) core cities and (b) growth cities received priority in the allocation of resources.","Biography information for Stephen Barclay","Stephen Barclay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189908","189908"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40590","2014-03-04","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent discussions she has had with the Chancellor of the Exchequer on providing tax relief to the video games sector.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189889","189889"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40591","2014-03-04","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what accommodation is available for the military in (a) Stirling Castle and (b) Edinburgh Castle; and how many personnel can be accommodated at each such location.","Biography information for Mr Russell Brown","Mr Russell Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189882","189882"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40592","2014-03-03","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 24 February 2014, Official Report, column 64W, on armed forces: pensions, what saving was made through the 10 voluntarily surrendered Armed Forces Pension Scheme 75 widows payments in 2013.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189943","189943"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40593","2014-03-06","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment his Department has made of the effectiveness of his Department's recent More than meets the eye recruitment campaign.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190006","190006"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40594","2014-03-03","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many new army reserve recruits there were in (a) Cannock Chase constituency and (b) Staffordshire in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Aidan Burley","Mr Aidan Burley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189970","189970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40595","2014-03-03","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 10 February 2014, Official Report, column 698W, on European Defence Agency, whether staff of the European Defence Agency paid out of the functional element of its budget perform any roles in the delivery or project management of (a) pooling and sharing and (b) other projects delivered by the Agency; and what estimate he has made of the proportion of the functional budget spent on any such activity.","Biography information for Sir Peter Luff","Sir Peter Luff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189964","189964"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40596","2014-03-03","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many pagers have been provided to staff by his Department since May 2010; and what the cost to the Department was of providing those pagers.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190047","190047"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40597","2014-03-03","Department for Education","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many informal exclusions of students with autism there were in (a) primary and (b) secondary schools in England in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189852","189852"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40598","2014-03-04","Department for Education","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 24 February 2014, Official Report, column 217W, on free schools, how many of the free schools that have a rental or leasehold agreement for the site of their school are owned by a (a) local authority and (b) company.","Biography information for Mr David Ward","Mr David Ward","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189901","189901"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40599","2014-03-04","Department for Education","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when the decision to let a contract for a package of help and advice on universal free school meals was made; for how much this contract is estimated to amount; and when he expects to announce the provider.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189888","189888"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40600","2014-03-03","Department for Education","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what requirements there are for maintained schools to have access to a specialist autism teacher.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189855","189855"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40601","2014-03-03","Department for Education","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the financial consequences are of moving to academy status for schools in the Metropolitan Borough of Dudley.","Biography information for Margot James","Margot James","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189857","189857"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40602","2014-03-03","Department for Education","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what guidance his Department offers to schools about the exclusion of students with autism.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189853","189853"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40603","2014-03-03","Department for Education","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what support and training exists in England for teachers to improve their ability to teach students with autism.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189854","189854"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40604","2014-03-03","Department for Education","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 12 February 2014 to the hon. Member for Christchurch, Official Report, columns 649-50W, for what reasons bursary decisions for the academic year 2014-15 were not made after enrolment data for 2013-14 became available.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mrs Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190021","190021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40605","2014-03-03","Department for Education","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many pagers have been provided to staff by his Department since May 2010; and what the cost to the Department was of providing those pagers.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190048","190048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40606","2014-03-04","Department for Education","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer to the hon. Member for Cardiff West, Official Report, column 360W, on teachers: surveys; on what date he plans to publish the findings of the Teacher Workload Diary Survey 2013.","Biography information for Mr David Ward","Mr David Ward","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190003","190003"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40607","2014-03-03","Department for Education","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what criteria are used to decide on the level of bursaries offered to (a) trainee religious education teachers and (b) teachers who specialise in other subjects.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mrs Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189979","189979"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40608","2014-03-03","Department for Education","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department plans to take to increase the number of trainee religious education teachers.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mrs Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189980","189980"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40609","2014-03-06","Department for Education","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what monitoring procedures his Department has in place to ensure that assessment of pupils' special needs are accurate.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190008","190008"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40610","2014-03-03","Department for Education","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to improve the morale of teachers.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190019","190019"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40611","2014-03-03","Department for Education","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when the Government expects to publish its detailed consultation on the National Funding Formula for schools.","Biography information for Mr Robin Walker","Mr Robin Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190025","190025"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40612","2014-03-03","Department for Education","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the total value of all land owned by schools where title deeds have been transferred from local authorities to academies.","Biography information for Mr Brian H. Donohoe","Mr Brian H. Donohoe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189956","189956"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40613","2014-03-03","Department for Education","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the total cost has been of legal fees involved in the transfer of title deeds for schools from local authorities to academies to date.","Biography information for Mr Brian H. Donohoe","Mr Brian H. Donohoe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189957","189957"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40614","2014-03-03","Department for Education","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department takes to monitor the value of land sold off by academies.","Biography information for Mr Brian H. Donohoe","Mr Brian H. Donohoe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189958","189958"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40615","2014-03-03","Department for Education","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 5 November 2013, Official Report, column 1158W, on pupils: disadvantaged, how many secondary school students sitting GCSEs were eligible for free schools meals in 2012-13; what number and proportion of such students were entered for the EBacc suite of subjects; how many and what proportion of such students achieved grades A* to C in EBacc subjects in 2012-13; and what proportion of such students entered for the EBacc achieved the required grades.","Biography information for Graham Stuart","Mr Graham Stuart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189963","189963"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40616","2014-03-03","Department for Education","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department takes to monitor the whereabouts of title deeds for schools in the UK.","Biography information for Mr Brian H. Donohoe","Mr Brian H. Donohoe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189955","189955"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40617","2014-03-06","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what criteria his Department used in its choice of Zig Bee wireless standard for the UK's smart meter roll-out.","Biography information for Graham Stringer","Graham Stringer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190010","190010"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40618","2014-03-06","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate he has made of the number of smart meters currently in use which do not meet Ofgem's regulations on smart meters.","Biography information for Graham Stringer","Graham Stringer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190011","190011"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40619","2014-03-06","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what recent estimate he has made of the cost of a smart meter which is compliant with government regulations.","Biography information for Graham Stringer","Graham Stringer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190012","190012"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40620","2014-03-06","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what recent estimate he has made of the total cost of the roll-out of smart meters to the year 2020.","Biography information for Graham Stringer","Graham Stringer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190013","190013"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40621","2014-03-06","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, which smart phones are compatible with the UK-regulated smart meters.","Biography information for Graham Stringer","Graham Stringer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190014","190014"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40622","2014-03-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many pagers have been provided to staff by his Department since May 2010; and what the cost to the Department was of providing those pagers.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190049","190049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40623","2014-03-04","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, when he will reply to the letter sent to him in February 2014 by the hon. Member for Broxbourne on behalf of the Procedure Committee on a parliamentary question from the right hon. Member for Don Valley on the introduction of a ring-fence between the generation and retail arms of vertically integrated energy companies.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189887","189887"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40624","2014-03-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps his Department plans to take to ensure energy companies meet the targets agreed with his Department for spending on efficiency schemes and reducing fuel poverty.","Biography information for Lord Watts","Mr Dave Watts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189950","189950"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40625","2014-03-04","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many Green Deal assessments were paid for by private individuals in 2013.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189928","189928"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40626","2014-03-04","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many Green Deal assessments were carried out through (a) the Carbon Emission Reductions Obligation, (b) the Carbon Savings Community Obligation, (c) the Home Heating Cost Reduction Obligation and (d) the Green Deal cash back in 2013.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189924","189924"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40627","2014-03-04","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many Green Deal assessments were carried out by local authorities in 2013.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189925","189925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40628","2014-03-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what recent assessment he has made of the performance of his Department in the roll-out of smart meters in the UK.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189848","189848"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40629","2014-03-04","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, when he will reply to the letter sent to him on 29 January 2014 by the right hon. Member for Don Valley on the introduction of a ring-fence between generation and retail within vertically integrated energy companies.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189895","189895"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40630","2014-03-03","Department of Health","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many food authenticity tests on composition, labelling and safety were carried out by (a) local authorities and (b) the Food Standards Authority as part of local authority audits in the UK in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189844","189844"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40631","2014-03-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he agrees with Professor Chris Elliott that there has been a culture of casual dishonesty in the food industry; and what measures his Department is considering to encourage strict adherence to the law and regulations in that industry.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189866","189866"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40632","2014-03-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make an estimate of the number of racehorses killed outright or destroyed at (a) Cheltenham and (b) Aintree racecourse in 2013.","Biography information for Chris Williamson","Chris Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189927","189927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40633","2014-03-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 28 November 2013, Official Report, column 395W, on organised crime, what recent assessment his Department and the Food Standards Agency has made of the annual cost to the economy of organised food crime.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189842","189842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40634","2014-03-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether there is a limit on business support, excluding rate relief, which can be provided to a single business to cover costs related to floods.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189883","189883"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40635","2014-03-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the Envrionment Agency's highest points for each of the rivers on the Isle of Wight are.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Turner","Mr Andrew Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189900","189900"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40636","2014-03-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make it his policy to allow (a) social housing providers and (b) local authorities to claim for flood relief funding provided to freehold owners of flood affected properties.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189884","189884"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40637","2014-03-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether leasehold tenants will be eligible for (a) Government assistance if they have been flooded or (b) flood insurance under the Flood Re scheme to cover household contents.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189885","189885"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40638","2014-03-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps the Environment Agency is taking to protect houses in Chester Road, Warrington next to the River Mersey from flooding.","Biography information for David Mowat","David Mowat","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189858","189858"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40639","2014-03-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions he has had on the UK receiving funding from the European Union Solidarity Fund following the recent floods.","Biography information for Sir Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189865","189865"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40640","2014-03-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department takes to prevent horses and ponies being exported for slaughter.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189860","189860"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40641","2014-03-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if his Department will make an estimate of (a) the proportion of households in the UK that would see a decrease in their annual water bills if their bills were calculated by water meters as opposed to rateable value and (b) what the average saving would be.","Biography information for Sir Graham Brady","Mr Graham Brady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189864","189864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40642","2014-03-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many pagers have been provided to staff by his Department since May 2010; and what the cost to the Department was of providing those pagers.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190050","190050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40643","2014-03-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 11 February 2014, Official Report, column 574W, on biodiversity offsetting, what assessment he has made of (a) the findings on offsetting of the report from the Commissioner for Environmental Sustainability on Victoria's environment and (b) reports from Canberra that conservation activities that would have happened anyway are being claimed as offsets in contravention of the principle of additionality; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190023","190023"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40644","2014-03-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent steps he has taken to ensure that local authorities lead on the management of local flood risk.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189978","189978"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40645","2014-03-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 26 February 2014, Official Report, column 355W, on cattle: transport, how many applications from farmers seeking to move individual animals or an entire herd subject to disease specific movement controls during the recent flooding period his Department has (a) received and (b) granted.","Biography information for Tracey Crouch","Tracey Crouch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189944","189944"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40646","2014-03-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many reptiles were imported into the EU according to Eurostat in each year from 2001 to 2013.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189906","189906"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40647","2014-03-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if his Department and the Food Standards Authority will bring forward legislative proposals to introduce greater maximum penalties for those convicted of food crime in the UK.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189965","189965"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40648","2014-03-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent steps he has taken to ensure that local authorities tackle local problems of flooding by working with all relevant parties, establishing ownership and legal responsibility.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189975","189975"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40649","2014-03-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent steps he has taken to ensure that local surface water management plans, as set out under PPS25 and co-ordinated by local authorities provide the basis for managing all local flood risk.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189976","189976"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40650","2014-03-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations his Department has received from the Bosnia-Herzegovinian government on the political and security situation in that country.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190007","190007"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40651","2014-03-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many pagers have been provided to staff by his Department since May 2010; and what the cost to the Department was of providing those pagers.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190051","190051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40652","2014-03-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to his Iranian counterpart for the release of Saeed Abedini.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189879","189879"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40653","2014-03-03","Department of Health","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how NHS England and the Health and Social Care Information Centre will monitor data collection against Quality Outcomes Framework disease management measures which will be retired in April 2014; and how often such data will be published.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189845","189845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40654","2014-03-03","Department of Health","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what clinical targets will remain within general practice to help identify and manage patients with high risk factors of (a) cardiovascular disease and (b) high cholesterol and HbA1C levels.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189846","189846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40655","2014-03-03","Department of Health","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress he has made in implementing the recommendations of the Cardiovascular Disease Outcomes Strategy.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189847","189847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40656","2014-03-03","Department of Health","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he has taken to ensure there is continuity in data collection on GP practice performance against Quality Outcomes Framework disease management measures which are to be retired in April 2014.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189849","189849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40657","2014-03-04","Department of Health","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 13 February 2014, Official Report, columns 840-1W, on meningitis, if he will publish the report to him by the Committee on Vaccinations and Immunisation of their two meetings in February. [R]","Biography information for Sir Paul Beresford","Sir Paul Beresford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189892","189892"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40658","2014-03-04","Department of Health","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to bring the new vaccine for Crohn's disease developed by Professor Hermon-Taylor forward to the human trial stage; and how much funding his Department has allocated to such work.","Biography information for Sir Paul Beresford","Sir Paul Beresford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189893","189893"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40659","2014-03-04","Department of Health","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the spending on locum doctors was in accident and emergency at the (a) Princess Royal Hospital in Haywards Heath and (b) Royal Sussex County Hospital in Brighton in each year since 2005; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189894","189894"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40660","2014-03-05","Department of Health","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many cancer treatments the National Institute for Health and Care Excellence has (a) recommended, (b) recommended on an optimised basis and (c) not recommended in (i) 2010-11, (ii) 2011-12, (iii) 2012-13 and (iv) 2013-14 to date; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Simon Burns","Mr Simon Burns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189902","189902"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40661","2014-03-05","Department of Health","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions his Department has had with NHS England on the Specialised Services budget; what the content of those discussions was; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Simon Burns","Mr Simon Burns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189903","189903"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40662","2014-03-05","Department of Health","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) outpatient and (b) inpatient admission episodes with a (i) primary and (ii) secondary diagnosis of cancer, for which Welsh commissioners were responsible there were in England in each of the last ten years.","Biography information for Sir Simon Burns","Mr Simon Burns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189904","189904"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40663","2014-03-05","Department of Health","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the effectiveness of the Cancer Drugs Fund.","Biography information for Sir Simon Burns","Mr Simon Burns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189905","189905"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40664","2014-03-03","Cabinet Office","2014-02-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many deaths of (a) infants, (b) children, (c) adults and (d) elderly people have been recorded in the UK from antibiotic-resistant bacterial meningitis infection by age group in each year since 1990.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189930","189930"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40665","2014-03-04","Department of Health","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many commissioning access policies are being developed by NHS England; when they will be completed; and what rules apply to patient treatment pending their completion.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189948","189948"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40666","2014-03-04","Department of Health","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many NHS staff were assigned to specialised commissioning in (a) 2011-12, (b) 2012-13 and (c) 2013-14; and what level of expenditure they were responsible for in each such year.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189949","189949"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40667","2014-03-03","Department of Health","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of the National Institute for Health and Care Excellence's conditions for treatment with mindfulness-based therapies; and which such treatments have been taken up by the NHS.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189874","189874"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40668","2014-03-04","Department of Health","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many trained nurses were not registered to practice in England in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190035","190035"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40669","2014-03-03","Department of Health","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many pagers have been provided to staff by his Department since May 2010; and what the cost to the Department was of providing those pagers.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190053","190053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40670","2014-03-04","Department of Health","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many nurses there were per 100,000 population in (a) the latest month for which figures are available and (b) the equivalent month in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190036","190036"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40671","2014-03-03","Department of Health","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Answer of 16 November 2010, Official Report, column 958W, on pathogens: climate change, what recent assessment he has made of the effect of climate change on (a) physical and (b) mental health of UK residents; and if he will produce an updated version of his Department's 2008 assessment of the possible effect of climate change on mental health entitled, Health Effects of Climate Change in the UK.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190028","190028"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40672","2014-03-04","Department of Health","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the total expenditure of the Cancer Drugs Fund was in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12 and (c) 2012-13.","Biography information for Sir Simon Burns","Mr Simon Burns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189994","189994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40673","2014-03-04","Department of Health","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, by what process and timetable commissioning access policies are developed and agreed when a treatment breaches the current maximum threshold of five individual funding requests in any one NHS England region.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190004","190004"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40674","2014-03-04","Department of Health","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information his Department holds on how many nurses will retire in the next five years.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190040","190040"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40675","2014-03-03","Department of Health","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much the NHS spent in Cannock Chase constituency in (a) 2006-07, (b) 2008-09, (c) 2010-11 and (d) 2012-13.","Biography information for Mr Aidan Burley","Mr Aidan Burley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189972","189972"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40676","2014-03-03","Department of Health","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many reported incidents of self-harm there were by people under the age of 18 in (a) Staffordshire and (b) Cannock Chase constituency in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Aidan Burley","Mr Aidan Burley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189971","189971"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40677","2014-03-03","Department of Health","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what criteria his Department will use to formulate new guidelines on compliance with the Abortion Act.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189909","189909"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40678","2014-03-03","Department of Health","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which organisations and individuals he is consulting prior to the publication of new guidelines on compliance with the Abortion Act; whether the British Pregnancy Advisory Service and Marie Stopes International will be, or have been, consulted; and whether he will publish draft proposals so that other parties may contribute to the process.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189910","189910"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40679","2014-03-03","Department of Health","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential demand for IVF if the NHS adopted universal provision.","Biography information for Paul Uppal","Paul Uppal","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189981","189981"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40680","2014-03-03","Department of Health","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what criteria are used to determine how many rounds of IVF are made available to those who qualify through the NHS.","Biography information for Paul Uppal","Paul Uppal","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189982","189982"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40681","2014-03-03","Department of Health","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions his Department has had with the General Medical Council on the inclusion of climate change effects on health in the next revision of the Tomorrow's Doctors publication on standards for teaching, learning and assessment of medical students; when  the next edition of this document will be published; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189987","189987"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40682","2014-03-03","Department of Health","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what change there has been in the time taken to pay NHS suppliers since May 2010.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189984","189984"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40683","2014-03-03","Department of Health","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidance his Department issues on the proportion of NHS spend which should be spent with small businesses.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189985","189985"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40684","2014-03-03","Department of Health","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what targets he has set for the time taken by the NHS to pay its suppliers.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189986","189986"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40685","2014-03-03","Department of Health","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his policy is on the NHS providing (a) one, (b) two and (c) three rounds of IVF to those who qualify through the NHS.","Biography information for Paul Uppal","Paul Uppal","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189988","189988"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40686","2014-03-03","Home Office","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many pagers have been provided to staff by her Department since May 2010; and what the cost to the Department was of providing those pagers.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190054","190054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40687","2014-03-04","Home Office","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what guidance her Department issues to police forces on circumstances under which it should refer a complaint to the Independent Police Complaints Commission.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189881","189881"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40688","2014-03-04","Home Office","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent advice she has received from the Child Exploitation and Online Protection Centre on written material used in child sexual abuse.","Biography information for Sir Paul Beresford","Sir Paul Beresford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189926","189926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40689","2014-03-04","Home Office","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of cases refused by entry clearance officers were overturned on appeal in the last year for which  data is available.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189923","189923"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40690","2014-03-03","Department for International Development","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many pagers have been provided to staff by her Department since May 2010; and what the cost to the Department was of providing those pagers.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190055","190055"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40691","2014-03-04","Department for International Development","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, which current contracts awarded by her Department did not go through ordinary tender processes.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189977","189977"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40692","2014-03-03","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what his latest estimate is of the average annual cost of custody in the secure estate.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189993","189993"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40693","2014-03-04","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many complaints his Department has received from (a) members of the public and (b) staff in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189990","189990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40694","2014-03-04","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many 18, 19 and 20 year olds are currently held in adult prisons.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189991","189991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40695","2014-03-03","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) 18, (b) 19 and (c) 20 year olds were held in the secure estate in England and Wales on 1 February 2014.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189911","189911"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40696","2014-03-03","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many vacancies there were for posts in the new (a) National Probation Service and (b) community rehabilitation companies on 1 February 2014.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189938","189938"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40697","2014-03-03","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many senior management posts there will be in the new National Probation Service and the community rehabilitation companies.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189939","189939"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40698","2014-03-06","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department is taking to tackle delays in the family justice system.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190005","190005"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40699","2014-03-03","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what fees are charged for proceedings in the Commercial Court.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189967","189967"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40700","2014-03-03","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many pagers have been provided to staff by his Department since May 2010; and what the cost to the Department was of providing those pagers.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190056","190056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40701","2014-03-03","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the proven re-offending rates were for 18 to 20 year olds in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190038","190038"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40702","2014-03-04","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what average length of custodial sentence was handed down to those aged 18, 19 or 20 and found guilty of criminal offences and receiving a custodial sentence in 2013.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189896","189896"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40703","2014-03-04","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of people aged 18, 19 or 20 who were found guilty of criminal offences received a custodial sentence in 2013.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189897","189897"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40704","2014-03-03","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many offenders convicted of (a) murder and (b) manslaughter and serving prison sentences were later reassessed and re-categorised to the open prison category; and how many of such offenders have absconded from an open prison since 1984.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189850","189850"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40705","2014-03-03","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many women with a registered home address in Wales were sentenced and remanded to prison in each year since 2006; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189867","189867"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40706","2014-03-03","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, in which prisons women with a registered home address in Wales were held in (a) 2011, (b) 2012 and (c) 2013; how many were held in each prison; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189868","189868"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40707","2014-03-03","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average length of custodial sentence for women with a registered home address in Wales was in each year since 2006; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189869","189869"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40708","2014-03-03","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many women prisoners with a registered home address in Wales have applied for a place in a mother and baby unit since 2006; how many have been given a place; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189870","189870"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40709","2014-03-03","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many senior management posts there were across all probation trusts on 1 February 2014.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189940","189940"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40710","2014-03-04","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many complaints have been received against named Ministers of his Department from (a) his Department's staff and staff of its agencies and (b) members of the public since May 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189945","189945"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40711","2014-03-04","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many transgender prisoners there were on 1 February (a) 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012, (d) 2013 and (e) 2014.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189946","189946"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40712","2014-03-03","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many Commercial Court proceedings lasted (a) one, (b) up to five, (c) up to 10 and (d) over 10 days in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189941","189941"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40713","2014-03-04","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many releases from prison in error there have been in each month since May 2010, by category of prisoner.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189947","189947"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40714","2014-03-03","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much was received in fees by the public purse through cases held in the Commercial Court in 2013 or most recent full year for which figures can be provided.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189931","189931"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40715","2014-03-03","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what average length of time a prison governor has spent in post in England and Wales over the last five years.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189934","189934"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40716","2014-03-03","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, for how many months each current incumbent governor of prisons in England and Wales has been in post.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189935","189935"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40717","2014-03-03","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the (a) operating costs were and (b) income was generated by the Commercial Court in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189936","189936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40718","2014-03-03","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many governors there have been in post since May 2010 in each prison in England and Wales.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189937","189937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40719","2014-03-03","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many previous prisons each prison governor in England and Wales has governed.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189933","189933"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40720","2014-03-03","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, in what proportion of cases heard in the Commercial Court in each of the last 10 years one or more of the parties was domiciled or registered outside the jurisdiction.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189932","189932"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40721","2014-03-04","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people aged 18, 19 or 20 received a custodial sentence of (a) under six months, (b) under 12 months, (c) under 18 months, (d) under 24 months, (e) under five years, (f) under 10 years, (g) under 20 years and (h) 20 years or over in 2013.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189898","189898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40722","2014-03-03","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners who have escaped prison have been re-captured and jailed at a different prison nearer to their home in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189856","189856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40723","2014-03-03","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what offences were committed by women with a registered home address in Wales sentenced to prison in each year since 2006; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189871","189871"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40724","2014-03-04","Northern Ireland Office","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many letters were sent to on-the-runs (a) between the signing of the Good Friday Agreement and December 2005 and (b) after December 2005.","Biography information for Mr Ben Wallace","Mr Ben Wallace","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189899","189899"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40725","2014-03-03","Northern Ireland Office","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many pagers have been provided to staff by her Department since May 2010; and what the cost to the Department was of providing those pagers.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190057","190057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40726","2014-03-03","Scotland Office","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how many pagers have been provided to staff by his Department since May 2010; and what the cost to the Department was of providing those pagers.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190058","190058"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40727","2014-03-03","Scotland Office","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what assessment he has made of the Scottish Government's plans for Scottish pensions in the event of independence.","Biography information for John Robertson","John Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190018","190018"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40728","2014-03-03","Department for Transport","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many pagers have been provided to staff by his Department since May 2010; and what the cost to the Department was of providing those pagers.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190059","190059"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40729","2014-03-04","Department for Transport","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 13 February 2014, Official Report, column 716W, on Office for Low Emission Vehicles, whether the 170 million projected to be unspent over the period 2010 to 2015 will roll over into the next Parliament in addition to or as part of the 500 million commitment for the uptake of ultra low emission vehicles from 2015 to 2020 referred to in the Answer of 25 November 2013 to the hon. Member for Strangford, Official Report, column 102W, on fuels.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190034","190034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40730","2014-03-03","Department for Transport","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he has a veto power in relation to ports on COM(2013)296 on the proposed regulation of European ports.","Biography information for Austin Mitchell","Austin Mitchell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190041","190041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40731","2014-03-04","Department for Transport","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 26 February 2014, Official Report, column 389W, on the Oxford to Hereford railway line, for what reasons he does not plan to ask train operators to break down the performance of individual routes within a large franchise area when publishing Passenger Charter figures.","Biography information for Sir Peter Luff","Sir Peter Luff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190001","190001"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40732","2014-03-04","Department for Transport","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 26 February 2014, Official Report, column 389W, on the Oxford to Hereford railway line, how many through passenger services operated between Evesham and London Paddington in the year immediately before the partial redoubling of the North Cotswold line; and how many such services operate under the present timetable.","Biography information for Sir Peter Luff","Sir Peter Luff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190002","190002"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40733","2014-03-03","Department for Transport","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the cost of rail electrification to electricity network operators.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189841","189841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40734","2014-03-04","Department for Transport","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what effect expansion at Gatwick would have on runoff water levels in West Sussex and surrounding areas in cases of severe weather; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189891","189891"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40735","2014-03-03","Department for Transport","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much was paid to Scotland under the Barnett formula as a consequence of his Department's expenditure on (a) roads and (b) railways in each of the last three years for which information is available.","Biography information for Michael Connarty","Michael Connarty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189851","189851"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40736","2014-03-03","Department for Transport","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate his Department has made of the (a) number of journeys affected by and (b) the total cost of road closures as a result of flooding in Worcester during February 2014.","Biography information for Mr Robin Walker","Mr Robin Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189942","189942"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40737","2014-03-03","Wales Office","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how many pagers have been provided to staff by his Department since May 2010; and what the cost to the Department was of providing those pagers.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190061","190061"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40738","2014-03-03","Women and Equalities","2014-02-27","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, how many pagers have been provided to staff by the Government Equalities Office since May 2010; and what the cost to the Government Equalities Office was of providing those pagers.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190052","190052"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40739","2014-03-04","Cabinet Office","2014-02-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many individuals moved (a) twice and (b) three or more times from (i) employment to unemployment or inactivity and (ii) unemployment or inactivity to employment in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190033","190033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40740","2014-03-04","Cabinet Office","2014-02-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will estimate how many people moved at least once from (a) employment to unemployment, (b) employment to inactivity, (c) unemployment to employment, (d) unemployment to inactivity, (e) inactivity to employment and (f) inactivity to unemployment in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190030","190030"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40741","2014-03-04","Cabinet Office","2014-02-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what proportion of people who moved from employment to unemployment or inactivity had (a) no qualifications, (b) a highest qualification below Level 2, (c) a highest qualification at Level 2, (d) a highest qualification at Level 3 and (e) a highest qualification at Level 4 or above.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190029","190029"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40742","2014-03-04","Cabinet Office","2014-02-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what proportion of the people who moved from employment to unemployment or inactivity in the last year had a partner in (a) full-time work and (b) part-time work at the point before they left employment.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190031","190031"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40743","2014-03-04","Cabinet Office","2014-02-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what proportion of the people who moved from employment to unemployment or inactivity in the last year had a household income (a) below 15,000, (b) below 25,000, (c) below 50,000 and (d) 50,000 or above at the point before they left employment.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190032","190032"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40744","2014-03-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of people who have died within six weeks of their benefits being stopped in each month of (a) 2011, (b) 2012, (c) 2013 and (d) 2014 to date.","Biography information for John Robertson","John Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190039","190039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40745","2014-03-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much of the former Remploy workers' individual funding grants have been distributed to these workers.","Biography information for Teresa Pearce","Teresa Pearce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190024","190024"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40746","2014-03-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many pagers have been provided to staff by his Department since May 2010; and what the cost to the Department was of providing those pagers.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190062","190062"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40747","2014-03-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to implement the report Getting in, staying in and getting on, published in June 2011.","Biography information for Teresa Pearce","Teresa Pearce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190020","190020"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40748","2014-03-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many self-employed people were fined by the Health and Safety Executive in each year since May 2010.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189983","189983"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40749","2014-03-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in Cannock Chase under the age of 25 years old are in receipt of housing benefit.","Biography information for Mr Aidan Burley","Mr Aidan Burley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189969","189969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40750","2014-03-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many benefit sanctions were issued in Cannock Chase constituency in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Aidan Burley","Mr Aidan Burley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189968","189968"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40751","2014-03-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the Government's Disability Confident campaign in helping more people with disabilities (a) into work and (b) to fulfil their potential.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190009","190009"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40752","2014-03-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of former Remploy workers' individual funding grants remain to be distributed before the conclusion of this programme; and what estimate he has made of whether any such funding will go unclaimed.","Biography information for Teresa Pearce","Teresa Pearce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189966","189966"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40753","2014-03-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many former Remploy workers have found employment.","Biography information for Teresa Pearce","Teresa Pearce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189959","189959"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40754","2014-03-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the proportion of former Remploy workers who are (a) unemployed, (b) in full-time employment and (c) in part-time employment is following the closure of the Remploy factory network.","Biography information for Teresa Pearce","Teresa Pearce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189960","189960"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40755","2014-03-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, for what purposes have grants given to former Remploy worker's individual funding grants been used.","Biography information for Teresa Pearce","Teresa Pearce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189962","189962"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40756","2014-03-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will provide additional funding to former workers in Remploy sites who have opened their own businesses.","Biography information for Teresa Pearce","Teresa Pearce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189953","189953"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40757","2014-03-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will take steps to provide former Remploy workers living in England a grant based on wage incentives.","Biography information for Teresa Pearce","Teresa Pearce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189954","189954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40758","2014-03-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will extend the former Remploy worker's financial support scheme.","Biography information for Teresa Pearce","Teresa Pearce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189961","189961"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40759","2014-03-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people who were receiving the higher rate of the mobility component of disability living allowance at 1 January 2013 have had this payment stopped; and what proportion of all such recipients of disability living allowance this represents.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189880","189880"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40760","2014-03-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people who used the Motability Scheme to lease a car from 1 January 2013 have had the car taken away from them as they no longer receive the higher rate of the mobility component of disability living allowance.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189862","189862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40761","2014-03-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made in the trends in successful welfare benefit appeals over the last six years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189878","189878"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40762","2014-03-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many appeals were made by recipients of welfare benefits against decisions made by his Department in each of the last five years for which data is available; how many such appeals were successful; and what proportion of total appeals they represent.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189876","189876"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40763","2014-03-03","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what plans he has to charge recipients of welfare benefit who appeal against decisions made by his Department.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189875","189875"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40764","2014-03-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he has taken to improve the quality of welfare benefit decisions.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189877","189877"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40765","2014-03-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people were leasing a car through the Motability scheme on 1 January 2013; and what proportion of all those eligible to lease a car through that scheme they represent.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189859","189859"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40973","2014-03-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what contribution he plans to make to address the humanitarian needs of Bedouin forcibly removed from the Negev.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame M. Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 902819","902819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41007","2014-03-05","Department for International Development","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to promote freedom of religion and belief.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 902827","902827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41008","2014-03-05","Department for International Development","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what plans the Government has to increase the proportion of the aid budget disbursed through the private sector; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 902824","902824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41009","2014-03-05","Department for International Development","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent steps her Department has taken to tackle female genital mutilation; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Nick de Bois","Nick de Bois","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 902828","902828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41283","2014-03-05","Department for International Development","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent assessment she has made of the humanitarian situation in Syria.","Biography information for Anas Sarwar","Anas Sarwar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 902831","902831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41369","2014-03-05","Department for International Development","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what work her Department is supporting to promote the re-establishment of democracy in Egypt.","Biography information for Roger Williams","Roger Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 902832","902832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41370","2014-03-05","Department for International Development","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to help reduce the number of preventable newborn deaths worldwide.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 902830","902830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41371","2014-03-05","Department for International Development","2014-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how her Department plans to develop, implement and monitor the strategic priority on violence against women and girls in its next operational plan starting in 2015.","Biography information for Baroness Blackwood of North Oxford","Nicola Blackwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 902829","902829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40147","2014-02-28","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many men have been charged under section 53A of the Sexual Offences Act 2003, as inserted by section 14 of the Policing and Crime Act 2009 since 1 April 2010; how many successful prosecutions resulted; and what penalty was imposed in each case.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189537","189537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40148","2014-03-03","Northern Ireland Office","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, whether information obtained from a case review undertaken by the Police Service of Northern Ireland Historic Enquiries Team which could lead to prosecution would be considered new evidence under the terms of the letters of comfort issued to so-called on-the-runs and therefore permitting prosecutions rather than as evidence already in existence at the time of the issue of the letter and therefore preventing prosecutions proceeding.","Biography information for Naomi Long","Naomi Long","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189728","189728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40149","2014-03-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what proportion of (a) all students and (b) students from a Muslim background have taken up student loan finance in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189743","189743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40150","2014-03-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the proportion of students eligible to receive student loan finance who are from a Muslim background.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189747","189747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40151","2014-02-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many apprentices the space industry supported in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12 and (c) 2012-13.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189695","189695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40152","2014-02-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, when the Government's response to the Whistleblowing framework: Call for Evidence will be published.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189651","189651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40153","2014-02-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what funding his Department provides for innovation in British food procurement.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189652","189652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40154","2014-02-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent assessment he has made of the work of the (a) National Apprenticeship Service and (b) Skills Funding Agency office in Princes Parade, Liverpool.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Mrs Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189536","189536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40155","2014-02-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will contact Google management to ask them to remove from Google all unofficial websites asking for money for services provided by the Land Registry.","Biography information for Mr George Galloway","Mr George Galloway","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189560","189560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40156","2014-03-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the Government's current definition of apprenticeships is for the purpose of reporting on apprenticeship starts and achievements.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189626","189626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40157","2014-03-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether he plans to amend his Department's definition of an apprenticeship as a result of the recommendations set out in The Future of Apprenticeships in England: Implementation Plan.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189627","189627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40158","2014-03-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the role of the Sector Skills Council will be in the formulation of the apprenticeships frameworks set out in The Future of Apprenticeships in England: Guidance for Trailblazers.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189628","189628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40159","2014-03-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, for what reasons grading was introduced as an essential feature of future apprenticeships frameworks.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189629","189629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40160","2014-02-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 24 February 2014, Official Report, column 168W, on telephone services, when his Department expects to implement the new Package Travel Directive Extending basic rate telephone provision.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189562","189562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40161","2014-02-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many post offices have been located in (a) Livingston constituency and (b) West Lothian in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Graeme Morrice","Graeme Morrice","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189524","189524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40162","2014-02-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many Post Office branches have closed in (a) Livingston constituency and (b) West Lothian in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Graeme Morrice","Graeme Morrice","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189525","189525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40163","2014-02-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many Post Office branches in (a) Livingston constituency and (b) West Lothian have reduced their opening hours in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Graeme Morrice","Graeme Morrice","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189526","189526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40164","2014-02-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many Post Office branches in (a) Livingston constituency and (b) West Lothian have reduced the number of services on offer in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Graeme Morrice","Graeme Morrice","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189527","189527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40165","2014-02-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many people were employed by the Post Office in (a) Livingston constituency and (b) West Lothian in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Graeme Morrice","Graeme Morrice","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189528","189528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40166","2014-02-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what support his Department has given to Post Office branches to diversify their services since May 2010.","Biography information for Graeme Morrice","Graeme Morrice","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189530","189530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40167","2014-02-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what research his Department has conducted into the social benefit of Post Office branches to local communities.","Biography information for Graeme Morrice","Graeme Morrice","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189529","189529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40168","2014-02-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what his future plans are for the (a) National Apprenticeship Service and (b) Skills Funding Agency office in Princes Parade, Liverpool.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Mrs Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189535","189535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40169","2014-02-28","Cabinet Office","2014-02-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what recent estimate the Office for National Statistics has made of the proportion of manufacturing jobs held by women in (a) each English region, (b) Scotland, (c) Wales and (d) Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189625","189625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40170","2014-02-28","Cabinet Office","2014-02-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will contact Google management to ask them to remove from Google all unofficial websites asking for money for services provided by DVLA.","Biography information for Mr George Galloway","Mr George Galloway","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189559","189559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40171","2014-02-28","Cabinet Office","2014-02-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much in public duty costs allowance has been paid to each former Prime Minister in each year since 2010; what the limit is of the public duty costs allowance for former Prime Ministers; when that limit was last reviewed; whether the public duty costs allowance is payable in addition to their parliamentary allowances to former Prime Ministers who remain Members of Parliament; what audit is undertaken of claims made under the public duty costs allowance by former Prime Ministers; what checks are made to ensure that claims against the allowance meet the criteria for funding from the allowance; what guidance is provided to former Prime Ministers on claiming from the public duty costs allowance; and if he will place in the Library a copy of that guidance.","Biography information for Pete Wishart","Pete Wishart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189655","189655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40172","2014-03-03","Cabinet Office","2014-02-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the oral Answer to the hon. Member for Vale of Glamorgan on 11 December 2013, column 224, on Civil Service (union facility time), in which Departments the trade union officers who were promoted in post while doing no work as a civil servant were employed; and in which Department the officer who was promoted twice was employed.","Biography information for Heidi Alexander","Heidi Alexander","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189659","189659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40173","2014-02-28","Cabinet Office","2014-02-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the standardised mortality rate from prostate cancer was in each year since 1997, broken down by (a) Government office region and (b) parliamentary constituency.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189609","189609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40174","2014-02-28","Cabinet Office","2014-02-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many deaths from prostate cancer there were in each (a) Government Office region and (b) age group in each year since 1997.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189613","189613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40175","2014-03-11","Cabinet Office","2014-02-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether any records relating to the loss of the escort aircraft carrier HMS Dasher in March 1943 have (a) been retained from transfer to and (b) remain closed in the National Archives; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Julian Lewis","Dr Julian Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189731","189731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40176","2014-03-03","HM Treasury","2014-02-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people claimed relief under the Rent-A-Room scheme in each of the last 10 years; and what the cost to the public purse of such relief has been.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189735","189735"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40177","2014-03-03","HM Treasury","2014-02-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of abolishing Air Passenger Duty bands D and C and moving all countries in these bands into Air Passenger Duty band B.","Biography information for Nick de Bois","Nick de Bois","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189664","189664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40178","2014-03-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will take steps to protect Eritreans working in this country from the Eritrean government's attempts to collect 2 per cent tax from them.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189663","189663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40179","2014-03-03","HM Treasury","2014-02-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 13 February 2014, Official Report, column 825W, on national insurance contributions, what the total value was of class 1 national insurance contribution paid by those earning less than the annualised primary threshold in each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189636","189636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40180","2014-03-03","HM Treasury","2014-02-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment he has made of the potential systemic and operational risks of high frequency trading.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189635","189635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40181","2014-02-28","HM Treasury","2014-02-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans his Department has to review the position of sixth form colleges in relation to VAT paid on purchases.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189573","189573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40182","2014-03-03","HM Treasury","2014-02-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent discussions he has had with UK and EU financial regulators about the regulation of high frequency trading.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189634","189634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40183","2014-03-03","HM Treasury","2014-02-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make it his policy to collect information on the number of employers who are not compliant with national minimum wage legislation at constituency level.","Biography information for Yvonne Fovargue","Yvonne Fovargue","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189569","189569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40184","2014-02-28","HM Treasury","2014-02-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what capital receipts have accrued to the Exchequer from the sale of UK housing in each year since 1984.","Biography information for Austin Mitchell","Austin Mitchell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189551","189551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40185","2014-03-03","HM Treasury","2014-02-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the total PAYE (income tax and national insurance) receipts were in each of the tax periods (a) November 2012 to January 2013 and (b) November 2013 to January 2014.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189565","189565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40186","2014-03-03","HM Treasury","2014-02-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what total employer liability for PAYE (income tax and national insurance) was reported by HM Revenue and Customs' PAYE RTI system for the three full tax months between November 2013 and January 2014.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189566","189566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40187","2014-03-03","HM Treasury","2014-02-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 24 February 2014, Official Report, columns 27-8W, on children: day care, by what method his Department has determined the estimated breakdown of basic and higher or additional rate taxpayers in receipt of employer-supported childcare vouchers.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189765","189765"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40188","2014-03-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many people in Chelmsford constituency in receipt of welfare and disability benefits are liable to pay council tax.","Biography information for Sir Simon Burns","Mr Simon Burns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189570","189570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40189","2014-02-28","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what advice his Department gives to local authorities on charging for sandbags.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189684","189684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40190","2014-02-28","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps she is taking to provide support to the families of problem and addicted gamblers.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189709","189709"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40191","2014-02-28","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions she has had with the Prime Minister about allowing British Overseas Territories and Crown Dependencies to lay individual wreaths at the Cenotaph on Remembrance Sunday.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189657","189657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40192","2014-02-28","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, on what dates a Type 45 destroyer has lost power resulting in the ship having to return to port for repairs; and where the repairs took place.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189654","189654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40193","2014-03-03","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what communications took place between the Director General of the Military Aviation Authority and the Air Chief Marshal on the Delete Tornado Warning System option in Planning Round 11.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189667","189667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40194","2014-03-03","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what communications his Department had with the Military Aviation Authority on the Delete Tornado Warning System option in Planning Round 11.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189668","189668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40195","2014-03-03","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the estimated cost saving was of the Delete Tornado Collision Warning System option in Planning Round 11.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189662","189662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40196","2014-03-03","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, who authorised the inclusion of the Delete Tornado Collision Warning System option in Planning Round 11; and what the reason was for its inclusion.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189660","189660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40197","2014-03-03","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, who cancelled the installation of the Tornado Collision Warning System proposed in Planning Round 11; and what the reason was for its cancellation.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189661","189661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40198","2014-02-28","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many serving members of the armed forces were issued with hearing aids from 2000 to 2013.","Biography information for Stephen Lloyd","Stephen Lloyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189677","189677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40199","2014-02-28","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what his policy on the use of cloud computing by NATO is; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189687","189687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40200","2014-02-28","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many NATO cyber exercises took place in each year from 2010; and how many such exercises are planned for 2014.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189696","189696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40201","2014-02-28","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent discussions he has had with (a) the NATO Secretary-General and (b) his NATO counterparts on bringing cyber-attacks against a member state under the Article 5 framework; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189683","189683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40202","2014-02-28","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he expects NATO's Computer Incident Response Capacity to reach full operating capacity.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189682","189682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40203","2014-02-28","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-02-26","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, pursuant to the Answer of 23 May 2013, Official Report, column 444W, on constituencies, what assessment he has made of the (a) fairness, (b) accuracy and (c) completeness of using the (i) census and midterm census and (ii) electoral register to determine the size of constituencies when drawing boundaries.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189639","189639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40204","2014-02-28","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-02-26","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, pursuant to the Answer of 5 March 2013, Official Report, column 971W, on Electoral Registration and Administration Act 2013, if he will give the ranking according to data matching rates of the authorities that took part in the data matching pilots for individual electoral registration.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189649","189649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40205","2014-02-28","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-02-26","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what steps he has taken to make hon. Members aware of the 4.2 million fund for increasing voter registration.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189637","189637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40206","2014-02-28","Department for Education","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will review his Department's guidance on school uniform in religion-specific schools to exclude items of clothing of religious significance so that they remain the right of the child to wear or not to wear.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189590","189590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40207","2014-02-28","Department for Education","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate his Department has made of the number of hours of additional support and extracurricular activities that young people aged 16-19 in the state sixth form college sector (a) received in each of the last six years and (b) will receive in each of the next four years.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189584","189584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40208","2014-02-28","Department for Education","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what representations he has received from the sixth form college sector on the effect of changes to its budget (a) on young people with special needs, (b) on young people who previously received free school meals and (c) generally.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189585","189585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40209","2014-02-28","Department for Education","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of expected increases in class sizes in sixth form colleges in each of the next four years.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189586","189586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40210","2014-02-28","Department for Education","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the (a) lowest and (b) highest number of children educated in a single free school class were in (i) 2012 and (ii) 2013.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189587","189587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40211","2014-02-28","Department for Education","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate his Department has made of the average class size in free schools open to date.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189588","189588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40212","2014-02-28","Department for Education","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the statistics published by his Department that demonstrate that a lower percentage than the average of children eligible for free school meals attend free schools compared with state primary schools.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189589","189589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40213","2014-02-28","Department for Education","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what representations he has received in the last three years on the effect of budget reductions on sixth form colleges.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189574","189574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40214","2014-02-28","Department for Education","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what his plans are for the future budget for sixth form college education beyond that already published.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189575","189575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40215","2014-02-28","Department for Education","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of reductions in funding for sixth form colleges on (a) careers guidance, (b) special educational needs support and (c) support for students with disabilities.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189576","189576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40216","2014-02-28","Department for Education","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of reductions in funding for sixth form colleges on (a) sports provision, (b) music and drama provision and (c) English language support.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189577","189577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40217","2014-02-28","Department for Education","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of reductions in funding for sixth form colleges on the availability of STEM courses in (a) England and (b) Yorkshire.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189578","189578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40218","2014-02-28","Department for Education","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of reductions in funding for sixth form colleges on the availability of modern language courses in (a) England and (b) Yorkshire.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189579","189579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40219","2014-02-28","Department for Education","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what consideration his Department has given to closing sixth form college provision in schools Ofsted Grade 3 or below to enable headteachers to focus on (a) core activity and (b) provision of GCSE-level education.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189580","189580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40220","2014-02-28","Department for Education","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what consideration his Department has given to Ofsted assessing and grading secondary and post-16 elements of joint provision separately in order to provide greater clarity for parents and young people choosing schools.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189581","189581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40221","2014-02-28","Department for Education","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what comparison his Department has made of value for money of free school sixth form places and existing sixth form places.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189582","189582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40222","2014-02-28","Department for Education","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what comparison his Department has made of the definition of a full-time 16-19 year old student in the UK with (a) other countries and (b) other European countries.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189583","189583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40223","2014-02-28","Department for Education","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking in schools to tackle female genital mutilation.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189707","189707"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40224","2014-03-03","Department for Education","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what guidance he has issued to schools on tackling (a) gender-based bullying and (b) sexual harassment; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189719","189719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40225","2014-02-28","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the net emissions reductions resulting from (a) onshore and (b) offshore wind has been in the last three years; and what such figures are including in the carbon footprint of (i) construction, (ii) backup technologies and (iii) connection to the grid of such turbines.","Biography information for Mr Stephen O'Brien","Mr Stephen O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189691","189691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40226","2014-02-28","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate he has made of overall savings in carbon dioxide emissions by 2020 as a result of (a) onshore and (b) offshore wind turbines; and what level of emissions will be emitted from the gas plants required for intermittent backup to such turbines in that period.","Biography information for Mr Stephen O'Brien","Mr Stephen O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189690","189690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40227","2014-02-28","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what recent discussions he has had with (a) Scottish Power and (b) Npower on the refunding of direct debit payments.","Biography information for John Robertson","John Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189706","189706"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40228","2014-02-28","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how much in total Government funding in subsidies for (a) onshore wind and (b) offshore wind was given in (i) 2012-13 and (ii) 2013-14.","Biography information for Mr Stephen O'Brien","Mr Stephen O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189686","189686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40229","2014-02-28","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how much carbon dioxide was emitted from backup technologies for wind turbines in the last year for which data is available.","Biography information for Mr Stephen O'Brien","Mr Stephen O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189688","189688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40230","2014-02-28","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, when he will announce his plans for the introduction of competitive auctions for renewable subsidies.","Biography information for Mr Stephen O'Brien","Mr Stephen O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189689","189689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40231","2014-02-28","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate his Department has made of the average consumption of energy for hot water and heating of a (a) two bedroom terrace house, (b) three bedroom semi-detached house and (c) four bedroom detached house.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189653","189653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40232","2014-02-28","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, when his Department will next review Renewables Obligation scheme banding levels under the Energy Act 2008; and when the outcome of this review will be published.","Biography information for Mr Stephen O'Brien","Mr Stephen O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189624","189624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40233","2014-02-28","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate he has made of the number of years it will take for (a) onshore and (b) offshore wind to be economically competitive without subsidies; and pursuant to the Written Statement of 6 June 2013, Official Report, columns 115-8WS, on onshore wind, what the evidential basis is for the statement that support levels represent good value for money to the taxpayer and that they reflect the true costs of deploying the technologies.","Biography information for Mr Stephen O'Brien","Mr Stephen O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189623","189623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40234","2014-02-28","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if he will hold a consultation with (a) individuals and (b) groups on the biomass conversion project at Eggborough power station.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189519","189519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40236","2014-03-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much has been (a) sought for and (b) spent on (i) the Medina, (ii) the Eastern Yar, (iii) the Western Yar and (iv) other brooks on the Isle of Wight by (A) the Environment Agency and (B) his Department in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Turner","Mr Andrew Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189568","189568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40237","2014-03-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many times (a) sea flooding and (b) land flooding has taken place in (i) the Medina, (ii) the Eastern Yar, (iii) the Western Yar and (iv) other brooks on the Isle of Wight in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Turner","Mr Andrew Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189564","189564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40238","2014-02-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many reptiles were seized by HM Customs under CITES in each year from 2001 to 2013; and how many such seizures there were.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189656","189656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40239","2014-02-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when he will next report on progress on implementing the Pitt review on flooding.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189674","189674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40240","2014-02-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many reptiles were imported into the UK from (a) within and (b) outside the EU each year between 2001 and 2013.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189641","189641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40241","2014-02-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the accuracy of the one in (a) 100, (b) 75 and (c) 30 years chance predictors of flooding.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189676","189676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40242","2014-02-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many times he has been briefed by the Government's Chief Scientific Advisor on the effects of climate change since coming to office.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189678","189678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40243","2014-02-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what funding his Department received from the European Commission for projects relating to bees in (a) 2009-10, (b) 2010-11, (c) 2011-12 and (d) 2012-13.","Biography information for Mark Lazarowicz","Mark Lazarowicz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189699","189699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40244","2014-02-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of expansion of Heathrow Airport on flood reservoir capacity in (a) Berkshire, (b) Surrey and (c) the surrounding areas.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189708","189708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40245","2014-03-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the highest proportion of discretion in the Environment Agency's budget that can be spent on routine maintenance of rivers.","Biography information for Stephen Barclay","Stephen Barclay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189616","189616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40246","2014-02-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with the Scottish Cabinet Secretary for Rural Affairs and the Environment on (a) the risk of flooding in Scotland and (b) the sharing of best practice in flood prevention.","Biography information for John Robertson","John Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189702","189702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40247","2014-02-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what response his Department made to the recommendation of the Association of Drainage Authorities in July 2013 on dredging key rivers in Somerset.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189685","189685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40248","2014-03-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what additional funds have been made available to each local authority in Cumbria since 1 January 2014 for flood defence enhancement, maintenance and post-flood clean-up.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189736","189736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40249","2014-02-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, which organisations are responsible for the ownership and maintenance of sustainable drainage systems.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189797","189797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40250","2014-02-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent progress he has made on ensuring that local authorities assess and enhance their technical capabilities to deliver a wide range of responsibilities in relation to local flood risk management.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189798","189798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40251","2014-02-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent progress he has made on ensuring all relevant organisations have a duty to share information and cooperate with local authorities and the Environment Agency to facilitate the management of flood risk.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189799","189799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40252","2014-02-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent progress has been made by the Environment Agency in developing its tools and techniques for predicting and modelling river flooding, taking account of extreme and multiple events and depths and velocity of water.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189787","189787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40253","2014-03-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent progress has been made on ensuring that the government of Burma releases or charges all prisoners currently detained as political prisoners.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189740","189740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40254","2014-03-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he plans to take to ensure that the UN addresses the issue of rape as a weapon of war.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189741","189741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40255","2014-03-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what (a) steps the Government has taken and (b) advice his Department has given to operators of cruise liners in respect of cruise liner companies being requested to remove the red ensign when docking in Argentina; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Julian Lewis","Dr Julian Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189730","189730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40256","2014-03-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received on the practice of Spain's Guardia Civil firing rubber bullets into the sea and using similar tactics used to repel immigrants.","Biography information for Alun Cairns","Alun Cairns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189729","189729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40257","2014-03-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the (a) field of expertise and (b) qualifications are of each member of the Preventing Sexual Violence Initiative multidisciplinary Team of Experts in Burma.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189619","189619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40258","2014-02-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations his Department has made to the Spanish government about the Alcaidesa marina in La Linea; (a) on what date and (b) by whom such representations were made; and what further action he intends to take on this issue.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189658","189658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40259","2014-02-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if the Secretary of State will clarify whether the Alcaidesa marina in La Linea has been partly constructed in British Gibraltar Territorial Waters.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189650","189650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40260","2014-02-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his German counterpart on compensation from Grunethal for UK born victims of thalidomide poisoning.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189522","189522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40261","2014-03-04","Department of Health","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when his Department has discussed with NHS England the operation of the Cancer Drugs Fund in the last six months; what the content of those discussions was; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Simon Burns","Mr Simon Burns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189571","189571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40262","2014-03-04","Department of Health","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the forecast outturn expenditure on the Cancer Drugs Fund is in 2013-14 across the year as a whole; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Simon Burns","Mr Simon Burns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189572","189572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40263","2014-03-03","Department of Health","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether a project assessment review into NHS Property Services has taken place since August 2012.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189540","189540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40264","2014-03-03","Department of Health","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the spending on locum doctors was in accident and emergency in each year since 2005 at Peterborough and Stamford Hospitals NHS Foundation Trust; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stewart Jackson","Mr Stewart Jackson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189541","189541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40265","2014-03-03","Department of Health","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans NHS England has to develop a patient registry and database for people diagnosed with familial hyper-cholesterolaemia.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189545","189545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40266","2014-03-03","Department of Health","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of people diagnosed with hepatitis C have received anti-viral treatments in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189546","189546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40267","2014-03-03","Department of Health","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to increase testing of hepatitis C.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189547","189547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40268","2014-02-28","Department of Health","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent representations he has made to his German counterpart on compensation from Grunethal to UK victims of thalidomide poisoning.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189523","189523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40269","2014-03-03","Department of Health","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of children entering secondary schools were classed as obese by the National Childhood Measurement programme in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189548","189548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40270","2014-03-03","Department of Health","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many midwives from overseas have registered with the Nursing and Midwifery Council in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189549","189549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40271","2014-02-28","Department of Health","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much was charged for the sale of NHS patient records to the Staple Inn Actuarial Society; what this money was used for; and what the cost to the NHS was of providing this information.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189521","189521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40272","2014-03-03","Department of Health","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people have died in ambulances en route for emergency admission to hospital in each ambulance trust area in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189563","189563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40273","2014-02-28","Department for Transport","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effects of stratospheric aerosol geoengineering and aerial aerosol spraying on public health.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189534","189534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40274","2014-02-28","Department of Health","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of any potential financial savings to the NHS of an increased take up of mindfulness-based therapy for the treatment of repeat depression.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189622","189622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40275","2014-03-04","Department of Health","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients have gained access to the Cancer Drugs Fund in (a) 2012-13 and (b) 2013-14 to date.","Biography information for Sir Simon Burns","Mr Simon Burns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189665","189665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40276","2014-02-28","Department of Health","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure people with prostate cancer are advised of their eligibility to participate in current clinical trials.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189591","189591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40277","2014-02-28","Department of Health","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many centres have conducted clinical trials for prostate cancer treatments in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189594","189594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40278","2014-02-28","Department of Health","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure people diagnosed with prostate cancer and living in isolated areas are supported to travel to a centre participating in a prostate cancer clinical trial.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189595","189595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40279","2014-02-28","Department of Health","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, on what dates technology appraisals relating to a treatment for prostate cancer conducted by the National Institute for Health and Care Excellence (NICE) were concluded in the last 10 years; in each case, whether the technology appraisal (a) recommended in full, (b) recommended in part and (c) rejected the routine use of the treatment on the NHS; what the eligible annual patient population estimated by NICE was in each case; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189599","189599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40280","2014-02-28","Department of Health","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of people with prostate cancer recruited into clinical trials for prostate cancer treatments in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189593","189593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40281","2014-03-03","Department of Health","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information he collects on assaults on NHS staff; and if he will publish statistics on (a) the gender of people so assaulted and (b) where such assaults took place in the last five years.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189673","189673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40282","2014-02-28","Department of Health","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many clinical trials on prostate cancer treatments on which the National Institute for Health Research has made information available through its UK Clinical Trials Gateway there were in each month since the Gateway was established.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189592","189592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40283","2014-03-03","Department of Health","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what comparative assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the enriched culture medium and the general purpose test for testing Group B streptococcus in babies.","Biography information for Mr Mike Thornton","Mr Michael Thornton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189675","189675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40284","2014-02-28","Department of Health","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of (a) clinical and (b) urological clinical nurse specialists working in the NHS in each of the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189596","189596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40285","2014-02-28","Department of Health","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of multidisciplinary teams caring for a patient with prostate cancer had prostate cancer nurse specialist provision at the time of (a) the most recent round of peer review and (b) previous rounds of peer review; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189597","189597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40286","2014-02-28","Department of Health","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many applications to the Cancer Drugs Fund for a treatment indicated for the treatment of prostate cancer were (a) approved and (b) rejected in each month since the Cancer Drugs Fund was established.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189598","189598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40287","2014-02-28","Department of Health","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of prostate cancer patients had prostate cancer diagnosed at (a) clinical stage I or II, (b) clinical stage III and (c) clinical stage IV in the latest period for which figures are available; and what assessment he has made of trends in these proportions.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189605","189605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40288","2014-02-28","Department of Health","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimates he has made of the proportion of prostate cancer patients who are cared for by a multidisciplinary team in (a) the most recent round of peer review and (b) all previous rounds of peer review.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189606","189606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40289","2014-02-28","Department of Health","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of cases of early prostate cancer were treated with (a) surgery, (b) radiotherapy, (c) hormone therapy and (d) other treatments in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189607","189607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40290","2014-02-28","Department of Health","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to conduct an audit of the number of (a) clinical and (b) urological clinical nurse specialists working in the NHS.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189610","189610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40291","2014-02-28","Department of Health","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of waiting times for people diagnosed with prostate cancer in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189611","189611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40292","2014-02-28","Department of Health","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information he collects on waiting times for people diagnosed with prostate cancer; if he will place information on waiting times for people with prostate cancer in the Library; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189612","189612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40293","2014-03-03","Department of Health","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will publish the name, job title and salary level of each director who has worked in his Department since May 2010.","Biography information for Lord Watts","Mr Dave Watts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189679","189679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40294","2014-02-28","Department of Health","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what representations he has received on the level of access people with prostate cancer have to clinical trials for treatmeants for their condition in the last two years; what the content of those representations was; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189601","189601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40295","2014-02-28","Department of Health","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps the Care Quality Commission has taken to date to ensure services for the treatment of prostate cancer are of a high standard; what steps the Care Quality Commission intends to take in the future; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189604","189604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40296","2014-02-28","Department of Health","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what representations he has received on the provision of clinical nurse specialists in the NHS in the last year; what the content of those representations was; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189602","189602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40297","2014-02-28","Department of Health","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps the Care Quality Commission is taking to ensure that adequate provision of clinical nurse specialists is covered in its inspections of NHS services; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189603","189603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40298","2014-02-28","Department of Health","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, on what dates all technology appraisals relating to a treatment for cancer conducted by the National Institute for Health and Care Excellence (NICE) were concluded in the last 10 years; in each case, whether the technology appraisal (a) recommended in full, (b) recommended in part and (c) rejected the routine use of the treatment on the NHS; what the eligible annual patient population estimated by NICE was in each case; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189600","189600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40299","2014-02-28","Department of Health","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to improve detection rates of ovarian cancer.","Biography information for Naomi Long","Naomi Long","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189711","189711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40300","2014-03-03","Department of Health","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will collect and publish statistics on the gender and ethnic background of (a) managers and (b) the work force of the NHS.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189620","189620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40301","2014-02-28","Cabinet Office","2014-02-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment he has made of the trend in prostate cancer (a) one-year, (b) two-year and (c) five-year survival rates over the last 20 years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189608","189608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40302","2014-03-03","Department of Health","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what (a) complaints and (b) other items of correspondence his Department has received expressing concern over children's heart surgery at University Hospitals Bristol NHS Foundation Trust; and on what date each such complaint or item of correspondence was received.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189723","189723"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40303","2014-03-03","Department of Health","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that recently-published National Institute for Health and Care Excellence guideline on diagnosing food allergy in children and young people in a primary care and community setting are read and adhered to by GPs.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189717","189717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40304","2014-03-03","Home Office","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the number of live births that were not registered in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Andrea Leadsom","Andrea Leadsom","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189753","189753"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40305","2014-03-03","Home Office","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what measures are in place to ensure that live births are registered.","Biography information for Andrea Leadsom","Andrea Leadsom","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189754","189754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40306","2014-03-03","Department of Health","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make an assessment of the effectiveness of enriched culture medium testing in (a) France, (b) Canada, (c) Spain, (d) the US and (e) other countries to identify Group B streptococcus.","Biography information for Mr Mike Thornton","Mr Michael Thornton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189763","189763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40307","2014-03-03","Department of Health","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to improve the level of diagnosis and treatment of people with familial hyper-cholesterolaemia using methods recommended in NICE Guideline CG71 issued in August 2008.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189766","189766"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40308","2014-03-03","Home Office","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the number of live births that were not registered in each of the last five years despite a registrar writing to the parents; and what measures are available to registrars to ensure parents register live births.","Biography information for Andrea Leadsom","Andrea Leadsom","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189752","189752"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40309","2014-03-03","Home Office","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will publish the outcome of the tri-monthly strategic reviews of the delivery of the COMPASS contract for asylum seekers in the North East, Yorkshire and Humber region.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189751","189751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40310","2014-03-03","Home Office","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much has been recovered in rebates to her Department from G4S for poor performance in delivering the COMPASS contract for asylum seekers in the North East, Yorkshire and Humber region.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189750","189750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40311","2014-03-03","Home Office","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the performance of G4S in delivering the COMPASS contract for asylum seekers in the North East, Yorkshire and Humber region.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189749","189749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40312","2014-03-03","HM Treasury","2014-02-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many vehicles have been stopped for red diesel theft in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Stephen Barclay","Stephen Barclay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189617","189617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40313","2014-03-03","Home Office","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the use of the Self Evident app to facilitate crime reporting by victims and evidence submissions by witnesses to the police.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189715","189715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40314","2014-03-03","Home Office","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many police forces in England have signed local protocols for those detained under the Mental Health Act 1983.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189645","189645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40315","2014-03-03","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many Rule 43 notices issued by the coroner's office have not received a response from the affected organisation in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189647","189647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40316","2014-03-03","Home Office","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many of the Independent Police Complaints Commission's investigations have been appeals after decisions by the local force in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189644","189644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40317","2014-03-03","Home Office","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many of the deaths identified by the Independent Police Complaints Commission as restraint-related have involved people with mental health issues in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189646","189646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40318","2014-03-03","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the total amount allocated to the provision of legal aid at inquest proceedings was in each of the last five years; and what the total number of such cases was in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189648","189648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40319","2014-02-28","Home Office","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what powers Chief Constables have to prevent police officers under investigation from leaving their force before the conclusion of those investigations.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189643","189643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40320","2014-02-28","Home Office","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what her future plans are for funding the national stalking hotline.","Biography information for Ms Nadine Dorries","Nadine Dorries","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189552","189552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40321","2014-02-28","Home Office","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the backlog was for cases supervised by the (a) permanent migration office, Liverpool, (b) temporary migration office, Sheffield and (c) older live cases unit, Liverpool in each year since 2010.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189531","189531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40322","2014-02-28","Home Office","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) permanent staff and (b) staff employed by a contractor are employed by her Department at the (i) permanent migration office, Liverpool, (ii) temporary migration office, Sheffield and (iii) older live cases unit, Liverpool in each year since 2010.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189532","189532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40323","2014-02-28","Home Office","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the overtime costs paid to permanent staff in the (a) permanent migration office, Liverpool, (b) temporary migration office, Sheffield and (c) older live cases unit, Liverpool in the last year.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189533","189533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40324","2014-02-28","Home Office","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department has taken to educate law enforcement agencies about the expanded definition of stalking contained in the Protection of Freedoms Act 2012.","Biography information for Ms Nadine Dorries","Nadine Dorries","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189517","189517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40325","2014-02-28","Home Office","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department has taken to ensure that the new definition of stalking contained in the Protection of Freedoms Act 2012 is enforced and observed by law enforcement agencies.","Biography information for Ms Nadine Dorries","Nadine Dorries","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189518","189518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40326","2014-02-28","Home Office","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will bring forward legislative proposals to expand the definition of stalking specifically to include the internet as a medium for stalking.","Biography information for Ms Nadine Dorries","Nadine Dorries","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189516","189516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40327","2014-03-03","Home Office","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department will continue using the immigration casework programme computer system.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189538","189538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40328","2014-03-03","Home Office","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will place in the Library any evaluation her Department has made of the immigration case work computer programme since May 2010.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189539","189539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40329","2014-03-03","House of Commons Commission","2014-02-26","To ask the hon. Member for Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross representing the House of Commons Commission, what steps the Commission has taken to ensure that office chairs for staff of hon. Members that regularly use ICT equipment are compliant with health and safety rules.","Biography information for Dr Thrse  Coffey","Dr Thrse Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189642","189642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40330","2014-02-28","Department for International Development","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much UK Official Development Assistance was provided by (a) each government department and (b) other sources in 2013.","Biography information for Sir Tony Cunningham","Sir Tony Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189640","189640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40331","2014-02-28","Department for International Development","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is taking with developing countries on reducing water pollution and increasing the quality and quantity of clean, safe water.","Biography information for Naomi Long","Naomi Long","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189712","189712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40332","2014-02-28","Department for International Development","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to address disproportionate use of water resources for industry and energy production.","Biography information for Naomi Long","Naomi Long","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189713","189713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40333","2014-03-03","Department for International Development","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what the (a) name and (b) country is of each current recipient of the Commonwealth Scholarship Commission.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189721","189721"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40334","2014-03-03","Department for International Development","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she plans to take to ensure that funding given to the Philippines in the aftermarth of Typhoon Haiyan is spent on assistance to those directly affected.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189738","189738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40335","2014-03-03","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many notifications of endorsement from a court or fixed penalty office of a driver who meets the criteria of the Road Traffic (New Drivers) Act 1995 were sent to the Driver and Vehicle Licensing Agency in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189542","189542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40336","2014-02-28","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many persons have been (a) prosecuted and (b) convicted following arrests by the British Transport Police under the Vagrancy Act 1824 in each of the last 10 years for which information is available.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189556","189556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40337","2014-02-28","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many persons found guilty of begging appealed their conviction in each of the last three years; and how many attempted prosecutions resulted in acquittals in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189557","189557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40338","2014-02-28","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prosecutions the British Transport Police brought for the offence of begging in each month since January 2012.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189558","189558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40339","2014-02-28","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many persons prosecuted following cases brought by British Transport Police for begging (a) were convicted and (b) appealed their conviction in the last three years.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189553","189553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40340","2014-02-28","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people were (a) prosecuted and (b) convicted following cases brought by the British Transport Police for the offence of begging in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189555","189555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40341","2014-03-03","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people were sent to prison in each year between 2007 and 2012 for offences relating to the non-payment of a television licence.","Biography information for Andrew Bridgen","Andrew Bridgen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189720","189720"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40342","2014-03-03","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prosecutions were heard in magistrates' courts for non-payment of television licences in each year between 2007 and 2012; and how many such cases failed to result in a prosecution.","Biography information for Andrew Bridgen","Andrew Bridgen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189718","189718"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40343","2014-03-03","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much has been spent by his Department using a Government Procurement Card on (a) temporary recruitment of staff, (b) catering and catering supplies, (c) clubs, associations and organisations, (d) office stationery equipment and supplies, (e) car rental, (f) hotels and accommodation, (g) restaurants and bars and (h) leisure activities in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189744","189744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40344","2014-03-03","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, on how many occasions wing closures occured due to shortfalls in staffing in each prison, in each month since May 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189716","189716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40345","2014-02-28","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will direct the Governor of HM Young Offender Institution Deerbolt to respond to the letter dated 24 January 2014 from the hon. Member for Hartlepool.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189704","189704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40346","2014-02-28","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people in the UK have a criminal record for offences relating to non-payment of the television licence.","Biography information for Andrew Bridgen","Andrew Bridgen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189697","189697"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40347","2014-03-03","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners sent to local prisons by courts have been sent on to a  alternative prison due to overcrowding in each month since September 2013.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189681","189681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40348","2014-03-03","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which prisons have been locked out in each month since May 2010; and on how many occasions each such prison has been locked out.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189680","189680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40349","2014-03-03","Northern Ireland Office","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, who (a) signed and (b) issued the 38 letters of comfort to on-the-runs issued since 2010 and since devolution of Policing and Justice to the Northern Ireland Assembly; on behalf of which Government department they were acting; and which Minister or Ministers had oversight of this process.","Biography information for Naomi Long","Naomi Long","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189724","189724"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40350","2014-03-03","Northern Ireland Office","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, who was responsible for fact-checking statements submitted by the Police Service of Northern Ireland to permit letters of comfort to be issued by officials to on-the-runs; and under whose ministerial authority were they acting.","Biography information for Naomi Long","Naomi Long","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189725","189725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40351","2014-03-03","Northern Ireland Office","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, who was responsible for obtaining and fact-checking information from UK mainland police forces to facilitate the issuing of letters of comfort to so-called On-the-Runs.","Biography information for Naomi Long","Naomi Long","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189726","189726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40352","2014-03-03","Northern Ireland Office","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, by which means letters of comfort issued to so-called On-the-Runs were requested, issued and transmitted to the individuals concerned.","Biography information for Naomi Long","Naomi Long","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189727","189727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40353","2014-02-28","Prime Minister","2014-02-26","To ask the Prime Minister, if he meet the hon. Member for Strangford and a group of problem gamblers to discuss steps to take to address this issue.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189710","189710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40354","2014-02-28","Speaker's Committee on the Electorial Commission","2014-02-26","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, whether the Electoral Commission has conducted any follow-up research on the 14 authorities which piloted data matching on the increase in registration rates on the wards with the lowest turnout.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189698","189698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40355","2014-02-28","Speaker's Committee on the Electorial Commission","2014-02-26","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, when online voter registration will start; and what steps the Commission has taken to inform hon. Members of this change.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189638","189638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40356","2014-02-28","Speaker's Committee on the Electorial Commission","2014-02-26","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, pursuant to the Answer of 25 February 2014, Official Report, columns 321-3W, on absent voting, whether the qualitative survey conducted by the Electoral Commission provided any information on current levels of electoral fraud.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189614","189614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40357","2014-03-03","Department for Transport","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many new drivers passed their first driving test in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189543","189543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40358","2014-03-03","Department for Transport","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many new drivers were awarded a probationary driving licence in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189544","189544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40359","2014-02-28","Department for Transport","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what effect Heathrow expansion would have on flood reservoir capacity in Berkshire, Surrey and surrounding areas.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189561","189561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40360","2014-02-28","Department for Transport","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many British Transport Police officers have faced disciplinary action for misconduct in dealing with cases relating to the offence of begging in the last three years.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189554","189554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40361","2014-02-28","Department for Transport","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what effect Heathrow expansion would have on runoff water levels in Berkshire, Surrey and surrounding areas in cases of severe weather; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189666","189666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40362","2014-03-03","Department for Transport","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent representations his Department has made to the EU for reforms to tyre requirements required during MOTs on (a) buses and (b) coaches.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189669","189669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40363","2014-03-03","Department for Transport","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what his policy is on introducing a maximum age on tyres for use on (a) buses and (b) coaches.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189670","189670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40364","2014-03-03","Department for Transport","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many passenger service (a) coaches and (b) buses have failed an MOT as a result of tyre failures in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189672","189672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40365","2014-03-03","Department for Transport","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many spot checks VOSA have undertaken on passenger service (a) buses and (b) coaches in each of the last 10 years; how many such checks have been undertaken in (i) Liverpool, (ii) Merseyside and (iii) the North West; and how many such checks have identified the presence of illegal tyres.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189671","189671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40366","2014-03-03","HM Treasury","2014-02-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate his Department has made of the cost to the rural economy of red diesel theft in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Stephen Barclay","Stephen Barclay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189618","189618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40367","2014-03-03","Department for Transport","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 24 February 2014, Official Report, column 238W on parking: fees and charges, what the (a) name and (b) region of registration is of each of the seven other companies which were suspended from requesting vehicle keeper details from the Driver and Vehicle Licensing Agency in 2013.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189722","189722"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40368","2014-03-03","Department for Transport","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what (a) criteria and (b) guidance his Department has issued to the Highways Agency on the (i) frequency of messaging and (ii) reasons for prioritising messages on overhead gantry signs.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189734","189734"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40369","2014-03-03","Department for Transport","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many responses were received to the High Speed 2 Environmental Statement; and if he will publish the names of those who responded.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189737","189737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40370","2014-03-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of all claims for (a) income-based incapacity benefit or employment and support allowance, (b) contributions-based incapacity benefit or employment and support allowance and (c) both income-based and contributions-based incapacity benefit or employment and support allowance over the last 10 years have lasted for (i) less than three months, (ii) between three and six months, (iii) between six and 12 months, (iv) between one and two years and (v) more than two years.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189758","189758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40371","2014-03-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many new claims for (a) income-based jobseeker's allowance, (b) contributions-based jobseeker's allowance and (c) both income-based and contributions-based jobseeker's allowance were made in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189755","189755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40372","2014-03-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of senior citizens who have not been primarily resident in the UK for five years or more that are still eligible for winter fuel payments.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189739","189739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40373","2014-03-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of all claims for (a) income-based jobseeker's allowance, (b) contributions-based jobseeker's allowance and (c) both income-based and contributions-based jobseeker's allowance over the last 10 years have lasted for (i) less than three months, (ii) between three and six months, (iii) between six and 12 months, (iv) between one and two years and (v) more than two years.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189757","189757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40374","2014-03-03","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the number of appeals against the refusal of employment and support allowance held on Saturdays in the last year.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189745","189745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40375","2014-03-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 24 February 2014, Official Report, column 11W, on Pensions Regulator, what the companies involved in the three cases were.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189733","189733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40376","2014-03-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 24 February 2014, Official Report, column 11W, on Pensions Regulator, how many companies have been investigated by the Pensions Regulator and had no subsequent action taken against them in the last five years.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189732","189732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40377","2014-03-03","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he (a) has taken and (b) plans to take to ensure that claimants required to present their appeals against the refusal of employment and support allowance on a Saturday have advocate support.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189746","189746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40378","2014-03-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many jobseeker's allowance claimants with refugee status in (a) Hull and (b) the UK have been sanctioned since 22 October 2012.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189748","189748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40379","2014-02-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answers of 24 February, Official Report, column 16W, on Work Capability Assessment: Isle of Wight, if he will provide the requested information for the smallest relevant geographical unit for which information is available.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Turner","Mr Andrew Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189714","189714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40380","2014-02-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many face-to-face work capability assessments have been carried out in each week of the last three months.","Biography information for Dame Anne Begg","Dame Anne Begg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189692","189692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40381","2014-02-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many incapacity benefit claimants have still to be migrated to employment and support allowance.","Biography information for Dame Anne Begg","Dame Anne Begg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189693","189693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40382","2014-02-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to encourage pensioners to switch annuities when they retire.","Biography information for John Robertson","John Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 189705","189705"
