"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679770","2017-01-31","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what agreements the Government has with the Government of India relating to the transfer of prisoners; and what effect those agreements have had on the number of prisoners exchanged with that country.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62017","62017"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679771","2017-01-31","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what agreements the Government has with the Government of Pakistan relating to the transfer of prisoners; and what effect those agreements have had on the number of prisoners exchanged with that country.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62018","62018"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679772","2017-01-31","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what agreements the Government has with the Government of Vietnam relating to the transfer of prisoners; and what effect those agreements have had on the number of prisoners exchanged with that country.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62019","62019"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679773","2017-01-31","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of offenders from Zimbabwe have been transferred to prisons in Zimbabwe from the UK in each year of the last five years.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62025","62025"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679774","2017-01-31","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what agreements the Government has with the Government of Iran relating to the transfer of prisoners; and what effect those agreements have had on the number of prisoners exchanged with that country.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62020","62020"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679775","2017-01-31","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what agreements the Government has with the Government of Iraq relating to the transfer of prisoners; and what effect those agreements have had on the number of prisoners exchanged with that country.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62021","62021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679776","2017-01-31","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of offenders from Bangladesh have been transferred to prisons in Bangladesh from the UK in each year of the last five years.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62026","62026"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679777","2017-01-31","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of offenders from Algeria have been transferred to prisons in Algeria from the UK in each year of the last five years.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62022","62022"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679778","2017-01-31","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of offenders from China have been transferred to prisons in China from the UK in each year of the last five years.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62027","62027"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679779","2017-01-31","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of offenders from Somalia have been transferred to prisons in Somalia from the UK in each year of the last five years.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62023","62023"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679780","2017-01-31","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of offenders from Ghana have been transferred to prisons in Ghana from the UK in each year of the last five years.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62024","62024"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679781","2017-01-31","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of offenders from Pakistan have been transferred to prisons in Pakistan from the UK in each year of the last five years.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62029","62029"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679782","2017-01-31","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of offenders from Vietnam have been transferred to prisons in Vietnam from the UK in each year of the last five years.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62030","62030"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679783","2017-01-31","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of offenders from Albania have been transferred to prisons in Albania from the UK in each year of the last five years.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62031","62031"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679784","2017-01-31","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of offenders from Turkey have been transferred to prisons in Turkey from the UK in each year of the last five years.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62032","62032"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679785","2017-02-01","Department for Transport","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if his Department will take direct control of the Thameslink, Southern and Great Northern passenger rail franchise.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62010","62010"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679786","2017-02-01","Department for Transport","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many bus services have been withdrawn in the top 10 most (a) rural and (b) urban parliamentary constituencies.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62093","62093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679787","2017-02-01","Department for Transport","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that trains are accessible for wheelchair-users at unmanned railway stations when trains do not have conductors on board.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62117","62117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679788","2017-02-09","Department for Transport","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the timetable is for the completion of the dualling programme for the A30/A303 link road.","Biography information for Kevin Foster","Kevin Foster","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62088","62088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679789","2017-01-31","Department for Transport","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to ensure that global opportunities for the Midlands provided by Birmingham Airport are highlighted in the Midlands connect strategy.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62056","62056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679790","2017-02-01","Department for Transport","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department is considering any alternative routes for High Speed 2 through South Yorkshire in addition to a line through Meadowhall and the route east of Rotherham with a branch to Sheffield Midland Station.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62138","62138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679791","2017-02-01","Department for Transport","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the estimated cost is of the Meadowhall station and viaduct as part of one option for the High Speed 2 route through South Yorkshire; and whether that cost has changed since the original route was announced.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62120","62120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679792","2017-02-01","Department for Transport","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 23 January 2017 to Question 61251, what steps he is taking to ensure that when the smart motorway opens between junctions 32 and 35a mitigation measures to improve air quality will at least offset any additional pollution from the expected increase in traffic volumes.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62124","62124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679793","2017-01-31","Wales Office","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what the value of exports to the EU from Welsh (a) agriculture, (b) aerospace, (c) construction, (d) electronics, (e) manufacturing, (f) renewable energy, (g) services, (h) textile and (i) fishing industries was in the last six years.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62058","62058"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679794","2017-01-31","Wales Office","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what proportion of products from Welsh (a) agriculture, (b) aerospace, (c) construction, (d) electronics, (e) manufacturing, (f) renewable energy, (g) services, (h) textile and (i) fishing industries were exported to the EU in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62013","62013"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679795","2017-01-31","Women and Equalities","2017-01-27","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what her policy is on continuing direct grant funding from her Department to support the revenge porn helpline.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62006","62006"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679796","2017-02-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the level of earnings is of the (a) highest and (b) lowest-paid employees of his Department, agencies and arms-length bodies; and what the median level of earnings is for such employees.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61996","61996"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679797","2017-01-31","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what financial support and advice on benefits his Department provides to help parents, children and carers who are affected by autism and Asperger's syndrome.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62012","62012"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679798","2017-02-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in which postcodes are covered by Newton-le-Willows Jobcentre.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62044","62044"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679799","2017-01-31","Department of Health","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, for what reason the Government is issuing European Health Insurance cards with expiry dates later than 31 March 2019; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Mr Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62009","62009"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679800","2017-02-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people have accessed services at Newton-le-Willows Jobcentre in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62043","62043"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679801","2017-02-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many staff of his Department are employed at Newton-le-Willows Jobcentre.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62045","62045"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679802","2017-01-31","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the cost of relocating staff and resources from Port Glasgow Jobcentre.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62109","62109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679803","2017-01-31","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will confirm that no compulsory redundancies will result from the closure of Port Glasgow Jobcentre.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62110","62110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679804","2017-01-31","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what criteria were used to select Port Glasgow Jobcentre for closure.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62111","62111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679805","2017-02-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many EU migrants registered for national insurance numbers in Ashfield between (a) July and December 2015, (b) January and June 2016 and (c) July and December 2016.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62134","62134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679806","2017-02-01","HM Treasury","2017-01-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many employers in (a) Ashfield, (b) Nottinghamshire and (c) England were found to be paying employees below the national minimum wage in 2015-16; and what action was taken against those employers.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62135","62135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679807","2017-02-02","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what discussions he has had with NFU Scotland to extend the Principle of Fair Dealing within the Groceries Supply Code of Practice so that it covers primary producers that supply supermarkets directly.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62143","62143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679808","2017-02-02","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when the Government plans to publish its response to the Groceries Code Adjudicator review.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62142","62142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679809","2017-01-31","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the effect on Swansea of a pathfinder tidal lagoon.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62085","62085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679810","2017-02-01","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether her Department plans to widen the markets of the water companies to enable home competition in areas where one sole provider has a monopoly.","Biography information for David Morris","David Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62086","62086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679811","2017-02-01","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the level of earnings is of the (a) highest and (b) lowest-paid employees of his Department, its agencies and arms-length bodies; and what the median level of earnings is for such employees.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61992","61992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679812","2017-01-31","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what plans he has to update and publish online the Better Regulations Framework Manual.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62005","62005"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679813","2017-01-31","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that (a) lagoons meet the criteria required to obtain a marine licence and (b) alternative habitats are found for wildlife affected by each lagoon.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62040","62040"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679814","2017-01-31","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what his Department's policy is on ensuring pathfinder tidal lagoons include a no regrets policy.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62039","62039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679815","2017-01-31","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 19 December 2016 to Question 56871, what proportion of the UK's fossil reserves need to be left in the ground to prevent global temperature change above two degrees centigrade.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62007","62007"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679816","2017-01-31","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the potential role of tidal lagoons in the cultivating world leading sectors pillar of his Department's industrial strategy.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62038","62038"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679817","2017-01-31","Department for International Trade","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what the (a) level of earnings is of the (i) highest and (ii) lowest-paid employee and (b) median earnings are of employees of his Department.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62071","62071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679818","2017-02-01","Department for International Trade","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what the cost to date has been of his Department's trade and investment campaign, launched on 25 January 2017; and how much of that cost has been incurred through advertising in international airport hubs.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62107","62107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679819","2017-02-01","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many overnight hotel stays for official purposes in other countries have been made by (a) him and other Ministers and (b) special advisers of his Department; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62115","62115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679821","2017-02-01","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to the Prime Minister's Answer of 25 January 2016 to Question 908364, Official Report, column 286, when he expects the Government's plan for the UK leaving the EU to be set out in a White Paper and published for the House.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62137","62137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679822","2017-02-01","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, if he will list the Cabinet sub-committees he regularly attends.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62136","62136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679823","2017-01-31","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what the (a) level of earnings is of the (i) highest and (ii) lowest-paid employee and (b) median earnings are of employees of his Department.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62066","62066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679824","2017-01-31","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what measures his Department has put in place to ensure that Gibraltar is represented during negotiations on the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Drew Hendry","Drew Hendry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62074","62074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679825","2017-01-31","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what measures his Department has put in place to ensure that Scotland is represented during negotiations on the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Drew Hendry","Drew Hendry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62075","62075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679826","2017-01-31","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what discussions he has had with the Government of Gibraltar on the potential effect of leaving the EU on relations between Gibraltar and Spain.","Biography information for Drew Hendry","Drew Hendry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62014","62014"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679827","2017-02-01","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what assessment he has made of the effect of World Trade Organisation rules on (a) reaching a new customs agreement, (b) making the UK an associate member of the customs union and (c) the UK remaining a signatory to some elements of the customs union, as set out by the Prime Minister in her speech at Lancaster House on 17 January 2017.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62133","62133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679828","2017-01-31","Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster","2017-01-27","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster, what the (a) level of earnings is of the (i) highest and (ii) lowest-paid employee and (b) median earnings are of employees of his Department.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62073","62073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679001","2017-01-30","HM Treasury","2017-01-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether his Department has made representations to the Clydesdale Bank after that Bank's announcement of 18 January 2017 to close 40 branches in Scotland; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61829","61829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679002","2017-01-31","HM Treasury","2017-01-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many new businesses registered for VAT in (a) 2014-15, (b) 2013-14, (c) 2012-13, (d) 2011-12 and (e) 2010-11.","Biography information for David Morris","David Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61847","61847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679003","2017-01-31","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to paragraph 3.36 of the Autumn Statement 2016, if his Department will support firms specialising (a) in video and mobile game development and (b) on artificial intelligence, data analytics and virtual reality.","Biography information for Chris White","Chris White","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61871","61871"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679004","2017-01-30","HM Treasury","2017-01-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department takes to help businesses to receive funds from Iran.","Biography information for Sir Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61916","61916"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679005","2017-01-30","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of changes to the planning system on achieving the National Planning Policy Framework's policies on sustainable development.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61828","61828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679006","2017-01-30","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he plans to respond to the findings of the Ollerenshaw review of local council tax support.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61851","61851"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679007","2017-01-30","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of parking charges on the viability of town centre economies.","Biography information for Margaret Greenwood","Margaret Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61857","61857"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679008","2017-01-31","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 8 September 2016 to Question 45729, what assessment he has made of the implications of his policies of the final recommendations of the Park Homes Working Group; and if he will place his plans to take forward those recommendations in the Library.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61818","61818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679009","2017-01-31","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when the Government's planned review of the Mobile Homes Act 2013 will begin; what that review's terms of reference will be; and whether that review will have an independent chair.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61819","61819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679010","2017-01-31","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate she has made of the potential effect on the amount of money provided for good causes by the National Lottery of the practice of betting on the result of the Euromillions draw.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61859","61859"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679011","2017-01-31","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the oral statement of the Minister of State for Defence of 23 January 2017, HL Official Report, column 463, how many (a) hon. Members and (b) Members of the House of Lords were (i) invited to be and (ii) onboard the survey vessels observing the trident missile test firing in July 2016.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61814","61814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679012","2017-01-31","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps are being taken to increase army recruiting prior to the introduction of the Army Recruiting Partnership Project.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61815","61815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679013","2017-01-31","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what his Department's annual recruiting target was for each year from 2010-11 to 2015-16; and what that target is in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61816","61816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679014","2017-01-31","Department for Education","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 9 January 2017 to Question 58494, what information her Department holds on the cost of school closures since 2010.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61836","61836"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679015","2017-01-31","Department for Education","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 19 December 2016 to Question 56283, if she will set out all of the apprenticeship standards which specifically address skill shortages in the green economy sector.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61837","61837"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679016","2017-01-31","Department for Education","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 10 January 2017 to Question 58097, whether any intervention from her Department in a school closure consultation subsequently led to a consultation being paused.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61838","61838"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679017","2017-01-31","Department for Education","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how her Department assesses the performance of Regional School Commissioners in their handling of failing schools.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61839","61839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679018","2017-01-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how much EU funding was received by the higher education sector in the (a) UK and (b) North West  in each financial year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Margaret Greenwood","Margaret Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61866","61866"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679019","2017-01-30","Department for Education","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will take steps to ensure that teaching assistants receive full remuneration for the responsibilities they undertake.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61868","61868"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679020","2017-01-31","Department for Education","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 25 January 2017 to Question 60976, if her Department will gather data on the number of (a) school teachers and (b) education sector workers who have been on leave of absence from work due to mental illness in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61900","61900"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679021","2017-01-31","Department for Education","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 25 January 2017 to Question 60977, if her Department will gather data on the number of young carers registered in schools.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61901","61901"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679022","2017-01-31","Department for Education","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the oral evidence to the Public Accounts Committee of 23 January 2017, Question 46, when the research commissioned by her Department into the running costs of schools will be published.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61904","61904"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679024","2017-01-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to the Israeli authorities as a result of the demolition of Umm al-Hiran.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61826","61826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679025","2017-01-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to his Colombian counterpart on the murder of Emilsen Manyoma on 17 January 2017; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61832","61832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679026","2017-01-30","Department of Health","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to increase the take-up of bowel cancer screening.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61834","61834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679027","2017-01-30","Cabinet Office","2017-01-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people under the age of 60 were diagnosed with bowel cancer in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61811","61811"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679028","2017-01-30","Department of Health","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make it his policy to make routine bowel cancer screening available to people between the ages of 50 and 60.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61812","61812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679029","2017-01-30","Department of Health","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people between the ages of 50 and 60 years of age are diagnosed with stage 4 bowel cancer.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61813","61813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679030","2017-01-31","Department of Health","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many clinical commissioning groups have stopped access to staple gluten-free substitute foods without public consultation in the last two years.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61820","61820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679031","2017-01-30","Department of Health","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he has instructed (a) officials of his Department and (b) the National Institute for Health and Care Excellence to carry out a financial impact assessment of the cost and benefits of prescribing bisphosphonates for the treatment of cancer.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61825","61825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679032","2017-01-31","Department of Health","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many full inspections of NHS trusts and foundation trusts the Care Quality Commission undertook in 2016-17, and in each of the previous three financial years; and how many inspections in each year were (a) outstanding, (b) good, (c) requires improvement and (d) inadequate.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61895","61895"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679033","2017-01-31","Department of Health","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients over the age of 80 were discharged from NHS hospitals during the night in each month in (a) 2016-17 and (b) 2015-16.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61896","61896"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679034","2017-01-31","Department of Health","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, (a) how many applications to work have been refused and (b) for what reasons by the General Medical Council in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61897","61897"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679035","2017-02-08","Department of Health","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the level of the misuse of ambulance services in (a) England and (b) each Ambulance NHS Trust; and what steps his Department is taking to reduce the cost incurred by such misuse.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61905","61905"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679036","2017-01-31","Department of Health","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, (a) how many applications to work have been refused and (b) for what reasons by the Nursing and Midwifery Council in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61898","61898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679037","2017-01-31","Department of Health","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the total cost of compensation payments made by NHS trusts and foundation trusts is in 2016-17 to date; and what such payments were in each of the previous three years.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61899","61899"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679038","2017-01-30","Department of Health","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that NICE guidance on the commissioning of IVF treatment is implemented in each clinical commissioning group.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61872","61872"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679039","2017-01-30","Department of Health","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent steps the Government has taken to improve diagnosis of Lyme disease.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61873","61873"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679040","2017-01-30","Department of Health","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people have been diagnosed with Lyme disease in each clinical commissioning group area in each year since 2009.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61874","61874"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679041","2017-01-31","Department of Health","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many attendances at emergency departments for self-harm per 100,000 people there were in 2015-16; and how many such people received a psychological assessment.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61893","61893"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679042","2017-01-31","Department of Health","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many children aged under 18 have been referred to Sexual Assault Referral Centres since mandatory reporting of age was introduced in each month since April 2016.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61892","61892"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679043","2017-01-31","Department of Health","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many finished admission episodes there were with a primary diagnosis of mental and behavioural disorder for patients aged 0 to 18 in 2015-16.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61890","61890"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679044","2017-01-30","Department of Health","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the Government has made a recent assessment of the disparity between Lyme disease diagnosis rates in the UK and in Germany.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61875","61875"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679045","2017-01-31","Department of Health","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much his Department has spent on the Healthy Start Scheme in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61891","61891"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679046","2017-01-31","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many incidents there were of (a) self-harm, (b) attempted self-inflicted death and (c) self-inflicted death by prisoners on remand in (i) 2015 and (ii) 2016; and what proportion of all prisoners on remand such incidents represented in each of those years.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61894","61894"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679047","2017-01-30","Department of Health","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with NHS England on potential reductions to services at North Devon District Hospital under the emerging Sustainability and Transformation Plan.","Biography information for Peter Heaton-Jones","Peter Heaton-Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61858","61858"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679048","2017-01-30","Department of Health","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to make cervical screening available in additional (a) GP surgeries and (b) local healthcare settings.","Biography information for Mr John Baron","Mr John Baron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61854","61854"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679049","2017-01-31","Department of Health","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the new Tobacco Control Plan will include funding for media campaigning to promote the reduction of smoking rates.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61855","61855"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679050","2017-01-31","Department of Health","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the new Tobacco Control Plan will include targets for reducing smoking rates.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61856","61856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679051","2017-01-30","Department of Health","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what account is taken of forecasts for the rate of inflation  in determining pay increases for nurses.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61862","61862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679052","2017-01-30","Department of Health","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he has to ensure local health providers are able to meet additional health care demands over winter 2016-17.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61863","61863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679053","2017-01-30","Department of Health","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he has taken to address the pressure alerts that have been issued by local clinical commissioning groups.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61864","61864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679054","2017-01-31","Department of Health","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the (a) average, (b) shortest and (c) longest length of time has been between the Care Quality Commission's inspections of NHS Trusts and the publication of report on those inspections.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61844","61844"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679055","2017-01-31","Department of Health","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how long it took between the Care Quality Commission's inspection of Bridgewater NHS Trust and the production of the report on that inspection.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61845","61845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679056","2017-01-31","Department of Health","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what reasons are for the time taken in the production of the Care Quality Commission's report on its inspection of Bridgewater NHS Trust.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61846","61846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679057","2017-01-31","Department of Health","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 25 January 2017 to Question 60306, if he will amend the definition of the philosophy of homeopathy in the guidance to better reflect the scientific evidence on that treatment.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61848","61848"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679058","2017-01-31","Department of Health","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of how many GPs working in the NHS will retire by 2020.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61849","61849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679059","2017-01-31","Department of Health","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of how many new GPs will be trained and employed in the NHS by 2020.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61850","61850"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679060","2017-01-30","Home Office","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will take steps to increase the number of police officers in Lancashire to 2009 levels.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61870","61870"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679061","2017-01-30","Home Office","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what Border Force's budget for 2017-18 will be.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Mr Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61918","61918"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679062","2017-01-31","Home Office","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether Dungavel IRC is in public ownership or privately owned.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61888","61888"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679063","2017-01-30","Home Office","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the service standard is for the processing of First-tier Tribunal decisions by UK Visas and Immigration.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61835","61835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679064","2017-01-31","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners who died by suicide in England and Wales in 2016 were known drug users.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61806","61806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679065","2017-01-31","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many self-inflicted deaths in prisons in England and Wales in 2016 were as a consequence of drug use.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61807","61807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679066","2017-01-31","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment her Department has made of the implications for its policies of levels of suicides in English and Welsh prisons in 2016.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61808","61808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679067","2017-01-31","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if she will make an assessment of the implications for the effectiveness of her Department's impact assessment which accompanied the consultation on Reforming the Soft Tissue Injury (whiplash) Claims Process, published in November 2016, of its lacking relevant data on seven protected characteristics.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61880","61880"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679068","2017-01-31","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the evidential basis was for the potential effect of the proposals in her Department's consultation on Reforming the Soft Tissue Injury (whiplash) Claims Process, published in November 2016, on people with protected characteristics.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61881","61881"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679069","2017-01-31","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment she has made of the implications of her policies of research published by (a) Thompson Solicitors in August 2016 and (b) Which? magazine in September 2016 on alleged discrimination in car insurance premium costs on the grounds of race; how her response to her Department's consultation on Reforming the Soft Tissue Injury (whiplash) Claims Process, published in November 2016, will take account of that evidence; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61882","61882"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679070","2017-01-30","Northern Ireland Office","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, on what dates (a) Ministers and (b) officials from his Department met with counterparts at the Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy to discuss productivity levels in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Dr Andrew Murrison","Dr Andrew Murrison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61805","61805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679071","2017-01-31","Prime Minister","2017-01-26","To ask the Prime Minister, on what date the Social Reform Committee last met; and how many meetings of that committee have taken place since it was established.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61817","61817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679072","2017-01-31","Prime Minister","2017-01-26","To ask the Prime Minister, whether she raised at her meeting with President Trump on 27 January 2017 the (a) Paris Agreement and international climate change co-operation, (b) treatment of ethnic, religious and sexual minorities in the US, (c) US commitment to NATO, (d) protection of women's rights in the international community and (e) US-UK Trade Policy.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61889","61889"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679073","2017-01-30","Scotland Office","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, whether his Department has made representations to the Clydesdale Bank after that Bank's announcement of 18 January 2017 to close 40 branches in Scotland; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61830","61830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679074","2017-01-30","Department for Transport","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to support the growth of Birmingham Airport.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61822","61822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679075","2017-01-30","Department for Transport","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to deliver an aviation strategy for the UK.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61823","61823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679076","2017-01-30","Department for Transport","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions he has had with representatives of Midlands Connect.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61824","61824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679077","2017-01-31","Department for Transport","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 20 December 2016 to Question 57840, on railways: industrial disputes, how many hours staff in his Department spent processing the 16 force majeure claims.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61886","61886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679078","2017-01-31","Department for Transport","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 20 December 2016 to Question 57840, on railways: industrial disputes, if he will list the payments made from the public purse to each train operating company in respect of each agreed claim for force majeure; and what the total was of those such payments.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61883","61883"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679079","2017-01-31","Department for Transport","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 20 December 2016 to Question 57840, on railways: industrial disputes, if he will list the train operating companies that submitted each force majeure claim.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61884","61884"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679080","2017-01-31","Department for Transport","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 20 December 2016 to Question 57840, on railways: industrial disputes, on what dates the force majeure claims were agreed by his Department.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61885","61885"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679081","2017-01-31","Department for Transport","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 20 December 2016 to Question 57840, on railways: industrial disputes, what the average time was for his Department to complete the 16 force majeure claims.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61887","61887"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679082","2017-01-30","Department for Transport","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment the Government has made of the benefit to the UK of membership of the European Aviation Safety Agency.","Biography information for Margaret Greenwood","Margaret Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61867","61867"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679083","2017-01-31","Department for Transport","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with Southern since 24 January 2017 on its performance against contract standards on punctuality, delays and cancellations since that date.","Biography information for Ms Nusrat Ghani","Nusrat Ghani","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61860","61860"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679084","2017-01-31","Department for Transport","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what performance penalties may apply in relation to Southern train services since 24 January 2017.","Biography information for Ms Nusrat Ghani","Nusrat Ghani","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61861","61861"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679085","2017-01-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether his Department's proposals to end disability benefit re-assessments for people who have severe lifelong conditions will include people who are blind.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61869","61869"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679086","2017-01-31","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Written Statement of 26 January 2017, HCWS439, on welfare delivery, how many of the 2,500 work coaches who are expected to be in post by March 2018 will be located in (a) Scotland, (b) England and (c) Wales.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61903","61903"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679087","2017-01-31","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Written Statement of 26 January 2017, HCWS439, on welfare delivery, what percentage of claims made online for (a) jobseeker's allowance and (b) universal credit are made using computer equipment at a jobcentre.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61902","61902"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679088","2017-01-31","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of assessments for personal independence payments were (a) paper-based and (b) face-to-face in (i) 2014, (ii) 2015 and (iii) 2016 in (A) the UK and (B) Edinburgh East constituency.","Biography information for Tommy Sheppard","Tommy Sheppard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61809","61809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679089","2017-02-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will launch a public consultation on setting a target to reduce child poverty.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61821","61821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679090","2017-01-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what guidance his Department provides to unsuccessful applicants for industrial injuries disablement benefit on the services offered by the Industrial Injuries Advisory Council where mandatory reconsideration is not appropriate.","Biography information for Stewart Malcolm McDonald","Stewart Malcolm McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61831","61831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679091","2017-01-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effect of changes in the Pensions Act 2011 on trends in the level of (a) the overall claimant count, (b) the employment support allowance claimant count and (c) unemployment.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61827","61827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679092","2017-01-31","HM Treasury","2017-01-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will take steps to ensure that HM Revenue and Customs immediately initiate the 1-2-1 redeployment consultation process for all staff working in its West Lothian offices to ensure that that process reflects ongoing dialogue between each worker and their manager.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61840","61840"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679093","2017-01-31","HM Treasury","2017-01-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the number of HM Revenue and Customs staff working in West Lothian who will not be able to relocate to a regional centre; and what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of exit packages for those staff.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61841","61841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679094","2017-01-31","HM Treasury","2017-01-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if Ministers of his Department will meet with local elected representatives and other key stakeholders in Bathgate to discuss the potential effect of proposals to relocate jobs to regional centres on the local communities affected.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61842","61842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679095","2017-01-31","HM Treasury","2017-01-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the number of HM Revenue and Customs staff working in West Lothian who will be able to relocate to a regional centre; and what estimate he has made of the cost of additional daily travel assistance for those staff.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61843","61843"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679096","2017-01-30","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the number of organisations with charitable status that will be affected by changes in business rates to be introduced from April 2017 in (a) East Lancashire and (b) the UK.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61833","61833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679097","2017-01-30","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the number of public houses that will be affected by the planned changes in business rates from April 2017 in (a) East Lancashire and (b) the UK.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61810","61810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679098","2017-01-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate he has made of the proportion of known fossil fuels that need to be left in the ground to prevent global temperature changes above 1.5 degrees centigrade.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61852","61852"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679099","2017-01-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to monitor the difference between the wholesale cost of petrol and diesel fuel and the price paid for those fuels by consumers.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61853","61853"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679100","2017-01-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment the Government has made of the benefit to the UK of membership of the European Chemicals Agency.","Biography information for Margaret Greenwood","Margaret Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61865","61865"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679101","2017-01-30","Department for International Trade","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the Tradeshow Access Programme.","Biography information for Sir Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61917","61917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679102","2017-01-30","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what the Government's policy is on remaining a member of the European Food Safety Authority after the UK leaves the EU; and whether the Government plans to maintain adherence to the standards of that authority after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61803","61803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679103","2017-01-30","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what the Government's policy is on remaining a member of the European Chemicals Agency after the UK leaves the EU; and whether the Government plans to maintain adherence to the standards and rules of that agency after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61804","61804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679105","2017-01-30","Cabinet Office","2017-01-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the average salary was in (a) Rutherglen and Hamilton West constituency, (b) Scotland and (c) the UK in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61920","61920"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679106","2017-01-30","Cabinet Office","2017-01-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what discussions Ministers or officials of his Department have had with representatives of the Parliamentary Contributory Pensions Fund on the review of its Statement of Investment Principles.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61923","61923"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679107","2017-01-31","HM Treasury","2017-01-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the Government's current policy is on maintaining similar levels of funding to that delivered through the European Regional Development Fund and European Social fund after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61971","61971"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679108","2017-01-31","HM Treasury","2017-01-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people benefitted from income tax relief through the Enterprise Investment Scheme in (a) 2013-14 and (b) 2014-15.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61979","61979"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679109","2017-01-31","HM Treasury","2017-01-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people benefitted from income tax relief through Enterprise Management Incentives in (a) 2013-14 and (b) 2014-15.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61953","61953"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679110","2017-01-31","HM Treasury","2017-01-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people benefitted from income tax relief through Save As You Earn in (a) 2013-14 and (b) 2014-15.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61954","61954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679111","2017-01-31","HM Treasury","2017-01-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people benefitted from income tax relief through the Seed Enterprise Investment Scheme in (a) 2013-14 and (b) 2014-15.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61955","61955"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679112","2017-01-31","HM Treasury","2017-01-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people benefitted from income tax relief for professional subscriptions in (a) 2013-14 and (b) 2014-15.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61957","61957"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679113","2017-01-31","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he plans to respond to the letters of 20 October and 30 November 2016 and the email of 12 January 2017 from the hon. Member for  Oldham East and Saddleworth on sitting councillors and child sex offences.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61960","61960"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679114","2017-01-30","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent estimate she has made of the proportion of (a) households and (b) business premises in Rutherglen and Hamilton West constituency that have access to superfast broadband.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61934","61934"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679115","2017-01-31","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps she is taking to secure a data adequacy decision for the UK from the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61972","61972"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679116","2017-01-30","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether Phase 2 superfast broadband delivery in Scotland will receive European funding.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61951","61951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679117","2017-01-30","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether her Department has made an estimate of the proportion of (a) households and (b) business premises in Rutherglen and Hamilton West constituency which are forecast to have signed up to receive superfast broadband by the end of 2017; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61913","61913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679118","2017-01-31","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much was spent on upgrading heating, washing and electrical facilities across the defence estate in each year since May 2010.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61963","61963"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679119","2017-01-31","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the time needed (a) to repair the boiler at Wellington Barracks and (b) for wider facilities upgrades at that barracks.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61961","61961"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679120","2017-01-31","Department for Education","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many citizenship teachers were trained in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61973","61973"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679121","2017-01-30","Department for Education","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 10 January 2017 to Question 56640, on how many occasions National Pupil Database data has been shared with the media in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61932","61932"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679122","2017-01-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the level of military presence on the Paracel Islands in the South China Sea; and what recent representations he has made to his Chinese counterpart of the security situation on those islands.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61879","61879"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679123","2017-01-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 16 January 2017 to Question 58877 and the Answer of 26 January 2017 to Question 60521, which Ministers were made aware of the text of the UN Security Council Resolution 2334 (2016) before the vote on that resolution took place.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61906","61906"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679124","2017-01-30","Department of Health","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients have been admitted to Huddersfield Royal Infirmary in each of the last six months.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61921","61921"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679125","2017-01-31","Department of Health","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what criteria are used to determine the price of gluten-free products accepted by the Advisory Committee on Borderline Substances recommended list which forms Part XV of the Drug Tariff.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61964","61964"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679126","2017-02-02","Department of Health","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the amount recovered from third party insurers for NHS treatment under the NHS Injury Recovery Scheme by each Ambulance Service NHS Trust in each of the last five years for which figures are available; and how much of that amount which is recoverable remains outstanding.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61980","61980"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679127","2017-01-31","Department of Health","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the amounts were of (a) interest charges, (b) repayments of finance lease abilities, (c) service elements, (d) capital lifecycle maintenance, (e) contingent rents and (f) other related private finance initiative (PFI) amounts payable for each of the financial years (i) 2005-06, (ii) 2006-07, (iii) 2007-08, (iv) 2008-09, (v) 2009-10, (vi) 2010-11, (vii) 2011-12, (viii) 2012-13, (ix) 2013-14, (x) 2014-15 and (xi) 2015-16 for all PFI schemes at Russells Hall Acute Hospital.","Biography information for Rob Marris","Rob Marris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61958","61958"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679128","2017-02-02","Department of Health","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the amount recovered from third party insurers for NHS treatment under the NHS Injury Recovery Scheme by (a) Lancashire Teaching Hospitals NHS Foundation Trust, (b) Blackpool Teaching Hospitals NHS Foundation Trust, (c) University Hospitals of Morecambe Bay NHS Foundation Trust and (d) East Lancashire Hospitals NHS Trust in each of the last five years for which figures are available; and how much of that amount which is recoverable remains outstanding.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61981","61981"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679129","2017-01-31","Department of Health","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his estimates are of the amounts of (a) interest charges, (b) repayments of finance lease abilities, (c) service elements, (d) capital lifecycle maintenance, (e) contingent rents and (f) other related private finance initiative (PFI) amounts payable for (i) 2016-17, (ii) 2017-18, (iii) 2018-19, (iv) 2019-20, (v) 2020-21, (vi) 2021-22, (vii) 2022-23, (viii) 2023-24, (ix) 2024-25, (x) 2025-26, (xi) 2026-27, (xii) 2027-28, (xiii) 2028-29, (xiv) 2029-30, (xv) 2030-31, (xvi) 2031-32, (xvii) 2032-33, (xviii) 2033-34, (xix) 2034-35, (xx) 2035-36, (xxi) 2036-37, (xxii) 2037-38, (xxiii) 2038-39, (xxiv) 2039-40, (xxv) 2040-41 and (xxvi) 2041-42 for all PFI schemes at Russells Hall Acute Hospital.","Biography information for Rob Marris","Rob Marris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61959","61959"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679130","2017-01-31","Department of Health","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what criteria determine the inclusion of gluten-free products on the Advisory Committee on Borderline Substances recommended list which forms Part XV of the Drug Tariff.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61965","61965"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679131","2017-01-31","Department of Health","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 16 December 2016 to Question 57501, what proportion of the population is registered with a dentist.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61970","61970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679132","2017-01-31","Home Office","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she plans to respond to the letter from the hon. Member for Wolverhampton South West of 30 November 2016 on non-EU students, reference ZA5879.","Biography information for Rob Marris","Rob Marris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61956","61956"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679133","2017-01-30","Home Office","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to simplify the process for applications for permanent residence in the UK for EU nationals who live in the UK.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Mrs Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61929","61929"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679134","2017-01-30","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 20 January 2017 to Question 59732, what the timetable will be for publishing an updated copy of the Macur Review with redactions relating to Gordon Angelsea reinstated.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61878","61878"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679135","2017-01-30","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what agreements the Government has with the Government of Bangladesh on the transfer of prisoners; and what effect those agreements have had on the number of prisoners exchanged with that country.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61919","61919"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679136","2017-01-30","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what agreements the Government has with the Government of Zimbabwe on the transfer of prisoners; and what effect those agreements have had on the number of prisoners exchanged with that country.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61947","61947"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679137","2017-01-30","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what agreements the Government has with the Government of Nigeria on the transfer of prisoners; and what effect those agreements have had on the number of prisoners exchanged with that country.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61948","61948"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679138","2017-01-30","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what agreements the Government has with the Government of Algeria on the transfer of prisoners; and what effect those agreements have had on the number of prisoners exchanged with that country.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61944","61944"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679139","2017-01-30","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what agreements the Government has with the Government of Somalia relating to the transfer of prisoners; and what effect those agreements have had on the number of prisoners exchanged with that country.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61945","61945"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679140","2017-01-30","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what agreements the Government has with the Government of Ghana on the transfer of prisoners; and what effect those agreements have had on the number of prisoners exchanged with that country.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61943","61943"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679141","2017-01-30","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average length of a prisoner's incarceration is at HM Prison Huntercombe; and for what reasons prisoners leave that prison.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61914","61914"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679142","2017-01-30","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much of the budget for HM Prison Maidstone is spent on (a) prisoner education and (b) prisoners' access to leisure activities.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61924","61924"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679143","2017-01-30","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what agreements the Government has with the Government of China relating to the transfer of prisoners; and what effect those agreements have had on the number of prisoners exchanged with that country.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61912","61912"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679144","2017-01-30","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average length of a prisoner's incarceration is at HMP Maidstone; and for what reasons prisoners leave that prison.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61933","61933"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679145","2017-01-31","Department of Health","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the total spend on mental health programmes for prisoners in England and Wales in each of the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61978","61978"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679146","2017-01-31","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been recalled to prison after being released on licence in each of the last 12 months; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61977","61977"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679147","2017-01-30","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the budget is of HMP Maidstone for 2017-18; and how that budget is broken down.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61928","61928"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679148","2017-01-31","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent representations she has received on the issue of self-inflicted deaths in prisons in England and Wales; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61969","61969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679149","2017-01-31","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps she is taking to reduce the number of self-inflicted deaths in prisons in England and Wales; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61967","61967"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679150","2017-01-30","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much of the budget of HM Prison Huntercombe is spent on (a) prisoner education and (b) prisoners' access to leisure activities.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61949","61949"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679151","2017-01-30","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the budget is of HM Prison Huntercombe for 2017-18; and how that budget is broken down.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61950","61950"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679152","2017-01-31","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate she has made of the number of self-inflicted deaths in prisons in England and Wales in each of the last five years; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61966","61966"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679153","2017-01-30","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of offenders from Nigeria have been transferred to prisons in Nigeria from the UK in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61946","61946"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679154","2017-01-31","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the cost to the public purse has been of the (a) Royal Courts of Justice and (b) Supreme Court in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61962","61962"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679155","2017-01-30","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of appeals to the tribunal service from appellants in Rutherglen and Hamilton West constituency for claims relating to (a) personal independence payment, (b) employment and support allowance, (c) income support, (d) jobseeker's allowance and (e) tax credits were successful in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61935","61935"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679156","2017-01-30","Department for Transport","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 24 January 2017 to Question 60205, when he expects Pendolino trains to (a) reach the end of their serviceable life and (b) be withdrawn from service on the West Coast Mainline.","Biography information for Michael Fabricant","Michael Fabricant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61930","61930"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679157","2017-01-30","Department for Transport","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the reasons for trends in lost scheduled bus mileage since 2011.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61940","61940"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679158","2017-01-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Written Statement of 26 January 2017, HCWS439, on welfare delivery, which of the jobcentres due to be closed or co-located elsewhere will be subject to public consultation.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61910","61910"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679159","2017-01-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what provision there is for his Department to sublet property covered by its Prime contract.","Biography information for Anne McLaughlin","Anne McLaughlin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61939","61939"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679160","2017-01-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in Rutherglen and Hamilton West constituency have had their benefit payments reduced after transferring from disability living allowance to personal independence payment in each year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61936","61936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679161","2017-01-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people have been sanctioned for not attending a jobseeker's allowance appointment within five minutes of the appointed time in Rutherglen and Hamilton West constituency in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61937","61937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679162","2017-01-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Written Statement of 26 January 2017, HCWS439, on welfare delivery, how many (a) existing and (b) new employees of his Department will be based at the newly acquired back-of-house site in Glasgow.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61907","61907"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679163","2017-01-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Written Statement of 26 January 2017, HCWS439, on welfare delivery, whether each of his Department's sites due to be closed or co-located elsewhere have been consulted on those proposals.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61908","61908"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679164","2017-01-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Written Statement of 26 January 2017, HCWS439, on welfare delivery, on what date further details will be released on the acquisition of a new back-of-house site in Glasgow.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61909","61909"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679165","2017-01-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many properties are covered by his Department's Prime contract.","Biography information for Anne McLaughlin","Anne McLaughlin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61938","61938"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679166","2017-01-31","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, on what dates leases for (a) Portcullis House, Glasgow and (b) Corunna House, Glasgow are due for renewal.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61975","61975"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679167","2017-01-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in (a) Rutherglen and Hamilton West constituency, (b) Scotland and (c) the UK received support through the Access to Work scheme in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61952","61952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679168","2017-01-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many blank (a) employment support allowance claim forms and (b) income support claim forms have been issued in the last year from Jobcentres in (i) Scotland, (ii) England and (iii) Wales.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61927","61927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679169","2017-01-31","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what his Department's staff headcount was in each year since 2010 at (a) Portcullis House, Glasgow and (b) Corunna House, Glasgow.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61968","61968"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679170","2017-01-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average time is between a claimant requesting by telephone that a  benefit claim form be sent to them by post and their receiving that form.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61925","61925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679171","2017-01-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether his Department has met (a) Citizens Advice Scotland and (b) Money Matters to discuss the current review of his Department's estate.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61926","61926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679172","2017-01-31","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, from which landlord his Department leases (a) Portcullis House, Glasgow and (b) Corunna House, Glasgow.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61976","61976"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679173","2017-01-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 23 December 2016 to Question 57830, if he will make an assessment of the implications for his Department's policy on future funding for Green Open Homes of the recommendations in Bristol Green Doors report, Closing Doors on Green Open Homes Events, published in December 2016.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61931","61931"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679174","2017-01-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 26 January 2017 to Question 60573, what estimate he has made of how much his Department will spend on large capital projects in each of the next five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61876","61876"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679175","2017-01-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 26 January 2017 to Question 60572, whether his Department has a budget for the employment of additional staff to work on the Great Repeal Bill; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61877","61877"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679176","2017-01-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 13 January 2017 to Question 59325, on the Green Investment Bank, what other activities have been undertaken by (a) his Department, (b) UK Government Investments and (c) the Green Investment Bank to facilitate the introduction of private capital into that Bank's offshore wind assets.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61911","61911"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679177","2017-01-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps the Government is taking to address trends in the market share of international students studying in the UK; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61982","61982"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679178","2017-01-30","Department for International Trade","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps UK Export Finance can take to simplify money transactions between the UK and Iran.","Biography information for Sir Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61922","61922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679180","2017-01-30","Department for International Trade","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps his Department is taking to improve the maximum period of notice businesses receive of acceptance onto the Tradeshow Access Programme to ensure adequate time to prepare promotions at international tradeshows.","Biography information for Sir Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61941","61941"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679181","2017-01-30","Department for International Trade","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what the budget is for the Tradeshow Access Programme; and when that budget was approved.","Biography information for Sir Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61942","61942"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679182","2017-01-30","Department for International Trade","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what assessment he has made of the ability of UK businesses to trade with Iran.","Biography information for Sir Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61915","61915"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/679183","2017-01-31","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether he plans that the Great Repeal Bill will include measures already agreed by the EU but not yet implemented in the UK.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61974","61974"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678511","2017-01-27","Cabinet Office","2017-01-25","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when his Department plans to respond to the recommendations of the Blackett Review of High Impact Low Probability Risks, published 3 November 2016.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61567","61567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678512","2017-01-30","Cabinet Office","2017-01-25","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will make an assessment of the implications for his policies of National Youth Parliament's Votes at 16 campaign.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61609","61609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678513","2017-01-30","Cabinet Office","2017-01-25","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the average salary for (a) men and (b) women was in (i) Greater London and (ii) the London borough of Newham in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61643","61643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678514","2017-01-30","Home Office","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 24 January 2017 to Question 60854, to which Minister in which Department hon. Members should address their concerns on the well-being of Syrian refugees who have entered mainland Europe.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61657","61657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678515","2017-01-27","HM Treasury","2017-01-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether there is a vacancy for a Chief Scientific Advisor to the Treasury.","Biography information for Stephen Metcalfe","Stephen Metcalfe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61709","61709"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678516","2017-01-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the reasons are for business rate relief (a) being provided to private health companies and (b) not being provided to publicly funded health services.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61561","61561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678517","2017-01-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether he has made an assessment of the effect of the level of business rates on NHS budgets.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61562","61562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678518","2017-01-30","HM Treasury","2017-01-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 23 January 2017 to Question 60692, on EU budget: contributions, whether funding commitments made by the Government to the EU as a final settlement, once negotiations on the UK leaving the EU are complete, will not be funded so as to acquire new debt.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61541","61541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678519","2017-01-27","HM Treasury","2017-01-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will estimate the contribution of UK continental shelf oil and gas to the annual tax yield.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61788","61788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678520","2017-01-30","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what his policy is on continuing regional aid funding at the same levels currently provided by the EU after 2020; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61759","61759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678521","2017-01-30","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the total amount of regional aid funding for the West Midlands from EU sources which will be discontinued when the UK leaves the EU; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61760","61760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678522","2017-01-30","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what plans he has to use the provisions of the Housing and Planning Act 2016 to protect sites of archaeological interest subject to development.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61763","61763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678523","2017-01-30","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, for what reasons pre-commencement conditions have been removed from planning applications relating to archaeological considerations on a site due for development; and what alternative protections will be put in place to protect such sites.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61764","61764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678524","2017-01-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much New Homes Bonus funding has been received by (a) Swindon Borough Council and (b) all local authorities in each year since the inception of that funding.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61781","61781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678525","2017-01-30","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he plans to publish the summary of responses to his Department's consultation on 100 per cent business rates retention; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61797","61797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678526","2017-01-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of devolution of the public health grant and 100 per cent business rates retention on local authorities' delivery of the public health outcomes framework from 2018-19.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61774","61774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678527","2017-01-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if the Government will undertake a specific public consultation on the potential effect on future arrangements for public health funding of proposals for business rate retention by local authorities.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61775","61775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678528","2017-01-30","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he plans to publish details of the pilot schemes for 100 per cent business rates retention; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61588","61588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678529","2017-01-30","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what data his Department holds on the extent to which first-time home buyers receive financial help from their parents or another family member.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61589","61589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678530","2017-01-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the retention rate is for newly-qualified social workers who were recorded in service in each year from November 2010 to November 2015; and how many such social workers entered service in that time period.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61564","61564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678531","2017-01-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will make it his policy to maintain payments of the New Homes Bonus at the current rate for those local authorities which use the funds received from that bonus to cover the cost of adult social care.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61618","61618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678532","2017-01-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what metrics his Department uses to calculate compensation for owners of agricultural land under compulsory purchase.","Biography information for Dr Andrew Murrison","Dr Andrew Murrison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61671","61671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678533","2017-01-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 1 December 2016 to Question HL3395, if the Government will hold a public consultation on the effect on future arrangements for public health funding of Government proposals on business rate retention by local authorities.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61637","61637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678534","2017-01-30","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what guidance his Department provides on rental of a property without provision of drinking water; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Selous","Andrew Selous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61747","61747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678535","2017-01-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the costs to local authorities of supporting people made intentionally homeless.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61688","61688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678536","2017-01-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Health on the potential effect on local authorities conduct of statutory duties and public health responsibilities of the Government's proposals for 100 per cent business rates retention from 2018-19 and the devolution of the public health grant.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61687","61687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678537","2017-01-30","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he plans to publish information on the Growth Deal allocation for each local enterprise partnership made under the Autumn Statement 2016.","Biography information for Anne Marie Morris","Anne Marie Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61656","61656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678538","2017-01-30","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the economic effect of the introduction of the Business Rate Retention Scheme in April 2013; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61659","61659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678539","2017-01-30","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Written Statement of 17 January 2017, Homelessness Reduction Bill, HCWS 418, if he will place in the Library the evidential basis used to determine the level of funding to local government to meet the new burden costs associated with the Homelessness Reduction Bill.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61704","61704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678540","2017-01-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect of its proposals for 100 per cent business rates retention and devolution of the public health grant on the capacity of local authorities to work to reduce health inequalities from 2018-19.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61691","61691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678541","2017-01-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many country parks managed by local authorities there are in each parliamentary constituency; and how many of those country parks charge for parking.","Biography information for Margaret Greenwood","Margaret Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61681","61681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678542","2017-01-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will take steps to establish a time-limit on the housing records of people made intentionally homeless.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61689","61689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678543","2017-01-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will take steps to establish a postcode for people made homeless which may be used for job applications and registration with GPs.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61690","61690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678544","2017-01-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of parking charges at country parks on visitor numbers.","Biography information for Margaret Greenwood","Margaret Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61680","61680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678545","2017-01-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if his Department will take steps to check whether recipients of loans from the Home Building Fund pay business taxes in the UK.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61611","61611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678546","2017-01-27","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if she will make an assessment of the potential effects of the UK exiting the EU on the likelihood of international broadcasting companies continuing to base themselves in the UK.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61686","61686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678547","2017-01-27","Department for Education","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate her Department has made of the cost of the amendments to the Digital Economy Bill on skills training on digital inclusion.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61566","61566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678548","2017-01-27","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to the National Infrastructure Commission's report, Connected future, published 15 December 2016, how standards for 5G coverage will be agreed.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61565","61565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678549","2017-01-30","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what her most recent estimate is of the percentage of geographic voice and data coverage provided by (a) O2, (b) EE, (c) Three and (d) Vodafone; and whether she expects those levels to reach 90 per cent geographic coverage for each of those operators by the end of 2017.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61548","61548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678550","2017-01-30","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether it will be a requirement of the independent review of S4C that the reviewer be proficient in the Welsh language.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61761","61761"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678551","2017-01-27","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether GPS guided parachutes have been used to facilitate arms drops to rebel forces in Syria in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Sammy Wilson","Sammy Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61768","61768"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678552","2017-01-27","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department has received requests from other government departments for the use of GPS guided parachutes to drop aid to besieged Syrian civilians in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Sammy Wilson","Sammy Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61769","61769"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678554","2017-01-30","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many UK (a) armed forces personnel and (b) guests attending (i) Royal Navy SSGN and Trident II D5 Demonstrations and (ii) Shakedown Operations in (A) 2013 and (B) 2016 were accommodated in US hotels; and for how long such people were so accommodated.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61542","61542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678555","2017-01-27","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether UK Trident missiles rely on (a) weather data and (b) navigational data provided by the US.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61534","61534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678556","2017-01-27","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans his Department has for the future of the depth servicing of helicopters at RNAS Culdrose.","Biography information for Derek Thomas","Derek Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61528","61528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678557","2017-01-30","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the number of (a) regular (i) soldiers, (ii) sailors and (iii) airmen and (b) reserve (A) soldiers, (B) sailors and (C) airmen was by medical category for each year since 2001.","Biography information for Anne-Marie Trevelyan","Mrs Anne-Marie Trevelyan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61575","61575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678558","2017-01-30","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent discussions he has had with his international counterparts on NATO's two per cent GDP spending target.","Biography information for Mr Peter Bone","Mr Peter Bone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61577","61577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678559","2017-01-27","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 2 December 2016 to Question 55493, what progress has been made on extending the availability of the HM Forces Railcard since the meeting of the Rail Delivery Group in December 2016.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61593","61593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678560","2017-01-27","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many soldiers are LGV qualified.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61638","61638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678561","2017-01-27","Cabinet Office","2017-01-25","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the Answer of 25 April 2016 to Question 34745, if his Department will take steps to recognise the contributions of veterans by introducing a National Defence Medal.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61696","61696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678562","2017-01-30","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which NATO allied countries provided Maritime Patrol Aircraft inside UK airspace on 25 January 2017.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61758","61758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678563","2017-01-30","Department for Education","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when the Institute for Apprenticeships route panels will be fully operational.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61757","61757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678564","2017-01-30","Department for Education","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the pass rate among students aged 17 years and over who achieved grade A* to C in GCSE (a) mathematics and (b) English in 2015-16.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61756","61756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678565","2017-01-30","Department for Education","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many statutory instruments she plans to lay for the Technical and Further Education Bill.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61755","61755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678566","2017-01-27","Department for Education","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many times in 2016 and 2017 the Education Funding Agency met Ofsted to discuss Durand Academy.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61713","61713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678567","2017-01-27","Department for Education","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions she has had with Ofsted on (a) recent closures of nurseries due to safety concerns and (b) the effectiveness of (i) pre-scheduled and unscheduled site inspections.","Biography information for Dr Andrew Murrison","Dr Andrew Murrison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61731","61731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678568","2017-01-27","Department for Education","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department plans to take to determine the efficiency of the provision of free childcare funding.","Biography information for Dr Andrew Murrison","Dr Andrew Murrison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61732","61732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678569","2017-01-27","Department for Education","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she plans to take to involve private sector childcare providers in assessing the efficacy of free childcare funding.","Biography information for Dr Andrew Murrison","Dr Andrew Murrison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61733","61733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678570","2017-01-27","Department for Education","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will place in the Library the mandate or remit given to the Standards and Testing Authority for the review of assessment that Authority is carrying out for her Department.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61666","61666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678571","2017-01-27","Department for Education","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 9 January 2017 to Question 57578, on apprentices, if she will make an assessment of the potential effect of advances in robotics on job opportunities for apprentices.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61708","61708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678572","2017-01-27","Department for Education","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the change in responsibilities of teaching assistants since 2010; and what steps her Department takes to support teaching assistants who have taken on additional responsibilities.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61683","61683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678573","2017-01-27","Department for Education","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 10 January 2017 to Question 56640, on pupils: nationality, whether her Department provides National Pupil Database data to named bodies and third parties free of charge.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61684","61684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678574","2017-01-27","Department for Education","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many academies or maintained schools with Key Stage 2 SATs results in the top 3 per cent of comparable schools have been judged inadequate.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61714","61714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678575","2017-01-27","Department for Education","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when she plans formally to consult on plans to reform (a) primary assessment and (b) baseline assessment.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61725","61725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678576","2017-01-27","Department for Education","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will publish all correspondence between the Education Funding Agency and Ofsted on Durand Academy in 2016 and 2017.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61712","61712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678577","2017-01-30","Department for Education","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to ensure that vulnerable children and young people who become mental health in-patients can continue their education without their treatment affecting their learning.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61765","61765"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678578","2017-01-30","Department for Education","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what information her Department holds on which children and family organisations have supported the provisions relating to power to innovate in the Children and Social Work Bill.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61766","61766"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678579","2017-01-27","Department for Education","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions she has had with providers on her Department's review of baseline assessment.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61723","61723"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678580","2017-01-27","Department for Education","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent meetings officials of her Department have had with providers of reception baseline assessment models.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61724","61724"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678581","2017-01-30","Department for Education","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what consultation she has carried out on the provisions relating to the power to innovate in the Children and Social Work Bill.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61767","61767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678582","2017-01-27","Department for Education","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many Ofsted inspections deployed in excess of 10 inspectors to one school in one inspection (a) 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012, (d) 2013, (e) 2014, (f) 2015 and (g) 2016.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61711","61711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678583","2017-01-30","Department for Education","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what evidence she used to calculate the weighting given to the pupil mobility factor in proposals for the school funding formula.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61642","61642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678584","2017-01-30","Department for Education","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 23 January 2017 to Question 60537, what the timescale will be for the Government's early years workforce strategy.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61664","61664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678585","2017-01-27","Department for Education","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the average salary was for (a) general teaching assistants, (b) higher-level teaching assistants and (c) all teaching assistants in (i) local authority maintained schools, (ii) academy schools and (iii) free schools in each year between 2010 and 2015.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61630","61630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678586","2017-01-27","Department for Education","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 20 January 2017 to Question 60334, and with reference to the Answer of 10 June 2015 to Question 856, whether the figures supplied in those answers for the average salaries of teaching assistants in November 2013 and November 2015 were calculated on the same basis.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61628","61628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678587","2017-01-27","Department for Education","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what information her Department holds relating to teaching assistants and other school support staff on trends in (a) teacher recruitment and retention, (b) performance and effectiveness, (c) days lost due to sickness, (d) skills attained and (e) employment on term-time-only contracts.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61629","61629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678589","2017-01-30","Department for Education","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of school-age children regularly attend a school breakfast club.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61705","61705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678590","2017-01-30","Department for Education","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of school-age children regularly attend an after-school club.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61706","61706"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678591","2017-01-30","Department for Education","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many students achieved three or more A grade or higher A-levels in each ethnic group for each year since 2006.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61549","61549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678592","2017-01-30","Department for Education","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 14 December 2016 to Question 56753, what mechanisms the national funding formula will use to account for the cost pressures which schools face.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61540","61540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678593","2017-01-30","Department for Education","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will take steps to prohibit subsidiaries of profit-making companies from contracting with local authorities to run child protection and other children's social care services.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61584","61584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678594","2017-01-30","Department for Education","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what funding is provided by her Department for safeguarding of students who are being educated at home.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61794","61794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678595","2017-01-30","Department for Education","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will guarantee apprenticeship funding for non-levy paying employers in (a) 2018-19, (b) 2019-20 and (c) 2020-21.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61753","61753"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678596","2017-01-30","Department for Education","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the oral contribution of the Minister of State for Apprenticeships and Skills of 9 January 2017, Official Report, column 114, how much of the 550 million disadvantage funding for post-16 places will be spent on subsidising college buses in 2016-17.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61752","61752"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678597","2017-01-30","Department for Education","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department takes to ensure that children who are being educated at home are safeguarded.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61795","61795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678598","2017-01-27","Department for Education","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what statutory guidance exists on protecting the welfare of students who are being educated at home.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61772","61772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678599","2017-01-27","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many instances of avian flu were identified in sites in England and Wales in each of the last 24 months; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61743","61743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678600","2017-01-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, (a) how many wild animals and (b) of which species are licensed in circuses.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61557","61557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678601","2017-01-27","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what information her Department holds of the number of instances of avian flu identified in sites across England and Wales in each of the last 24 months; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61614","61614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678602","2017-01-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she plans to take to secure access to EU markets for (a) UK exports and (b) Scotch whisky in negotiations on the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Calum Kerr","Calum Kerr","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61651","61651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678603","2017-01-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, for what reason local authorities have no direct responsibility to control PM2.5 concentrations; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Selous","Andrew Selous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61707","61707"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678604","2017-01-27","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether it is her policy that the EU Urban Wastewater Treatment Directive will be incorporated in full into UK law when the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61729","61729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678605","2017-01-27","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, on what dates she has met representatives of the (a) agricultural and (b) retail sectors to discuss the decline in oilseed rape harvests; and what steps she has taken as a result of those meetings.","Biography information for Dr Andrew Murrison","Dr Andrew Murrison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61734","61734"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678606","2017-01-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the human rights situation in West Papua.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61742","61742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678607","2017-01-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the level of threat from piracy in (a) current and (b) prospective shipping lanes of economic interest to the UK.","Biography information for Dr Andrew Murrison","Dr Andrew Murrison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61735","61735"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678608","2017-01-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his Indonesian counterpart on conflict in West Papua.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61719","61719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678609","2017-01-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to promote peace in West Papua.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61720","61720"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678610","2017-01-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his counterpart from Papua New Guinea on conflict in West Papua.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61722","61722"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678611","2017-01-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether (a) he and (b) the Minister for Asia and the Pacific plans to visit Papua New Guinea in the near future.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61721","61721"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678612","2017-01-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that President Kabila abides by the 31 December 2016 agreement reached in the Democratic Republic of Congo to ensure that free and fair elections take place in that country before the end of 2017.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61662","61662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678614","2017-01-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 24 January 2017 to Question 60166, what preparations (a) his Department and (b) the British Embassy in Belgrade undertook prior to his official visit to Serbia in November 2016.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61655","61655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678615","2017-02-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his Department identified any human rights risks in the Overseas Security and Justice Assistance assessment it conducted for the regional MSc in Security Sector Management in Ethiopia.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61665","61665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678617","2017-01-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his Chinese counterpart on building on disputed islands in the South China Sea.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61535","61535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678618","2017-01-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his counterpart in the Philippines on building on disputed islands in the South China Sea.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61536","61536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678619","2017-01-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with the UK's Permanent Representative at the UN on the security situation in the South China Sea.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61537","61537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678620","2017-01-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when he plans to visit the US; and when he plans to meet his US counterpart.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61538","61538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678621","2017-01-30","Department of Health","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when the UK National Screening Committee plans to begin its review of systematic population screening for atrial fibrillation.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61543","61543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678622","2017-01-30","Department of Health","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the annual financial cost is of atrial fibrillation-related stroke to the NHS.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61544","61544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678623","2017-01-30","Department of Health","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department took to support Cervical Cancer Prevention Week.","Biography information for Mr John Baron","Mr John Baron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61545","61545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678624","2017-01-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in each parliamentary constituency who receive employment and support allowance have been diagnosed with (a) hidradenitis suppurativa and (b) a dermatological condition in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61546","61546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678625","2017-01-30","Department of Health","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many finished admission episodes there were in each parliamentary constituency where a patient was diagnosed as having (a) hidradenitis suppurativa and (b) a dermatological condition in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61547","61547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678626","2017-01-27","Department of Health","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent progress his Department has made on recovering money from overseas visitors and other chargeable NHS patients.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61532","61532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678627","2017-01-27","Department of Health","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether cervical screening is available to all women at contraception and sexual health clinics.","Biography information for Mr John Baron","Mr John Baron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61533","61533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678629","2017-01-27","Department of Health","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, on how many occasions section 35 of the Freedom of Information Act 2000 has been applied to cases where Valporate has been prescribed to pregnant women.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61599","61599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678630","2017-01-30","Department of Health","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much was reclaimed in health costs from foreign governments in each of the last three years by Northern General Hospital.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61606","61606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678631","2017-01-30","Department of Health","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much was reclaimed in health costs from foreign governments in each of the last three years by Doncaster and Bassetlaw Hospitals NHS Foundation Trust.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61607","61607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678632","2017-01-30","Department of Health","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how NHS processes for the purchase of medicines are taken into account in decisions of allocating funding for research and development in life sciences; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61608","61608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678633","2017-01-30","Department of Health","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information his Department holds on the number of people aged 50- years and under who have Parkinson's disease.","Biography information for Nick Thomas-Symonds","Nick Thomas-Symonds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61574","61574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678634","2017-01-27","Department of Health","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what substances are included in the active homeopathic substances referred to in medicines and healthcare products regulatory guidance on module 3 of the homeopathic medicinal products dossier.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61600","61600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678635","2017-01-27","Department of Health","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much was reclaimed in health costs from non-UK Governments in each of the last three years by the Rotherham NHS Foundation Trust.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61601","61601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678636","2017-01-30","Department of Health","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect of councils charging fees to undertake needs assessments for adult social care on people with social care needs; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61558","61558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678637","2017-01-27","Department of Health","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make cervical screening available to women at every contraception and sexual health clinic; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61552","61552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678638","2017-01-30","Department of Health","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many NHS clinical commissioning groups have a no access policy in relation to staple gluten-free substitute foods via FP10 prescription in England.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61569","61569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678639","2017-01-30","Department of Health","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 16 December 2016 to Question 57424, on dental services, for what reason his Department does not hold the data requested.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61553","61553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678640","2017-01-30","Department of Health","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 16 December 2016 to Question 57424, how many dental surgeries there are in England.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61554","61554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678641","2017-01-30","Department of Health","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 16 December 2016 to Question 57423, what estimate he has made of the number of children who are registered with a dentist.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61555","61555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678642","2017-01-30","Department of Health","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the (a) number of repeat dispensing prescriptions issued in England in each year from 2010 to 2015 and (b) savings made in each year as a result of repeat dispensing; and what steps the Government is taking to encourage greater use of repeat dispensing.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61571","61571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678643","2017-01-30","Department of Health","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what new drugs for the potential treatment of Parkinson's disease are being considered for licensing.","Biography information for Nick Thomas-Symonds","Nick Thomas-Symonds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61573","61573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678644","2017-01-30","Department of Health","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of people in England diagnosed with coeliac disease who are unable to access staple gluten-free substitute foods.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61570","61570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678645","2017-01-27","Department of Health","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of access to country parks on children's health and well-being.","Biography information for Margaret Greenwood","Margaret Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61677","61677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678646","2017-01-27","Department of Health","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of access to country parks on health inequalities.","Biography information for Margaret Greenwood","Margaret Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61678","61678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678647","2017-01-27","Department of Health","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the effect that 20 minutes of brisk walking has on improving health.","Biography information for Margaret Greenwood","Margaret Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61679","61679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678648","2017-01-30","Department of Health","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of community hospitals are in (a) Devon and (b) East Devon.","Biography information for Sir Hugo Swire","Sir Hugo Swire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61649","61649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678649","2017-01-27","HM Treasury","2017-01-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to reduce demand for illicit tobacco.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61624","61624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678650","2017-01-27","Department of Health","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much was reclaimed in costs to the NHS from foreign governments by Leeds General Infirmary in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61639","61639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678651","2017-01-27","Department of Health","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much was reclaimed in costs to the NHS from foreign governments by Leicester Royal Infirmary Infirmary in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61640","61640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678652","2017-01-27","Department of Health","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much was reclaimed in costs to the NHS from foreign governments by King's Mill Hospital in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61641","61641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678653","2017-01-30","Department of Health","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much was reclaimed in costs to the NHS from foreign governments by Chesterfield Royal Hospital in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61645","61645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678654","2017-01-30","Department of Health","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much was reclaimed in costs to the NHS from foreign governments by United Lincolnshire Hospitals NHS Trust in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61646","61646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678655","2017-01-27","Department of Health","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the merits of reducing the age for screening for bowel cancer to people aged 50.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61685","61685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678656","2017-01-27","Department of Health","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 13 January 2017 to Question 59918, whether he attended the Departmental Board meeting that took place after the publication of the NHS Annual Report and Accounts 2015-16.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61634","61634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678657","2017-01-30","Department of Health","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make it his policy to include prison mental health services within the Care Quality Commission's remit for inspection.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61749","61749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678658","2017-01-30","Department of Health","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many unpaid NHS jobs in mental health were advertised in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61750","61750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678659","2017-01-30","Department of Health","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect of cancelled elective surgeries on the development and training of trainee surgeons.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61748","61748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678660","2017-01-27","Department of Health","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which medical discipline has had the greatest vacancy rate in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61716","61716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678661","2017-01-30","Department of Health","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the UK leaving the EU on healthcare standards and patient access to medicines in the UK.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61746","61746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678662","2017-01-27","Department of Health","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the Government issued any guidelines to insurance companies on the effects of Government advice in February 2016 to consult a medical professional before travelling to areas where there were Zika outbreaks.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61778","61778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678663","2017-01-30","Department of Health","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many broader scope meetings have been held by the Medicines and Healthcare Products Regulatory Agency since May 2015.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61762","61762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678664","2017-01-27","Department of Health","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much was reclaimed in health costs from foreign governments in each of the last three years by Derby Hospitals NHS Trust.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61782","61782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678665","2017-01-30","Department of Health","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of clinical commissioning groups offer three full cycles of IVF treatment paid for by the NHS.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61799","61799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678666","2017-01-30","Department of Health","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure equal access to IVF treatment across the UK.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61798","61798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678667","2017-01-27","Department of Health","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps the General Dental Council (GDC) is taking to manage cases that fall under section 6.1.3 in the GDC's standard for the dental team document.","Biography information for Mr Steve Baker","Steve Baker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61790","61790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678668","2017-01-27","Department of Health","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many General Dental Council registered dentists have filed for bankruptcy since 2006; and how many dental practices with Limited status have filed for individual voluntary arrangements since 2006.","Biography information for Mr Steve Baker","Steve Baker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61791","61791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678669","2017-01-27","Department of Health","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many General Dental Council registered dentists have been prosecuted or been subject to fitness to practice judgements as a result of failing to pay dental laboratory accounts since 2006.","Biography information for Mr Steve Baker","Steve Baker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61792","61792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678670","2017-01-27","Department of Health","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if the Government will bring forward proposals to include the sale of illicit tobacco as an offence under the Restricted Premises Order.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61625","61625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678671","2017-01-27","HM Treasury","2017-01-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans the Government has to increase the penalties for recidivist offenders caught selling illegal products.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61626","61626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678672","2017-01-27","Home Office","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if the Government will take steps to increase the powers of trading standards officers to allow them to withdraw alcohol licences for those caught selling illicit tobacco.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61627","61627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678673","2017-01-27","HM Treasury","2017-01-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to reduce the sale of illicit tobacco.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61623","61623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678674","2017-01-30","Home Office","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions she has had with Cabinet colleagues on when to commence the second part of the Leveson inquiry; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61700","61700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678675","2017-01-27","Home Office","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what changes in funding from the public purse to Crimestoppers were made in each year from 2010-11.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61699","61699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678676","2017-01-27","Home Office","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much was accrued to the public purse in nationality fees in 2016.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61632","61632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678677","2017-01-27","Home Office","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate her Department has made of the cost of monitoring and policing anti-fracking protests since 2010 in (a) Lancashire and (b) the UK.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61635","61635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678678","2017-01-27","Home Office","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when the term of office of the current Chief Scientific Adviser to her Department ends; and what the timescale will be for filling that vacancy when it arises.","Biography information for Stephen Metcalfe","Stephen Metcalfe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61633","61633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678679","2017-01-30","Home Office","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many European Arrest Warrant requests have been made by UK police forces to each of the other EU countries in the last five years; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61591","61591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678680","2017-01-30","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many Irish citizens in prison within the UK have requested transfers to prisons in the Republic of Ireland in the last 12 months; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61592","61592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678682","2017-01-30","House of Commons Commission","2017-01-25","To ask the right hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington, representing the House of Commons Commission, what recent assessment the Commission has made of the level of online abuse of female hon. Members.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61644","61644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678683","2017-01-27","Department for International Development","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether the Halo Trust is working on behalf of the Government in carrying out its de-mining work in Colombia; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Clive Efford","Clive Efford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61682","61682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678684","2017-01-27","Department for International Development","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what estimate her Department has made of the potential shortfall in funding to charities and non-governmental organisations as a result of the revocation in the US of the Presidential Memorandum of 23 January 2009 Mexico City Policy and Assistance for Voluntary Population Planning and the reinstatement of the Presidential Memorandum of 22 January 2001 Restoration of Mexico City Policy; and what plans her Department has to ensure continued access to (a) family planning advice and (b) safe termination and contraception through its programmes.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61717","61717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678685","2017-01-27","Department for International Development","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment her Department has made on the success of the World Food Programme's use of the Joint Precision Airdrop System (JPADS) for aid air-drops into Deir Ezzor; and what steps her Department has taken to assess the feasibility of the Government using JPADS for aid air-drops into besieged areas of Syria.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61715","61715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678686","2017-01-27","Department for International Development","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, with reference to her Department's Bilateral Development Review 2016, how the analysis of demographic trends took into account the ageing population in developing countries.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61636","61636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678687","2017-01-27","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what plans she has for the future of the courts and tribunals estate in England and Wales; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61539","61539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678688","2017-01-27","Department of Health","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent steps he has taken on improving mental health support for young offenders.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61595","61595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678689","2017-01-27","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent discussions she has had with (a) representatives of the paralegal profession, (b) the Professional Paralegal Register and (c) the Institute of Paralegals on the effectiveness of the registration system for that profession.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61615","61615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678690","2017-01-27","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what discussions she has had with the Professional Paralegal Register on the level of registration on that register since that body was created.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61616","61616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678691","2017-01-27","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if she will add the Professional Paralegal Register to the statutory list of approved regulators under the Legal Services Act 2007.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61617","61617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678692","2017-01-27","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if she will make it her policy to increase public funding for the Streetgames programme.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61619","61619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678693","2017-01-27","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent discussions she has had with Network Rail on engineering apprenticeships for youth offenders.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61620","61620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678694","2017-01-27","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what discussions she has had with court staff trade union representatives on their remuneration and training for judicial decision-making as set out in the Transforming our Justice System, consultation paper, published in September 2016.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61551","61551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678695","2017-01-30","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when the Government plans to publish its legislative proposals stemming from its consultation, Reforming the Soft Tissue Injury (Whiplash) Claims Process, of November 2016.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61550","61550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678696","2017-01-27","Attorney General","2017-01-25","To ask the Attorney General, what information his Department holds on the number of plea bargains offered to defendants in England since 2010.","Biography information for Dr Andrew Murrison","Dr Andrew Murrison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61736","61736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678697","2017-01-30","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much was spent on education and training for prisoners in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61751","61751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678698","2017-01-30","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if she will take steps to introduce guidance for courts on providing both parents with 50-50 access to their children on divorce as a default unless specific circumstances demonstrate otherwise; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61660","61660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678699","2017-01-30","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State's oral contribution of 24 January 2017, Official Report, column 156, when she plans to publish the findings of her investigation into self-inflicted deaths in prisons.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61605","61605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678700","2017-01-27","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many youth offenders have participated in the Duke of Edinburgh Award Scheme in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61698","61698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678701","2017-01-30","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, (a) how many and (b) what proportion of appeals listed by the (a) first-tier and (b) upper tribunal of the Immigration and Asylum Chamber since 2015 have taken more than 12 months to be heard; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61796","61796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678702","2017-01-27","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, for how long the post of Chief Scientific Adviser to her Department has been vacant; and what plans she has to advertise for and fill that vacancy.","Biography information for Stephen Metcalfe","Stephen Metcalfe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61771","61771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678703","2017-01-27","Northern Ireland Office","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, for how long the post of Chief Scientific Adviser to his Department has been vacant; and what plans he has to advertise for and fill that vacancy.","Biography information for Stephen Metcalfe","Stephen Metcalfe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61770","61770"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678704","2017-01-27","Northern Ireland Office","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of integrated schooling programmes in Northern Ireland in promoting community cohesion since 2013.","Biography information for Dr Andrew Murrison","Dr Andrew Murrison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61737","61737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678705","2017-01-27","Northern Ireland Office","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the recommendations of the Boundary Commission for Northern Ireland on political stability in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Dr Andrew Murrison","Dr Andrew Murrison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61730","61730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678706","2017-01-30","Northern Ireland Office","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what recent meetings he has had with businesses in Northern Ireland to discuss the UK's exit from the EU.","Biography information for Mr Peter Bone","Mr Peter Bone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61578","61578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678707","2017-01-27","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what criteria the Government uses to determine whether to announce the (a) date and (b) outcome of tests of Trident missiles.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61728","61728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678708","2017-01-30","Prime Minister","2017-01-25","To ask the Prime Minister, what plans she has to discuss with President Trump his policy on reducing nuclear weapons through negotiations during her forthcoming visit to the US.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61754","61754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678709","2017-01-27","Department for Transport","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to reduce the number of roadworks sites which are unmanned overnight and at weekends.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61780","61780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678710","2017-01-27","Department for Transport","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether funds paid out to properties under the HS2 Exceptional Hardship Scheme or Need to Sell Scheme which no longer fulfil the criteria of those schemes where the route of High Speed 2 is changed will be recovered.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61783","61783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678711","2017-01-27","Department for Transport","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the average amount is that has been paid out to people under the HS2 Exceptional Hardship Scheme.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61784","61784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678712","2017-01-30","Department for Transport","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will take steps to allow (a) Devon County Council and (b) other councils to decide how and where to spend the Bus Service Operators Grant.","Biography information for Sir Hugo Swire","Sir Hugo Swire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61745","61745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678713","2017-01-27","Department for Transport","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which local authorities were successful in their bids for the Access Fund for funding to improve access to jobs and education through cycling and walking; and how much funding each authority secured.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61727","61727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678714","2017-01-27","Department for Transport","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what analysis of the effectiveness of additional gearbox condition monitoring on the AS332 L2 and the EC225 was undertaken by (a) his Department and (b) regulatory authorities after the accident at Peterhead on 1 April 2009.","Biography information for Drew Hendry","Drew Hendry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61738","61738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678715","2017-01-27","Department for Transport","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what monitoring his Department has undertaken of implementation of the Air Accident Investigation Branch's safety recommendations made as a result of its report on the accident at Peterhead on 1 April 2009.","Biography information for Drew Hendry","Drew Hendry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61739","61739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678716","2017-01-27","Department for Transport","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions his Department has had with helicopter operators and manufacturers on steps to reassure workers in the North Sea about the maintenance and operational record of the helicopter fleet.","Biography information for Drew Hendry","Drew Hendry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61726","61726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678717","2017-01-30","Department for Transport","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when his Department plans to make a final decision on Govia Thameslink Railway's existing force majeure claims.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61654","61654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678718","2017-01-30","Department for Transport","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if his Department will assess the potential merits of allowing local authorities to take responsibility for the Bus Service Operators Grant.","Biography information for Sir Hugo Swire","Sir Hugo Swire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61650","61650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678719","2017-01-30","Department for Transport","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many driving tests have been taken at the Southend driving test centre; and how many of those tests resulted in a pass in each of the last five years.","Biography information for James Duddridge","James Duddridge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61652","61652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678720","2017-01-27","Department for Transport","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much funding from the public purse has been paid to owners of Leicestershire properties under the HS2 Exceptional Hardship Scheme.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61631","61631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678721","2017-01-30","Department for Transport","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps the Government is taking to accelerate the rate of performance improvement on the Southern rail network.","Biography information for Ms Nusrat Ghani","Nusrat Ghani","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61586","61586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678722","2017-01-30","Department for Transport","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government to ensure that constituencies increasing in population size will be adequately supported by (a) road and (b) rail infrastructure.","Biography information for Ms Nusrat Ghani","Nusrat Ghani","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61585","61585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678723","2017-01-27","Department of Health","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his policy is on co-location of GP surgeries within hospital accident and emergency units.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61594","61594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678724","2017-01-27","Department for Transport","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to improve (a) the A38 and (b) other transport links to the South West.","Biography information for Mrs Sheryll Murray","Mrs Sheryll Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61563","61563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678725","2017-01-27","Department for Transport","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what total amount has been paid out under the HS2 Exceptional Hardship Scheme.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61602","61602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678726","2017-01-27","Department for Transport","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many people have (a) applied and (b) had an application accepted for compensation under the HS2 Exceptional Hardship Scheme.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61603","61603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678727","2017-01-27","Department for Transport","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if his Department will make an assessment of the effect on the motorsport industry of the European Court of Justice ruling of September 2014, Damijan Vnuk v Zavarovalnica Triglav C-162/13, that introduced the requirement for all motorised vehicles used off-road to be insured.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61596","61596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678728","2017-01-27","Department for Transport","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many people in Leicestershire have (a) applied and (b) had an application accepted for compensation under the HS2 Exceptional Hardship Scheme.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61604","61604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678729","2017-01-27","Department for Transport","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions he has had with Virgin Trains on consistency in ticket pricing within their franchise terms.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61597","61597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678730","2017-01-27","Department for Transport","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will discuss with Virgin Trains the extent to which its franchise agreement permits differentiation in ticket pricing for similar journeys to end from (a) Preston and (b) Lancaster stations.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61598","61598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678731","2017-01-27","Department for Transport","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether Government contracts for the procurement of new rolling stock contain provisions specifying the use of local contents in the supply chains for manufacturers who win those contracts.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61529","61529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678732","2017-01-27","Department for Transport","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what account his Department took of the potential merits of including in Government contracts for the procurement of new rolling stock provisions to support UK engineering capability.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61530","61530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678734","2017-01-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will publish the total number of people assessed for personal independence payment (PIP) who have been awarded a total score of zero in the assessment process for the (a) mobility and (b) daily living component part in each year since the introduction of PIP.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61776","61776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678735","2017-01-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, for what reasons a person is required to meet a minimum level of national insurance contributions before they are eligible to receive employment support allowance.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61587","61587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678736","2017-01-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when his Department will implement plans to cease work capability assessments re-assessments for employment and support allowance claimants with the most severe health conditions and disabilities where the condition is unlikely to improve; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Mrs Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61568","61568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678737","2017-01-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the total amount in maintenance arrears of non-resident parents is under the (a) Child Support Agency and (b) Child Maintenance Service.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61576","61576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678738","2017-01-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many additional work coaches will be employed in (a) Rutherglen Jobcentre and (b) total across Glasgow's jobcentres as a result of the planned jobcentre closures there.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61610","61610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678739","2017-01-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of people excluded from auto-enrolment as a result of changes to the earnings trigger in the Pensions Act 2011 and reviews subsequent to that Act.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61621","61621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678740","2017-01-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of people excluded from auto-enrolment as a result of the introduction of the three-month waiting period in the Pensions Act 2011.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61622","61622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678741","2017-01-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether Jobcentre Plus offices have made referrals to Asos' online distribution centre in Barnsley.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61590","61590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678742","2017-01-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what training is provided to assessors on dealing with young people who have Parkinson's disease.","Biography information for Nick Thomas-Symonds","Nick Thomas-Symonds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61572","61572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678743","2017-01-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of people receiving hardship payments have had recovery of money suspended as a result of the claimant finding work at or above their earnings threshold in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61676","61676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678744","2017-01-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of unsuccessful claims for personal independence payments were overturned at the mandatory reconsideration stage in the last 12 months for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mr Mark Francois","Mr Mark Francois","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61703","61703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678745","2017-01-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of unsuccessful claims for employment support allowance were overturned at the mandatory reconsideration stage in the last 12 months for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mr Mark Francois","Mr Mark Francois","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61702","61702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678746","2017-01-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when his Department plans to publish the unlikely to pay guidance given to child maintenance staff to assist them in the determination of whether a non-paying parent should be required to pay child maintenance due via the Collect and Pay Service.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61692","61692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678747","2017-01-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will assess the potential merits of allowing government agencies to share information in cases where there are concerns for a claimant's wellbeing as a result on non-contact with that client.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61697","61697"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678748","2017-01-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will increase the maximum age for teacher deaths in occupational data beyond the age of 74.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61695","61695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678749","2017-01-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, for what reasons 74 is the maximum age at which occupational data include a teacher death.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61694","61694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678750","2017-01-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make it his policy to introduce a one-stop process for claimants who are required to update their personal information with government agencies.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61674","61674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678751","2017-01-27","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will make an assessment of the potential effects of making sector-by-sector deals with certain industries after the UK leaves the EU on the competitiveness of those industries' supply chains.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61675","61675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678752","2017-01-27","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what progress has been made by the Aerospace Growth Partnership.","Biography information for Drew Hendry","Drew Hendry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61740","61740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678753","2017-01-27","HM Treasury","2017-01-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what representations he has received from (a) parliamentarians and (b) members of the public on the closure of HSBC branches.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61741","61741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678754","2017-01-27","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 23 December 2016 to Question 57829, on energy: conservation, what role the new apprenticeship standards will play in improving energy efficiency and decarbonisation in buildings.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61718","61718"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678755","2017-01-27","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 23 December 2016 to Question 57827, on housing: carbon emissions, what future policy options he is considering.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61667","61667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678756","2017-01-27","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 23 December 2016 to Question 57827, on housing: carbon emissions, how much seed funding the Government provided for Green Open Homes.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61668","61668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678757","2017-01-27","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, on what dates he has had meetings with the representatives of small and medium-sized enterprises to discuss strengthening UK supply chains in advance of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Dr Andrew Murrison","Dr Andrew Murrison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61670","61670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678758","2017-01-27","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what discussions he has had with the owners of Savvibuy on that company's service to consumers since 1 December.","Biography information for Jeff Smith","Jeff Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61672","61672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678759","2017-01-27","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the effect of current charging arrangements on the ability of gas plants which already possesses capacity contracts to bid into the early capacity auction on 31 January 2017.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61673","61673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678760","2017-01-27","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the effect on (a) UK security of supply and (b) consumer costs of holding the early capacity auction prior to Ofgem reporting its final decision on charging arrangements.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61669","61669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678761","2017-01-30","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what representations he has received from small businesses and their trade bodies on the potential effect of business rates revaluation on their businesses.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61653","61653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678762","2017-01-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what representations his Department has received on Savvibuy's refunding practices for customers who have experienced delayed deliveries and refunds.","Biography information for Jeff Smith","Jeff Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61701","61701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678763","2017-01-27","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that companies in the UK aerospace supply chain benefit from increasing aircraft orders.","Biography information for Drew Hendry","Drew Hendry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61612","61612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678764","2017-01-27","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps the Government is taking to build on the UK's strengths in aerospace innovation and manufacturing.","Biography information for Drew Hendry","Drew Hendry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61613","61613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678765","2017-01-27","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that the aerospace sector remains globally competitive.","Biography information for Drew Hendry","Drew Hendry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61693","61693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678766","2017-01-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will support the establishment of local low pay commissions.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61658","61658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678767","2017-01-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps the Government is taking to build on the UK's strengths in aerospace innovation and manufacturing before and after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61583","61583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678768","2017-01-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the contribution of the aerospace industry to economic growth in the (a) South West and (b) UK.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61579","61579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678769","2017-01-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that the aerospace sector remains globally competitive after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61580","61580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678770","2017-01-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that companies in the aerospace supply chain benefit from increasing aircraft orders before and after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61581","61581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678771","2017-01-27","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether his Department plans for the increase in Post Office outreach services in rural communities over the last five years to continue; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61560","61560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678772","2017-01-27","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the effect of late payment by large firms on small businesses and suppliers in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61531","61531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678773","2017-01-27","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent discussions he has had with the Minister for Women and Equalities on encouraging involvement by women in business at all levels.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61787","61787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678774","2017-01-27","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what (a) advice and (b) support his Department provides to people who incurred a financial loss by cancelling travel plans as a result of following government advice in February 2016 to consult a medical professional before travelling to areas where there were Zika outbreaks.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61777","61777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678775","2017-01-27","Department for Education","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to encourage skills development in UK businesses in response to the UK's decision to leave the EU.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61786","61786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678776","2017-01-27","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what progress he has made on establishing the office of the Small Business Commissioner.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61789","61789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678777","2017-01-27","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when he plans to meet energy industry representatives to discuss the cancellation of the carbon capture and storage competition.","Biography information for Dr Andrew Murrison","Dr Andrew Murrison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61793","61793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678778","2017-01-27","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he has taken to maintain the level of investment in research and development in Scotland in response to the UK's decision to leave the EU.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61785","61785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/678779","2017-01-27","HM Treasury","2017-01-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what guidelines there are to insurance companies on considering claims of people who cancelled travel plans as a result of following Government travel advice relating to health concerns in the areas they plan to travel to.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61779","61779"
