"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228478","2015-03-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many start-up loans have been awarded since the introduction of that scheme in (a) Rutherglen and Hamilton West constituency, (b) South Lanarkshire, (c) Scotland and (d) the UK; and what the total value is of those loans.","Biography information for Tom Greatrex","Tom Greatrex","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228490","228490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228479","2015-03-24","Cabinet Office","2015-03-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what proportion of members of Government Boards identify as from Black, Asian or other minority ethnic groups.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228466","228466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228480","2015-03-24","Cabinet Office","2015-03-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what proportion of Government appointments were made to people identified as from Black, Asian or other minority ethnic groups in each year from 2010 to date.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228467","228467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228481","2015-03-23","Cabinet Office","2015-03-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the average hourly pay is of employees at each grade in the Prime Minister's Office identified as (a) White or White British and (b) from a black, Asian or other minority ethnic group.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228301","228301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228482","2015-03-24","Cabinet Office","2015-03-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what progress has been made on introducing the £40 million local sustainability fund for voluntary, community and social enterprise organisations.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228372","228372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228483","2015-03-24","Cabinet Office","2015-03-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the median hourly pay is for all employees in each ethnic group in his Department.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228327","228327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228484","2015-03-23","Cabinet Office","2015-03-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what recent progress he has made on civil contingencies planning.","Biography information for Baroness McIntosh of Pickering","Miss Anne McIntosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228353","228353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228485","2015-03-24","HM Treasury","2015-03-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make it his policy to exempt community groups, charities and other not-for-profit organisations from the requirement to pay VAT on the installation of government-funded high-speed broadband cabinets; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228362","228362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228486","2015-03-24","HM Treasury","2015-03-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the (a) total and (b) staff cost to his Department was of producing the document, An alternative fiscal path beyond 2016-17, published on 19 March 2015.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228370","228370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228487","2015-03-24","HM Treasury","2015-03-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many officials in his Department were involved in producing the document, An alternative fiscal path beyond 2016-17, published on 19 March 2015.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228371","228371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228488","2015-03-24","Department for Transport","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make an estimate of the number of freight containers that will be moved from (a) Felixstowe and (b) Tilbury port by (i) rail and (ii) road in the next two years.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228413","228413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228489","2015-03-24","HM Treasury","2015-03-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the effects of changes in oil prices since August 2014 on the cost of moving freight by (a) rail, (b) road and (c) sea.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228412","228412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228490","2015-03-23","HM Treasury","2015-03-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many VAT-registered property rental companies there were in each year since May 2010.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228302","228302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228491","2015-03-23","HM Treasury","2015-03-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent representations his Department has received on the level of VAT applicable to small tourist businesses.","Biography information for Mr Geoffrey Cox","Mr Geoffrey Cox","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228304","228304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228492","2015-03-23","HM Treasury","2015-03-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the average hourly pay is of employees at each grade within his Department identified as (a) White or White British and (b) from a Black, Asian or other minority ethnic group.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228317","228317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228493","2015-03-24","HM Treasury","2015-03-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether HM Revenue and Customs has made special arrangements with English Premier League clubs about their tax affairs.","Biography information for Mr Mike Hancock","Mr Mike Hancock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228454","228454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228494","2015-03-24","HM Treasury","2015-03-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the number of car wash businesses in the UK; and what estimate he has made of the tax paid by such businesses in the last year.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228455","228455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228495","2015-03-24","HM Treasury","2015-03-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what meetings (a) Ministers and (b) officials in his Department had on alcohol duty with representatives of (i) the Wine and Spirits Trade Association, (ii) the Scotch Whisky Association, (iii) the British Beer and Pub Association, (iv) Diageo, (v) SAB Miller and (vi) the Portman Group between 1 November 2014 and 18 March 2015.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228414","228414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228496","2015-03-24","HM Treasury","2015-03-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much in VAT revenue accrued to the public purse from the Severn Crossings tolls in (a) 2013-14 and (b) 2012-13.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228410","228410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228497","2015-03-24","HM Treasury","2015-03-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much additional revenue accrued to the public purse from the Severn Crossings as a result of the abolition of the Industrial Buildings Allowance in (a) 2013-14, (b) 2012-13 and (c) 2011-12.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228411","228411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228498","2015-03-25","HM Treasury","2015-03-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will publish an (a) environmental impact and (b) environmental sustainability assessment of Budget 2015, HC 1093.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228439","228439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228499","2015-03-24","HM Treasury","2015-03-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what meetings Ministers and officials in his Department had with alcohol companies and their representative organisations on alcohol duty between 1 November 2014 and 18 March 2015.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228429","228429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228500","2015-03-24","HM Treasury","2015-03-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he will provide additional funding to enable Government Digital Service (GDS) to work with local government on digital services; to which bodies that will be allocated; and whether he expects GDS to grow in size.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228497","228497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228501","2015-03-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to paragraph 1.185 of Budget 2015, which bodies he expects to provide co-funding for the Collaboratorium for Research in Infrastructure and Cities; and what steps he is taking to encourage such co-funding.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228495","228495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228502","2015-03-24","HM Treasury","2015-03-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the real terms change in Grant in Aid for the Arts Council (England) will be from 2014-15 to 2015-16 using the Office for Budget Responsibility forecast for the GDP deflator; and when the Arts Council (England) was informed of that change.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228507","228507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228503","2015-03-23","HM Treasury","2015-03-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to paragraphs 1.103, 1.122 and 2.231 of Budget 2015, on the availability of ultrafast broadband, what the Government's definition is of "available to".","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228477","228477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228504","2015-03-24","HM Treasury","2015-03-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to paragraph 1.108 of Budget 2015, whether people will be able to opt out of the digital tax accounts.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228496","228496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228505","2015-03-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the average hourly pay is of employees at each grade within his Department identified as (a) White or White British and (b) from a Black, Asian or other minority ethnic group.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228306","228306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228506","2015-03-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much waste was recycled in (a) Pendle constituency and (b) Lancashire in 2009-10 and each subsequent year.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228349","228349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228507","2015-03-24","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to his Answer of 17 March 2015 to Question 227432, if he will place in the Library a copy of his letter to the Planning Inspectorate of February 2015.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228329","228329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228508","2015-03-24","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he has taken to support internet service providers and ensure they remain a facilitator for the online industry.","Biography information for Mike Weatherley","Mike Weatherley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228399","228399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228509","2015-03-23","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what the average hourly pay is of employees at each grade within his Department identified as (a) White or White British and (b) from a Black, Asian or other minority ethnic group.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228307","228307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228510","2015-03-23","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he is taking to safeguard the future of local newspapers.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228476","228476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228511","2015-03-24","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate he has made of the number of people employed in the (a) acting and (b) singing professions from lower income families in each year since May 2010.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228484","228484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228512","2015-03-24","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what representations his Department has received from internet service providers on safe harbour provisions.","Biography information for Mike Weatherley","Mike Weatherley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228459","228459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228513","2015-03-24","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent representations his Department has received from rights holders on safe harbour provisions.","Biography information for Mike Weatherley","Mike Weatherley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228460","228460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228514","2015-03-24","Ministry of Defence","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent assessment he has made of the progress on recruitment of Army reservists  against his Department's target of 30,000 by 2019.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228492","228492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228515","2015-03-23","Ministry of Defence","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 7 August 2014 to Question 205237, what the cost to the public purse was of running and maintaining each residence formerly referred to as an official service residence provided by his Department to senior figures from the armed forces in 2012-13.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228445","228445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228516","2015-03-24","Ministry of Defence","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much (a) his Department and (b) its executive agencies and associated bodies spent on legal fees in each year since 2010; and if he will publish a detailed breakdown of that expenditure.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228426","228426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228517","2015-03-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the effect of changes in funding to local authorities on their ability to support Armed Forces Community Covenants.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228485","228485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228518","2015-03-23","Ministry of Defence","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the average hourly pay is of employees at each grade within his Department identified as (a) White or White British and (b) from a Black, Asian or other minority ethnic group.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228308","228308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228519","2015-03-23","Ministry of Defence","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether there are official email addresses in his Department which do not accept emails from members of the public.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Turner","Mr Andrew Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228382","228382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228520","2015-03-24","Ministry of Defence","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many people have been made redundant from (a) his Department and (b) its executive agencies and associated bodies in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228355","228355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228521","2015-03-24","Ministry of Defence","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will publish a list of equipment gifted by his Department in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228365","228365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228522","2015-03-24","Ministry of Defence","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the transportation costs were for equipment gifted by his Department in each year since 2010; and what equipment that has been gifted by his Department remains outstanding for delivery.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228366","228366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228523","2015-03-24","Ministry of Defence","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many people have found (a) full-time, (b) part-time and (c) casual employment within six months of leaving service with the help of the Career Transition Partnership in each region and constituent part of the UK since that partnership was established.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228363","228363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228524","2015-03-24","Ministry of Defence","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many people have received assistance from the Career Transition Partnership's (a) employment support and (b) full support programme in each region and constituent part of the UK since that partnership was established.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228364","228364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228525","2015-03-24","Ministry of Defence","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) military and (b) civilian staff in his Department are proficient in (i) Arabic, (ii) Persian, (iii) Turkish, (iv) Berber, (v) Kurdish, (vi) Polish and (vii) Russian.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228367","228367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228526","2015-03-23","Deputy Prime Minister","2015-03-19","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what recent discussions he has had with the (a) First Minister of Scotland and (b) Secretary of State for Scotland on the Government's agenda for constitutional reform; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Baroness McIntosh of Pickering","Miss Anne McIntosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228352","228352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228527","2015-03-23","Department for Education","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 29 January 2015 to Question 221699, on which occasions Ofsted has officially reported to her Department instances where a local authority had not complied with the statutory responsibility of six-week visits for privately fostered children.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228386","228386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228528","2015-03-24","Department for Education","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 12 March 2015 to Question 226581, what support her Department provides to primary schools to ensure that the free school meals offered by those schools are healthy.","Biography information for Nick de Bois","Nick de Bois","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228392","228392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228529","2015-03-23","Department for Education","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 29 January 2015 to Question 221701, how many teenage mothers became pregnant while in residential care in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228387","228387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228530","2015-03-23","Department for Education","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 2 February 2015 to Question 222185, how many times a court has overruled a young person's decision to refuse treatment for substance abuse.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228388","228388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228531","2015-03-23","Department for Education","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 29 January 2015 to Question 221702, whether local authorities have a statutory obligation to notify her Department when a child in their care becomes pregnant.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228389","228389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228532","2015-03-24","Department for Education","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what support her Department provides to teaching professionals affected by work-related stress.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228486","228486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228533","2015-03-24","Department for Education","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of the number of teachers who have taken leave from work because of stress in each year since May 2010.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228487","228487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228534","2015-03-24","Department for Education","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 16 March 2015 to Question 227136, for what reasons the names of schools which applied for but were not allocated funding will not be published until July 2015.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228428","228428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228535","2015-03-24","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the oral Answer of 19 March 2015 from the Minister of State for Energy, when he plans to publish the advice he has received on the effect on security of supply of the potential closure of Longannet.","Biography information for Tom Greatrex","Tom Greatrex","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228508","228508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228536","2015-03-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the average hourly pay is of employees at each grade within his Department identified as (a) White or White British and (b) from a Black, Asian or other minority ethnic group.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228309","228309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228537","2015-03-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the average hourly pay is of employees at each grade within her Department identified as (a) White or White British and (b) from a Black, Asian or other minority ethnic group.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228310","228310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228538","2015-03-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 15 December 2014 to the hon. Member for Washington and Sunderland West to Question 217417, how many of the 215 people paid less than the living wage employed on two major contracts reside in Scotland.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228336","228336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228539","2015-03-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if it is her policy to begin the badger cull scheduled for 2015 in June; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228330","228330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228540","2015-03-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many fires were recorded at regulated and unregulated recycling or waste sites in (a) 2013 and (b) 2014.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228494","228494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228541","2015-03-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, which five recruitment agencies have received the largest amount of money from (a) his Department and (b) associated bodies since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Pat McFadden","Mr Pat McFadden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228379","228379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228542","2015-03-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the Defence Attaché in post in the British Embassy in Ukraine was aware when the Government gave export licence approval in December 2014 for the export of 75 Saxon Armoured Personnel Carriers to Ukraine that they might be armed on their arrival in Ukraine; and what steps were taken by the British Embassy in Ukraine to inform the Government of this possibility.","Biography information for Sir John Stanley","Sir John Stanley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228444","228444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228543","2015-03-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how much has been paid to recruitment agencies by (a) his Department and (b) its executive agencies and associated bodies in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Pat McFadden","Mr Pat McFadden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228440","228440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228544","2015-03-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many times the Minister for Europe has met with (a) the President of the European Commission, (b) Vice Presidents of the European Commission, (c) the High Representative of the Union for Foreign Affairs and Security Policy and (d) European Commissioners since January 2014.","Biography information for Mr Pat McFadden","Mr Pat McFadden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228380","228380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228545","2015-03-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many times he has met with (a) the President of the European Commission, (b) Vice Presidents of the European Commission, (c) the High Representative of the Union for Foreign Affairs and Security Policy and (d) European Commissioners since July 2014.","Biography information for Mr Pat McFadden","Mr Pat McFadden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228381","228381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228546","2015-03-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how much his Department has spent on (a) cancelled and (b) missed transport in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228401","228401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228547","2015-03-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions Ministers in his Department have had with their Israeli counterparts since the Israeli elections on 17 March 2015; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228397","228397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228548","2015-03-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, which five political risk consultancies have received the largest total amount from (a) his Department and (b) his Department's executive agencies and associated bodies since 2010.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228402","228402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228549","2015-03-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how much has been paid to political risk consultancies by (a) his Department and (b) his Department's executive agencies and associated bodies in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228403","228403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228550","2015-03-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what he plans to discuss at his first meeting with his Human Rights Advisory Group in the week commencing 23 March 2015.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228447","228447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228551","2015-03-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many staff from his Department have been seconded to external organisations in each year since 2010; to which external organisations and for how long such staff were seconded; and what the cost to his Department was of such secondments.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228356","228356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228552","2015-03-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his Burmese counterpart on allowing international observers to monitor a future national ceasefire agreement; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228359","228359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228553","2015-03-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what support his Department is providing to the UN for ongoing negotiations between political parties in Yemen.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228346","228346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228554","2015-03-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what contact his Department has with President Hadi of Yemen in his new residence in Aden.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228347","228347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228555","2015-03-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the average hourly pay is of employees at each grade within his Department identified as (a) White or White British and (b) from a Black, Asian or other minority ethnic group.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228311","228311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228556","2015-03-23","Department of Health","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average hourly pay is of employees at each grade within his Department identified as (a) White or White British and (b) from a Black, Asian or other minority ethnic group.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228312","228312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228557","2015-03-23","Department of Health","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many family members looking after a relative at home were registered as carers with Pendle Borough Council in (a) April 2010 and (b) each subsequent April.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228332","228332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228558","2015-03-23","Department of Health","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what representations the Joint Committee on Vaccination and Immunisation has received on the efficacy of vaccinating adolescent boys against human papillomavirus and the timetable for reaching a decision on the matter.","Biography information for Mr John Baron","Mr John Baron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228303","228303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228559","2015-03-24","Department of Health","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent representations he has had from his counterpart in (a) Spain, (b) Italy, (c) the Philippines, (d) Italy and (e) the Republic of Ireland on the number of nurses from those countries being recruited to work in the NHS.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228396","228396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228560","2015-03-23","Department of Health","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of cancer patients received (a) intensity modulated and (b) stereotactic radiotherapy in the last month for which figures are available.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228390","228390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228561","2015-03-23","Department of Health","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many falls (a) at home and (b) in total were recorded by health and social care providers in Pendle constituency in 2010 and each subsequent year.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228348","228348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228562","2015-03-23","Department of Health","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what NHS spending per head of population in East Lancashire has been in each of the last two years.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228384","228384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228563","2015-03-24","Department of Health","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of nurses registered with the Nursing and Midwifery Council in each of the last five years were from overseas.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228394","228394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228564","2015-03-23","Department of Health","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, on how many occasions since he has taken office he has spoken to Health Trust Chief Executives on (a) A&E performance, (b) referral to treatment times, (c) delayed discharges, (d) bed availability and occupancy and (e) ambulance response times.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228391","228391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228565","2015-03-24","Department of Health","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 5 February 2015 to the hon. Member for Pudsey to Question 222863, by what date he plans for the negotiations about the supply of meningococcal B vaccine to be concluded.","Biography information for Julie Hilling","Julie Hilling","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228326","228326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228566","2015-03-24","Department of Health","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the longest wait was on 19 March 2015 for a patient awaiting NHS treatment.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228337","228337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228567","2015-03-24","Department of Health","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to his Answer of 17 March 2015 to Question 227433, for what reasons NICE has scheduled development of the clinical guidelines to begin in 2016 and not earlier; and if he will take steps to expedite that process.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228328","228328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228568","2015-03-24","Department of Health","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress his Department has made in working with the Royal British Legion to assess how the disregard for payments under the War Pensions Scheme may be applied under the adult social care charging rules in future; and when he plans for that work to be concluded.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228331","228331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228569","2015-03-24","Department of Health","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much his Department has spent on interior decoration since May 2010.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228318","228318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228570","2015-03-24","Department of Health","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of nurses registered with the Nursing and Midwifery Council were from overseas in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228319","228319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228571","2015-03-24","Department of Health","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the change in prescription charges has been in real terms in each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228320","228320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228572","2015-03-24","Department of Health","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of patients attending A&E departments arrive by car.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228321","228321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228573","2015-03-24","Department of Health","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the financial position of the NHS trust and foundation trust sector at the end of the current financial year; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228322","228322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228574","2015-03-24","Department of Health","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the progress update to recommendation 97 in the supporting annex to his Department's report, Culture change in the NHS, published in February 2015, which responsibilities of NHS England his Department is considering transferring to a single national body.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228417","228417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228575","2015-03-24","Department of Health","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many and what proportion of GP surgeries in England offer extended opening hours.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228418","228418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228576","2015-03-24","Department of Health","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of cancer patients in England have received radiotherapy treatment in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228419","228419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228577","2015-03-24","Department of Health","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) child and (b) adult patients with a diagnosis of psychiatric conditions waited longer that four hours in A&E to be seen in (i) each month in 2015 to date and (ii) each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228434","228434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228578","2015-03-24","Department of Health","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the effect on NHS patient services of income accrued by foundation trusts from private patients.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228416","228416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228579","2015-03-24","Department of Health","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when his Department plans to publish the remaining stages of the Keogh Review into hospital mortality rates.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228404","228404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228580","2015-03-24","Department of Health","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of safeguarding concerns responded to by the Care Quality Commission were responded to within the target time frame in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Liz Kendall","Liz Kendall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228405","228405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228581","2015-03-24","Department of Health","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many finished hospital admission episodes with a primary diagnosis of chronic obstructive pulmonary disease there were in each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Liz Kendall","Liz Kendall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228406","228406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228582","2015-03-24","Department of Health","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether NHS England will remain the sole budget-holder for prescribed specialised services in 2016-17.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228424","228424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228583","2015-03-24","Department of Health","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions he has had with the senior national clinical lead for mental health to coordinate education, training and workforce development.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228435","228435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228584","2015-03-24","Department of Health","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much of the funding allocated to clinical commissioning group's for expanding the Improving Access to Psychological Therapies programme has been spent on that programme.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228436","228436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228585","2015-03-24","Department of Health","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many NHS patients in England with chronic obstructive pulmonary disease were subject to a delayed transfer of care from an acute care setting in each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Liz Kendall","Liz Kendall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228407","228407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228586","2015-03-24","Department of Health","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the spending per in-patient in England on NHS meals was per (a) hospital stay and (b) day in each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Liz Kendall","Liz Kendall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228408","228408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228587","2015-03-23","Department of Health","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether it is his policy that local authorities should be required to provide appropriate support where it is identified through an official safeguarding inquiry that further support is needed to protect a person from the risk of abuse or neglect.","Biography information for Mr Tom Clarke","Mr Tom Clarke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228441","228441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228588","2015-03-23","Department of Health","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to encourage the provision of dental treatment in domiciliary settings.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228442","228442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228589","2015-03-24","Department of Health","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the cost to the economy of alcohol-related harm in the last year.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228427","228427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228590","2015-03-24","Department of Health","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to paragraph 4.6 of the Government's mandate to Health Education England: April 2014 to March 2015, when the e-learning package to support continuing professional development in mental health went live.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228438","228438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228591","2015-03-24","Department of Health","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people have had a stroke or a transient ischemic attack in each clinical commissioning group area since April 2012.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228493","228493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228592","2015-03-24","Department of Health","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people attended at hospital A&E departments in the Blackpool NHS Trust area in each year from 2010 to 2015.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228509","228509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228593","2015-03-23","Department of Health","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many non-admitted patients had been waiting for over (a) 18, (b) 26 and (c) 52 weeks for treatment in each NHS and NHS foundation trust in each month since May 2010.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228478","228478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228594","2015-03-24","Department of Health","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients in the Blackpool NHS Trust had to wait longer than 48 hours for a GP appointment in (a) 2010 and (b) 2015.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228511","228511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228595","2015-03-23","Department of Health","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, in respect of how many patients referral to treatment pathways were recorded as incomplete in each NHS and NHS foundation trust in each month since May 2010.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228479","228479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228596","2015-03-23","Department of Health","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many admitted patients waited over (a) 18, (b) 26 and (c) 52 weeks for treatment in each NHS and NHS foundation trust since May 2010.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228480","228480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228597","2015-03-24","Department of Health","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people in Blackpool NHS Trust area had to wait longer than 62 days to start cancer treatment after being referred by their GP in (a) 2010 and (b) 2015.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228512","228512"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228598","2015-03-24","Department of Health","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) GPs and (b) nurses were employed in the Blackpool NHS Trust in (i) 2010 and (ii) 2015.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228510","228510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228599","2015-03-24","Department of Health","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the Government has announced that the Cancer Drugs Fund will continue beyond April 2016.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228500","228500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228600","2015-03-24","Department of Health","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress the Government is making in implementing the recommendations in his Department's Innovative Medicines Review.","Biography information for Neil Parish","Neil Parish","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228482","228482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228601","2015-03-23","Department of Health","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which NHS trusts have failed to meet their referral to treatment targets since May 2010; and in what months each such failure occurred.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228481","228481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228602","2015-03-24","Department of Health","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people were on the waiting list for NHS treatment in Blackpool NHS Trust area on (a) 1 March 2015 and (b) 1 March 2010.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228513","228513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228603","2015-03-24","Department of Health","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans the Government has to publish a new dementia strategy.","Biography information for Neil Parish","Neil Parish","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228483","228483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228605","2015-03-23","Home Office","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have (a) applied and (b) successfully resettled in the UK under the Vulnerable Persons Relocation Scheme (i) in total and (ii) in each month since September 2014.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228475","228475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228606","2015-03-24","Home Office","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many full-time equivalent Border Force staff worked on implementing the Government's Tackling Tobacco Smuggling strategy in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228437","228437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228607","2015-03-23","Home Office","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will take steps to ensure that people held in immigration removal centres have access to the websites of organisations that provide advice and support services for those people.","Biography information for Sarah Teather","Sarah Teather","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228448","228448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228608","2015-03-23","Home Office","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many incidents of anti-Muslim hate crime were reported to the police in (a) Pendle and (b) Lancashire in (i) 2010, (ii) 2011, (iii) 2012, (iv) 2013 and (v) 2014.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228335","228335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228609","2015-03-24","Home Office","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, for what reasons Terence McCormick and Patrick Maguire have not been extradited from the US to face questioning in relation to the murder of Captain Robert Nairac.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228358","228358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228610","2015-03-23","Home Office","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department sets targets for reductions in rural crime; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Baroness McIntosh of Pickering","Miss Anne McIntosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228350","228350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228611","2015-03-23","Home Office","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment she has made of the performance of the Passport Office against its performance targets for new passport applications.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228339","228339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228612","2015-03-23","Home Office","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average length of time taken by the Passport Office to make a decision on renewal of an expired passport was in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228340","228340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228613","2015-03-23","Home Office","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average length of time taken by the Passport Office to make a decision on a new passport application was in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228341","228341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228614","2015-03-23","Home Office","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many staff were employed by her Department to process passport applications of any kind in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228342","228342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228615","2015-03-24","Home Office","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much each police force in the North West charged to each football club in their area for policing of football matches in 2014; and how much of those charges are currently outstanding.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228373","228373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228616","2015-03-23","Home Office","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to ensure that women are informed about all of their specific rights and entitlements within the asylum process.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228305","228305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228617","2015-03-23","Home Office","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average hourly pay is of employees at each grade within her Department identified as (a) White or White British and (b) from a Black, Asian or other minority ethnic group.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228313","228313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228618","2015-03-24","House of Commons Commission","2015-03-19","To ask the hon. Member for Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross representing the House of Commons Commission, pursuant to the Answer of 18 March 2015 to Question 227500, what consideration was given to putting the contract for the supply of tablets for hon. Members out to competitive tender; and what the minimum value is for contracts that must be put out to competitive tender.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228502","228502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228619","2015-03-24","House of Commons Commission","2015-03-19","To ask the hon. Member for Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross representing the House of Commons Commission, pursuant to the Answer of 18 March 2015 to Question 227498, to which budget the mobile charges for hon. Members' iPads fall; what plans the Commission has to offer hon. Members a platform other than iOS; and what provision PICT is making for hon. Members who do not wish to use iPads.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228501","228501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228620","2015-03-24","Department for International Development","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department (a) has taken and (b) plans to take in respect of (i) funding the Plant for Peace pomegranate cultivation programme in Afghanistan and (ii) supporting Afghan nationals to take up educational opportunities in the UK; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Julian Lewis","Dr Julian Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228515","228515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228621","2015-03-24","Department for International Development","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, which 10 consultancies have received the largest amount from herDepartment since 2010; and how much her Department paid each such consultancy.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228468","228468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228622","2015-03-24","Department for International Development","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much funding her Department has lost as a result of the financial collapse of (a) an NGO, (b) a financial lender and (c) other institutions in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228433","228433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228623","2015-03-24","Department for International Development","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, which countries her Department has supported to train, recruit and retain health workers since May 2010.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228395","228395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228624","2015-03-24","Department for International Development","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much has been paid to consultancies for (a) programme delivery and (b) monitoring and evaluation by her Department in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228430","228430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228625","2015-03-24","Department for International Development","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much funding from her Department is currently held by Microking in Zimbabwe; and what steps her Department is taking to recover those funds.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228431","228431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228626","2015-03-24","Department for International Development","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much funding her Department has allocated to Microking in Zimbabwe in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228432","228432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228627","2015-03-23","Department for International Development","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what the average hourly pay is of employees at each grade within her Department identified as (a) White or White British and (b) from a Black, Asian or other minority ethnic group.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228314","228314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228628","2015-03-23","Department for International Development","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, with reference to the demolition by Israeli authorities in October 2014 of a latrine unit, constructed using funding from her Department, in Khashem ad Daraj in the occupied Palestinian territory, what estimate she has made of the cost of replacing that unit.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228343","228343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228629","2015-03-23","Department for International Development","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, with reference to the demolition by Israeli authorities in October 2014 of a latrine unit, constructed using funding from her Department, in Khashem ad Daraj in the occupied Palestinian territory, what discussions she has had with her Israeli counterparts on the reasons for that demolition.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228344","228344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228630","2015-03-23","Department for International Development","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, with reference to the demolition by Israeli authorities in October 2014 of a latrine unit, constructed using funding from her Department, in Khashem ad Daraj in the occupied Palestinian territory, what the cost of that construction project was.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228345","228345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228631","2015-03-24","Department for International Development","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what proportion of funding to the Thailand Burma Border Consortium was provided by her Department in each of the last five years; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228360","228360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228632","2015-03-24","Department for International Development","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what funding her Department provided to support refugees from Burma living in refugee camps in Thailand in each of the last five years; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228361","228361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228633","2015-03-23","Department for International Development","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, with reference to the demolition by Israeli authorities in October 2014 of a latrine unit, constructed using funding from her Department, in Khashem ad Daraj in the occupied Palestinian territory, whether compensation has been requested from the Israeli authorities.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228338","228338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228634","2015-03-23","Ministry of Justice","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, on how many occasions appeals involving adverse possession have been brought in the last six months.","Biography information for Baroness McIntosh of Pickering","Miss Anne McIntosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228354","228354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228635","2015-03-24","Ministry of Justice","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been convicted of cruelty to persons under 16 under the provisions of Section 1(1) of the Children and Young Persons Act 1933 at each magistrates' and Crown court in the North West in 2014.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228375","228375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228636","2015-03-24","Ministry of Justice","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been convicted under the provisions of section (a) 444(1) and (b) 444(1A) of the Education Act 1966 each magistrates' and Crown court in the North West in 2014.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228376","228376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228637","2015-03-23","Ministry of Justice","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average hourly pay is of employees at each grade within his Department identified as (a) White or White British and (b) from a Black, Asian or other minority ethnic group.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228315","228315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228638","2015-03-23","Ministry of Justice","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment his Department has made of (a) changes in the length of prison sentences received by paedophiles since 2010 and (b) the reasons for such changes.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228446","228446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228639","2015-03-24","Ministry of Justice","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when the first drug scanner will be installed in a prison in England or Wales.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228456","228456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228640","2015-03-24","Ministry of Justice","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much is being spent on drug scanners for jails in England and Wales.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228457","228457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228641","2015-03-24","Ministry of Justice","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many drug scanners are being purchased for jails in England and Wales.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228458","228458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228642","2015-03-23","Northern Ireland Office","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what the average hourly pay is of employees at each grade within her Department identified as (a) White or White British and (b) from a Black, Asian or other minority ethnic group.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228316","228316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228643","2015-03-24","Prime Minister","2015-03-19","To ask the Prime Minister, if, during the discussions of the effect on UK micro-businesses of EU digital VAT legislation since its implementation on 1 January 2015 at the March 2015 European Council meeting in Brussels, he will negotiate for a derogation for micro-businesses; if he will publish details of changes that he plans to call for in those discussions; if he will report to the House before the Dissolution of Parliament on the outcome of those discussions; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228461","228461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228644","2015-03-23","Scotland Office","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what the average hourly pay is for employees at each grade within his Department identified as (a) White or White British and (b) from a Black, Asian or other minority ethnic group.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228449","228449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228645","2015-03-24","Department for Transport","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much the Severn Bridges cost to run and maintain in (a) 2013-14 and (b) 2012-13.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228409","228409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228646","2015-03-24","Department for Transport","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make an assessment of the potential effect of anticipated levels of rail freight activity at (a) Felixstowe and (b) Tilbury port in the next year will have on (i) rail and (ii) dock workers at those ports.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228415","228415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228647","2015-03-23","Department for Transport","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the average hourly pay is for employees at each grade within his Department identified as (a) White or White British and (b) from a Black, Asian or other minority ethnic group.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228450","228450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228648","2015-03-24","Department for Transport","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many passengers have been compensated for the recent disruption to rail services at London Bridge; and what the average such payment has been.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228503","228503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228649","2015-03-24","Department for Transport","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will review compensation for passengers affected by the recent disruption to rail services at London Bridge.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228504","228504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228650","2015-03-23","Department for Transport","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when his Department plans to announce its decision on the route of Phase Two of High Speed 2 between Birmingham, Manchester, Sheffield and Leeds.","Biography information for Mr Dominic Grieve","Mr Dominic Grieve","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228471","228471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228651","2015-03-24","Department for Transport","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, for how long he expects the disruption to rail services at London Bridge to continue.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228505","228505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228652","2015-03-23","Department for Transport","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the cost to the public purse was of the Exceptional Hardship Scheme from its inception to its replacement by the Need to Sell scheme.","Biography information for Mr Dominic Grieve","Mr Dominic Grieve","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228472","228472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228653","2015-03-24","Department for Transport","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he next plans to meet (a) Network Rail and (b) Southern Railway to discuss the recent disruption to rail services at London Bridge station.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228506","228506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228654","2015-03-23","Department for Transport","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make an estimate of the costs of operating a discretionary compensation scheme along the planned High Speed 2 Phase One route in the period to one year after the opening of Phase One.","Biography information for Mr Dominic Grieve","Mr Dominic Grieve","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228473","228473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228655","2015-03-23","Department for Transport","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent estimate his Department has made of the cost of maintaining the High Speed 2 network over the 60 year appraisal period set out in his Department's publication, The Economic Case for HS2.","Biography information for Mr Dominic Grieve","Mr Dominic Grieve","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228470","228470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228656","2015-03-23","Department for Transport","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent estimate his Department has made of the cost of construction of the proposed tunnel for High Speed 2 from Old Oak Common to Euston.","Biography information for Mr Dominic Grieve","Mr Dominic Grieve","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228474","228474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228657","2015-03-23","Department for Transport","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he has taken to reduce traffic congestion in Lancashire since 2010.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228333","228333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228658","2015-03-23","Department for Transport","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he has taken to improve transport links between Pendle constituency and (a) Manchester and (b) London since 2010.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228334","228334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228659","2015-03-23","Department for Transport","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much has been spent on cycling improvements in Pendle constituency in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228383","228383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228660","2015-03-23","Department for Transport","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many (a) accidents and (b) fatal accidents involving cyclists there have been in Pendle in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228368","228368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228661","2015-03-25","Department for Transport","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will take steps to instruct Network Rail to resolve the land ownership issues at Honeybourne railway station.","Biography information for Sir Peter Luff","Sir Peter Luff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228378","228378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228662","2015-03-23","Wales Office","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what the average hourly pay is for employees at each grade within his Department identified as (a) White or White British and (b) from a Black, Asian or other minority ethnic group.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228451","228451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228663","2015-03-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average hourly pay is for employees at each grade within his Department identified as (a) White or White British and (b) from a Black, Asian or other minority ethnic group.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228452","228452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228664","2015-03-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many Child Support Agency (CSA) cases have been closed as part of the phased three-year CSA case closure programme.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228463","228463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228665","2015-03-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many Child Support Agency cases are being dealt with by the legal enforcement section of that Agency.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228464","228464"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228666","2015-03-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many calls the Child Maintenance Options Service has received in each month from September 2014 to date.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228465","228465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228667","2015-03-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the support by Work Programme providers for participants seeking to become self-employed.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228453","228453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228668","2015-03-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many six months' notice warning letters of case closure have been sent to Child Support Agency customers in each month since December 2014.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228425","228425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228669","2015-03-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 18 March 2015 to Question 227137, how many applications have been made by police forces to his Department for information on the addresses of wanted persons in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228443","228443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228670","2015-03-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many reminder letters giving one month's warning of case closure have been sent to Child Support Agency customers in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228462","228462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228671","2015-03-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 11 March 2015 to Question 226586, whether his Department's review of complex cases where claimants died has identified cases in which his Department's processes were not followed; and for each such case what recommendations for improvement have been made.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228498","228498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228672","2015-03-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 12 March 2015 to Question 226706, whether the peer reviews that his Department's (a) processes had been followed and (b) actions were either inappropriate or incorrect; what recommendations for improvement have been made; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228499","228499"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228673","2015-03-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the change has been in the amount of (a) employment and support allowance and (b) other incapacity benefit paid in each month since May 2013.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228514","228514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228674","2015-03-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in Halton constituency waited more than (a) one month, (b) three and (c) six months for a decision on their personal independence payment claim in the last three years.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228491","228491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228675","2015-03-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when was the last time a Minister in his Department visited Scotland.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228385","228385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228676","2015-03-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the cost of the Access to Work scheme in (a) Airdrie and Shotts constituency, (b) North Lanarkshire, (c) Scotland and (d) the UK has been in each month since May 2010.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228369","228369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228677","2015-03-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans he has to introduce text or email notifications for claimants of the employment and support allowance required to attend a medical assessment.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228377","228377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228678","2015-03-24","HM Treasury","2015-03-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people have been contacted by (a) Sigma, (b) Rossendales and (c) other debt collection agencies instructed by HM Revenue and Customs to collect overpaid tax credits in Preston constituency in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228374","228374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228679","2015-03-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent estimate he has made of the average time between a claim being made for employment and support allowance and the claimant receiving a work capability assessment.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228323","228323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228680","2015-03-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will place in the Library a copy of the service level agreement with Maximus relating to work capability assessments; what penalties exist under that agreement for a failure to adhere to the terms of the agreement; and what requirements exist under that agreement for the clearance of the backlog of existing cases.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228324","228324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229457","2015-03-25","Cabinet Office","2015-03-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps he is taking to support youth services.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 908320","908320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229458","2015-03-25","Cabinet Office","2015-03-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps he is taking to support youth services.","Biography information for Julie Hilling","Julie Hilling","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 908317","908317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229459","2015-03-25","Cabinet Office","2015-03-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what plans he has to achieve savings through the work of his Efficiency and Reform Group.","Biography information for Andrew Bridgen","Andrew Bridgen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 908318","908318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229460","2015-03-25","Cabinet Office","2015-03-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of mutuals in the public sector.","Biography information for Richard Graham","Richard Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 908321","908321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229461","2015-03-25","Cabinet Office","2015-03-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many (a) organisations in total and (b) trade unions receive income by means of a government check-off facility.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 908316","908316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229462","2015-03-25","Cabinet Office","2015-03-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps he is taking to support youth services.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 908319","908319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229463","2015-03-25","Cabinet Office","2015-03-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what his policy is on the deduction of trade union subscriptions from payroll in the Civil Service.","Biography information for Graeme Morrice","Graeme Morrice","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 908315","908315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228063","2015-03-20","Attorney General","2015-03-18","To ask the Attorney General, how many dedicated staff there are to deal with domestic violence cases at each Crown Prosecution Service office in the North West.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228086","228086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228064","2015-03-20","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the contribution of the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills of 25 November 2014, Official Report, column 257WH, what progress he has made on reviewing proposals to amend the Furniture and Furnishing (Fire) (Safety) Regulations 1988.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228089","228089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228065","2015-03-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent steps he has taken to encourage asset owners to do more to engage with investee companies as part of their stewardship duties.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228100","228100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228066","2015-03-20","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many technology businesses were supported by the UK Trade & Investment Global Entrepreneur Programme to relocate to the UK in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228056","228056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228067","2015-03-20","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much his Department has invested in start-up accelerators and incubators in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228057","228057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228068","2015-03-20","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department is taking to address the adult skills gap in Pendle and East Lancashire.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228059","228059"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228069","2015-03-20","Cabinet Office","2015-03-18","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what proportion of the workforce was paid no more than the minimum wage in (a) Huddersfield, (b) Kirklees, (c) Yorkshire, (d) London, (e) England and (f) the UK in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228092","228092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228070","2015-03-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what non-apprenticeship adult skills budget was allocated for Leeds City College in 2014-15; and what such allocation he plans to make in 2015-16.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228113","228113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228071","2015-03-20","Cabinet Office","2015-03-18","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what proportion of the workforce was paid at least the living wage in (a) Huddersfield, (b) Kirklees, (c) Yorkshire, (d) London, (e) England and (f) the UK in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228157","228157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228072","2015-03-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will bring forward legislative proposals for regulating the sale of ouija boards.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228164","228164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228073","2015-03-20","Cabinet Office","2015-03-18","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many new business start-ups by women there were in Pendle constituency in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228174","228174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228074","2015-03-23","HM Treasury","2015-03-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he plans to take in relation to the future operation of the Wrexham tax office.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228099","228099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228075","2015-03-23","HM Treasury","2015-03-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he had discussions with the Welsh Government on the future of the Wrexham tax office; and what matters were discussed on those occasions.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228103","228103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228076","2015-03-23","HM Treasury","2015-03-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions have taken place with staff at the Wrexham tax office on the future of that office.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228104","228104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228077","2015-03-23","HM Treasury","2015-03-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he plans to take in relation to the future operation of the Cardiff tax office.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228093","228093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228078","2015-03-23","HM Treasury","2015-03-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many sales of property worth £1,000,000 or more there were in (a) the UK, (b) Scotland, (c) England, (d) Wales and (e) Northern Ireland in each of the last five years for which records are available.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228065","228065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228079","2015-03-23","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what timetable he has set for introducing the new horse race betting right; what assessment he has made of the potential benefits that betting right will bring to York Racecourse; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Sir Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228262","228262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228080","2015-03-23","HM Treasury","2015-03-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what representations he has received about issuing notices of fines without declarations of VAT by private parking companies; and what enforcement action he is taking against companies that fail to comply with the law in that way.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228269","228269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228081","2015-03-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 18 March 2015 to Question 227530, if he will make an assessment of the potential effect on the planning system of the decision by McDonald's to move from business to residential areas; and whether he plans to offer guidance to local authorities on taking decisions on applications for planning permission arising from that decision in this matter.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228277","228277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228082","2015-03-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of spending on adult social care in (a) Portsmouth and (b) Southampton local authority areas in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr John Denham","Mr John Denham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228169","228169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228083","2015-03-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to allow City of York Council to join the West Yorkshire Combined Authority; whether the new city deal announced in the Budget for the West Yorkshire Combined Authority will apply also to City of York Council; when City of York Council first notified his Department of its wish to join the West Yorkshire Combined Authority; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Sir Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228261","228261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228084","2015-03-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to his Department's announcement, Government delivers on parking promises to help local shops, published on 6 March 2015, if he will take further steps to ensure that local authority parking schemes are more advantageous to motorists.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228091","228091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228085","2015-03-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will take steps to ensure that the Better Care Fund helps councils provide services faster and with improved value for money.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228088","228088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228086","2015-03-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment his Department has made of the local economic benefits arising from the small business rate relief scheme.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228090","228090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228087","2015-03-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department has taken to explore the use of flat-pack housing as a means of tackling housing shortages.","Biography information for Annette Brooke","Annette Brooke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228031","228031"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228088","2015-03-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of flat-pack housing as a solution to housing shortages in rural areas.","Biography information for Annette Brooke","Annette Brooke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228032","228032"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228089","2015-03-20","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many Ofcom decisions were subject to (a) successful and (b) unsuccessful on the merits appeals in each year for which data is available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228051","228051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228090","2015-03-20","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, which Ofcom decisions have been subject to the most appeals in each year since 2003.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228048","228048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228091","2015-03-20","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, on how many occasions each communication provider has asked for an on the merit review of an Ofcom decision in each year for which data is available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228052","228052"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228092","2015-03-20","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department is taking to introduce arrangements for broadband and landline providers gaining a customer to lead the switching process.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228049","228049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228093","2015-03-20","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what information his Department holds on the number of customers who switched between mobile phone providers in each year for which data is available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228050","228050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228094","2015-03-20","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate his Department has made of the number of (a) residential and (b) commercial properties that will be in complete mobile not-spots in the period 2015 to 2018.","Biography information for Baroness McIntosh of Pickering","Miss Anne McIntosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228152","228152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228095","2015-03-20","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate his Department has made of the proportion of the (a) major road network and (b) rail network that will be in complete not-spots in the period 2015 to 2018.","Biography information for Baroness McIntosh of Pickering","Miss Anne McIntosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228153","228153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228096","2015-03-20","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent discussions his Department has had with mobile network operators on complete not-spots in Great Britain not covered by the agreement announced on 18 December 2014.","Biography information for Baroness McIntosh of Pickering","Miss Anne McIntosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228154","228154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228097","2015-03-20","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions his Department has had with mobile network operators on complete not-spots where sites are not eligible for Mobile Infrastructure Project funding.","Biography information for Baroness McIntosh of Pickering","Miss Anne McIntosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228155","228155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228098","2015-03-20","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment his Department has made of the roll-out of 4G to areas of Great Britain that are complete or partial not-spots since the agreement with the mobile network operators announced on 18 December 2014.","Biography information for Baroness McIntosh of Pickering","Miss Anne McIntosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228156","228156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228099","2015-03-23","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assistance he plans to provide through tax support to (a) local newspapers in general, (b) the York Press, Yorkshire Post and Northern Echo and (c) other local newspapers; what his timetable is for introducing such support; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Sir Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228263","228263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228100","2015-03-20","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he is taking to increase the availability of fibre-optic broadband to businesses in (a) Pendle constituency, (b) Lancashire and (c) the North West.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228173","228173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228101","2015-03-23","Ministry of Defence","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many and what proportion of staff in (a) his Department and (b) its executive agencies and associated bodies are former members of the armed forces.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228117","228117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228102","2015-03-23","Ministry of Defence","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many and what proportion of staff in (a) his Department and (b) its executive agencies and associated bodies are members of the armed forces.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228118","228118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228103","2015-03-23","Ministry of Defence","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the contribution of the Minister of State for Defence of 9 March 2015, Official Report, column 47, on Armed Forces (Service Complaints and Financial Assistance) Bill, whether his Department has reached a decision on whether to transfer the outstanding unresolved complaints within the existing service complaints system to the remit of the new Service Complaints Ombudsman.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228134","228134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228104","2015-03-23","Ministry of Defence","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much LIBOR funding to date has been awarded to organisations or projects that benefit from the wider armed forces community (a) nationwide, (b) in England, (c) in Northern Ireland, (d) in Scotland and (e) in Wales.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228139","228139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228105","2015-03-23","Ministry of Defence","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many reserves have been called up for service since the Strategic Defence and Security Review 2010; where those reserves have served; and in what capacity those reserves served.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228141","228141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228106","2015-03-23","Ministry of Defence","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the annual targets are for recruitment to the Joint Cyber Reserve.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228142","228142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228107","2015-03-20","Ministry of Defence","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much the (a) withdrawal from Afghanistan and (b) environmental clean-up in Afghanistan has cost to date; and how much has been spent on each element of each cost.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228110","228110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228108","2015-03-23","Ministry of Defence","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many people in (a) England, (b) Northern Ireland, (c) Scotland and (d) Wales (i) have benefited and (ii) are expected to benefit from the LIBOR funding for armed forces and veterans' organisations that has been granted in each tranche to date.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228140","228140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228109","2015-03-23","Ministry of Defence","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what frontline Royal Navy ships are currently in refit.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228027","228027"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228110","2015-03-23","Ministry of Defence","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what Royal Navy ships are currently in extended readiness; and when those ships will be available for service.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228028","228028"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228111","2015-03-23","Ministry of Defence","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will list the Order of Battle of the Commando Brigade.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228029","228029"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228112","2015-03-23","Ministry of Defence","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what Royal Navy ships are currently available for operational service.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228030","228030"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228113","2015-03-23","Ministry of Defence","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what proportion of vehicles and equipment earmarked for return from Afghanistan (a) have been returned, (b) have been processed, (c) remain in transit and (d) remain in Afghanistan.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228069","228069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228114","2015-03-23","Ministry of Defence","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many locally-employed Afghan interpreters who worked alongside the British Army have (a) applied for relocation to the UK and (b) been resettled in the UK under his Department's resettlement package to date.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228070","228070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228115","2015-03-23","Ministry of Defence","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the potential need for an increase to the budget of the Office of the Service Complaints Ombudsman arising from (a) changes to the powers of the Ombudsman as a result of the Armed Forces (Service Complaints and Financial Assistance) Bill and (b) the inclusion of issues of delay in the remit of the Ombudsman.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228071","228071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228116","2015-03-26","Ministry of Defence","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what progress he has made on the sale of the Government pipeline and storage systems.","Biography information for Mark Garnier","Mark Garnier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228038","228038"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228117","2015-03-26","Ministry of Defence","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what contribution the UK plans to make to international efforts to train and equip Syrian moderate opposition forces.","Biography information for Mark Garnier","Mark Garnier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228039","228039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228118","2015-03-26","Ministry of Defence","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans he has to introduce a post-nominal decoration for long service in the Reserve Forces.","Biography information for Mr Marcus Jones","Mr Marcus Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228040","228040"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228119","2015-03-23","Deputy Prime Minister","2015-03-18","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what remit Tech North will have to work with existing business infrastructure in the North.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228287","228287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228120","2015-03-23","Deputy Prime Minister","2015-03-18","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, when he plans to publish the business plan for Tech North.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228278","228278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228121","2015-03-23","Department for Education","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many state-funded schools in each local authority area as at 31 August 2010 had received a three or four judgement for pupil behaviour in their most recent Ofsted inspection.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228270","228270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228122","2015-03-23","Department for Education","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many state-funded schools in each local authority area are currently assessed by Ofsted to be inadequate or require improvement had been assessed to be good or outstanding at their previous inspection.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228271","228271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228123","2015-03-23","Department for Education","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she has taken in (a) primary and (b) secondary schools to reduce the incidence of suicide.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228146","228146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228124","2015-03-23","Department for Education","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many new (a) academies, (b) free schools, (c) university technical colleges and (d) new school sixth forms that are entitled to VAT reimbursements have been created in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228137","228137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228125","2015-03-20","Department for Education","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 9 March 2015 to Question 226295, what assessment her Department has made of the appropriateness of decisions taken by individual awarding organisations on the future of particular A levels; and what guidance she provided to those organisations on that issue.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228127","228127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228126","2015-03-23","Department for Education","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 3 March 2015 to Question 225406, what estimate she has made of the value of the VAT reimbursed to new (a) academies, (b) free schools and (c) university technical colleges created since 2010.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228136","228136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228127","2015-03-23","Department for Education","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the maximum number of cases in a supervisor's name is that can be allocated to a newly qualified children's social worker.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228107","228107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228128","2015-03-23","Department for Education","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what funding was provided to each local authority in 2014 to remove asbestos in schools.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228116","228116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228129","2015-03-23","Department for Education","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions her Department has had with the awarding organisations on the number of people needed to mark A Level examinations in summer 2015; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228131","228131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228130","2015-03-20","Department for Education","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much of the money disbursed from the budget of her Department's Children's Social Care Innovation Programme has been allocated to organisations in the (a) public, (b) private and (c) voluntary sectors in (i) 2013-14 and (ii) 2014-15 to date.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228124","228124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228131","2015-03-20","Department for Education","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much of the money disbursed from the budget for her Department's Children's Social Care Innovation Programme has been allocated to (a) practice and (b) evaluation of practice funded by that Programme in (i) 2013-14 and (ii) 2014-15 to date.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228122","228122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228132","2015-03-20","Department for Education","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much has been disbursed from the budget for her Department's Children's Social Care Innovation Programme in (a) 2013-14 and (b) 2014-15 to date.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228123","228123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228133","2015-03-23","Department for Education","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the maximum number of cases in a supervisor's name is that may be allocated to a participant in the Frontline programme without a local authority incurring a financial penalty.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228095","228095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228134","2015-03-20","Department for Education","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many free child care places there were in Lancashire in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228061","228061"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228135","2015-03-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps have been taken to monitor current levels of air pollution from Central and Eastern Europe in the South and East of England.","Biography information for Lord Blunkett","Mr David Blunkett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228094","228094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228136","2015-03-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment his Department has made of the effectiveness of Display Energy Certificates in reducing the energy costs and improving the energy efficiency of public buildings.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228112","228112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228137","2015-03-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent representations she has received on difficulties in registering land on the Rural Payments Agency system for connection with basic form payments; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Baroness McIntosh of Pickering","Miss Anne McIntosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228163","228163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228138","2015-03-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the implications for her policy on self-regulation of the animal establishment licensing industry of the performance of (a) the City of London Corporation and Ornamental Aquatic Trade Association partnership in being the first primary authority scheme to include an inspection plan to cover animal establishments and to be a co-ordinated partnership and (b) other similar recent schemes; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Tracey Crouch","Tracey Crouch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228026","228026"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228139","2015-03-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to reduce the incidence of trichomoniasis in pigeons.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228015","228015"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228140","2015-03-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to (a) reduce accidental deaths on farms and (b) improve safety in the vicinity of slurry pits.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228016","228016"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228141","2015-03-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment the Government has made of Shaker Aamer's continued detention in Guantanamo in light of the Government's on going celebration of Magna Carta.","Biography information for John Pugh","John Pugh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228019","228019"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228142","2015-03-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the implications of the recent crackdown on protesting students in Burma for the credibility of Burma's reform process; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228033","228033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228143","2015-03-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to his Colombian counterpart to request that the Colombian government investigates and ensures appropriate action against the perpetrators of death threats towards (a) Senator Ivan Cepeda, (b) members of the organisation CPDH and (c) David Florez.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228102","228102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228144","2015-03-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of levels of political freedoms in eastern Sudan.","Biography information for Mark Durkan","Mark Durkan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228078","228078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228145","2015-03-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make further representations to the Colombian government on the security of (a) Senator Ivan Cepeda, (b) members of the organisation CPDH and (c) David Florez.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228101","228101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228146","2015-03-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the Government has taken a position on the viability of forthcoming elections in Sudan; and what discussions he has had with his Sudanese counterpart on ensuring that conditions are met for those elections to be free and fair.","Biography information for Mark Durkan","Mark Durkan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228073","228073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228147","2015-03-20","Department for International Development","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assistance the UK has provided to Vanuatu in dealing with the aftermath of the recent cyclone.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228012","228012"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228148","2015-03-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department has taken to implement the recommendations of the report Rape as torture in the DRC, published by Freedom from Torture in June 2014.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228161","228161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228149","2015-03-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to help the Gambian government to improve that country's human rights record.","Biography information for Richard Harrington","Richard Harrington","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228171","228171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228150","2015-03-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the Houthi rebellion in Yemen on stability in the Middle East.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228175","228175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228151","2015-03-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the operational capability of Al Qaeda in Yemen.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228176","228176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228152","2015-03-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when the Government first became aware that Philip Blackwood, who is in custody in Burma, is a British citizen.","Biography information for Mr David Ward","Mr David Ward","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228111","228111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228153","2015-03-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many official meetings representatives of the UK have attended in the run-up to the UN Framework Convention on Climate Change conference in late 2015; and who those representatives are.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228274","228274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228154","2015-03-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how much (a) his Department and (b) its executive agencies and associated bodies has spent on legal fees in each year since 2010; and if he will publish a detailed breakdown of that expenditure.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228276","228276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228155","2015-03-23","Department of Health","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Deputy Prime Minister's press release of 18 March 2015, on children's mental health services, what the access and waiting time standards will be; when such standards will be introduced; and if he will estimate current performance against such standards.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228266","228266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228156","2015-03-23","Department of Health","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect of the Headsmart Campaign in raising awareness of child brain tumours; and what steps he is taking to ensure that, after diagnosis of such tumours, (a) children and (b) adults receive the support they need for emotional and mental wellbeing.","Biography information for Tracey Crouch","Tracey Crouch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228285","228285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228157","2015-03-23","Department of Health","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many of the local authorities that have signed up to the Crisis Care Concordat have produced an action plan for the implementation of the provisions of that concordat.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228265","228265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228158","2015-03-23","Department of Health","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he has taken to ensure that family carers for dementia patients receive the training they need to care appropriately for them.","Biography information for Tracey Crouch","Tracey Crouch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228284","228284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228159","2015-03-23","Department of Health","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients spent 12 hours from the decision to admit to admission in A&E in (a) 2013, (b) 2014 and (c) 2015.","Biography information for Andy Burnham","Andy Burnham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228283","228283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228160","2015-03-23","Department of Health","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his plans are for future funding of drugs for those with rare and less common cancers.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228135","228135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228161","2015-03-23","Department of Health","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to his Department's recent report, Culture change in the NHS, Cm 9009, whether he plans to place responsibility for patient safety alerts within (a) NHS England or (b) an arms-length organisation.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228119","228119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228162","2015-03-23","Department of Health","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether it is his policy that specialised commissioning hubs will be able to deviate from national standards in their commissioning of specialised care.","Biography information for Stephen Gilbert","Stephen Gilbert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228108","228108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228163","2015-03-23","Department of Health","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information his Department holds on income earned from parking charges in each hospital in Lancashire in (a) 2011, (b) 2012, (c) 2013 and (d) 2014.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228114","228114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228164","2015-03-23","Department of Health","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 27 November 2014 to Question 215787, whether NHS England plans to publish the independent review of the adequacy of capacity planning and execution of delivery plans for A&E service changes that have taken place across north west London.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228106","228106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228165","2015-03-20","Department of Health","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the real terms budget of NHS Protect was in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228128","228128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228166","2015-03-20","Department of Health","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the average annual cost to the NHS of overpayments to suppliers caused by fraud or error.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228129","228129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228167","2015-03-20","Department of Health","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps are being taken to improve adult outreach services from King's College Hospital to the South East Coast region.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228130","228130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228168","2015-03-20","Department of Health","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many NHS beds per 100,000 people were provided for mental health patients in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228125","228125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228169","2015-03-20","Department of Health","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans Barts and the London NHS Trust has for neuromuscular care co-ordinator support to meet the neurosciences: specialised neurology (adult) service specification.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228126","228126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228170","2015-03-23","Department of Health","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions he has had with the British Medical Association and the Royal Colleges on the implications for the NHS of links between obesity and cancer; and what steps he is taking to reduce the incidence of obesity-related cancer.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228143","228143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228171","2015-03-20","Department of Health","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what funding there has been from the public purse for research into treatment of (a) Crohn's disease and (b) ulcerative colitis in the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228177","228177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228172","2015-03-23","Department of Health","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the table in Paragraph 123 of the Impact Assessment to the Government's 2011 Cancer Strategy, whether the projected increase in staff numbers required to deliver that strategy by 2014-15 was achieved for (a) radiographers, (b) consultant radiologists, (c) ultrasonographers, (d) technicians and (e) endoscopists.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228259","228259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228173","2015-03-23","Department of Health","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average cost to the NHS was of a (a) hip replacement, (b) knee replacement, (c) cataract operation and (d) hernia operation in England in 2014.","Biography information for Andy Burnham","Andy Burnham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228279","228279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228174","2015-03-23","Department of Health","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 17 March 2015 to Question 227480, what campaigns were funded from the social marketing budget; and how much was allocated to each such campaign.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228260","228260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228175","2015-03-23","Department of Health","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make an assessment of the effect of recent social care budget changes on people with dementia.","Biography information for Andy Burnham","Andy Burnham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228280","228280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228176","2015-03-23","Department of Health","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much NHS trusts have spent on agency and contract staff in (a) each year since 2009-10 and (b) 2014-15 to date; and how much NHS trusts plans to so spend in 2015-16.","Biography information for Andy Burnham","Andy Burnham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228281","228281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228177","2015-03-23","Department of Health","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many NHS and foundation trusts expect to be in deficit at the end of the 2014-15 financial year; and whether he expects the NHS trust sector as a whole to be in deficit at the end of that year.","Biography information for Andy Burnham","Andy Burnham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228282","228282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228178","2015-03-23","Department of Health","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if NHS England will publish specialised commissioning policies for the 2015-16 financial year alongside the response to the Investing in Specialised Commissioning - Public Consultation; and when that response will be published.","Biography information for Mr Stewart Jackson","Mr Stewart Jackson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228170","228170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228179","2015-03-23","Department of Health","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the annual cost of fraud in the NHS.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228168","228168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228180","2015-03-23","Department of Health","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 16 March 2015 to Question 227363, when he expects the system-wide solutions to address the financial problems within the local health economy to be announced; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228162","228162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228181","2015-03-20","Department of Health","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of the ability of patients with inflammatory bowel disease (IBD) to access (a) a specialist IBD nurse, (b) specialist dietetic support and (c) defined psychological support.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228148","228148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228182","2015-03-20","Department of Health","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information his Department holds on the number of incidents in which a pregnant mother was told that her baby was dead but it subsequently proved to be alive in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228013","228013"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228183","2015-03-20","Department of Health","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he expects the NHS to introduce titanium splints to stabilise rib fractures.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228014","228014"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228184","2015-03-23","Department of Health","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he expects his Department's planned mental health app to be available across the NHS.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228010","228010"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228185","2015-03-20","Department of Health","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with the Royal Colleges and the British Medical Association about possible links between use of the contraceptive pill and Crohn's disease.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228011","228011"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228186","2015-03-23","Department of Health","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the (a) mean and (b) median time to (i) assessment, (ii) treatment and (iii) departure was in (A) type one and (B) all A&E departments in (1) each quarter of 2013-14 and (2) 2014-15 to date.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228066","228066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228187","2015-03-23","Department of Health","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many NHS trusts and foundation trusts have had action taken against them for not implementing guidance from patient safety alerts since May 2010; and what action was taken in each such case.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228067","228067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228188","2015-03-23","Department of Health","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans (a) his Department, (b) NHS England and (c) the Care Quality Commission have to ensure that patient safety alert guidance is implemented; and how his Department plans to monitor compliance with that guidance.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228068","228068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228189","2015-03-20","Department of Health","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many doctors were employed by (a) Lancashire Teaching Hospitals and (b) Lancashire Care NHS Foundation Trust in (i) 2010, (ii) 2011, (iii) 2012, (iv) 2013 and (v) 2014.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228083","228083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228190","2015-03-20","Department of Health","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many nurses were employed by (a) Lancashire Teaching Hospitals and (b) Lancashire Care NHS Foundation Trust in (i) 2010, (ii) 2011, (iii) 2012, (iv) 2013 and (v) 2014.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228084","228084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228191","2015-03-20","Department of Health","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many midwives were employed by (a) Lancashire Teaching Hospitals and (b) Lancashire Care NHS Foundation Trust in (i) 2010, (ii) 2011, (iii) 2012, (iv) 2013 and (v) 2014.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228085","228085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228192","2015-03-23","Department of Health","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many staff are paid (a) above and (b) below the living wage by (i) Lancashire Teaching Hospitals NHS Foundation Trust and (ii) Lancashire Care NHS Foundation Trust.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228105","228105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228193","2015-03-23","Department of Health","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what support is available to help people who lack capacity and who fund their own care, to set up and manage their contributions to their carers' workplace pensions.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228096","228096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228194","2015-03-20","Department of Health","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with University Hospitals of Leicester Trust on steps to ensure that patients with complex respiratory issues have access to specialist physiotherapy.","Biography information for Lord Garnier","Sir Edward Garnier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228079","228079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228195","2015-03-23","Department of Health","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what support is available to help people who fund their own care to enrol qualifying carers into a workplace pension.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228097","228097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228196","2015-03-20","Department of Health","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department and NHS England are taking to accelerate the access of hepatitis C patient to interferon-free medicines; and what estimate he has made of the number of patients who will commence treatment with such medicines in 2015.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228063","228063"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228197","2015-03-20","Department of Health","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will discuss with Nottingham University Hospital Trust steps to ensure that patients have access to specialist physiotherapy.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228064","228064"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228198","2015-03-20","Department of Health","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of Community First Responders supporting ambulance responses in (a) England, (b) the North West and (c) East Lancashire.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228058","228058"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228199","2015-03-20","Department of Health","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with the Royal Colleges and the British Medical Association about steps to reduce excessive usage of aspirin leading to internal bleeding or strokes.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228017","228017"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228200","2015-03-20","Department of Health","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of people in each age group who have suffered from chronic fatigue syndrome in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228018","228018"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228201","2015-03-20","Department of Health","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which properties in the NHS estate his Department has identified as being surplus to requirements.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228047","228047"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228202","2015-03-20","Department of Health","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the cost has been of implementing the Health and Social Care Act 2012.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228045","228045"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228203","2015-03-20","Department of Health","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much his Department and each of its non-departmental public bodies has spent on vacant properties since May 2010.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228046","228046"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228204","2015-03-20","Home Office","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many dedicated staff there were at each rank dealing with domestic violence at each police station in Lancashire in (a) 2013, (b) 2014 and (c) 2015.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228087","228087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228205","2015-03-20","Cabinet Office","2015-03-18","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many incidents of shoplifting and theft from shops were reported to police in (a) Preston constituency, (b) Lancashire and (c) the North West in (i) 2010, (ii) 2011, (iii) 2012, (iv) 2013 and (v) 2014.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228082","228082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228206","2015-03-20","Home Office","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department has taken to implement the recommendations in the report, Rape as torture in the DRC, published by Freedom from Torture in June 2014.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228160","228160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228207","2015-03-23","Home Office","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what funding her Department provided in police pension top-up grants to each police force in England and Wales in each year since 2006-07.","Biography information for Mr Stewart Jackson","Mr Stewart Jackson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228167","228167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228208","2015-03-23","Home Office","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many full-time police officers have been in the employ of Merseyside Police in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Mrs Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228138","228138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228209","2015-03-23","Home Office","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what account her Department took of the effects of and reasons for the removal of embarkation procedures in 1996 when making the decision to re-establish such procedures in the current Parliament.","Biography information for Lord Blunkett","Mr David Blunkett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228120","228120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228210","2015-03-23","Home Office","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what expenditure UK Border Force has incurred in operating x-ray scanners to tackle tobacco smuggling in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228272","228272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228211","2015-03-23","Home Office","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the cost to the public purse was of the salaries of officials working in the Border Force employed in tackling tobacco smuggling in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228273","228273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228212","2015-03-23","Home Office","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have been (a) referred to the UK's Vulnerable Persons Relocation scheme by the UN High Commissioner for Refugees and (b) successfully resettled in the UK under the Vulnerable Persons Relocation scheme in each year since 2013.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228275","228275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228213","2015-03-20","Department for International Development","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department has taken to implement the recommendations in the report, Rape as torture in the DRC, published by Freedom from Torture in June 2014.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228159","228159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228214","2015-03-20","Department for International Development","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent assessment she has made of humanitarian conditions in eastern Sudan.","Biography information for Mark Durkan","Mark Durkan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228072","228072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228215","2015-03-20","Department for International Development","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to support the Nigerian general elections on 28 March 2015.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228060","228060"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228216","2015-03-20","Ministry of Justice","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of women in prison have been victims of (a) domestic violence and (b) sexual abuse.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228055","228055"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228217","2015-03-20","Ministry of Justice","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department plans to take to assist local contractors in the tendering process for work at HM Prison Wrexham.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228121","228121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228218","2015-03-20","Ministry of Justice","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners there were in HM Prison Preston in (a) 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012, (d) 2013 and (e) 2014.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228080","228080"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228219","2015-03-25","Ministry of Justice","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the letter sent on 2 February 2015 to the hon. Member for Birmingham, Yardley by HM Courts and Tribunals Service's Performance, Analysis and Reporting Team, what the (a) name of the judge, (b) date, (c) period of committal and (d) court was of each court order issued by courts in Leeds for contempt of court since November 2014.","Biography information for John Hemming","John Hemming","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228034","228034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228220","2015-03-25","Ministry of Justice","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the letter sent on 2 February 2015 to the hon. Member for Birmingham, Yardley by HM Courts and Tribunals Service's Performance, Analysis and Reporting Team, what the (a) name of the judge, (b) date, (c) period of committal and (d) court was of each court order issued by courts in Manchester for contempt of court since November 2014.","Biography information for John Hemming","John Hemming","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228035","228035"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228221","2015-03-25","Ministry of Justice","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the letter sent on 2 February 2015 to the hon. Member for Birmingham, Yardley by HM Courts and Tribunals Service's Performance, Analysis and Reporting Team, what the (a) name of the judge, (b) date, (c) period of committal and (d) court was of each court order issued by courts in Sheffield for contempt of court since November 2014.","Biography information for John Hemming","John Hemming","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228036","228036"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228222","2015-03-25","Ministry of Justice","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the letter sent on 2 February 2015 to the hon. Member for Birmingham, Yardley by HM Courts and Tribunals Service's Performance, Analysis and Reporting Team, what the (a) name of the judge, (b) date, (c) period of committal and (d) court was of each court order issued by courts in Bristol for contempt of court since November 2014.","Biography information for John Hemming","John Hemming","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228037","228037"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228223","2015-03-23","Ministry of Justice","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many complaints relating to data protection breaches were upheld by the Information Commissioner in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228165","228165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228224","2015-03-20","Home Office","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the effectiveness of powers under the Immigration Act 2014 to stop criminals using family life arguments to delay deportation.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228149","228149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228225","2015-03-20","Ministry of Justice","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what best practice his Department has learnt from leading the EU-funded Serious Offending by Mobile European Criminals project.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228150","228150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228226","2015-03-20","Ministry of Justice","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what guidance his Department publishes on assisting young and vulnerable victims and witnesses to give evidence in court.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228151","228151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228227","2015-03-23","Ministry of Justice","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many assaults by prisoners on other prisoners there were in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228144","228144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228228","2015-03-23","Ministry of Justice","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many assaults by prisoners on prison officers there were in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228145","228145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228229","2015-03-20","Ministry of Justice","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect of GPS tagging on the efficacy of monitoring of offenders released on probation.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228158","228158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228230","2015-03-23","Department for Transport","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answers of 12 March 2015 to Questions 226857 and 226812, which 33 stations were nominated for Access to All funding; and which 25 stations were selected for that funding.","Biography information for Gordon Banks","Gordon Banks","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228109","228109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228231","2015-03-23","Department for Transport","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the value is per capita for people living in (a) London and (b) Yorkshire and the Humber of his Department's capital investment in (i) roads, (ii) railways, (iii) airports and (iv) all transport infrastructure between 2010-11 and 2014-15.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Sir Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228264","228264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228232","2015-03-23","Department for Transport","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions his Department has had with officials from the Health and Safety Executive regarding worker exposure to diesel fumes at railway stations.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228021","228021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228233","2015-03-20","Department for Transport","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the number of jobs his Department supports (a) directly and (b) indirectly in the supply chain in (i) the North West, (ii) Lancashire and (iii) Preston constituency.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228081","228081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228234","2015-03-20","Department for Transport","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the reason is for the changes planned to High Level Output Statement resource DEL expenditure classified under Other Railways in 2015-16.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228020","228020"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228235","2015-03-20","Wales Office","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how much his Department spent on (a) television advertising, (b) radio advertising, (c) national newspaper advertisements, (d) local newspaper advertisements, (e) social media advertising and (f) other types of advertising in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228062","228062"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228236","2015-03-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to help reduce the health problems caused by exposure to diesel fumes at work.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228022","228022"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228237","2015-03-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what guidance his Department has produced on the prevention of health problems caused by exposure to solar radiation at work.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228023","228023"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228238","2015-03-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the cost to the UK economy of carcinogen exposure at work.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228024","228024"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228239","2015-03-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average duration is to date spent claiming jobseeker's allowance by people who have returned to Jobcentre Plus after being on the Work Programme for two years.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228025","228025"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228240","2015-03-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many disabled people have entered employment following participation in the Work Programme in (a) Pendle, (b) Lancashire and (c) the North West to date.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228041","228041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228241","2015-03-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of people in Pendle who do not have a bank account.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228042","228042"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228242","2015-03-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make an assessment of the progress and effectiveness of the Disability Confident campaign in Lancashire.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228043","228043"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228243","2015-03-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effect of the benefit cap on rates of employment in (a) Pendle, (b) Lancashire and (c) the North West.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228044","228044"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228244","2015-03-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people have found employment through (a) the Work Programme, (b) the Youth Contract and (c) an apprenticeship in Pendle in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228053","228053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228245","2015-03-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people have been assessed by the Work Programme in (a) Pendle, (b) Lancashire and (c) the North West to date.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228054","228054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228246","2015-03-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will direct Jobcentre-plus districts to address the geographical variations in the distribution of jobseeker's allowance sanctions as set out in the report by Crisis entitled Benefit sanctions and homelessness: a scoping report, published March 2015.","Biography information for Dame Joan Ruddock","Dame Joan Ruddock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228286","228286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228247","2015-03-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of recipients of employment and support allowance referred to the Work Programme in (a) Blackpool South constituency and (b) Blackpool local authority area moved into sustained employment in (i) 2012, (ii) 2013, (iii) 2014 and (iv) 2015.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228267","228267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228248","2015-03-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many jobseeker's allowance (JSA) sanctions there were per 100 JSA claimants in each London borough in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Dame Joan Ruddock","Dame Joan Ruddock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228288","228288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228249","2015-03-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of people appealed against a work capability assessment decision in (a) Blackpool South constituency and (b) Blackpool local authority area since the introduction of such assessments; and how many and what proportion of those appeals were successful.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228268","228268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228250","2015-03-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make it his policy that trustees of defined benefit pension schemes are required to have a policy on stewardship.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228098","228098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228251","2015-03-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what arrangements have been made to train Jobcentre staff to deal with the needs of claimants who have left the armed forces.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228115","228115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228252","2015-03-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make it his policy, in respect of past interim maintenance assessments, that only that proportion of resultant child maintenance arrears  which is deemed to be collectable will be transferred to the Child Maintenance Service.","Biography information for Dame Anne Begg","Dame Anne Begg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228147","228147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228253","2015-03-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many Jobcentre Plus staff were put on a performance improvement plan as a result of making (a) too few and (b) too many sanction referrals in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228132","228132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228254","2015-03-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much has been claimed in (a) short-term benefit advances and (b) hardship payments in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228133","228133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228255","2015-03-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent discussions he has had with the Health and Safety Executive on worker exposure to diesel fumes during roadworks.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228166","228166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228256","2015-03-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many applications have been made for (a) short-term benefit advances and (b) hardship payments in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228172","228172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228257","2015-03-20","Attorney General","2015-03-18","To ask the Attorney General, whether there is a point of contact for members of the public who wish to help the Serious Fraud Office investigation into GlaxoSmithKline.","Biography information for Eric Ollerenshaw","Eric Ollerenshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228186","228186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228258","2015-03-24","Ministry of Justice","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent representations his Department has received from rights holders on safe harbour provisions.","Biography information for Mike Weatherley","Mike Weatherley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228199","228199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228259","2015-03-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to the Government's response to the First Joint Report of the Committees on Arms Export Controls, Cm 935, published in October 2014, what progress has been made on the review of the Memorandum of Understanding (MoU) between Clarion Events and the Export Control Organisation; and if he will publish the (a) findings of that review and (b) revised MoU.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228210","228210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228260","2015-03-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 12 March 2015 to Question 226805, where in the weblinks provided the information requested can be found on how much the Government has made available in adult skills funding in (a) York Central constituency, (b) City of York Council and (c) all areas using York College in 2015-16; how much such funding was made available in each of the last six years (i) in cash terms and (ii) at current prices; and if he will place in the Library a table showing that information.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Sir Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228227","228227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228261","2015-03-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether he plans to increase the resources and staffing available to the Employment Agency Standards Inspectorate; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228233","228233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228262","2015-03-20","Cabinet Office","2015-03-18","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many new business start-ups there have been in (a) Pendle constituency, (b) Lancashire and (c) the North West since May 2010.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228217","228217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228263","2015-03-23","Cabinet Office","2015-03-18","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what instructions and guidance his Department has given to other Government departments on the destruction of paper and electronic records potentially relevant to the Independent Panel inquiry into Child Sexual Abuse; and whether that guidance is in line with the provisions of the Inquiries Act 2005 on the production of evidence.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228193","228193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228264","2015-03-20","HM Treasury","2015-03-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make a response to the 38 Degrees petition calling for active Government support for community energy co-operatives.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228195","228195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228265","2015-03-20","HM Treasury","2015-03-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, for what reasons the Financial Conduct Authority does not use the definition agreed by the International Labour Organisation of a co-operative society.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228196","228196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228266","2015-03-20","HM Treasury","2015-03-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will extend eligibility for the Enterprise Industrial Scheme by two years to all co-operative energy suppliers.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228197","228197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228267","2015-03-23","HM Treasury","2015-03-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions Ministers in his Department had with the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Public Health on alcohol duty prior to the publication of the Budget 2015; what issues were raised during those discussions; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228208","228208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228268","2015-03-20","HM Treasury","2015-03-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will take steps to clarify when measures in the Autumn Statement 2014 which relate to the tax treatment of UK community energy co-operatives will take effect.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228198","228198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228269","2015-03-20","HM Treasury","2015-03-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people in Pendle constituency had their income tax reduced as a result of personal allowance increases since May 2010.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228200","228200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228270","2015-03-20","HM Treasury","2015-03-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, by what date does he plan to grant the Green Investment Bank powers to borrow from the private capital markets.","Biography information for Joan Walley","Joan Walley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228182","228182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228271","2015-03-23","HM Treasury","2015-03-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with whom he consulted prior to making proposals on the future of HM Revenue and Customs offices in Wales as part of the Building our Future programme.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228187","228187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228272","2015-03-20","HM Treasury","2015-03-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 9 March 2015 to Question 225717, if he will request that the Prudential Regulation Authority and the Financial Conduct Authority report on their performance in relation to sustainable growth in their annual reports.","Biography information for Joan Walley","Joan Walley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228181","228181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228273","2015-03-23","HM Treasury","2015-03-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect on UK micro businesses of EU digital VAT legislation since its implementation on 1 January 2015; what discussions he has had with such businesses on the effect of that legislation; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228209","228209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228274","2015-03-23","HM Treasury","2015-03-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether parking notices (a) constitute taxable supply and (b) are subject to VAT.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228248","228248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228275","2015-03-23","HM Treasury","2015-03-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 2 February 2015 to Question 221881, whether he expects to publish the Action Plan on Modern Slavery before the Dissolution of Parliament.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228290","228290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228276","2015-03-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans his Department has to review the ability of pensions schemes to indirectly invest in companies linked with the manufacture of cluster munitions.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228249","228249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228277","2015-03-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent representations he has received from the pensions industry on investment in companies linked with the manufacture of cluster munitions.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228250","228250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228278","2015-03-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to ban the indirect investment by pension schemes in companies linked with the manufacture of cluster munitions; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228251","228251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228279","2015-03-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will produce guidance to pensions schemes to assist those schemes in avoiding investment in companies linked with the manufacture of cluster munitions.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228252","228252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228280","2015-03-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of current legislation for preventing the indirect involvement of pensions schemes in companies linked with the manufacture of cluster munitions.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228253","228253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228281","2015-03-23","HM Treasury","2015-03-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to paragraph 1.164 of Budget 2014, what estimate he has made of the number of people who have taken their pension pots as a lump sum as a result of the decision to increase the small pot limit from £2,000 to £10,000 and the number of pensions that can be taken as small pot lump sums from two to three.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228298","228298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228282","2015-03-23","HM Treasury","2015-03-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to paragraph 2.57 of Budget 2014, what estimate he has made of the number of people who have cashed in their pension pots in a lump sum as a result of the decision to increase the upper limit for trivial commutation from £18,000 to £30,000.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228299","228299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228283","2015-03-23","HM Treasury","2015-03-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to paragraph 2.54 of Budget 2014, what estimate he has made of the number of people who have accessed flexible drawdown as a result of the decision to reduce the guaranteed income requirement from £20,000 to £12,000.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228300","228300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228284","2015-03-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 28 January 2015 to Question 221886, how many cases of forced labour have been found by local authorities during pro-active inspection of houses of multiple occupation in the last five years; and what training his Department provides to officials in local authorities on (a) the indicators of forced labour and (b) working with victims of trauma.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228292","228292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228285","2015-03-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 28 January 2015 to Question 221886, when he expects the updated guidance to local authorities on dealing with rogue landlords to be published.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228291","228291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228286","2015-03-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the number of small firms and shops likely to be affected by the planned reduction in business rates in (a) Pendle constituency and (b) Lancashire in 2015-16.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228218","228218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228287","2015-03-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what level of net migration was assumed in his Department's 2012-based household projections for England.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228201","228201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228288","2015-03-23","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether the £600 million announced in Budget 2015 to support the delivery of the change of use of 700Mhz spectrum includes provision to assist and compensate users of existing equipment in the programme making and special events sector.","Biography information for Sir Peter Luff","Sir Peter Luff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228235","228235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228289","2015-03-23","Ministry of Defence","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many military personnel, dependents and civilian staff from his Department are based in Germany.","Biography information for Gemma Doyle","Gemma Doyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228236","228236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228290","2015-03-20","Ministry of Defence","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many companies received financial payments when reserve employees were called up for duty in each year since 2013; and what the total amount was of such payments.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228226","228226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228291","2015-03-20","Ministry of Defence","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many NHS staff have joined the reserves in each service in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228225","228225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228292","2015-03-23","Ministry of Defence","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much has been paid to recruitment agencies by (a) his Department and (b) its executive agencies and associated bodies in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Gemma Doyle","Gemma Doyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228190","228190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228293","2015-03-23","Ministry of Defence","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which five recruitment agencies have received the largest total amount of money from (a) his Department and (b) its executive agencies and associated bodies since 2010.","Biography information for Gemma Doyle","Gemma Doyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228191","228191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228294","2015-03-23","Ministry of Defence","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much has been spent on the planned withdrawal from Germany under the Army Basing Plan to date; and what progress has been made on that withdrawal to date.","Biography information for Gemma Doyle","Gemma Doyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228192","228192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228295","2015-03-23","Ministry of Defence","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many people were recruited to the regular army, navy and air force between 1 January 2015 and 15 March 2015; and what the targets were for such recruitment in each such category.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228296","228296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228296","2015-03-23","Ministry of Defence","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many former regular soldiers joined the Army Reserve in each year since 2010; and how much has been paid to such individuals as an incentive to join the Reserve.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228297","228297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228297","2015-03-20","Deputy Prime Minister","2015-03-18","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, when he intends to reply to the letter to him of 21 October 2014 from the hon. Member for Oxford East, reference TF/TAYL01013/01131611.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228179","228179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228298","2015-03-20","Department for Education","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, by what date she plans for schools to be sent sample assessment materials for the new GCSE mathematics examination; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Joan Walley","Joan Walley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228183","228183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228299","2015-03-23","Department for Education","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many participants in the Troops to Teachers programme have (a) not completed training and (b) dropped out on completion of training.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228293","228293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228300","2015-03-23","Department for Education","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many (a) women and (b) BAME people there are in previous cohorts of the Troops to Teachers programme; and what proportion of people in each such category formed the overall participants.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228294","228294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228301","2015-03-23","Department for Education","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the average number of months was that recruits in previous cohorts served in the Troops to Teachers programme.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228295","228295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228302","2015-03-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the (a) scope and (b) findings were of research commissioned by his Department into unintended consequences of energy efficiency refurbishments; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228189","228189"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228303","2015-03-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to leaders in South Sudan on the recent abduction of children from a school in Malakal.","Biography information for Mr Gordon Brown","Mr Gordon Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228185","228185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228304","2015-03-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many staff in his Department have been seconded to which other Government departments, for what time periods and at what cost to his Department in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Nick Smith","Nick Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228207","228207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228305","2015-03-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the total cost was of the GREAT campaign launch in Shanghai; what the cost was of each element of that launch; and if he will publish a list of attendees at that launch.","Biography information for Nick Smith","Nick Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228206","228206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228306","2015-03-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the (a) total cost and (b) cost per area of expenditure was of the GREAT campaign launch in Los Angeles in February 2015; and who the attendees were at that launch.","Biography information for Nick Smith","Nick Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228204","228204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228307","2015-03-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what proportion of staff in each British (a) Embassy, (b) High Commission and (c) Consulate is classified as locally-engaged.","Biography information for Nick Smith","Nick Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228205","228205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228308","2015-03-23","Department of Health","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the contribution of the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Health of 31 October 2012, Official Report, column 93WH, what his Department's definition of viability is for the gestational time limit for abortion.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228203","228203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228309","2015-03-23","Department of Health","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what account his Department took of the findings of the Care Quality Commission on services provided by Care UK when reaching its decision to award a new NHS contract to that company; and what steps he plans to take to ensure the high quality of services provided by that company.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228213","228213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228310","2015-03-23","Department of Health","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether it is his policy that his Department should not take into account private healthcare companies' previous track records when deciding on whether to allow those companies new NHS contracts.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228214","228214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228311","2015-03-20","Department of Health","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to meet the psychological needs of those with (a) inflammatory bowel disease and (b) other long-term health conditions.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228180","228180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228312","2015-03-20","Department of Health","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidance his Department issues to providers and commissioners on the NICE Quality Standard on inflammatory bowel disease.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228178","228178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228313","2015-03-20","Department of Health","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many non-NHS providers have registered with the Care Quality Commission in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228223","228223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228314","2015-03-20","Department of Health","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many new licences Monitor has granted to a non-NHS provider in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228222","228222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228315","2015-03-20","Department of Health","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the Joint Committee on Vaccination and Immunisation is subject to the general equality duty under the Equality Act 2010.","Biography information for Mr John Baron","Mr John Baron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228219","228219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228316","2015-03-20","Department of Health","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many staffing reviews of NHS foundation trusts Monitor has undertaken in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228220","228220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228317","2015-03-20","Department of Health","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of the cost savings from reductions in NHS management since 2010 have been part of his Department's QIPP savings programme.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228221","228221"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228318","2015-03-23","Department of Health","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many NHS trusts have (a) responded to the request from NHS England and Monitor to choose between the Enhanced Tariff Option and the Default Tariff Rollover for 2015-16 and (b) reserved the right to challenge those new tariff arrangements.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228202","228202"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228319","2015-03-24","Department of Health","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the five neuroscience tertiary centres in the north west of England have committed to funding a neuromuscular clinical network for the region.","Biography information for Julie Hilling","Julie Hilling","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228215","228215"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228320","2015-03-24","Department of Health","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps NHS England has taken to meet the Neurosciences: Specialised Neurology (Adult) service specification in Lancashire and Southern Cumbria for providing neuromuscular care co-ordinator support to adults and outreach clinics in that region.","Biography information for Julie Hilling","Julie Hilling","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228216","228216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228321","2015-03-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what information his Department holds on research into possible links between chronic obstructive pulmonary disease and employment in heavy industry.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228245","228245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228322","2015-03-23","Department of Health","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information his Department holds on the prevalence of chronic obstructive pulmonary disease in (a) Wansbeck constituency, (b) Northumberland, (c) the North East and (d) nationally.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228246","228246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228323","2015-03-20","Home Office","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 14 January 2015 to Question 220089, what assessment her Department has made of the UK's compliance with the provisions of the Protocol of 2014 to the Forced Labour Convention; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228224","228224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228324","2015-03-23","Home Office","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she plans to expand the size of the immigration detention estate.","Biography information for Sarah Teather","Sarah Teather","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228234","228234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228325","2015-03-23","Home Office","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 14 January 2015 to Question 220089, whether the UK plans to ratify the Protocol of 2014 to the Forced Labour Convention before the Dissolution of Parliament.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228289","228289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228326","2015-03-23","Department for International Development","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many experts on the protection of (a) women and (b) children in conflict her Department currently employs.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228232","228232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228327","2015-03-23","Department for International Development","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many people who have completed a placement under the International Citizen Service are (a) female and (b) BAME.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228229","228229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228328","2015-03-23","Department for International Development","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many people have (a) applied for and (b) completed a placement under the International Citizen Service in each year since 2012.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228228","228228"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228329","2015-03-23","Department for International Development","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much her Department has spent on advertising for the International Citizen Service in each year since 2012.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228230","228230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228330","2015-03-23","Department for International Development","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what proportion of the funding allocated by her Department to alleviate  humanitarian disasters in each year since 2013 (a) remains held by multilateral organisations and (b) is yet to be disbursed.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228231","228231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228331","2015-03-20","Ministry of Justice","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people were convicted of theft in (a) Preston constituency, (b) Lancashire and (c) the North West in (i) 2010, (ii) 2011, (iii) 2012, (iv) 2013 and (v) 2014.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228184","228184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228332","2015-03-20","Ministry of Justice","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will publish the number of licence recalls activated during the (a) licence and (b) supervision period for the Community Rehabilitation Company service in Birmingham, Yardley constituency.","Biography information for John Hemming","John Hemming","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228194","228194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228333","2015-03-23","Ministry of Justice","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many times the victims' surcharge has been (a) imposed, (b) collected, (c) cancelled and (d) outstanding for people receiving a (i) conditional discharge, (ii) fine, (iii) suspended sentence, (iv) community sentence and (v) custodial sentence in each financial year since 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228212","228212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228334","2015-03-23","Ministry of Justice","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the value was of the victims' surcharge (a) imposed, (b) collected, (c) cancelled and (d) outstanding for (i) adults, (ii) youths and (iii) organisations in each financial year since 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228211","228211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228335","2015-03-23","Ministry of Justice","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many foreign national prisoners there are in UK prisons from each of the 10 countries with the largest number of nationals in UK prisons.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228237","228237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228336","2015-03-23","Ministry of Justice","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many foreign national prisoners (a) by nationality and (b) of no known country of origin were held in prisons in England and Wales on 31 December 2014.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228238","228238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228337","2015-03-23","Ministry of Justice","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average cost is to the public purse of repatriating a foreign national prisoner; and how many such prisoners have been repatriated since 2010.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228239","228239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228338","2015-03-23","Ministry of Justice","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many foreign national prisoners there are in England and Wales by (a) country and (b) security category of each prison.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228240","228240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228339","2015-03-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many literacy courses were enrolled on by offenders assessed as having a literacy need in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228241","228241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228340","2015-03-23","Ministry of Justice","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, for what offences the foreign nationals in prison in England and Wales were convicted on the most recent date for which figures are available.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228242","228242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228341","2015-03-23","Ministry of Justice","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the cumulative total is of (a) uncollected and (b) cancelled victims' surcharges.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228243","228243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228342","2015-03-23","Ministry of Justice","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many babies were born to women in prison in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228258","228258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228343","2015-03-23","Ministry of Justice","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much has been (a) imposed, (b) collected, (c) cancelled and (d) outstanding under the victims' surcharge in each financial year since 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228244","228244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228344","2015-03-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make an assessment of the consequences for his policies of the cost benefit analysis of the uprating of frozen pensions contained in the report from the International Consortium of British Pensioners, published in October 2014; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228254","228254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228345","2015-03-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in (a) Blackpool South constituency and (b) Blackpool local authority area have applied for personal independence payments; and how many of those have received a decision on that application.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228255","228255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228346","2015-03-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many (a) people in the Work Programme entered employment and (b) people in the Work Programme were subject to benefit sanctions in (i) Blackpool South constituency and (ii) Blackpool local authority area in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228257","228257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228347","2015-03-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many recipients of jobseeker's allowance in (a) Blackpool South constituency and (b) Blackpool local authority area were sanctioned in (i) 2012, (ii) 2013, (iii) 2014 and (iv) 2015; and what the total amount of benefits withheld was as a result of those sanctions in each of those areas in each of those years.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228256","228256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228348","2015-03-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what progress he has made in implementing the recommendations of (a) the review to Government by Liz Sayce titled Getting in, staying in and getting on, published in June 2011 and (b) the expert panel chaired by Mike Adams in 2013 on Access to Work.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228188","228188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228349","2015-03-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 16 March 2015 to Question 226915, which specific issues have been discussed by which Ministers on which dates in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Meg Munn","Meg Munn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228247","228247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228766","2015-03-24","Attorney General","2015-03-18","To ask the Attorney General, what recent discussions he has had with cabinet colleagues on implementation of the UK's domestic and international legal obligations on human rights.","Biography information for Mr William Bain","Mr William Bain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 908282","908282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229313","2015-03-24","Deputy Prime Minister","2015-03-18","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what assessment he has made of the extent of inequalities in the distribution of the electorate between constituencies; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lord Robathan","Mr Andrew Robathan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 908263","908263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229314","2015-03-24","Deputy Prime Minister","2015-03-18","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what recent reports he has received on levels of inequality in the UK.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 908261","908261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229315","2015-03-24","Deputy Prime Minister","2015-03-18","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what plans he has to devolve further powers to rural areas.","Biography information for Jason McCartney","Jason McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 908259","908259"
