"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437399","2015-12-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department has taken to seek the views of pensioners on (a) his Department's policies and (b) winter fuel allowance since the closure of the UK Advisory Forum on Ageing.","Biography information for Nick Thomas-Symonds","Nick Thomas-Symonds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19732","19732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437400","2015-12-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, from what funding stream he plans to fund educational providers to provide training to jobseeker's allowance and universal credit claimants mandated to improve their English skills.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19729","19729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437401","2015-12-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the implications of differences in the administration of universal credit amongst the different local authorities involved in the Universal Support Delivered Locally pilot programme for the effectiveness of that pilot.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19764","19764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437402","2015-12-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of Britain's exit from the EU on access to pensions for older British citizens who are resident in other EU countries.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19751","19751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437057","2015-12-14","Attorney General","2015-12-10","To ask the Attorney General, how many alleged human traffickers have been prosecuted by the CPS as a result of calls made to the NSPCC human trafficking and modern slavery helpline between July 2014 and June 2015.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19543","19543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437058","2015-12-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent discussions his Department has had with the Northern Ireland Executive on Small Business Saturday and its benefits to promoting the value of small businesses to the economy.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19513","19513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437059","2015-12-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what modelling his Department conducted on the effect of the Apprenticeship Levy prior to its announcement.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19529","19529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437060","2015-12-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what information his Department holds on satisfaction levels of (a) non-disabled and (b) disabled students of their experience in higher education.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19503","19503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437061","2015-12-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what evaluation he has conducted on the extent to which universities cater to the needs of disabled students.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19504","19504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437062","2015-12-14","Ministry of Defence","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department has made an assessment of the accuracy of reports by Amnesty International and Human Rights Watch that a UK-produced bomb was used in an airstrike against a civilian factory in Yemen.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19547","19547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437063","2015-12-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what representations his Department has received on working practices at Sports Direct; and whether his Department has made an assessment of the compliance of working conditions and practices at that company with employment standards.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19553","19553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437064","2015-12-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if his Department will investigate recent reports on working practices and conditions at Sports Direct.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19554","19554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437065","2015-12-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what consultations he or officials in his Department have had with (a) further education college representatives, (b) further education providers and (c) sector skills councils about the structures on board composition of the proposed Institute for Apprenticeships announced in the Spending Review and Autumn Statement 2015.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19588","19588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437066","2015-12-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many staff made up the BIS Automotive sector team in each of the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19589","19589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437067","2015-12-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether apprentices are required to achieve a Level 2 Qualification including mathematics and English in order to be entered for an Advanced Level apprenticeship and for those entries to be in accordance with Trailblazer apprenticeships standards.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19581","19581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437068","2015-12-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether the apprenticeship targets for public sector organisations announced in the report, English Apprenticeships: Our 2020 Vision, published on 7 December 2015, will include targets for the creation of apprenticeships at Level 3 and above.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19685","19685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437069","2015-12-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what representations he has received from the Automotive Council on the long-term sustainability of automotive manufacturing in the UK; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19645","19645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437070","2015-12-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the cost to the public purse was of the internal review commissioned by his Department from McKinsey.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19649","19649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437071","2015-12-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will make an assessment of the implications for his policies on social mobility of the findings of research by the Resolution Foundation, set out in its report, The Pinch, published in December 2015, on differences in household wealth between generations; and what steps the Government plans to take to address such differences.","Biography information for Philip Boswell","Phil Boswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19592","19592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437072","2015-12-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the implications are for his Department's policy of the analysis undertaken by the Resolution Foundation set out in its report, The Pinch, published on 10 December 2015, of (a) the effects of the financial events of the last 10 years on those aged 16 to 44 relative to those aged 55 to 64 and (b) the changes in that period in levels of real median weekly earnings across different cohorts of the population.","Biography information for Philip Boswell","Phil Boswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19607","19607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437073","2015-12-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department is taking to increase inclusivity for disabled people of the Approved Apprenticeship programmes.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19608","19608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437074","2015-12-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many staff were employed by full-time equivalence (a) in total and (b) by region in the National Apprenticeship Service in (i) 2010-11, (ii) 2012-13 and (iii) 2014-15; and how many staff will be employed by full-time equivalence in the National Apprenticeship Service  in (A) 2015-16, (B) 2016-17 and (C) 2017-18.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19691","19691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437075","2015-12-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether apprentices are required to achieve a Level 2 qualification, including mathematics and English, in order (a) to be entered for an Advanced Level Apprenticeship and (b) for entries to be in accordance with the Specification of Apprenticeships Standards for England.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19656","19656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437076","2015-12-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether apprentices are required to achieve a Level 1 qualification, including mathematics and English, in order (a) to be entered for an Intermediate Level Apprenticeship and (b) for entries to be in accordance with the Specification of Apprenticeships Standards for England.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19657","19657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437077","2015-12-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether apprentices are required to achieve a Level 1 qualification, including mathematics and English, in order (a) to be entered for an Intermediate Level Apprenticeship and (b) for entries to be in accordance with the Trailblazer Apprenticeships Standards.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19658","19658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437078","2015-12-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many staff by full-time equivalence there were in his Department in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2012-13 and (c) 2014-15; and how many staff by full-time equivalence he expects there will be in his Department in (i) 2015-16, (ii) 2016-17 and (iii) 2017-18.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19692","19692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437079","2015-12-15","Cabinet Office","2015-12-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will make representations to the Office for National Statistics to include earnings from self-employment in its weekly earnings series.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19698","19698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437080","2015-12-15","Cabinet Office","2015-12-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what proportion of the population can the Verify identity assurance system assure the identity of.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19576","19576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437081","2015-12-15","Cabinet Office","2015-12-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what credentials individuals are required to have in order to register for GOV.UK Verify.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19584","19584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437082","2015-12-15","HM Treasury","2015-12-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the average award of working tax credits is in Salford and Eccles constituency.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19508","19508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437083","2015-12-14","HM Treasury","2015-12-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department has taken to investigate whether employees of Sports Direct are paid the minimum wage.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19516","19516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437084","2015-12-14","HM Treasury","2015-12-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if HM Revenue and Customs will investigate enforcement of the minimum wage at Sports Direct.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19517","19517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437085","2015-12-15","HM Treasury","2015-12-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what information the Financial Conduct Authority holds on (a) the reasons for which Mourant Fund Services Ltd did not complete its transaction to take over the operation of the Connaught Income Fund in 2009 and (b) whether at the time Mourant Fund Services Ltd was in possession of information about the Connaught Income Fund which should have been reported to the regulatory authorities.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19565","19565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437086","2015-12-15","HM Treasury","2015-12-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to reduce waiting times for the HMRC public service helpline.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19566","19566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437087","2015-12-15","HM Treasury","2015-12-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to his Oral statement of 25 November 2015, Official Report, column 1369, on the Spending Review and Autumn Statement, what the evidential basis is for his statement that inequality is down.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19555","19555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437088","2015-12-15","HM Treasury","2015-12-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps HM Revenue and Customs is talking to ensure that payroll taxes are collected from employers who pay wages in cash; what recent estimate he has made of the number of (a) employers using cash in hand for payroll and (b) employees receiving wages in cash; and what information he holds on the prevalence of payment of wages in cash in different sectors.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19561","19561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437089","2015-12-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in Salford and Eccles constituency are in receipt of (a) pension credit and (b) the carer addition.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19562","19562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437090","2015-12-15","HM Treasury","2015-12-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that lorry drivers have the correct status for the purposes of tax payment.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19551","19551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437091","2015-12-14","HM Treasury","2015-12-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate his Department has made of (a) the current proportion of air passenger duty revenues which are raised from Manchester Airport and (b) the potential effect on that proportion of air passenger duty in Scotland being reduced by 50 per cent.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19572","19572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437092","2015-12-15","HM Treasury","2015-12-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what were the total receipts from the sale of Government assets (a) from 1 January to 7 May 2015 and (b) from 8 May 2015 to date; and whether any further such sales are expected to take place before the end of the calendar year.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19580","19580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437093","2015-12-15","HM Treasury","2015-12-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people in Salford and Eccles constituency are in receipt of working tax credits.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19644","19644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437094","2015-12-14","HM Treasury","2015-12-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much from the Funding for Lending scheme has been lent to small and medium-sized enterprises in (a) Scotland and (b) Coatbridge, Chryston and Bellshill constituency.","Biography information for Philip Boswell","Phil Boswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19670","19670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437095","2015-12-14","HM Treasury","2015-12-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what statistical information his Department holds on small- and medium-sized enterprises which have defaulted on a loan received through the Funding for Lending Scheme.","Biography information for Philip Boswell","Phil Boswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19662","19662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437096","2015-12-14","HM Treasury","2015-12-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how his Department and the Bank of England assess the performance of small and medium-sized enterprises which have received a loan through the Funding for Lending scheme.","Biography information for Philip Boswell","Phil Boswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19668","19668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437097","2015-12-14","HM Treasury","2015-12-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much from the Funding for Lending scheme has been allocated (a) for lending on mortgages prior to the change in rules for such lending in 2014 and (b) for lending to small and medium-sized enterprises since the change in those rules.","Biography information for Philip Boswell","Phil Boswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19669","19669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437098","2015-12-14","HM Treasury","2015-12-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much of the £70 billion due to be allocated under the Funding for Lending Scheme has been allocated so far.","Biography information for Philip Boswell","Phil Boswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19659","19659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437099","2015-12-14","HM Treasury","2015-12-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the Bank of England is able to recover funds lent under the Funding for Lending Scheme from small and medium-sized enterprises which have subsequently defaulted on the loan.","Biography information for Philip Boswell","Phil Boswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19664","19664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437100","2015-12-15","HM Treasury","2015-12-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to paragraph 4.2 of the Government response to the 49th Report from the Committee of Public Accounts, Session 2014-15, for the effective management of tax reliefs, if he will (a) list and (b) place in the Library the external research reports commissioned by his Department which covers the use of tax reliefs.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19632","19632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437101","2015-12-14","HM Treasury","2015-12-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with the EU Commissioner on Competition on plans for recovering unpaid taxes and preventing multinationals avoiding tax.","Biography information for Richard Arkless","Richard  Arkless","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19684","19684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437102","2015-12-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what proportion of green belt land in the Poole Unitary Authority area has been redesignated in the last five years.","Biography information for Michael Tomlinson","Michael Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19682","19682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437103","2015-12-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what proportion of green belt land in the Purbeck District Council area has been redesignated in the last five years.","Biography information for Michael Tomlinson","Michael Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19683","19683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437104","2015-12-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what effect the policies outlined in the Spending Review and Autumn Statement 2015 will have on the amount his Department plans to spend on policies and services which in Scotland are devolved to the Scottish Government.","Biography information for Richard Arkless","Richard  Arkless","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19678","19678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437105","2015-12-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what proportion of green belt land in the East Dorset District Council area has been redesignated in the last five years as community land trust.","Biography information for Michael Tomlinson","Michael Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19679","19679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437106","2015-12-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what proportion of green belt land in the Dorset County Council area has been redesignated in the last five years.","Biography information for Michael Tomlinson","Michael Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19680","19680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437107","2015-12-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what proportion of green belt land in Mid Dorset and North Poole has been redesignated in the last five years.","Biography information for Michael Tomlinson","Michael Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19681","19681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437108","2015-12-15","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what his Department's target is for time taken to respond to letters and emails from hon. Members; what the average time taken by his Department to respond to such letters and emails is; and how many such letters and emails received between 1 January and 30 September 2015 remained unanswered after eight weeks.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19650","19650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437109","2015-12-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what proportion of green belt land in Mid Dorset and North Poole has been redesignated as community land trust in the last five years.","Biography information for Michael Tomlinson","Michael Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19611","19611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437110","2015-12-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will establish a standards setting body with a code of practice and an appeals service for all accredited trade associations for the management of parking on private land.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19603","19603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437111","2015-12-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what proportion of green belt land in the Dorset County Council area has been redesignated as community land trust in the last five years.","Biography information for Michael Tomlinson","Michael Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19612","19612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437112","2015-12-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what proportion of green belt land in the East Dorset District Council area has been redesignated in the last five years.","Biography information for Michael Tomlinson","Michael Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19604","19604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437113","2015-12-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what proportion of brownfield land in the Purbeck District Council area has been redesignated as community land trust in the last five years.","Biography information for Michael Tomlinson","Michael Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19614","19614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437114","2015-12-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what proportion of brownfield land in the Poole Unitary Authority area has been redesignated as community land trust in the last five years.","Biography information for Michael Tomlinson","Michael Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19615","19615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437115","2015-12-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what proportion of brownfield land in Mid Dorset and North Poole has been redesignated as community land trust in the last five years.","Biography information for Michael Tomlinson","Michael Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19616","19616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437116","2015-12-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what proportion of brownfield land in the East Dorset District Council area has been redesignated as community land trust in the last five years.","Biography information for Michael Tomlinson","Michael Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19613","19613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437117","2015-12-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what proportion of green belt land in the Purbeck District Council area has been redesignated as community land trust in the last five years.","Biography information for Michael Tomlinson","Michael Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19609","19609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437118","2015-12-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what proportion of green belt land in the Poole Unitary Authority area has been redesignated as community land trust in the last five years.","Biography information for Michael Tomlinson","Michael Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19610","19610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437119","2015-12-15","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the level of Government spending will be on the Disabled Facilities Grant for each year until 2020.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19637","19637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437120","2015-12-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he will respond to the submissions to his Department's consultation, Parking reform: tackling unfair practices, of March 2015.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19654","19654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437121","2015-12-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether his Department's policy remit on off-street parking includes parking for healthcare facilities, railway stations and local authority housing estates.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19655","19655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437122","2015-12-15","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the accessibility requirements will be for the 8,000 new accessible homes announced in the Spending Review and Autumn Statement 2015; and where those homes will be located.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19621","19621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437123","2015-12-15","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will commission research on the proportion of public and private service providers which offer access to their services through video relay.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19531","19531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437124","2015-12-15","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions he has had with (a) Talk Talk and (b) other internet service providers on measures that can be taken to prevent breaches of security relating to customer data.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19629","19629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437125","2015-12-15","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, when he plans to respond to Question 12142, tabled by the hon. Member for Coventry South on 15 October 2015.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19633","19633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437126","2015-12-15","Ministry of Defence","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 4 December 2015 to Question 18406, whether his Department assesses the cost of any training courses undertaken by (a) RAF, (b) navy and (c) army personnel at (i) Granton-on-Spey, (ii) Llanrwst, (iii) Crickhowell and (iv) Fairbourne; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19569","19569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437127","2015-12-14","Ministry of Defence","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to reduce shortages in the number of trained air warfare personnel; and what assessment he has made of the effect of that shortage on military operations in Iraq and Syria.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19518","19518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437128","2015-12-14","Ministry of Defence","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Reaper drones are currently deployed in (a) Iraq and (b) Syria.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19519","19519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437129","2015-12-14","Department for Education","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment her Department has made of the relationship between faith-based admissions policies and ethnic diversity in (a) primary and (b) secondary schools.","Biography information for Maria Caulfield","Maria Caulfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19520","19520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437130","2015-12-14","Department for Education","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what comparative assessment her Department has made of the ethnic diversity among pupils of Catholic schools and non-Catholic schools.","Biography information for Maria Caulfield","Maria Caulfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19521","19521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437131","2015-12-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that the Independent Adjudicator can monitor the implementation by higher education institutions of provision for disabled students who do not have complex needs.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19505","19505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437132","2015-12-14","Department for Education","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment her Department has made of the effectiveness of Catholic schools in supporting the integration of minority communities in (a) their student body and (b) the wider community.","Biography information for Maria Caulfield","Maria Caulfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19522","19522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437133","2015-12-14","Department for Education","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to promote coding as part of the curriculum or otherwise amongst young people.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19546","19546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437134","2015-12-14","Department for Education","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the page on the National Crime Agency website entitled, Cyber crime: Preventing young people from getting involved, what discussions she has had with the Home Secretary on interest in coding and possession of independent learning material on computing being considered possible indicators of risk of involvement in cyber crime.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19545","19545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437135","2015-12-15","Department for Education","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that children and young people acquire the skills necessary to make healthy food choice.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19586","19586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437136","2015-12-14","Department for Education","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will introduce additional support for children experiencing bullying.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19591","19591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437137","2015-12-14","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how much overspend against original estimates within the levy control framework has arisen from variations in (a) performance of offshore wind, (b) levels between strike price and reference price and (c) variations in allocations feed in tariff payments for solar PV installations in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19617","19617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437138","2015-12-15","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many legal challenges have been made against her Department related to renewable energy policy in the last year.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19696","19696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437139","2015-12-15","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether the feed-in tariff scheme will be paused in January 2015; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19697","19697"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437140","2015-12-15","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the change in the number of jobs in the UK solar industry has been since the Summer Budget 2015; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19695","19695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437141","2015-12-14","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what level of actual or projected overspend against original projections of expenditure under the Levy Control Framework she has identified for each year from 2014 to 2018; and in which of those years overspend has exceeded the 20 per cent headroom within the Levy Control Framework agreement between her Department and HM Treasury.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19534","19534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437142","2015-12-14","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what form of transport she used to travel to the COP21 conference in Paris in December 2015; and for what reasons she used that form of transport.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19533","19533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437143","2015-12-14","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether she has written to the European Commissioner for Trade on ending the minimum import price on Chinese solar panels.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19514","19514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437144","2015-12-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate she has made of the number of farmers who received payments under the Environment Stewardship Scheme in October rather than August 2015 as a result of the withdrawal of online applications for such payments.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19575","19575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437145","2015-12-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate she has made of the cost of disallowance penalties relating to the Common Agricultural Policy as a result of the return to paper-assisted digital applications in 2015.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19642","19642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437146","2015-12-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the definition of paper-assisted digital applications is for the Common Agricultural Policy Delivery Programme.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19643","19643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437147","2015-12-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to tackle the illegal transport of farmed puppies from the Republic of Ireland and southern Europe into the UK.","Biography information for Richard Arkless","Richard  Arkless","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19671","19671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437148","2015-12-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 16 November 2015 to Question 16031, how much the Environment Agency spent directly on maintaining flood defences in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12, (c) 2012-13 and (d) 2013-14; and how much the agency projects it will spend on such defences in (i) 2015-16, (ii) 2016-17, (iii) 2017-18, (iv) 2018-19 and (v) 2019-20.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19606","19606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437149","2015-12-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many full-time equivalent Environment Agency staff were employed on maintenance of flood defences on 1 April (a) 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012, (d) 2013, (e) 2014 and (f) 2015.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19674","19674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437150","2015-12-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of the Environment Agency's 2014 Long Term Investment Scenarios recommended optimum overall investment in flood defences of £750m to £800m each year to 2019-20; and whether she expects that level of overall investment to be achieved.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19675","19675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437151","2015-12-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what measures in the Spending Review and Autumn Statement 2015 will affect the level of funding for flood defences up to 2019-20.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19676","19676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437152","2015-12-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many of her officials are engaged in preparing the Government's next Climate Change Risk Assessment.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19677","19677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437153","2015-12-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 3 December 2015 to Question 18118, when she plans to announce the level of funding for flood defence maintenance in each year until 2019-20.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19605","19605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437154","2015-12-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what his Department's target is for time taken to respond to letters and emails from hon. Members; what the average time taken by his Department to respond to such letters and emails is; and how many such letters and emails received between 1 January and 30 September 2015 remained unanswered after eight weeks.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19651","19651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437155","2015-12-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when he plans to reply to the letter of 26 November 2015 from the hon. Member for Rutherglen and Hamilton West regarding mass executions in Saudi Arabia.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19623","19623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437156","2015-12-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, which UK embassies have a human rights adviser on their staff.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19577","19577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437157","2015-12-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations his Department has received from diplomatic representatives in the UK of states where the trade of dog meat for consumption is active subsequent to the debate in the House on the dog meat trade of 5 November 2015.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19548","19548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437158","2015-12-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations his Ministers have made to their counterparts abroad or to their diplomatic representatives in the UK on the practice of consuming and selling dog meat for consumption subsequent to the debate in the House on the dog meat trade of 5 November 2015.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19549","19549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437159","2015-12-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department has taken or plans to take on the practice of consuming and selling dog meat for consumption in addition to the steps he set out in the debate in the House on the dog meat trade of 5 November 2015.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19550","19550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437160","2015-12-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will issue a response to Early Day Motion 846, Use of explosive weapons and human rights violations in Yemen.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19536","19536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437161","2015-12-14","Department of Health","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions his Department has had with the Northern Ireland Executive on improving access to high-quality services for people affected by Parkinson's disease.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19509","19509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437162","2015-12-14","Department of Health","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the cost to the NHS was of treating cold-related admissions to hospitals in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19510","19510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437163","2015-12-14","Department of Health","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many full-time sight loss adviser posts there are in hospitals in England.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19511","19511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437164","2015-12-14","Department of Health","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much has been spent on the provision of eye clinic care liaison officers in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19512","19512"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437165","2015-12-15","Department of Health","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of finance options available to student nurses; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19564","19564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437166","2015-12-15","Department of Health","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, for what reasons he has not yet announced funding for the Time to Change campaigns beyond March 2016.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19556","19556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437167","2015-12-15","Department of Health","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he plans to report on the progress of the pilot being run in conjunction with the Department for Education to give schools access to a single point of contact for mental health.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19557","19557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437168","2015-12-15","Department of Health","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to improve the mental health of young carers and young adult carers as part of the Future in Mind policy.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19558","19558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437169","2015-12-15","Department of Health","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make an assessment of the effects of zero-hour and uncertain hour contracts on the mental health of people holding such contracts.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19559","19559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437170","2015-12-15","Department of Health","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he plans to publish details of his proposal to introduce Ofsted-style ratings for clinical commissioning groups' mental health services.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19560","19560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437171","2015-12-15","Department of Health","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department plans to take to (a) identify and (b) support young people at risk of cardiac problems.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19585","19585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437172","2015-12-14","Department of Health","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that funding is sufficient to meet patient demand in (a) community mental healthcare and (b) inpatient mental healthcare; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19583","19583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437173","2015-12-15","Department of Health","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what representations his Department has received (a) since his appointment as Secretary of State and (b) since the appointment of his predecessor in that post expressing concerns about Southern Health NHS Foundation Trust.","Biography information for Heidi Alexander","Heidi Alexander","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19686","19686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437174","2015-12-15","Department of Health","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when (a) his Department, (b) NHS England and (c) Southern Health NHS Foundation Trust first received a copy of the Mazers report on Southern Health NHS Foundation Trust.","Biography information for Heidi Alexander","Heidi Alexander","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19687","19687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437175","2015-12-15","Department of Health","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with his Cabinet colleagues on making additional funding available to local authorities to help fund the introduction of the national living wage into social care from April 2016; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19646","19646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437176","2015-12-15","Department of Health","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of GP surgeries which will pay increased rental charges for their premises after NHS Property Services Ltd moves to market value rents; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19641","19641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437177","2015-12-15","Department of Health","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much funding Lancashire Teaching Hospitals NHS Trust received for treating people from outside the EU in (a) 2011, (b) 2012, (c) 2013 and (d) 2014.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19634","19634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437178","2015-12-15","Department of Health","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions Ministers of his Department have had with Harrow Clinical Commissioning Group about providing a polyclinic in the eastern part of the London Borough of Harrow; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19640","19640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437179","2015-12-15","Department of Health","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of introducing the national living wage into social care from April 2016.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19638","19638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437180","2015-12-15","Department of Health","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of the performance of Brighton and Sussex University Hospitals NHS Trust services.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19639","19639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437181","2015-12-14","Department of Health","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how the Government plans to phase increases to funding for NHS England over the next five years; and what the Barnett consequentials of decisions on such phasing will be.","Biography information for Richard Arkless","Richard  Arkless","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19661","19661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437182","2015-12-15","Home Office","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what level of co-operation there is between the National Crime Agency and authorities in the Republic of Ireland on combatting organised criminal activities taking place between Northern Ireland and the Republic of Ireland.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19694","19694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437183","2015-12-14","Home Office","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, for what reasons she selected St Mary's University, Twickenham, to host a specialist international centre for research into modern slavery and human trafficking; and whether any other institution was considered for this role.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19620","19620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437184","2015-12-14","Home Office","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many of those listed in table P.04 of the September 2015 Statistical Bulletin 04/15, Operation of police powers under the Terrorism Act 2000 and subsequent legislation: Arrests, outcomes and stop and search, Great Britain, financial year ending 31 March 2015, were (a) charged with and (b) convicted of offences.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19618","19618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437185","2015-12-15","Home Office","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what her Department's target is for time taken to respond to letters and emails from hon. Members; what the average time taken by her Department to respond to such letters and emails is; and how many such letters and emails received between 1 January and 30 September 2015 remained unanswered after eight weeks.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19652","19652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437186","2015-12-14","Home Office","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the effect of the Government's immigration policies on the number of international students enrolling in UK universities.","Biography information for Richard Arkless","Richard  Arkless","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19663","19663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437187","2015-12-14","Home Office","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment the Government has made of the implications of its decision to remove border staff at the ports of Stranraer and Cairnryan for UK security.","Biography information for Richard Arkless","Richard  Arkless","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19667","19667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437188","2015-12-15","Home Office","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, (a) what the average waiting time was for checks by the Disclosure and Barring Service to be completed and (b) how long on average the Police National Computer search took in (i) 2010-11, (ii) 2011-12, (iii) 2012-13, (iv) 2013-14, (v) 2014-15 and (vi) 2015-16 to date.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19688","19688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437189","2015-12-15","Home Office","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many serious fraud cases are under investigation by Merseyside Police Force; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19689","19689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437190","2015-12-15","Home Office","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many arrests have been made in connection with gun crime in the West Midlands metropolitan area in (a) each of the last 10 years and (b) each quarter of 2015.","Biography information for Mr Khalid Mahmood","Mr Khalid Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19626","19626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437191","2015-12-15","Home Office","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to tackle gang-related gun crime.","Biography information for Mr Khalid Mahmood","Mr Khalid Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19627","19627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437192","2015-12-15","Home Office","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to support the West Midlands Police Force respond to an increase in the levels of gun crime in Birmingham.","Biography information for Mr Khalid Mahmood","Mr Khalid Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19628","19628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437193","2015-12-14","Home Office","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what progress her Department has made on the evaluation of the Child Trafficking Advocates Trial.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19582","19582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437194","2016-01-05","Home Office","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when the Right to Rent Scheme for landlords to perform immigration checks on tenants will come into force in Scotland.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19590","19590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437195","2015-12-14","Home Office","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will set up a dedicated correspondence team in her Department to liaise with applicants solicitors on the processing of asylum claims.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19574","19574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437196","2015-12-15","Home Office","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many convictions resulted from reports to Action Fraud in each year since it was set up.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19578","19578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437197","2015-12-14","Home Office","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the page on the National Crime Agency website entitled, Cyber crime: Preventing young people from getting involved, what the statistical evidence is for the statement that more and more teenagers and young people are involved in cyber crime.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19544","19544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437198","2016-01-05","Home Office","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when the residential tenancy provisions of the Immigration Bill would come into force in Scotland if enacted.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19568","19568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437199","2015-12-14","Home Office","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many victims of human trafficking have been identified and their identities subsequently forwarded to the police as a result of people calling the NSPCC human trafficking and slavery helpline between July 2014 and June 2015.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19542","19542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437200","2015-12-15","Home Office","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how UK citizens living in the UK can apply for a visa for relatives living in Yemen.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19523","19523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437201","2015-12-14","Department for International Development","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what form of transport she used to travel to the COP21 conference in Paris in December 2015; and for what reasons she used that form of transport.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19532","19532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437202","2015-12-15","Department for International Development","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the potential contribution of aid to Syria to strengthening the moderate opposition's capacity to provide governance and basic services.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19563","19563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437203","2015-12-15","Department for International Development","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment her Department has made of (a) the effect of the drought in the Horn of Africa on Eritrea and (b) the response of the Eritrean government and the international community to that drought.","Biography information for Keir Starmer","Keir Starmer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19567","19567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437204","2015-12-14","Ministry of Justice","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which prisons he intends to close; and what consultation is taking place or is planned to take place on those closures.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19570","19570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437205","2015-12-14","Ministry of Justice","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many secondments into his Department there were in each year since 2013; from which organisations each such person was seconded; and into which areas of his Department they were seconded.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19571","19571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437206","2015-12-14","Ministry of Justice","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether his Department knew of any restrictive covenant on the use and disposal of HMP Holloway, the land upon which it is situated or its buildings before publication of the Spending Review and Autumn Statement 2015.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19540","19540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437207","2015-12-14","Ministry of Justice","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what restrictive covenants exist on the use and disposal of each prison establishment in England and Wales.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19541","19541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437208","2015-12-14","Ministry of Justice","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what account the prison estates review took of the existence of restrictive covenants prior to the Government's announcement of the programme of prison closures and new prison construction.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19538","19538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437209","2015-12-14","Home Office","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many immigration detainees were held in each prison establishment in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19539","19539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437210","2015-12-15","Ministry of Justice","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to raise awareness amongst solicitors of the risks of their clients being targeted in scams by people purporting to operate in the name of their solicitor requesting transfer of funds; and what estimate he has made of the number of such scams that took place in the last three years.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19587","19587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437211","2015-12-15","Ministry of Justice","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many suspended sentences were given for people with (a) one, (b) between one and 10 and (c) more than 10 previous convictions in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Wayne David","Wayne David","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19624","19624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437212","2015-12-15","Department of Health","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many prisoners are taking part in drug and alcohol treatment programmes (a) in total and (b) in each prison in England and Wales.","Biography information for Wayne David","Wayne David","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19625","19625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437213","2015-12-15","Ministry of Justice","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate his Department has made of the number of children in England and Wales who have a parent in custody.","Biography information for Wayne David","Wayne David","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19648","19648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437214","2015-12-15","Ministry of Justice","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many visits have been made by one or more children to a parent in custody in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Wayne David","Wayne David","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19647","19647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437215","2015-12-15","Ministry of Justice","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners are employed in prisons in (a) the most recent period for which figures are available and (b) each of the last five years.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19528","19528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437216","2015-12-15","Ministry of Justice","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prison workshops have (a) opened, (b) closed and (c) changed function in each of the last seven years.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19530","19530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437217","2015-12-14","Ministry of Justice","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of whether the current sentencing framework for mothers with children takes sufficient account of the needs of those children.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19506","19506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437218","2015-12-15","Ministry of Justice","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average waiting time is on prison visit booking lines (a) in each prison and (b) overall.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19507","19507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437219","2015-12-15","Ministry of Justice","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many new criminal offences have been (a) created and (b) proposed since May 2015; and if he will make an assessment of the (i) effect on and (b)cost to the prison estate of the creation of those offences.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19524","19524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437220","2015-12-15","Ministry of Justice","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners were in open prisons (a) in the most recent period for which figures are available and (b) in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19527","19527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437221","2015-12-15","Ministry of Justice","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the budget is for prison libraries in (a) total and (b) each prison in 2015; and what the cost was in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19525","19525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437222","2015-12-15","Ministry of Justice","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which prisons have libraries; and which organisations (a) run and (b) fund each such library.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19526","19526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437223","2015-12-14","Ministry of Justice","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prosecutions were brought to court under the provisions of the Human Rights Act in each year since 2005.","Biography information for Richard Arkless","Richard  Arkless","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19666","19666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437224","2015-12-14","Ministry of Justice","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether he plans for the proposed British Bill of Rights to apply to Scotland.","Biography information for Richard Arkless","Richard  Arkless","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19673","19673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437225","2015-12-15","Department of Health","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many prisoners received treatment for (a) alcohol addiction, (b) drug addiction and (c) any other addiction in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19690","19690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437226","2015-12-14","Ministry of Justice","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many NOMS staff have been dismissed for corruption in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19593","19593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437227","2015-12-14","Ministry of Justice","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prison officers have been granted retirement on the grounds of ill health in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19594","19594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437228","2015-12-15","Ministry of Justice","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prison officer grade staff were employed by NOMS on 31 March in each year since 2010; and how many such people were employed on the latest day for which statistics are available.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19635","19635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437229","2015-12-15","Ministry of Justice","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prison officer grade staff have (a) joined and (b) left the prison service in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19636","19636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437230","2015-12-15","Northern Ireland Office","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, whether financial penalties related to welfare reform have been ceased since legislation on that subject was agreed by the Northern Ireland Assembly; and whether there has been reimbursement of such penalties since that agreement.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19693","19693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437231","2015-12-15","Prime Minister","2015-12-10","To ask the Prime Minister, when he plans to reply to the letter of 26 November 2015 from the hon. Member for Rutherglen and Hamilton West regarding mass executions in Saudi Arabia.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19622","19622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437232","2015-12-14","Scotland Office","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what recent discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions on the effect of the Government's welfare programme on social and economic inequalities in Scotland.","Biography information for Richard Arkless","Richard  Arkless","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19660","19660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437233","2015-12-14","Department for Transport","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans his Department has to encourage an increase in the number of HGV drivers in the UK to meet demand for such drivers.","Biography information for Richard Arkless","Richard  Arkless","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19665","19665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437234","2015-12-17","Department for Transport","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how Rail North will work with existing transport bodies in the area in which it operates.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19653","19653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437235","2015-12-14","Department for Transport","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he plans to give local authorities the power to enforce moving traffic contraventions under the provisions of the Traffic Management Act 2004.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19602","19602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437236","2015-12-15","Department for Transport","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that (a) lorry drivers from outside the UK have the appropriate licences and skills to drive on roads safely and (b) left-hand drive lorries have appropriate extra mirrors to improve visibility of cyclists and other road users to the lorry driver.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19579","19579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437237","2015-12-15","Department for Transport","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what representations have been made to his Department on fraud involving the tax status of lorry drivers.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19552","19552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437238","2015-12-14","Department for Transport","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans the Government has to hold a consultation with the Scottish Government on the future of the NATS centre at Prestwick.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19537","19537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437239","2015-12-14","HM Treasury","2015-12-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of a 50 per cent reduction in air passenger duty in Scotland on Manchester Airport.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19573","19573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437240","2015-12-14","Department for Transport","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what representations he has received on extension of the Unizone reduced fares rail scheme to the University of Brighton's Hastings campus; if he will provide funding to allow that extension to be implemented immediately; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19515","19515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437241","2015-12-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to correct the computer error in the child maintenance system on the collection of arrears.","Biography information for Ian Blackford","Ian Blackford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19535","19535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437242","2015-12-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to his Written Statement of 10 December 2015, HCWS377, on universal credit and local authorities, how he will define reasonable efforts to redeploy staff.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19630","19630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437243","2015-12-14","Cabinet Office","2015-12-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many young people are classified as long-term unemployed in Mid Dorset and North Poole constituency.","Biography information for Michael Tomlinson","Michael Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19596","19596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437244","2015-12-14","Cabinet Office","2015-12-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many young people are classified as long-term unemployed in Poole Unitary Authority area.","Biography information for Michael Tomlinson","Michael Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19597","19597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437245","2015-12-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will review the transition arrangements for women who have seen their pensionable age increase with limited transition.","Biography information for Ian Blackford","Ian Blackford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19601","19601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437246","2015-12-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what support his Department is providing to young people who are classified as long-term unemployed in Mid Dorset and North Poole constituency.","Biography information for Michael Tomlinson","Michael Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19595","19595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437247","2015-12-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to his Written Statement of 10 December 2015, HCWS377, on universal credit and local authorities, what estimate he has made of (a) the number of people employed by local authorities to administer housing benefit, (b) the number of such employees likely to be made redundant as a result of the universal credit roll-out, (c) the total cost to the public purse of such redundancies, (d) the total number of staff that will be required to administer universal credit at a local level once the roll-out is complete and (e) the number of people currently employed by his Department in that capacity.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19631","19631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437248","2015-12-14","Cabinet Office","2015-12-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many young people are classified as long-term unemployed in the East Dorset District Council area.","Biography information for Michael Tomlinson","Michael Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19599","19599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437249","2015-12-14","Cabinet Office","2015-12-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many young people are classified as long-term unemployed in the Dorset County Council area.","Biography information for Michael Tomlinson","Michael Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19598","19598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437250","2015-12-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how agreement was sought on how to amend the investment regulations as recommended in the report by the Law Commission, Fiduciary Duties of Investment Intermediaries, published in June 2014.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19619","19619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437251","2015-12-14","Cabinet Office","2015-12-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many young people are classified as long-term unemployed in the Purbeck District Council area.","Biography information for Michael Tomlinson","Michael Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19600","19600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/437252","2015-12-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many benefits claimants in Dumfries and Galloway were sanctioned between the months of October and December for each year from 2010 until the most recent date for which figures are available.","Biography information for Richard Arkless","Richard  Arkless","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19672","19672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438816","2015-12-16","Department for International Development","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what funding and other resources her Department has provided for Syrian refugee camps.","Biography information for Scott Mann","Scott Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 902756","902756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438817","2015-12-16","Department for International Development","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much her Department has spent on humanitarian assistance in (a) Syria and (b) neighbouring countries receiving Syrian refugees in the last two years.","Biography information for Lord Davies of Gower","Byron Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 902755","902755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438818","2015-12-16","Department for International Development","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what proportion of Overseas Development Aid her Department used to tackle the refugee crisis in the last 12 months; and how much her Department plans to allocate in future years to tackling that situation.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 902758","902758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438819","2015-12-16","Department for International Development","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what funding her Department has allocated to support resettlement of Syrian refugees.","Biography information for Will Quince","Will Quince","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 902761","902761"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438820","2015-12-16","Department for International Development","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will make it her policy to continue to invest in the Global Fund to Fight AIDS, Tuberculosis and Malaria.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 902760","902760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438821","2015-12-16","Department for International Development","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what proportion of the international aid budget she plans to allocate to support communities managing the consequences of climate change in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Callum McCaig","Callum McCaig","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 902759","902759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438822","2015-12-16","Department for International Development","2015-12-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent assessment she has made of the humanitarian situation in the Occupied Palestinian Territories.","Biography information for Tommy Sheppard","Tommy Sheppard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 902757","902757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436624","2015-12-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the legal position is on the use of prefixes or styles granted by virtue of honours in Commonwealth realms in the UK to (a) either to a citizen of a Commonwealth realm and (b) to a dual national who is also national of Great Britain and Northern Ireland; how such honours are recognised; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19412","19412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436626","2015-12-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the relationship will be between the new Institute for Apprentices and the industry-led body that will administer the Apprenticeships Levy.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19485","19485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436628","2015-12-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent discussions he has had with the devolved administrations on the distribution and use of funds raised by the proposed Apprenticeship Levy.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19462","19462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436634","2015-12-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the effect of poverty and inequalities on entrepreneurialism and economic growth.","Biography information for Natalie McGarry","Natalie McGarry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19345","19345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436635","2015-12-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will estimate the UK's current trade deficit with the EU.","Biography information for Mr Peter Bone","Mr Peter Bone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19366","19366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436637","2015-12-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the implications for implementing his Department's policies for combatting climate change and decarbonising electricity generation of the Trade in Services Agreement.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19375","19375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436639","2015-12-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps the Government is taking to maintain current spending levels on the core elements of the science budget in real terms over the course of the Parliament.","Biography information for Mark Durkan","Mark Durkan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19387","19387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436641","2015-12-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the relationship will be between the Institute for Apprentices and the body that will administer the Apprenticeship Levy.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19388","19388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436643","2015-12-14","Cabinet Office","2015-12-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether there is, or has been within the last 10 years, a requirement on (a) applicants to the civil service and (b) civil servants upon entry to the civil service to disclose party political membership.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19367","19367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436644","2015-12-14","Cabinet Office","2015-12-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the total cost to the public purse was of ministerial special advisors in the last financial year; and how much is projected to be so spent in the next financial year.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19361","19361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436650","2015-12-14","Cabinet Office","2015-12-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what plans the Government has to raise the level of skills and technical capability in the civil service to support the Government's digital transformation programme.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19397","19397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436652","2015-12-14","Cabinet Office","2015-12-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what technology platforms and services the Government plans to develop as part of the (a) Government as a Platform and (b) Common Technology Services strategy to support the digital transformation of public services; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19398","19398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436654","2015-12-14","Cabinet Office","2015-12-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what progress has been made on the GOV.UK Verify programme; and what plans the Government has to develop it further in the future.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19399","19399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436656","2015-12-14","Cabinet Office","2015-12-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what recent assessment has been made of people's attitudes towards public bodies using and sharing their data with other parts of the public sector as part of digitally transformed public services; and what plans the Government has to build trust and assurance among people on the Government's use of their data as part of those public services.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19400","19400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436657","2015-12-14","Cabinet Office","2015-12-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how the £450 million funding allocated to the Government Digital Service in the Spending Review and Autumn Statement 2015 will be spent; and what the priorities for the Government Digital Service will be over the next (a) 12 and (b) 24 months.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19402","19402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436659","2015-12-14","HM Treasury","2015-12-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans he has to procure the replacement for the HM Revenue and Customs IT Aspire contract; what consultation there will be with HM Revenue and Customs staff and their representatives; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19419","19419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436661","2015-12-14","HM Treasury","2015-12-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the Barnet consequentials for Northern Ireland are of the £50 million additional funding for flood relief; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19478","19478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436663","2015-12-14","HM Treasury","2015-12-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of changing the VAT status of care providers to zero-rated in order to assist them in meeting the cost of complying with the national living wage.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19492","19492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436665","2015-12-14","HM Treasury","2015-12-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the Autumn Statement and Spending Review 2015, paragraph 1.309, whether any reduction is planned in (a) Cranborne money and (b) Representative money.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19449","19449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436666","2015-12-14","HM Treasury","2015-12-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he plans to offer deadline extensions for tax due by businesses affected by flooding in Cumbria.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19456","19456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436667","2015-12-14","HM Treasury","2015-12-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will introduce an instalment scheme to allow businesses in Cumbria affected by flooding to spread tax payments.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19457","19457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436670","2015-12-14","HM Treasury","2015-12-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the practice of HM Revenue & Customs is to deal with illegal fuel seized by that body.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19310","19310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436672","2015-12-14","HM Treasury","2015-12-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether it is his policy that the changes to interest rate relief on buy-to-let mortgages announced in the Summer Budget 2015 apply to purchasers within a limited company structure.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19312","19312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436674","2015-12-14","HM Treasury","2015-12-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the Government plans to relocate all 650 HM Revenue & Customs jobs at Sidlaw House, Dundee, to the Department for Work and Pensions.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19322","19322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436675","2015-12-14","HM Treasury","2015-12-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make an assessment of the potential effect on jobs in Dundee of the policies outlined in the Spending Review and Autumn Statement 2015.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19323","19323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436676","2015-12-14","HM Treasury","2015-12-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the evidential basis is for his contribution of 25 November 2015, Official Report, column 1366, that Britain topped the league table of the best places in the world to invest in infrastructure.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19333","19333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436677","2015-12-15","HM Treasury","2015-12-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what progress HM Revenue and Customs has made in recovering VAT and business rates from the shooting industry in the last five years.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19371","19371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436678","2015-12-14","HM Treasury","2015-12-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many charities registered in Wakefield constituency have claimed back Gift Aid on small cash donations using the Gift Aid Small Donation Scheme since that scheme's inception.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19380","19380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436679","2015-12-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what progress is being made on the Glasgow and Clyde Valley City Deal.","Biography information for Philip Boswell","Phil Boswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19381","19381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436680","2015-12-14","HM Treasury","2015-12-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the cost to the Exchequer was of disposing of illegal fuel in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19377","19377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436682","2015-12-14","HM Treasury","2015-12-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what support his Department is offering to businesses affected by flooding in Cumbria in advance of tax payment deadlines.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19458","19458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436683","2015-12-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to tackle landlords who knowingly rent out unsafe and substandard accommodation.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19317","19317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436684","2015-12-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of trends in the number of young people who own their own home since 2010.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19318","19318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436685","2015-12-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the extent of financial and operational links between the social housing sector in Scotland and England.","Biography information for Natalie McGarry","Natalie McGarry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19344","19344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436686","2015-12-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what encouragement he has given local authorities to switch street lighting to LED light sources since May 2015.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19297","19297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436688","2015-12-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many planning refusals for greenfield sites have been overturned on appeal in each year between 2010 to 2015.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19305","19305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436692","2015-12-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the average weekly rent and service charge for supported accommodation including (a) foyers, (b) direct access hostels, (c) supported housing for older people and (d) other supported housing has been in each (i) region and (ii) local authority area in the last three years.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19465","19465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436693","2015-12-14","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether his Department plans to establish a statutory levy on greyhound racing to help support the welfare of retired greyhounds.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19491","19491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436695","2015-12-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will encourage the use of the customer services centre at Kettering Borough Council as an example of good practice for other local authorities to follow.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19477","19477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436696","2015-12-14","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what proportion of the total declared claw back from BT under National Broadband Scheme contracts has been reallocated to local authorities for additional roll-out under the Scheme.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19470","19470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436697","2015-12-14","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what additional funding allocations have been provided to each local authority as a result of declared claw back from BT under the National Broadband Scheme.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19471","19471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436698","2015-12-14","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he is taking to assist bookmakers in reducing (a) crime on their premises and (b) the incidence of malicious damage to fixed odds betting terminals.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19331","19331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436699","2015-12-14","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will make an assessment of whether the Code of Conduct for bookmakers is meeting the aims for which it was drawn up.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19332","19332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436700","2015-12-14","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, with regard to fixed odds betting terminals, what steps are being taken to (a) ensure that the player protection measures introduced from April 2015 are effectively evaluated and (b) independently assess whether the £50 threshold for supervised play is set at an effective level.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19328","19328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436701","2015-12-14","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to the contribution of the Minister of State for Culture and the Digital Economy of 3 December 2015, Official Report, column 510, what the purpose was of the two one-off grants paid to MG Alba.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19385","19385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436702","2015-12-14","Ministry of Defence","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many strikes were made using the Brimstone missile during Operation HERRICK.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19368","19368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436703","2015-12-14","Ministry of Defence","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many remotely piloted aircraft system pilots are employed in the RAF; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19382","19382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436704","2015-12-14","Ministry of Defence","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 30 November 2015 to Question 17622, if he will identify separately the marginal costs associated with maintaining the Vanguard submarines in service for five years longer then envisaged.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19334","19334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436705","2015-12-14","Ministry of Defence","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which memoranda of understanding have been agreed with the French government in support of Project Teutates.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19342","19342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436706","2015-12-14","Ministry of Defence","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) joint Anglo-French and (b) solely French experiments have been conducted using (i) laser and (ii) hydrodynamics facilities at Atomic Weapons Establishment Aldermaston to date.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19343","19343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436707","2015-12-14","Ministry of Defence","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many reserves were recruited in Scotland in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12, (c) 2013-14 and (d) 2014-15.","Biography information for Steven Paterson","Steven Paterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19330","19330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436708","2015-12-14","Ministry of Defence","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what guidance his Department provides to service personnel on choosing state and private schools for their children's education.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19347","19347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436709","2015-12-14","Ministry of Defence","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what evaluation his Department made of the number and location of civilian workers who work at the al-Omar oil field in Syria before ordering Royal Air Force planes to bomb that facility; and how many civilians have been killed as a result of UK military action on targets in Syria to date.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19294","19294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436710","2015-12-14","Ministry of Defence","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the sources of (a) arms and (b) armed vehicles obtained by Daesh.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19296","19296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436711","2015-12-14","Ministry of Defence","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessments he has made of the future security needs of Ministry of Defence (MoD) establishments in the UK; whether responsibility for guarding any MoD sites, assets and infrastructure will be transferred from the MoD Police to the Armed Forces in the next five years; how and when such changes might be decided upon and implemented; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19461","19461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436712","2015-12-16","Ministry of Defence","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to his evidence to the Defence Committee on UK military operations in Syria and Iraq on 1 December 2015, HC 657, Q36, if he will publish a breakdown of the groups comprising the estimated 70,000 fighters in Syria described by the UK government as moderate.","Biography information for Dr Julian Lewis","Dr Julian Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19490","19490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436713","2015-12-14","Ministry of Defence","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 1 December 2015 to Question 17678, how many (a) military and (b) civil servant personnel of each rank and grade are employed at (i) MoD Grantown-on-Spey, (b) MoD Llanwrst, (c) MoD Fairbourne and (d) MoD Crickhowell; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19463","19463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436714","2015-12-14","Ministry of Defence","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Answer of 19 June 2013, Official Report, column 718W, on AWE Aldermaston, what the final write-off costs were of the cancellation of Project Hydrus at the Atomic Weapons Establishment.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19414","19414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436715","2015-12-14","Ministry of Defence","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Type 45 destroyers are in Portsmouth dockyards; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19415","19415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436716","2015-12-14","Ministry of Defence","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether (a) HMS Brocklesby M33 mine sweeper will be refitted at Portsmouth naval dockyards and (b) that refitting will include new propulsion capability; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19417","19417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436717","2015-12-14","Ministry of Defence","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Answer of 26 September 2014 to Question 209770 asked by the hon. Member for Moray, how much his Department has spent on studies on whether to refurbish or replace the existing Trident warhead design to date.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19392","19392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436718","2015-12-14","Ministry of Defence","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the in-service dates are for the Technology Development Centre at the Atomic Weapons Establishment Aldermaston and the Epure facility at the CEA site at Valduc; and when UK experiments are scheduled to commence at Epure.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19393","19393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436719","2015-12-14","Ministry of Defence","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 22 October 2015 to Question 12325, whether encouraging UK military exports to that country form part of the Defence Attaché's duties in each case.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19404","19404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436720","2015-12-14","Ministry of Defence","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what support his Department is providing to fund mental health services for military personnel on active military duty; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19454","19454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436721","2015-12-14","Ministry of Defence","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment his Department has made the effectiveness and reliability of small arms equipment issued as standard across the armed forces; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19455","19455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436722","2015-12-14","Ministry of Defence","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he is negotiating for a UK support element within the contact negotiations for the P8; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19427","19427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436723","2015-12-14","Ministry of Defence","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what level of UK support has been negotiated for the Rivetjoint platforms; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19428","19428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436724","2015-12-14","Ministry of Defence","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the air to air refuelling capability is of the P8 MPA with the UK Voyager fleet; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19429","19429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436725","2015-12-14","Ministry of Defence","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether (a) stormshadow and (b) stingray will be utilised on the P8 MPA; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19430","19430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436726","2015-12-14","Ministry of Defence","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, (a) when and (b) where the Type 26 frigates will be built; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19431","19431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436727","2015-12-14","Ministry of Defence","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when the Type 45 refits will commence; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19425","19425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436728","2015-12-14","Ministry of Defence","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many support jobs were lost when the Nimrod MRA4 was decommissioned; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19426","19426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436729","2015-12-14","Department for Education","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if her Department will publish the guidance it has issued to schools and colleges for the implementation of Prevent strategy activities for all age groups.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19487","19487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436730","2015-12-14","Cabinet Office","2015-12-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will take steps to ensure equitable application of the Freedom of Information Act 2000 across all UK exam boards.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19291","19291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436731","2015-12-14","Department for Education","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many parents have taken their children off the school roll after being threatened with prosecution for their child truanting in (a) academies and (b) local authority schools in the last three years.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19292","19292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436732","2015-12-14","Department for Education","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans the Government has to increase the study of Japanese in schools.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19314","19314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436733","2015-12-14","Department for Education","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when she intends to meet the hon. Member for North Herefordshire to discuss Brockhampton school.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19351","19351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436734","2015-12-14","Department for Education","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the effect of the National Funding Formula on (a) schools, (b) teachers and (c) pupils in Liverpool.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19389","19389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436735","2015-12-14","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what support her Department provides for community solar projects.","Biography information for Meg Hillier","Meg Hillier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19360","19360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436736","2015-12-14","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment she has made of the implications for her Department's policies of the report published in December 2015 by the Global Carbon Project on trends in greenhouse gas emissions.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19346","19346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436737","2015-12-14","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what (a) presentation and (b) other documentary contribution her Department has made to the World Climate Summit held in Paris alongside the UN COP21.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19298","19298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436738","2015-12-14","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what criteria will need to be satisfied for sites to qualify for inclusion in a list of potential new build nuclear sites for the development of a small modular reactor.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19459","19459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436739","2015-12-14","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether Trawsfynydd former nuclear power station site in North Wales qualifies for inclusion in a list of possible small nuclear reactor sites in the UK.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19460","19460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436740","2015-12-14","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if she will add further sites for the development of small modular reactor technology in the UK in addition to those identified in the 2009 strategic site assessment.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19466","19466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436741","2015-12-14","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, with reference to the announcement by the Prime Minister at the UN climate change conference in Paris on 30 November, how much from the public purse has been allocated to Mission Innovation to accelerate clean energy investment and innovation.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19408","19408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436742","2015-12-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what proposals she plans to submit to the European Union Council of Fisheries Ministers on 14 and 15 December 2015 to safeguard fishing effort and quotas in terms of Cod, Haddock, Hake and Nephrops in the Irish Sea (Area VIIA); and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19411","19411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436743","2015-12-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what food security planning her Department has undertaken for the UK in times of conflict, crisis and war situations.","Biography information for Dr Liam Fox","Dr Liam Fox","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19453","19453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436744","2015-12-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether the animal licensing review will include a review of how to tackle internet sales of rare animals.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19500","19500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436745","2015-12-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much of the £1.7 billion of capital spending on flood defences between 2010 and 2015 was disbursed in each of those years.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19493","19493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436746","2015-12-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment she has made of the risk to the UK of (a) rabies, (b) the Echinococcus multilocularis tapeworm and (c) other zoonotic diseases.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19290","19290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436747","2015-12-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what review her Department has conducted on flood protection measures since the recent floods in Cumbria and Lancashire.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19295","19295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436748","2015-12-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will bring forward legislative proposals to require enforcers of the Pet Travel Scheme to carry out visual checks on dogs entering the UK.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19293","19293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436749","2015-12-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will review sentencing guidelines for serious animal cruelty offences to ensure that the gravity of offences is adequately reflected.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19321","19321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436750","2015-12-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of the Pet Travel Scheme Regulations.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19378","19378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436751","2015-12-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment she has made of the efficacy of existing legislation to stop the illegal importation of puppies into the UK.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19386","19386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436752","2015-12-14","Department for International Development","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department takes to ensure that UK funding to Nigeria reaches the people most in need.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19435","19435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436753","2015-12-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions his Department has had with the government of Romania on (a) improving media freedom and media pluralism in that country and (b) the activities of (i) Central Media Enterprise, (ii) Adrian Sârbu and (iii) Ronald Lauder.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19436","19436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436754","2015-12-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of progress in building security in Nigeria and the neighbouring countries which are often entered by Boco Haram; and what assessment he has made of the adequacy of funding by the UK and EU for this purpose.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19432","19432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436755","2015-12-14","Department for International Development","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assistance the UK has provided to the government of Nigeria for (a) development of the education system in that country and (b) promotion of education aimed at countering extremist ideologies; and what support the UK provides to the government of Nigeria in monitoring what is taught in madrassas in that country.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19433","19433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436756","2015-12-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what support the UK has provided to interfaith peace-building initiatives in Nigeria; and what assessment he has made of the outcomes of such initiatives.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19434","19434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436757","2015-12-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what meetings officials in his Department have had with their Iranian counterparts on the detention of Kamal Foroughi in Evin Prison.","Biography information for Oliver Dowden","Oliver Dowden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19374","19374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436758","2015-12-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his counterpart in the government of Saudi Arabia on the death sentence for Ashraf Fayadh.","Biography information for Dr Tania Mathias","Dr Tania Mathias","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19362","19362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436759","2015-12-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effect of continuing violence by paramilitaries in Colombia on the progress of peace talks in that country.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19348","19348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436760","2015-12-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 5 November 2015 to Question 13962, when he most recently made representations to his Ethiopian counterpart on the detention of Andargachew Tsege.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19315","19315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436761","2015-12-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his international counterparts on forced disappearances in Syria.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19311","19311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436762","2015-12-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his international counterparts on establishing a regime of sanctions against nations and other entities which trade with Daesh.","Biography information for Mr David Jones","Mr David Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19308","19308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436763","2015-12-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government is taking through the UN to tackle international recruitment of people for terrorist activity in Syria and Iraq.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19499","19499"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436764","2015-12-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to promote international support for and defence of religious minority communities in the Middle East.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19502","19502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436765","2015-12-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the rules and regulations are on the use, style and designation in the UK accorded to dual nationals or nationals of Commonwealth realms who are recipients of a knighthood in any of those realms; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19413","19413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436766","2015-12-14","Department of Health","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of the total number of recipients of NHS bursaries in each of the last five years; how much has been so allocated; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19479","19479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436767","2015-12-14","Department of Health","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many nurses were employed in each NHS region in the latest month for which figures are available.","Biography information for Heidi Alexander","Heidi Alexander","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19480","19480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436768","2015-12-14","Department of Health","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many nurses were employed in each Agenda for Change band in the latest month for which figures are available.","Biography information for Heidi Alexander","Heidi Alexander","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19481","19481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436769","2015-12-14","Department for Education","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to help prevent loneliness and social isolation among younger people.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19482","19482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436770","2015-12-14","Department of Health","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is take to ensure that the £22 billion NHS efficiency savings proposed in the NHS Five-Year Forward View, published in October 2014, do not affect the quality of services which people with Parkinson's Disease require to assist them with their condition.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19483","19483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436771","2015-12-14","Department of Health","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make it his policy to collect information centrally on how many doctors and nurses have been signed off work as a result of stress and other mental illness.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19445","19445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436772","2015-12-14","Department of Health","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make it his policy to collect information centrally on the proportion of people who received consultant-led mental health treatment within 18 weeks of referral.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19446","19446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436773","2015-12-14","Department of Health","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make it his policy to collect information centrally on how much clinical commissioning groups are overspending on mental health.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19437","19437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436774","2015-12-14","Department of Health","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make it his policy to collect information centrally on the proportion of the mental health budget that is spent on forensic psychiatry.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19447","19447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436775","2015-12-14","Department of Health","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department and NHS England are taking to ensure that autism diagnosis waiting times for (a) children and (b) adults meet NICE guidance (a) in Halton and (ii) nationally.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19405","19405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436776","2015-12-14","Department of Health","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans the NHS has to make use of (a) information technology and (b) informatics to improve the delivery of healthcare.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19403","19403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436777","2015-12-14","Department of Health","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to work with other governments and international NGOs to increase stem cell and bone marrow donor registration globally.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19418","19418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436778","2015-12-14","Department of Health","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make it his policy to collect information centrally on how many local authorities have suicide prevention groups.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19438","19438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436779","2015-12-14","Department of Health","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make it his policy to collect information centrally on how many local authorities have suicide prevention strategies.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19439","19439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436780","2015-12-14","Department of Health","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of the total number of student nurses in England and Wales in each of the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19467","19467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436781","2015-12-14","Department of Health","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make it his policy to collect information centrally on how many children and young people are admitted to hospital due to mental health problems.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19440","19440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436782","2015-12-14","Department of Health","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make it his policy to collect information centrally on how much local clinical commissioning groups spend on independent sector providers.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19441","19441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436783","2015-12-14","Department of Health","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make it his policy to collect information centrally on how many mental health beds are available on specific dates.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19442","19442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436784","2015-12-14","Department of Health","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make it his policy to collect information centrally on how many specialist midwives have been trained in mental health.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19443","19443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436785","2015-12-14","Department of Health","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make it his policy to collect information centrally on how many people diagnosed with a mental health condition receive a custodial sentence.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19444","19444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436786","2015-12-14","Department of Health","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what support in (a) monetary terms and (b) skills his Department provides for research into motor neurone disease.","Biography information for Michelle Donelan","Michelle Donelan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19410","19410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436787","2015-12-14","Department of Health","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with Health Education England to ensure that the number of speech and language therapy student commissions for 2016-17 is sufficient to meet demand.","Biography information for Geraint Davies","Geraint Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19423","19423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436788","2015-12-14","Department of Health","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will implement the recommendations made in the Independent Cancer Taskforce's new Cancer Strategy.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19407","19407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436789","2015-12-14","Department of Health","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when the Government plans to undertake its public consultation on whether or not homeopathic products should be available through NHS prescriptions; and what estimate he has made of the likely cost of that consultation to the public purse.","Biography information for David Tredinnick","David Tredinnick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19448","19448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436790","2015-12-14","Department of Health","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to promote compliance by clinical commissioning groups with the NICE Quality Standard on Autism.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19396","19396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436791","2015-12-14","Department of Health","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people who died by suicide were social security claimants in (a) the UK and (b) Scotland in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19324","19324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436792","2015-12-14","Department of Health","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress has been made on the roll-out of liaison and diversion services; and what timetable he has set for completion of the business case for completing the national roll-out of those services.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19313","19313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436793","2015-12-14","Department of Health","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what reports NHS England has produced on progress in achieving parity of esteem for mental health.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19357","19357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436794","2015-12-14","Department of Health","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to raise awareness of female genital mutilation among mental health professionals.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19355","19355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436795","2015-12-14","Department of Health","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information his Department holds on the proportion of people identified as having experienced child abuse who are diagnosed with a mental health condition as a young person or adult.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19356","19356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436796","2015-12-14","Department of Health","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many and what proportion of clinical commissioning groups have (a) had their transformation plans approved by NHS England and received funding and (b) been told their transformation plans need further work.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19337","19337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436797","2015-12-14","Department of Health","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect of the Equality Act 2010 on the care of older adult mental health patients.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19338","19338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436798","2015-12-14","Department of Health","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many instances of readmission to inpatient psychiatric units there were in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19339","19339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436799","2015-12-14","Department of Health","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many specialist inpatient services for older adult mental health patients have closed in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19340","19340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436800","2015-12-14","Department of Health","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with mental health charities on the sections of the Editors' Code of Practice that cover reporting on mental health and suicide.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19341","19341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436801","2015-12-14","Department of Health","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the spend per head of population was on mental health in (a) England, (b) the North West and (c) Lancashire in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19376","19376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436802","2015-12-14","Department of Health","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make it his policy to allocate enough funding to cover predicted changes in the cost of cancer care beyond treatment.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19391","19391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436803","2015-12-14","Department of Health","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much his Department and each of its agencies and non-departmental public bodies plans to spend on (a) Christmas cards, (b) postage of Christmas cards, (c) Christmas parties and (d) Christmas decorations and trees in 2015.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19369","19369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436804","2015-12-14","Department of Health","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much money will be devolved to clinical commissioning groups (CCGs) to coincide with the transfer of obesity surgery commissioning responsibilities from NHS England to CCGs in April 2016; and what NHS England spent on such services in (a) 2014-15 and (b) 2015-16.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19372","19372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436805","2015-12-14","Department of Health","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of whether clinical commissioning groups  are fully prepared to assume active commissioning of tier 4 obesity from April 2016.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19373","19373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436806","2015-12-14","Department of Health","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the annual cost is of the health needs of UK thalidomide survivors.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19349","19349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436807","2015-12-14","Department of Health","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to improve services for people with coeliac disease; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Johnson","Gareth Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19353","19353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436808","2015-12-15","Ministry of Justice","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been convicted and given mandatory sentences for two knife crime convictions in the last three years.","Biography information for Mr David Burrowes","Mr David Burrowes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19370","19370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436809","2015-12-14","Home Office","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will assess the practicality of putting in place standard blocks to child pornography on the internet similar to those obtained by members of the BPI British Recorded Music Industry Ltd on material where access would cause commercial damage.","Biography information for Derek Thomas","Derek Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19327","19327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436810","2015-12-14","Home Office","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the range of waiting times is for the return of Disclosure and Barring Service documentation for applications in Dorset.","Biography information for Michael Tomlinson","Michael Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19309","19309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436811","2015-12-14","Home Office","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make representations to the Essex Police and Crime Commissioner to (a) extend the consultation period for closures of police stations in Essex and (b) ensure frontline policing is not reduced following proposed police station closures.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19306","19306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436812","2015-12-14","Home Office","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 7 December 2015 to Question 17661, if she will recompense spousal visa applicants using the premium service but not receiving a determination on the day of application; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19475","19475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436813","2015-12-14","Home Office","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 7 December 2015 to Question 17662, if she will recompense postal applicants for a spousal visa whose application is not determined within eight weeks; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19474","19474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436814","2015-12-14","Home Office","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, on what basis Action Fraud determines which reported frauds to pursue for investigation; and whether the amount defrauded influences such decisions.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19468","19468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436815","2015-12-14","Home Office","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what Action Fraud's budget has been in each year of its existence; how many cases it has pursued in each such year; and what proportion of such cases involved cybercrime.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19469","19469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436816","2015-12-14","Home Office","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if her Department will publish all guidance it has issued to schools and colleges for the implementation of PREVENT strategy activities for all age groups.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19496","19496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436817","2015-12-14","Department for International Development","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assistance the Government is providing to countries in West Africa to reduce the chances of Ebola returning to areas from which it has been eradicated.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19501","19501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436818","2015-12-14","Department for International Development","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, which charities her Department has funded to assist people affected by the Syria crisis since 2012.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19476","19476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436819","2015-12-14","Department for International Development","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the extent of electoral fraud in Ghana; and whether her Department has participated in election observation in Ghana in the past and what plans it has to do so in future.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19416","19416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436820","2015-12-14","Department for International Development","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to protect the welfare of vulnerable older people in developing countries.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19329","19329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436821","2015-12-14","Department for International Development","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how the £1 billion Ross Fund will be spent.","Biography information for Fabian Hamilton","Fabian Hamilton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19383","19383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436822","2015-12-14","Department for International Development","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much of the £1 billion over five years for use by the Ross Fund in conjunction with the Gates Foundation is UK Aid funded.","Biography information for Fabian Hamilton","Fabian Hamilton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19384","19384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436823","2015-12-14","Ministry of Justice","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the recent Inspectorate report of HM Prison Maghaberry.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19379","19379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436824","2015-12-14","Ministry of Justice","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 8 December 2015 to Question 18492, what assessment he has made of the level of compliance in magistrates' and crown courts with the procedures set out in that Answer for seeking confirmation of defendants' income.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19335","19335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436825","2015-12-14","Department of Health","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 7 December 2015 to Question 18596, if he will make it his policy to collect data on the proportion of the prison population who have mental health problems and identify as LGBT.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19358","19358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436826","2015-12-14","Ministry of Justice","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many magistrates there were on 1 April (a) 1989, (b) 1994, (c) 2000, (d) 2005, (e) 2010, (f) 2014 and (g) 2015.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19303","19303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436827","2015-12-14","Ministry of Justice","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prison officers who have received (a) severance and (b) redundancy packages since May 2010 have subsequently been re-employed as prison officers.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19304","19304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436828","2015-12-14","Ministry of Justice","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the monthly cost is of (a) each court building which has been closed but not disposed of since May 2010 and (b) the 91 courts considered for closure in his Department's recent consultation on that subject.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19301","19301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436829","2015-12-14","Ministry of Justice","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which contracts worth more than £5 million his Department has signed since 1 September 2014; with which organisations such contracts have been signed; what the purpose was of each contract; what the (a) annual and (b) total cost is of each such contract; and what the length is of each such contract.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19302","19302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436830","2015-12-14","Ministry of Justice","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the total cost to the public purse has been of legislating for and implementing the criminal courts change to date.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19486","19486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436831","2015-12-14","Ministry of Justice","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 8 December 2015 to Question 18370, on criminal proceedings, how many (a) men and (b) women make up the 9,578 figure; and what the sex of the lead defendant was in each case.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19395","19395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436832","2015-12-14","Ministry of Justice","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the status is of each prison building and site for prisons closed since May 2010.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19421","19421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436833","2015-12-14","Ministry of Justice","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisons allow children to take school books in with them when visiting.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19473","19473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436834","2015-12-14","Ministry of Justice","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisons have children's play areas.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19472","19472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436835","2015-12-15","Ministry of Justice","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what his plans are for the future ownership of HM Prison Manchester; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Graham Stringer","Graham Stringer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19498","19498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436836","2015-12-14","Ministry of Justice","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many forced marriage prevention orders have been issued in West Yorkshire since the Forced Marriage (Civil Protection) Act 2007 came into force.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19494","19494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436837","2015-12-14","Ministry of Justice","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 27 October 2015 to Question HL2604, what the cost to the public purse is of salary, expenses and bonuses of the 3.5 full-time staff who worked under the JSi brand.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19495","19495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436838","2015-12-14","Ministry of Justice","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of the National Offender Management Service budget in (a) staffing resources, (b) allocation of civil service time and (c) funding was set aside for the operation of Just Solutions International throughout its lifespan.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19452","19452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436839","2015-12-14","Ministry of Justice","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many times the National Tactical Response Group (NTRG) has been called out in each month in 2015; and to which prison the NTRG was called out in each case.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19422","19422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436840","2015-12-14","Ministry of Justice","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 9 December 2015 to Question 18367, what length of sentence was handed down to each offender convicted of offences involving inciting terrorism in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19424","19424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436841","2015-12-14","Department for Transport","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what response his Department has made to requests for more rail travel paths from North Wales to Manchester Airport.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19450","19450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436842","2015-12-14","Department for Transport","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent representations he has received on rail paths from North Wales to Manchester Airport.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19451","19451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436843","2015-12-16","Department for Transport","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 8 December 2015 to Question 18162, if he will place in the Library a summary of the internal findings following his Department's consideration of the Quality Contract Scheme Board report.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19489","19489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436844","2015-12-16","Department for Transport","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 4 December 2015 to Question 18160, on lorry parking, if he will update the House on his Department's progress on this issue once the initial discussions are complete.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19488","19488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436845","2015-12-14","Department for Transport","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what his plans are for the Government's 49 per cent stake in NATS; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19420","19420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436846","2015-12-14","Department for Transport","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to page 2 of the Government response to the Fifth Report from the Transport Committee, Session 2013-14, on Access to transport for disabled people, HC870, whether he plans to review his Department's Inclusive Mobility guidance in 2015.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19401","19401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436847","2015-12-14","Department for Transport","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if his Department will estimate the number of passengers from North Wales and Cheshire who are projected to use Manchester Airport in (a) 2015, (b) 2020 and (c) 2025.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19300","19300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436848","2015-12-14","Department for Transport","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate his Department has made of the number of passengers using Manchester Airport in (a) 2015, (b) 2020 and (c) 2025.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19299","19299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436849","2015-12-14","Department for Transport","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if his Department will estimate the number of passengers from North Wales and Cheshire who are projected to use Liverpool Airport in (a) 2015, (b) 2020 and (c) 2025.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19289","19289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436850","2015-12-14","Department for Transport","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if his Department will make a comparative assessment of rail links to (a) Cumbria and (b) North Wales from Manchester Airport.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19307","19307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436851","2015-12-14","Department for Transport","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make it his policy to include a commitment to constructing safe paths alongside busy roads in rural areas in the forthcoming National Road Safety Strategy to improve cycle safety.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19316","19316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436852","2015-12-14","Department for Transport","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the timetable is for the replacement of pacer trains that form part of the Northern franchise deal with Arriva Rail North Limited.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19363","19363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436853","2015-12-14","Department for Transport","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make an assessment of the implications for his policy and guidance of the 13 day closure of the Sudbury to Marks Tey railway line in November 2015 as a result of leaf damage to diesel rolling stock; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for James Cartlidge","James Cartlidge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19336","19336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436854","2015-12-14","Department for Transport","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what upgrades are planned for Newmarket railway station.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19319","19319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436855","2015-12-14","Department for Transport","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with Network Rail and Suffolk County Council on increasing the number of services stopping at Newmarket railway station.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19320","19320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436856","2015-12-16","Department for Transport","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the cost to the public purse was of the negotiations on the TransPennine Express rail franchise agreement.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19325","19325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436857","2015-12-16","Department for Transport","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the cost to the public purse was of the negotiations on the Northern rail franchise agreement.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19326","19326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436858","2015-12-14","Department for Transport","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what funding his Department plans to allocate to (a) increasing the number of journeys undertaken by bicycle and (b) reducing the number of cyclists killed or seriously injured on roads over the next five years.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19352","19352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436859","2015-12-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much will be made available in additional discretionary housing payments for people in supported accommodation in each financial year from 2018-19 to 2020-21.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19364","19364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436860","2015-12-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to support parents of babies who spend time in neonatal care; if he will take steps to extend the statutory maternity pay of premature babies; and if he will estimate the cost to the public purse of such steps.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19350","19350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436861","2015-12-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the (a) housing benefit claimant count and (b) average weekly housing benefit award is for tenants in supported accommodation in each (i) county, (ii) region, (iii) local authority and (iv) valuation office agency area.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19365","19365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436862","2015-12-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what procedures the Child Support Agency (CSA) has to ensure that it takes account of a person's assets as well as their income when calculating child maintenance payments; and if he will make it his policy to require the CSA to take into account the value of retained profit of any company controlled by the non-resident parent when calculating child maintenance payments from that parent.","Biography information for Alex Chalk","Alex Chalk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19354","19354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436863","2015-12-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans he has to make decisions about changes to housing benefit entitlements for tenants of supported accommodation before the completion of research in this area which has been commissioned by the Department.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19390","19390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436864","2015-12-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of changes to the severe disability premium on young carers.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19359","19359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436865","2015-12-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether injured army veterans are exempt from personal independence payment assessments.","Biography information for Angela Crawley","Angela Crawley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19406","19406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436866","2015-12-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the level of change of housing benefit for tenants in supported accommodation as a result of changes to housing benefit announced in the Autumn Statement 2015.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19394","19394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436867","2015-12-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effect of changes to the number of people in the work-related activity group on people with restrictive medical conditions; and what alternative measures he plans to put in place to assist such people.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19484","19484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436868","2015-12-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether the application of local housing allowance rates for housing benefit paid in the social sector will take into account core rent and housing service charge elements.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19464","19464"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436869","2015-12-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the finding of the report, Halving the Gap, published by Mencap in December 2015, that the proposed change in employment and support allowance to claimants in the work-related activity group is likely to move those claimants further away from the labour market rather than closer.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19497","19497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436870","2015-12-14","Department for Education","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to ensure that people under the age of 16 are paid for employment; and what assessment she has made of the adequacy of legal protection of children under the age of 16 who are employed.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19409","19409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438469","2015-12-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to encourage business start-ups and entrepreneurship.","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 902720","902720"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438470","2015-12-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent progress he has made on reducing the proportion of 16 to 24 year olds not in education, employment or training.","Biography information for Michael Tomlinson","Michael Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 902716","902716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438471","2015-12-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will ensure that the Green Investment Bank continues to pursue its principal objectives after its privatisation.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 902718","902718"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/438472","2015-12-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to increase the number of apprentices.","Biography information for Chris White","Chris White","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 902719","902719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436126","2015-12-10","Ministry of Justice","2015-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prosecutions for dishonest concealment of material information under Section 397 of the Financial Services and Markets Act 2000 there have been since 2008.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19198","19198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436127","2015-12-15","Department for Transport","2015-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many prosecutions there have been for tachograph violations in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19163","19163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436128","2015-12-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the time needed to devolve the adult skills budget; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19167","19167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436129","2015-12-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will set a target for apprenticeship achievements over this Parliament.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19168","19168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436130","2015-12-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what his most recent estimate is of the proportion of people in apprenticeships who have a disability.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19155","19155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436131","2015-12-14","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what the level of take-up by (a) micro, (b) small and (c) medium-sized enterprises has been of the cyber essentials programme.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19259","19259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436132","2015-12-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the costs of implementing the Teaching Excellence Framework.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19283","19283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436133","2015-12-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the implications for the financial position of students of offering loans to 19 to 23 year olds who are undertaking further education.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19087","19087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436134","2015-12-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on students of replacing maintenance grants with loans.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19088","19088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436135","2015-12-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the effect of the National Living Wage on wage growth in Calder Valley.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19092","19092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436136","2015-12-14","Cabinet Office","2015-12-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the pay bands are for special advisers; and how many there are in each band, in each Department.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19265","19265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436138","2015-12-14","Cabinet Office","2015-12-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many special advisers there are in each Department.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19266","19266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436139","2015-12-14","Cabinet Office","2015-12-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the cost is of special advisers in each Department.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19264","19264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436140","2015-12-10","Cabinet Office","2015-12-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people of what age and sex have died as a result of volatile substance abuse in each region of England and Wales in each year since 2013.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19244","19244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436141","2015-12-10","Cabinet Office","2015-12-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people of what age and sex have died as a result of the abuse of nitrous oxide in each region of England and Wales in each year since 2013.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19245","19245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436142","2015-12-10","HM Treasury","2015-12-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent steps the Government has taken to reduce the incidence of money-laundering in the UK.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19232","19232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436143","2015-12-10","HM Treasury","2015-12-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he expects the new income tax powers for Wales announced in the Comprehensive Spending Review to be available to Welsh Ministers.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19251","19251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436144","2015-12-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will publish his Department's analysis of the effects of proposed changes to business rates retention and the local government grant on the income of local authorities.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19222","19222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436145","2015-12-14","HM Treasury","2015-12-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the Autumn Statement of 25 November 2015, Official Report, column 1361, what the evidential basis is for the statement that an investment of £800 million to fight tax evasion will return almost 10 times that amount in additional tax.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19223","19223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436146","2015-12-14","HM Treasury","2015-12-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the purchase of buy-to-let property by a person whose current residence derives only from their job will be deemed as a second home for tax purposes under the new Rules on Stamp Duty coming into force in April 2016.","Biography information for Dr Tania Mathias","Dr Tania Mathias","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19272","19272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436147","2015-12-14","HM Treasury","2015-12-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make an assessment on the financial effect on the UK manufacturing sector of reductions to (a) capital allowances and (b) corporation tax since 2010.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19258","19258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436148","2015-12-14","HM Treasury","2015-12-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to paragraph 3.23 of the Spending Review and Autumn Statement 2015, what assessment he has made of the effect of removing entitlement to social investment tax relief from community energy organisations; and what consultation he undertook on this issue.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19281","19281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436149","2015-12-10","HM Treasury","2015-12-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans he has to obtain a reduction or removal of VAT on children's headstones and planters in cemeteries; and if he will donate the proceeds of such VAT to charities aiding parents and other family members of children who have died.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19254","19254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436150","2015-12-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to paragraph 3.15 of the Spending Review and Autumn Statement 2015, what steps he plans to take to address the effects of regional variation in council tax revenue on funding for social care under the proposed council tax precept for social care.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19152","19152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436151","2015-12-14","HM Treasury","2015-12-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what legal and regulatory obligations apply to members of the public identified by banks as Politically Exposed Persons; and what information his Department holds on how such people are identified by banks.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19177","19177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436152","2015-12-14","HM Treasury","2015-12-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, on which date his Department announced the creation of each enterprise zone in (a) urban and (b) rural areas of each region; and what plans he has to create new enterprise zones in what (i) rural and (ii) urban areas.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19178","19178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436153","2015-12-10","HM Treasury","2015-12-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of (a) the number of investors who lost money in the collapse of the Connaught Fund and (b) their combined loss.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19197","19197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436154","2015-12-10","HM Treasury","2015-12-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, which designated professional bodies have professional indemnity insurance requirements compliant with clause 2.3 of the Financial Conduct Authority handbook PRU-INV sch13.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19196","19196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436155","2015-12-10","HM Treasury","2015-12-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he is satisfied that the Financial Conduct Authority's minimum professional indemnity insurance requirements for Independent Financial Advisers provide investors with adequate protection for medium and long-term investments.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19195","19195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436156","2015-12-10","HM Treasury","2015-12-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what representations he has received on the provisions in the Financial Conduct Authority handbook IPRU-INV sch13 which allows independent financial advisers and insurers to retrospectively exclude failed schemes from an IFA's professional indemnity insurance.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19199","19199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436157","2015-12-10","HM Treasury","2015-12-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he became aware that Connaught Fund investors pursuing compensation awarded by the Financial Ombudsman Service are having their professional indemnity claims rejected because the Financial Conduct Authority handbook IPRU-INV sch13 allows independent financial advisers to operate with insurer-imposed restrictions on their insurance that exclude schemes the adviser had already recommended to clients.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19200","19200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436158","2015-12-10","HM Treasury","2015-12-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, on how many occasions the Financial Conduct Authority and the Financial Services Authority used powers under Section 382 of the Financial Services and Markets Act 2000 to compel a registered firm to compensative investors for losses incurred as a result of that firm's breaches of its statutory obligations; and whether he is satisfied that the legislation is being implemented effectively.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19201","19201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436159","2015-12-14","HM Treasury","2015-12-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to paragraph 2.10 of the Spending Review and Autumn Statement 2015, if he will publish the analysis and methodology used to estimate that the proposed apprenticeship levy will raise £3 billion by 2020-21.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19084","19084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436160","2015-12-10","HM Treasury","2015-12-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he plans to ring-fence the capital and resource elements of the science budget settlement announced in the Spending Review and Autumn Statement 2015.","Biography information for Carol Monaghan","Carol Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19182","19182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436161","2015-12-10","HM Treasury","2015-12-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he last met the Financial Conduct Authority to discuss how its uses its powers under section 382 of the Financial Services and Markets Act 2000 to compel a registered firm to compensate investors for losses incurred as a result of that firm's breaches of its statutory obligations; and what the outcome of that meeting was.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19202","19202"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436162","2015-12-10","HM Treasury","2015-12-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the number of and outcomes achieved by (a) Connaught Fund investors and (b) other investors who have sought payment from the Financial Services Compensation Scheme when their independent financial adviser has declared a default on an award of compensation by the Financial Ombudsman's Service; and if he will publish that assessment.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19204","19204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436163","2015-12-10","HM Treasury","2015-12-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he is satisfied by the proportion of Connaught Fund investors who received the full level of compensation awarded to them.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19191","19191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436164","2015-12-10","HM Treasury","2015-12-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will encourage the Financial Conduct Authority to bring its investigation into the Connaught Fund to an early conclusion; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19203","19203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436165","2015-12-10","HM Treasury","2015-12-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he last received advice on the adequacy of the Financial Conduct Authority's requirements for professional indemnity to underpin advice given by independent financial advisers; and what action he took in response to that advice.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19192","19192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436166","2015-12-10","HM Treasury","2015-12-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he was first told that Capital Financial Managers Limited knew by September 2009 that investors' funds were exposed to risks not provided for in the information memorandum for the Connaught Fund.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19193","19193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436167","2015-12-10","HM Treasury","2015-12-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what representations he has received on differences in the (a) criteria used by the Financial Ombudsman's Service and Financial Services Compensation Scheme to determine cases and (b) determinations reached by those bodies.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19194","19194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436168","2015-12-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what progress he has made on plans to allow local councils to retain business rates.","Biography information for Michael Tomlinson","Michael Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19142","19142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436169","2015-12-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to paragraph 1.149 of the Spending Review and Autumn Statement 2015, on what basis the total amount allocated to local authorities for funding temporary accommodation has been calculated.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19078","19078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436170","2015-12-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what information his Department holds on the number of (a) local authorities and (b) housing associations which had planned, prior to the announcement in paragraph 1.125 of the Spending Review and Autumn Statement 2015, to raise rents above any of the relevant local housing allowance rates between 2016 and 2020.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19079","19079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436171","2015-12-10","Department for Transport","2015-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what guidance his Department provides for local authorities on the administration of blue badge disabled parking arrangements.","Biography information for Michael Tomlinson","Michael Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19143","19143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436172","2015-12-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what help his Department will provide to assist local authorities to resettle Syrian refugees over the next five years.","Biography information for Michael Tomlinson","Michael Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19144","19144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436173","2015-12-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what recent steps his Department has taken to help councils to house refugees.","Biography information for Michael Tomlinson","Michael Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19145","19145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436174","2015-12-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, which Ministers of his Department attended events to celebrate Chanukah in (a) 2014 and (b) 2015.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19174","19174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436175","2015-12-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether the Greater Manchester Life Science Enterprise Zone will cover the Salford and Eccles constituency.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19166","19166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436176","2015-12-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what his policy is on creation of new unitary authorities.","Biography information for Mr Peter Bone","Mr Peter Bone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19212","19212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436177","2015-12-14","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that landlords in the private rented sector comply with the requirement for properties to be a minimum of energy efficiency rating E by April 2017.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr   Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19268","19268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436178","2015-12-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he plans to take to require social landlords to improve the energy efficiency of their housing stock.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr   Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19267","19267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436179","2015-12-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 14 September 2015 from the Parliamentary Under-Secretary for Communities and Local Government, on Brownfield Land, Official Report, column 742, when further details of the £1 billion brownfield regeneration fund will be announced; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19236","19236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436180","2015-12-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what financial support his Department plans to provide to local authorities to resettle Syrian refugees in years two to five of the vulnerable persons relocation scheme.","Biography information for Michael Tomlinson","Michael Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19243","19243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436181","2015-12-10","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department is taking to work with sports clubs to discourage young people from taking performance enhancing drugs.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19238","19238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436182","2015-12-10","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent progress he has made on the delivery of superfast broadband in the Yorkshire and Humber region.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19239","19239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436183","2015-12-10","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the prevalence of the use of performance drugs among young people in sport.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19237","19237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436184","2015-12-14","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what proportion of (a) homes and (b) businesses in Wales have access to superfast broadband.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19273","19273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436185","2015-12-14","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what proportion of (a) homes and (b) businesses in Scotland have access to superfast broadband.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19274","19274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436186","2015-12-14","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what proportion of (a) homes and (b) businesses in England have access to superfast broadband.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19275","19275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436187","2015-12-14","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 8 December 2015 to Question 18148, if he will provide a breakdown of public appointments by his Department its executive agencies and non-governmental bodies by (a) gender, (b) ethnicity, (c) socio-economic group, (d) sexual orientation and (e) disability status in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19257","19257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436188","2015-12-14","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what proportion of (a) homes and (b) businesses in Northern Ireland have access to superfast broadband.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19276","19276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436189","2015-12-14","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 9 November 2015 to Question 13628, whether the £230 million spend incurred by BT is an addition to the £683 million recorded as state aid receipts in BT's accounts.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19214","19214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436190","2015-12-14","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, which Ministers of his Department attended events to celebrate Chanukah in (a) 2014 and (b) 2015.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19173","19173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436191","2015-12-14","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of grassroots sports funding; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19124","19124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436192","2015-12-14","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 7 December 2015 to Question 18388, when he expects to publish the results of the Government's evaluation of the effects of ending unsupervised stakes above £50 on fixed odds betting terminals in betting shops.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19215","19215"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436193","2015-12-10","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether the Government (a) has made or (b) plans to make any contribution to the cost of (i) the construction and (ii) the running of the National Tennis Centre at Roehampton.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19159","19159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436194","2015-12-10","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will take steps to ensure that the Deaflympics are recognised as equal to the Olympic and Paralympic Games.","Biography information for Lucy Frazer","Lucy Frazer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19190","19190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436195","2015-12-10","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether he has had discussions with the London Legacy Development Corporation about EU state aid rules and West Ham United Football Club's occupancy of the Olympic Stadium.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19080","19080"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436196","2015-12-14","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what research his Department has conducted or commissioned on the economic benefit of major sports teams to local economies; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19083","19083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436197","2015-12-10","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will make an assessment of the effectiveness of the self-exclusion pilot schemes introduced by bookmakers in Medway and Glasgow.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19094","19094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436198","2015-12-10","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, when the next Triennial Review of Gaming Machine Stake and Prize Limits will begin.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19093","19093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436199","2015-12-10","Ministry of Defence","2015-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that there is sufficient lift capacity to airlift the two new strike brigades to theatres of operation.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19099","19099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436200","2015-12-10","Ministry of Defence","2015-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what representations the UK has made to other NATO member states on committing two per cent of their gross domestic product to defence.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19098","19098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/436201","2015-12-10","Ministry of Defence","2015-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to paragraph 4.62 in the Strategic Defence and Security Review, published on 23 November 2015, what areas his Department plans to sell to reduce the size of the built estate by 30 per cent; and by what process those areas were chosen.","Biography information for Steven Paterson","Steven Paterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 19188","19188"
