"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521999","2016-06-06","HM Treasury","2016-05-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, on what dates in each of the last three months officials of his Department have discussed the UK's plans for an exemption of VAT on sanitary products with the European Commission.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38611","38611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522000","2016-06-06","HM Treasury","2016-05-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will publish all correspondence between his Department and the European Commission on the UK's request to introduce a zero rate of VAT on women's sanitary products.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38612","38612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522001","2016-06-06","HM Treasury","2016-05-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, on what date he expects  the planned removal of VAT on women's sanitary products to take effect.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38610","38610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522002","2016-06-06","HM Treasury","2016-05-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the Answer of 12 May 2016 to Question 36479, to where the £10 million funding for the multi-agency taskforce has been allocated; and what proportion of that funding has not yet been allocated.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38701","38701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522003","2016-06-06","HM Treasury","2016-05-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to page 148 of his Department's analysis: the long-term economic impact of EU membership and the alternatives, Cm 9250, if he will set out which EU regulations are to be reformed to cause an increase in UK gross domestic product of four per cent after 15 years.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38690","38690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522004","2016-06-06","HM Treasury","2016-05-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the soft drinks industry levy on levels of employment; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38692","38692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522005","2016-06-06","HM Treasury","2016-05-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he has made an estimate of the potential effect of the soft drinks industry levy on the (a) consumer price index and (b) cost of uprating index-linked benefits; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38693","38693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522006","2016-06-06","HM Treasury","2016-05-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the Answer of 12 February 2016 to Question 26015, when he plans to undertake a comprehensive review of the performance of HM Revenue and Customs in dealing with correspondence and telephone calls from members of the public.","Biography information for Tommy Sheppard","Tommy Sheppard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38687","38687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522007","2016-06-06","HM Treasury","2016-05-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the Answer of 2 February 2016 to Question 24013, if he will publish HM Revenue and Customs call handling data for (a) London and (b) each region of the UK.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38688","38688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522008","2016-06-06","Ministry of Justice","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what plans he has to bring forward legislative proposals to make banks and large companies criminally responsible for employees who embezzle funds, launder money and evade tax.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38677","38677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522009","2016-06-06","HM Treasury","2016-05-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when the Government plans to bring forward legislative proposals to comply with the policy of the European Court of Justice of 4 June 2015 on the rate of VAT on energy saving materials, Case C-161/14 Commission v United Kingdom.","Biography information for John Redwood","John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38626","38626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522010","2016-06-06","HM Treasury","2016-05-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the potential implications of the EU Economic and Monetary Affairs Committee's decision of 27 May 2016 to introduce European Taxpayer Identification Numbers for the administration of tax in the UK.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38668","38668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522011","2016-06-06","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the benefits of international students at the University of Sunderland to the economy of Sunderland in the last five years.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38878","38878"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522012","2016-06-06","HM Treasury","2016-05-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, who in Government is responsible for overseeing the cross-agency taskforce set up to examine the Panama Papers.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38863","38863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522013","2016-06-06","HM Treasury","2016-05-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, which government department has responsibility for the cross-agency taskforce established to examine the Panama Papers.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38862","38862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522014","2016-06-06","HM Treasury","2016-05-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the HM Revenue and Customs publication, entitled Tax Credits Statistics on non-UK EEA Nationals, of 22 February 2016, how many (a) in-work and (b) out-of-work claims of what amount were made by families with at least one (i) EEA national and (ii) recently arrived EEA national in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Chris Heaton-Harris","Chris Heaton-Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38886","38886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522015","2016-06-06","HM Treasury","2016-05-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what activity the cross-agency taskforce on the Panama Papers has undertaken since it was established.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38869","38869"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522016","2016-06-06","HM Treasury","2016-05-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the level and amount of the UK EU rebate in each year to 2030.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38927","38927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522017","2016-06-06","HM Treasury","2016-05-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many (a) press officers and (b) other officials of his Department have been or are undertaking work related to the referendum on UK membership of the EU; for how long each such official has been working on that matter; and what the salary is of each such official.","Biography information for Chris Heaton-Harris","Chris Heaton-Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38924","38924"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522018","2016-06-06","Cabinet Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much the Government (a) has spent to date and (b) plans to spend before 23 June 2016 on promoting the Government's policy on the UK's membership of the EU.","Biography information for Chris Heaton-Harris","Chris Heaton-Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38929","38929"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522019","2016-06-08","HM Treasury","2016-05-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on (a) the UK economy and (b) the public finances of a slowdown in the economies (i) in the Eurozone and (ii) of other EU member states.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38946","38946"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522020","2016-06-08","HM Treasury","2016-05-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the economic events in other EU member states that would have an adverse impact on the UK economy; and what steps he has taken to model the effects of such risks.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38947","38947"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522021","2016-06-08","HM Treasury","2016-05-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on (a) the UK economy and (b) public finances of higher unemployment levels in (i) the Eurozone and (ii) other EU member states.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38948","38948"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522022","2016-06-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what plans his Department has to improve access to the Help to Buy scheme.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38926","38926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522023","2016-06-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will take steps to review his policy on the green belt to take account of changes in the levels of migration.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38657","38657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522024","2016-06-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what indicators the Government uses to determine levels of community integration.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38645","38645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522025","2016-06-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what requirements are in place to ensure that local authorities seeking to introduce a low emission zone follow government guidance when so doing; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38703","38703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522026","2016-06-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to reduce littering.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38854","38854"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522027","2016-06-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 25 May 2016 to Question 37198, how many of the leaflets entitled Why the Government believes that voting to remain in the European Union is the best decision for the UK have been returned to his Department; and what the postage cost to the Government has been of such returns.","Biography information for Tom Pursglove","Tom Pursglove","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38766","38766"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522028","2016-06-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will place in the Library copies of all letters, leaflets and other material from his Department circulated to (a) stakeholders and (b) members of the public on the EU Referendum; what the costs of the production and distribution of that material has been since 1 January 2016; and what he estimates the cost of any further production and distribution of such material will be between 6 May 2016 and 23 June 2016.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38812","38812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522029","2016-06-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment his Department has made of the efficacy of the current priority need system for allocating emergency housing in preventing homelessness.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38807","38807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522030","2016-06-06","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what the proportion of increased coverage of mobile signal to UK premises is since the December 2014 agreement with the four mobile network operators was secured.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38736","38736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522031","2016-06-06","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what information his Department holds on how many telecommunications masts have been removed in rural areas since December 2014.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38737","38737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522032","2016-06-06","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will place in the Library copies of all letters, leaflets and other material from his Department circulated to (a) stakeholders and (b) members of the public on the EU Referendum; what the costs of the production and distribution of that material has been since 1 January 2016; and what he estimates the cost of any further production and distribution of such material will be between 6 May 2016 and 23 June 2016.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38813","38813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522033","2016-06-06","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 25 May 2016 to Question 37198, how many of the leaflets entitled Why the Government believes that voting to remain in the European Union is the best decision for the UK have been returned to his Department; and what the postage cost to the Government has been of such returns.","Biography information for Tom Pursglove","Tom Pursglove","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38767","38767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522034","2016-06-06","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many telecommunications masts were in operation in (a) England and (b) Wales in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38745","38745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522035","2016-06-06","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many telecommunications masts were in operation in rural areas in (a) England and (b) Wales in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38746","38746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522036","2016-06-06","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will undertake or commission research to measure the (a) the effect of remote casinos on the terrestrial casino industry and (b) the benefits and disbenefits of remote casinos to the UK economy.","Biography information for Mark Pritchard","Mark Pritchard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38890","38890"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522037","2016-06-06","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, when he plans to launch the Triennial Review of gambling machine stakes and prize limits.","Biography information for Mark Pritchard","Mark Pritchard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38887","38887"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522038","2016-06-06","Cabinet Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, by what date feedback should be submitted to the Data Science Ethical Framework.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38909","38909"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522039","2016-06-06","Cabinet Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how the membership of the Council for Data Science Ethics will be decided; how many members there will be of that Council; and how long those members will be appointed for.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38910","38910"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522040","2016-06-06","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what EU legislation affects the roll-out of superfast broadband in the UK.","Biography information for John Redwood","John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38604","38604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522041","2016-06-06","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many new telecommunications masts have been erected in rural areas since the agreement with the four mobile network operators in December 2014 guaranteeing voice and text coverage from each operator across 90 per cent of the UK by 2017.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38711","38711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522042","2016-06-06","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what plans he has to bring forward proposals to update the (a) Gaming Act 1968 and (b) Gambling Act 2005.","Biography information for Mark Pritchard","Mark Pritchard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38891","38891"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522043","2016-06-06","Ministry of Defence","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking in response to the Armed Forces 2015 survey findings that (a) 12 per cent of women surveyed reported that someone had made unwelcome attempts to touch them and (b) only three per cent of servicewomen who were very upset about an incident of sexual harassment made a formal complaint.","Biography information for Owen Thompson","Owen Thompson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38899","38899"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522044","2016-06-06","Ministry of Defence","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the Royal Air Force plans to issue policy instructions along the lines of those recently issued by the Army and Royal Navy on cases with a sexual element being referred to the Service Police for investigation.","Biography information for Owen Thompson","Owen Thompson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38901","38901"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522045","2016-06-06","Ministry of Defence","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if his Department will make it his policy to seek international protection for maritime military graves by ratifying the UNESCO Convention and the Protection of Underwater Cultural Heritage.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38932","38932"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522046","2016-06-06","Ministry of Defence","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he became aware that the Dutch salvage company Friendship Offshore had removed salvage from the wrecks of HMS Queen Mary and HMS Indefatigable, sunk at the battle of Jutland.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38931","38931"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522047","2016-06-06","Ministry of Defence","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking assert the UK's right of Sovereign Immunity over wrecks from the Battle of Jutland and other Sovereign Immune Royal Navy wrecks.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38933","38933"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522048","2016-06-06","Ministry of Defence","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will make it his policy to seek compensation from Rolls-Royce for the remedial work for the power and propulsion systems of the Type 45 Destroyers.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38719","38719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522049","2016-06-06","Ministry of Defence","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Second World War veterans who have applied through his Department to receive the Légion d'Honneur have not yet received medals.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38675","38675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522050","2016-06-06","Ministry of Defence","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much rent his Department has paid in each financial year on properties within the Married Quarters Estate that have been unoccupied for the majority of the years (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12, (c) 2012-13, (d) 2013-14, (e) 2014-15 and (f) 2015-16.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38682","38682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522051","2016-06-06","Ministry of Defence","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many properties within the Married Quarters Estate have been unoccupied for the majority of (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12, (c) 2012-13, (d) 2013-14, (e) 2014-15 and (f) 2015-16.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38683","38683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522052","2016-06-06","Ministry of Defence","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much his Department has spent on dilapidation payments in respect of properties within the Married Quarters Estate in the years (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12, (c) 2012-13, (d) 2013-14, (e) 2014-15 and (f) 2015-16.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38684","38684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522053","2016-06-06","Ministry of Defence","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many aerial strikes have been conducted by RAF aircraft in Syria in each month since December 2015.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38846","38846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522054","2016-06-06","Ministry of Defence","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many members of the armed forces were convicted (a) by courts martial and (b) in civilian courts of sexual assault or rape in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Owen Thompson","Owen Thompson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38876","38876"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522055","2016-06-06","Ministry of Defence","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the number of UK service personnel currently deployed on EU missions.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38800","38800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522056","2016-06-06","Ministry of Defence","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will bring forward proposals to amend the Armed Forces Act 2006 to introduce more stringent procedures to deal with sexual harassment and sexual assault in the armed forces.","Biography information for Owen Thompson","Owen Thompson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38851","38851"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522057","2016-06-06","Ministry of Defence","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 25 May to Question 37624, when the UK representative to Eurocorps was withdrawn.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38799","38799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522058","2016-06-06","Ministry of Defence","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the obligations of the Government are under its Memorandum of Understanding with the government of Saudi Arabia on the supply of military aircraft and associated equipment and weapons which apply when Saudi Arabia is participating in an armed conflict.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38803","38803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522059","2016-06-06","Ministry of Defence","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 25 May 2016 to Question 37198, how many of the leaflets entitled Why the Government believes that voting to remain in the European Union is the best decision for the UK have been returned to his Department; and what the postage cost to the Government has been of such returns.","Biography information for Tom Pursglove","Tom Pursglove","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38768","38768"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522060","2016-06-06","Ministry of Defence","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what progress has been made on the remedial work for the power and propulsion systems of the Type 45 Destroyers; and what the total cost has been since the issues were identified.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38717","38717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522061","2016-06-06","Ministry of Defence","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when his Department will publish the Type 45 Destroyer - Independent Power and Propulsion System Performance Review.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38718","38718"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522062","2016-06-06","Ministry of Defence","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will place in the Library copies of all letters, leaflets and other material from his Department circulated to (a) stakeholders and (b) members of the public on the EU Referendum; what the costs of the production and distribution of that material has been since 1 January 2016; and what he estimates the cost of any further production and distribution of such material will be between 6 May 2016 and 23 June 2016.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38814","38814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522063","2016-06-06","Department for Education","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will place in the Library copies of all letters, leaflets and other material from her Department circulated to (a) stakeholders and (b) members of the public on the EU Referendum; what the costs of the production and distribution of that material has been since 1 January 2016; and what she estimates the cost of any further production and distribution of such material will be between 6 May 2016 and 23 June 2016.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38815","38815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522064","2016-06-06","Department for Education","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children (a) with autism and (b) identified as having autistic spectrum disorder as their primary type of need were enrolled in general hospital schools in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38738","38738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522065","2016-06-06","Department for Education","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children (a) diagnosed with autism and (b) identified as having autistic spectrum disorder as a special educational need (i) are and (ii) have been educated in independent schools in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38739","38739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522066","2016-06-06","Department for Education","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children (a) with autism and (b) identified as having autistic spectrum disorder as their primary type of need were enrolled in pupil referral units in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38740","38740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522067","2016-06-06","Department for Education","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 25 May 2016 to Question 37198, how many of the leaflets entitled Why the Government believes that voting to remain in the European Union is the best decision for the UK have been returned to her Department; and what the postage cost to the Government has been of such returns.","Biography information for Tom Pursglove","Tom Pursglove","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38769","38769"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522068","2016-06-06","Department for Education","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children (a) with autism and (b) identified has having autistic spectrum disorder as their primary type of need who were receiving School Action or School Action Plus support at the start of 2014 have subsequently been assessed as not requiring Special Educational Needs support of an Education, Health and Care plan.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38798","38798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522069","2016-06-06","Department for Education","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions the Careers and Enterprise Company has held with the South East Local Enterprise Partnership on improving careers information advice and guidance in secondary schoolher within Tonbridge and Malling constituency.","Biography information for Tom Tugendhat","Tom Tugendhat","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38613","38613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522070","2016-06-06","Department for Education","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will review funding levels for the care of 2 year old children.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38638","38638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522071","2016-06-06","Department for Education","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many (a) nursery schools, (b) day-care facilities and (c) children's centres have closed due to funding shortages in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38640","38640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522072","2016-06-06","Department for Education","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what information her Department holds on preaching of intolerance, hate and isolationism in Islamic out-of-school education settings.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38678","38678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522073","2016-06-06","Department for Education","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the press notice entitled Next Steps to spread educational excellence everywhere announced, published on 6 May 2016, how long before she made the announcement of her decision to change her policy on schools becoming academies that decision was made.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38686","38686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522074","2016-06-06","Department for Education","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what representations she has received from local authorities on the effect on school places of immigration from (a) EU and (b) non-EU countries.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38928","38928"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522075","2016-06-06","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether local planning authorities can only grant hydraulic fracturing consent for a well after an environment impact assessment directive compliance assessment has taken place.","Biography information for Mr Mark Williams","Mr Mark Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38792","38792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522076","2016-06-06","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment her Department has made on the viability of using rivers with tidal streams as a source of tidal energy.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38664","38664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522077","2016-06-06","Department for Transport","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to improve investor confidence in the production of (a) renewable fuel in general and (b) sustainable aircraft fuel.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38665","38665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522078","2016-06-06","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps her Department is taking to raise awareness of (a) firms pretending to be authorised Green Deal providers and (b) the means available to secure redress against such firms.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38660","38660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522079","2016-06-06","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many people from which non-governmental organisations and energy companies are on secondment to her Department.","Biography information for Callum McCaig","Callum McCaig","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38609","38609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522080","2016-06-06","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what analysis her Department has undertaken on the effect of limiting the role which diesel generators play in the Capacity Market on increased contract awards for new gas power stations.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38858","38858"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522081","2016-06-06","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 25 May 2016 to Question 37198, how many of the leaflets entitled Why the Government believes that voting to remain in the European Union is the best decision for the UK have been returned to her Department; and what the postage cost to the Government has been of such returns.","Biography information for Tom Pursglove","Tom Pursglove","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38770","38770"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522082","2016-06-06","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what financial and other support her Department plans to provide to help non-domestic landlords meet the requirements of the Private Rented Sector Energy Efficiency Regulations (Non-domestic) (England and Wales) 2015.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38723","38723"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522083","2016-06-06","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if she will place in the Library copies of all letters, leaflets and other material from her Department circulated to (a) stakeholders and (b) members of the public on the EU Referendum; what the costs of the production and distribution of that material has been since 1 January 2016; and what she estimates the cost of any further production and distribution of such material will be between 6 May 2016 and 23 June 2016.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38816","38816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522084","2016-06-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will place in the Library copies of all letters, leaflets and other material from her Department circulated to (a) stakeholders and (b) members of the public on the EU Referendum; what the costs of the production and distribution of that material has been since 1 January 2016; and what she estimates the cost of any further production and distribution of such material will be between 6 May 2016 and 23 June 2016.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38817","38817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522085","2016-06-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 25 May 2016 to Question 37198, how many of the leaflets entitled Why the Government believes that voting to remain in the European Union is the best decision for the UK have been returned to her Department; and what the postage cost to the Government has been of such returns.","Biography information for Tom Pursglove","Tom Pursglove","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38771","38771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522086","2016-06-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what her policy is on foregoing the running hour exemptions permitted by the Medium Combustion Plant Directive on the total annualised emissions of the energy sector; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38861","38861"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522087","2016-06-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much funding was allocated to local authority recycling schemes in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38853","38853"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522088","2016-06-06","Department of Health","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) incidents have been reported to trading standards teams of and (b) prosecutions have taken place for making false statements about the source of ingredients in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Nick Smith","Nick Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38648","38648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522089","2016-06-06","Department of Health","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) incidents have been reported to trading standards teams of and (b) prosecutions have taken place for knowingly selling goods past their sell by date in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Nick Smith","Nick Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38649","38649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522090","2016-06-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many claims made under the 2015 Basic Payment Scheme are still outstanding; and when all the those claims will be settled.","Biography information for Sir Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38616","38616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522091","2016-06-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether she expects all applications made before the deadline for the applications for the 2016 Payment Scheme to be paid this year.","Biography information for Sir Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38617","38617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522092","2016-06-06","Department of Health","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) incidents have been reported to trading standards teams of and (b) prosecutions have taken place for recycling animal by-products back into the food chain in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Nick Smith","Nick Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38650","38650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522093","2016-06-06","Department of Health","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) incidents have been reported to trading standards teams of and (b) prosecutions have taken place for packing and selling beef and poultry with an unknown origin in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Nick Smith","Nick Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38651","38651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522094","2016-06-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the Government's policy will be on supporting further protection through an uplisting of (a) elephants, (b) rhinos and (c) lions at the forthcoming CITES Conference of the Parties in September 2016.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38789","38789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522095","2016-06-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the effect of fireworks on animal welfare.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38937","38937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522096","2016-06-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the Government's policy is on (a) European Commission and Parliament proposals to reduce the routine overuse of antibiotics in farming and (b) proposals for (i) an EU-wide ban on the routine use of antibiotics in groups of food-producing animals where no disease has been diagnosed in any of the animals and (ii) restrictions on metaphylactic use.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38945","38945"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522097","2016-06-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many UK nationals has been on the staff of the European Court of Justice in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38671","38671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522098","2016-06-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many UK nationals have been on the staff of the European Court of Auditors in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38672","38672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522099","2016-06-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many UK nationals have been on the staff of (a) each of the Directorates-General and (b) other services of the European Commission in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38673","38673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522100","2016-06-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to encourage more UK nationals to take up traineeships in the European Parliament and European Commission.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38674","38674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522101","2016-06-06","Cabinet Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what criteria are used for decisions on the (a) removal and (b) denial of UK honours.","Biography information for Dr Andrew Murrison","Dr Andrew Murrison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38694","38694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522102","2016-06-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will initiate a resolution of the UN Security Council related to whether genocide is being committed against religious minorities in Syria and Iraq.","Biography information for Dawn Butler","Dawn Butler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38614","38614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522103","2016-06-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when he expects negotiations on the new EU treaty to incorporate the new settlement for the UK in the EU to begin in the event of the UK voting to stay in the EU.","Biography information for John Redwood","John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38603","38603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522104","2016-06-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what legal status UK citizens currently resident elsewhere in the EU will have in the event of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38794","38794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522105","2016-06-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent reports he has received on allegations of torture and threats of physical and sexual violence against Baha'is sentenced to prison terms in Golestan province, Iran.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38802","38802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522106","2016-06-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the statement of the UN High Commissioner for Human Rights, Zeid Ráad al Hussein, of 10 May 2016, what his policy is on the government of Turkey conducting prompt and independent investigations into alleged violations of human rights by Turkish security forces, alleged extra-judicial killings and disproportionate use of force.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38762","38762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522107","2016-06-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions the Government has had with the Burmese government on repealing or amending provisions of that country's (a) penal code, (b) Peaceful Assembly Act, (c) Unlawful Associations Act 1908, (d) Telecommunications Act 2013, (e) Official Secrets Act 1923 and (f) other laws that affect the rights to freedom of expression, peaceful assembly and association.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38796","38796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522108","2016-06-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the statement of the UN High Commissioner for Human Rights, Zeid Ráad al Hussein, of 10 May 2016, what his policy is on the government of Turkey giving independent investigators, including UN staff, unimpeded access to South East Turkey to investigate alleged violations of human rights.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38763","38763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522109","2016-06-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received on (a) the mass arrest of members of the Baha'i community in Golestan province, Iran and (b) the length of their sentence of imprisonment.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38797","38797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522110","2016-06-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received on alleged serious abuses of human rights by Turkish security forces in Cizre.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38761","38761"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522111","2016-06-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to promote religious freedom in Saudi Arabia; and what recent representations the Government has made to Saudi Arabia on that matter.","Biography information for Dawn Butler","Dawn Butler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38785","38785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522112","2016-06-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 25 May 2016 to Question 37198, how many of the leaflets entitled Why the Government believes that voting to remain in the European Union is the best decision for the UK have been returned to his Department; and what the postage cost to the Government has been of such returns.","Biography information for Tom Pursglove","Tom Pursglove","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38772","38772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522113","2016-06-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the implications for his policies of the finding of the report from Human Rights Watch entitled, We Feel We Are Cursed: Life under ISIS in Sirte, Libya, published on 18 May 2016.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38725","38725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522114","2016-06-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will place in the Library copies of all letters, leaflets and other material from his Department circulated to (a) stakeholders and (b) members of the public on the EU referendum; what the costs of the production and distribution of that material have been since 1 January 2016; and what he estimates the cost of any further production and distribution of such material will be between 6 May 2016 and 23 June 2016.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38818","38818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522115","2016-06-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his Iranian counterpart on allegations that Baha'i people sentenced to prison terms in Golestan province were tortured, forced to sign confessions and denied access to legal representation.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38733","38733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522116","2016-06-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the EU budget is for assistance to Turkey for strengthening its external border with Syria, Iran and Iraq in (a) 2016-17 and (b) 2017-18.","Biography information for John Redwood","John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38750","38750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522117","2016-06-06","Department of Health","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will place in the Library copies of all letters, leaflets and other material from his Department circulated to (a) stakeholders and (b) members of the public on the EU referendum; what the costs of the production and distribution of that material has been since 1 January 2016; and what he estimates the cost of any further production and distribution of such material will be between 6 May 2016 and 23 June 2016.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38820","38820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522118","2016-06-06","Department of Health","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of bringing forward legislative proposals to prevent the publication of books, papers and  other material containing health advice which does not have a sound evidence base; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38715","38715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522119","2016-06-06","Department of Health","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 25 May 2016 to Question 37198, how many of the leaflets entitled Why the Government believes that voting to remain in the European Union is the best decision for the UK have been returned to his Department; and what the postage cost to the Government has been of such returns.","Biography information for Tom Pursglove","Tom Pursglove","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38773","38773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522120","2016-06-06","Department of Health","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of potential links between hand hygiene compliance levels across the NHS and rates of C. Difficile bacteraemia in 2015.","Biography information for Nigel Mills","Nigel Mills","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38734","38734"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522121","2016-06-06","Department of Health","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of potential links between hand hygiene compliance levels across the NHS and rates of MSSA bacteraemia in 2015.","Biography information for Nigel Mills","Nigel Mills","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38735","38735"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522122","2016-06-06","Department of Health","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans his Department has to review and update NICE guidance to take account of emerging new technologies in electronic auditing.","Biography information for Nigel Mills","Nigel Mills","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38786","38786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522123","2016-06-06","Department of Health","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many cases of Ehlers-Danios Syndrome have been diagnosed in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Wendy Morton","Wendy Morton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38845","38845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522124","2016-06-06","Department of Health","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the Parliamentary Under Secretary of State for Public Health has seen the complaint by the Nordic Cochrane Centre to the European Medicines Agency regarding maladministration at that organisation; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38834","38834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522125","2016-06-06","Department of Health","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what compliance procedures the Medicines and Healthcare Products Regulatory Agency has to ensure that its pharmacovigilance functions do not conflict with the relationships it builds with private companies when seeking business from such companies.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38832","38832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522126","2016-06-06","Department of Health","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the Medicines and Healthcare Products Regulatory Agency holds any clinical trial data for HPV vaccines which is not in the public domain.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38833","38833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522127","2016-06-06","Department of Health","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what measures are in place to support people who have had adverse reactions to vaccines administered by the NHS.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38831","38831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522128","2016-06-06","Department of Health","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to address barriers faced by people with ME in accessing care and support; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38801","38801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522129","2016-06-06","HM Treasury","2016-05-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what data from which year of the National Diet and Nutrition Survey has been  used to inform the development of the soft drinks industry levy.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38608","38608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522130","2016-06-06","Department of Health","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many emergency readmissions within 28 days of discharge there were for patients with a primary or secondary diagnosis of dementia in (a) England and (b) each clinical commissioning group and primary care trust area in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38623","38623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522131","2016-06-06","Department of Health","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients were discharged from hospital between 11pm and 6am in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38624","38624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522132","2016-06-06","Department of Health","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much was paid by the NHS Trust Development Authority to meet the salary costs of the former Chief Executive of Liverpool Community Trust, Bernie Cuthell, during her (a) secondment to Manchester Mental Health Trust and (b) employment at the Betsi Cadwaladr NHS Trust.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38629","38629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522133","2016-06-06","Department of Health","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which GP practice lists in West Sussex have been closed in the last 12 months; and for what reasons each such list was closed.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38636","38636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522134","2016-06-06","Department of Health","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his policy is on e-cigarettes as a potential gateway to smoking.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38658","38658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522135","2016-06-06","Department of Health","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many readmissions within 28 days of discharge from hospital there were for patients over the age of (a) 65, (b) 80 and (c) 90 in (i) England and (ii) each clinical commissioning group and primary care trust area in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38622","38622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522136","2016-06-06","Department of Health","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) incidents have been reported to trading standards teams and (b) prosecutions there have been related to food and drink products substituted with a cheaper alternative in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Nick Smith","Nick Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38647","38647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522137","2016-06-06","Department of Health","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect on the range of free services offered by community pharmacies of the planned changes in funding for such pharmacies.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38720","38720"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522138","2016-06-06","Department of Health","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what funding has been allocated by Health Education England for clinical placements for the new nurse training places his Department plans to deliver by the end of the Parliament.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38721","38721"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522139","2016-06-06","Department of Health","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the proportion of e-cigarette users who will return to smoking tobacco products in the year ending May 2017 as a result of the Tobacco Products Directive.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38712","38712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522140","2016-06-06","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate his Department has made of the proportion of nursing, midwifery and allied healthcare graduates who are expected to pay off their student loan in full.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38702","38702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522141","2016-06-06","Department of Health","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average length is of nursing, midwifery and allied healthcare students' clinical placements taken in each year of their degree.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38700","38700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522142","2016-06-06","Department of Health","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the relationship between hand hygiene compliance levels across the NHS and rates of E.coli bacteraemia in 2015.","Biography information for Nigel Mills","Nigel Mills","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38666","38666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522143","2016-06-06","Department of Health","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what measures his Department is implementing to emphasise the importance of hand hygiene in the prevention of infection in hospitals.","Biography information for Nigel Mills","Nigel Mills","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38667","38667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522144","2016-06-06","Department of Health","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Answer of 12 May 2016 to Question 37016, what assessment he has made of the change in the number of full-time equivalent paramedics employed by the London Ambulance Service over the last three years.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38685","38685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522145","2016-06-06","Department of Health","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to reduce the cost to the NHS of postage of appointment notifications to patients.","Biography information for Dr Tania Mathias","Dr Tania Mathias","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38670","38670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522146","2016-06-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the meeting of the Minister of State with the Sheep Dip Sufferers': Support Group on 19 November 2015, if she will disclose papers relating to the decision to end compulsory sheep dipping which was taken in 1992.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38944","38944"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522147","2016-06-06","Department of Health","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether it is planned that the Government's childhood obesity strategy will include measures restricting the marketing of unhealthy foods to children.","Biography information for Michelle Donelan","Michelle Donelan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38943","38943"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522148","2016-06-06","Department of Health","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, on what date in June 2016 the HPV vaccination pilot for men who have sex with men is planned to commence; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38848","38848"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522149","2016-06-06","Department of Health","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information his Department holds on the use of peptide receptor radionuclide therapy treatments to target carcinoid tumours.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38897","38897"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522150","2016-06-06","Department of Health","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, for what reasons the Lutathera drug was removed from the list of drugs available under the Cancer Drugs Fund.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38894","38894"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522151","2016-06-06","Department of Health","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to findings presented at the 2015 European Cancer Congress on Lutathera, what assessment he has made of the reported benefits of that drug on treating patients with neuroendocrine tumours.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38895","38895"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522152","2016-06-06","Department of Health","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the financial effect on people caring for family members of the closure of the Independent Living Fund and the introduction of the Care Act 2014.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38788","38788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522153","2016-06-06","Department of Health","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he made of the utility of data from the clinic in Brent and Harrow which has been providing men who have sex with men with HPV vaccinations since 2012 when determining that it was necessary to conduct an HPV vaccination pilot before deciding on a national roll-out; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38847","38847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522154","2016-06-06","Department of Health","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what change there was in the level of emergency admissions of older people between 2010-11 and 2014-15 in the Brighton and Sussex University Hospitals NHS Trust.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38902","38902"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522155","2016-06-06","Department of Health","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of treatment and provision of support through the NHS for patients of neuroendocrine cancer.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38882","38882"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522156","2016-06-06","Department of Health","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, for what reasons the budget for the revised Cancer Drugs Fund was established at £340 million.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38896","38896"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522157","2016-06-06","Department of Health","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what research the Advisory Committee on the Safety of Blood, Tissues and Organs plans to undertake or commission on the risk of blood-borne viruses for former sex workers and ex-intravenous drug users.","Biography information for Victoria Borwick","Victoria Borwick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38916","38916"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522158","2016-06-06","Department of Health","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether it is planned that the Government's childhood obesity strategy will include targets for industry to reduce levels of (a) fat and (b) salt in food and drink.","Biography information for Michelle Donelan","Michelle Donelan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38942","38942"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522159","2016-06-06","Department of Health","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many children under the age of 18 in England have cystic fibrosis.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38905","38905"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522160","2016-06-06","Department of Health","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will estimate the additional costs incurred by a family raising a child with cystic fibrosis.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38906","38906"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522161","2016-06-06","Department of Health","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to increase provision of neuromuscular care advisor support in (a) London and (b) the South East.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38885","38885"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522162","2016-06-06","Department of Health","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the cost to (a) Brighton and Sussex University Hospitals NHS Trust and (b) West Sussex County Council of delays in discharging older patients from hospital in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38903","38903"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522163","2016-06-06","Department of Health","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many bed days were lost due to delayed transfers of care in Brighton and Sussex University Hospitals NHS Trust in 2015.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38904","38904"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522164","2016-06-06","Home Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what measures are in place to ensure that the appropriate health services, mental health services and sexual health services are available to asylum seekers dispersed to (a) current dispersal areas, (b) new dispersal areas and (c) Scotland.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38920","38920"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522165","2016-06-06","Home Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what annual per-person rate her Department provides to each of its Compass contractors for the accommodation of asylum seekers.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38941","38941"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522166","2016-06-06","Home Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions took place between December 2015 and May 2016 between Ministers and (b) officials of her Department with the Scottish Legal Aid Board and the Law Society of Scotland on plans to widen asylum dispersal in Scotland; and whether any further such discussions are planned.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38918","38918"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522167","2016-06-06","Home Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what arrangements have been made to guarantee access to legal representation for an asylum claim for asylum seekers dispersed to (a) current dispersal areas, (b) new dispersal areas and (c) Scotland.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38917","38917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522168","2016-06-06","Home Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what measures are in place to ensure that local communities are involved and considered in discussions on the dispersal of asylum seekers to (a) current dispersal areas, (b) new dispersal areas and (c) Scotland.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38940","38940"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522169","2016-06-06","Home Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the oral contribution of the Minister for Immigration of 20 January 2016, Official Report, columns 1425-30, whether there is no predominant colour for the front doors of properties used to house asylum seekers in Teesside.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38900","38900"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522170","2016-06-06","Home Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will publish the terms of reference and the membership of the Prevent Oversight Board.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38877","38877"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522171","2016-06-06","Home Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) people, (b) nominated officers and (c) other nominated officers were prosecuted for failure to disclose under Section 19, Part III of the Terrorism Act 2000 in each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38938","38938"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522172","2016-06-06","Home Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what measures are in place to ensure that the appropriate educational provision is in place for asylum seekers dispersed to (a) current dispersal areas, (b) new dispersal areas and (c) Scotland.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38919","38919"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522173","2016-06-06","Home Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the oral contribution of the Minister for Immigration of 3 May 2016, Official Report, column 45WH, on asylum seeker dispersal, if she will provide the names of the (a) 103 local authorities that are currently asylum dispersal areas, (b) 20 local authorities signed up to be asylum dispersal areas and (c) 28 local authorities that her Department is in discussions with to become asylum dispersal areas.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38939","38939"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522174","2016-06-06","Home Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many visas were processed using the priority visa service in 2015.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38652","38652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522175","2016-06-06","Home Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the effect of the planned increase in UK visa fees on the number of people coming to the UK.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38653","38653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522176","2016-06-06","Home Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of settlement visas using the priority visa service were processed in Islamabad, Pakistan within (a) 10, (b) 15, (c) 30, (d) 60, (e) 90 and (f) 120 days.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38654","38654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522177","2016-06-06","Home Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average processing time is for settlement visas using the priority visa service.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38655","38655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522178","2016-06-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how his Department is monitoring the effectiveness of the Community Engagement Forum; how frequently that forum has met; and how many Muslims that forum has engaged.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38633","38633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522179","2016-06-06","Home Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will estimate the number and proportion of British violent extremists who were radicalised by people promoting (a) non-violent extremism and (b) views that conflict with British values.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38644","38644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522180","2016-06-06","Home Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the number of prospective migrants who will be deterred from entering the UK from other EU member states upon implementation of the emergency brake.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38707","38707"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522181","2016-06-06","Home Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the potential number of short-term EU migrants who are expected to enter the UK to live and work in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38706","38706"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522182","2016-06-06","Home Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department has taken to ensure (a) compliance with and (b) appropriate implementation of COMPASS contracts in Teeside.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38728","38728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522183","2016-06-06","Home Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will estimate how many and what proportion of British citizens identified as violent extremists were radicalised by (a) extremist material on the internet, (b) contact with extremists through e-mail or social media, (c) contact with extremists through family connections, (d) contact with extremists through street gangs, (e) contact with extremists through prisons and (f) contact with extremists in Islamic out-of education settings.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38646","38646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522184","2016-06-06","Home Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which teams in her Department work on counter-extremism strategy and policy; how many staff are employed in each of those teams; what the grade is of each of those staff; what the budget is for each team; and what the budget is for external expert consultancy services for each of those teams.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38679","38679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522185","2016-06-06","Home Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the effect on levels of inward migration from other EU member states of (a) an economic downturn and (b) a rise in unemployment in such states.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38691","38691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522186","2016-06-06","Home Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Answer of 3 March 2016 to Question 28999, how many (a) credibility interviews were conducted and (b) students did not undergo such interviews in each year from 2009-10 to 2015-16.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38689","38689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522187","2016-06-06","Home Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what information she holds on the number of 999 calls abandoned before being answered in (a) England, (b) Yorkshire and (c) Calderdale.","Biography information for Holly Lynch","Holly Lynch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38618","38618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522188","2016-06-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the security implications for the UK of the Association Agreement between the EU and Ukraine.","Biography information for John Redwood","John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38605","38605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522189","2016-06-06","Home Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people from Yemen have claimed asylum in the UK in (a) 2015 and (b) 2016 to date.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38756","38756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522190","2016-06-06","Home Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, for what reasons she has not produced an estimate of the potential effect on inward migration from the EU of the UK's negotiated settlement with the EU; and when she plans to publish that estimate.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38795","38795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522191","2016-06-06","Home Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what her policy is on whether non-UK EU citizens will have to leave the UK after the two-year Article 50 negotiation period in the event of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38793","38793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522192","2016-06-06","Home Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what work her Department has undertaken with international partners on access to sources of data that can be used to enhance the security of the UK border.","Biography information for Victoria Atkins","Victoria Atkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38836","38836"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522193","2016-06-06","Home Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answers of 23 May 2016 to Questions 37209 and 37235, whether official guidelines on the policing of football matches abroad state that authority must be granted by her Department under section 26 of the Police Act 1996 to permit UK police officers to perform operational police duties abroad.","Biography information for Jack Dromey","Jack Dromey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38859","38859"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522194","2016-06-06","Home Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many curfew orders have been issued for anti-social behaviour in Stafford constituency since the introduction of such orders.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38843","38843"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522195","2016-06-06","Home Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the trends in the level of crime in Stafford constituency in each of the last three years; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38844","38844"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522196","2016-06-06","Home Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many offences involving the fraudulent use of personal information have been reported to Staffordshire Police in each year since 2006; and how many such reports led to a (a) prosecution and (b) conviction.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38840","38840"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522197","2016-06-06","Home Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to Managing migratory flows in Calais: joint ministerial declaration on UK/French co-operation, published on 20 August 2015, what progress has been made on implementing the measures in that declaration to reinforce border security in northern France where the UK operates a juxtaposed border control.","Biography information for Ms Nusrat Ghani","Nusrat Ghani","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38888","38888"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522198","2016-06-06","Home Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the oral contribution of the Minister for Immigration of 3 May 2016, Official Report, column 45WH, on asylum seeker dispersal policy, if she will publish the template letter she plans to send to leaders of local authorities on widening dispersal.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38749","38749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522199","2016-06-06","Home Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many reports of criminal offences against residents of properties used to house asylum seekers have been recorded in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38729","38729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522200","2016-06-06","Home Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department has made an assessment of the progress of the programme to re-paint the red doors of properties used to house asylum seekers on Teesside.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38730","38730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522201","2016-06-06","Home Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many claims for asylum from people from Yemen have been refused in 2016 to date.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38741","38741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522202","2016-06-06","Home Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which companies were contracted to facilitate enforced returns to Yemen for failed asylum seekers from that country in 2015.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38742","38742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522203","2016-06-06","Home Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, on which dates in 2015 enforced removals of people from Yemen who had unsuccessfully claimed asylum took place.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38743","38743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522204","2016-06-06","Home Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will place in the Library copies of all letters, leaflets and other material from her Department circulated to (a) stakeholders and (b) members of the public on the EU referendum; what the costs of the production and distribution of that material has been since 1 January 2016; and what she estimates the cost of any further production and distribution of such material will be between 6 May 2016 and 23 June 2016.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38821","38821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522205","2016-06-06","Home Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 25 May 2016 to Question 37198, how many of the leaflets entitled Why the Government believes that voting to remain in the European Union is the best decision for the UK have been returned to her Department; and what the postage cost to the Government has been of such returns.","Biography information for Tom Pursglove","Tom Pursglove","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38774","38774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522206","2016-06-06","Department for International Development","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 25 May 2016 to Question 37198, how many of the leaflets entitled Why the Government believes that voting to remain in the European Union is the best decision for the UK have been returned to her Department; and what the postage cost to the Government has been of such returns.","Biography information for Tom Pursglove","Tom Pursglove","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38775","38775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522207","2016-06-06","Department for International Development","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will place in the Library copies of all letters, leaflets and other material from her Department circulated to (a) stakeholders and (b) members of the public on the EU referendum; what the costs of the production and distribution of that material has been since 1 January 2016; and what she estimates the cost of any further production and distribution of such material will be between 6 May 2016 and 23 June 2016.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38822","38822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522208","2016-06-06","Department for International Development","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment her Department has made of the potential use and effectiveness of unmanned aerial vehicle technology in supporting the UK's international development agenda.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38662","38662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522209","2016-06-06","Department for International Development","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether her Department is carrying out trials to assess the suitability of unmanned aerial vehicle technology as part of the UK's humanitarian disaster response capability.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38661","38661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522210","2016-06-06","Department for International Development","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the potential effect of the outcomes of the World Humanitarian Summit on gender equality; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38681","38681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522211","2016-06-06","Department for International Development","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether her Department plans to increase the number of interventions to tackle violence against women and girls through programmes funded by her Department at (a) donor and (b) country level.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38676","38676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522212","2016-06-06","Department for International Development","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether her Department has made an assessment of (a) the adequacy of its expenditure on and (b) the value for money of its work on violence against women and girls.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38656","38656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522213","2016-06-06","Ministry of Justice","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) court judgments have been made against Tivium and (b) such judgments have been satisfied in (i) England, (ii) the North West and (iii) Lancashire.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38659","38659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522214","2016-06-06","Ministry of Justice","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment his Department has made of the effectiveness of the methodology used to calculate the employment tribunal fees increase in preventing a reduction in the number of cases coming to tribunal.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38619","38619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522215","2016-06-06","Ministry of Justice","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will place in the Library copies of all letters, leaflets and other material from his Department circulated to (a) stakeholders and (b) members of the public on the EU referendum; what the costs of the production and distribution of that material has been since 1 January 2016; and what he estimates the cost of any further production and distribution of such material will be between 6 May 2016 and 23 June 2016.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38823","38823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522216","2016-06-06","Ministry of Justice","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 25 May 2016 to Question 37198, how many of the leaflets entitled Why the Government believes that voting to remain in the European Union is the best decision for the UK have been returned to his Department; and what the postage cost to the Government has been of such returns.","Biography information for Tom Pursglove","Tom Pursglove","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38776","38776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522217","2016-06-06","Ministry of Justice","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the reoffending rates are for offenders who have had a conviction (a) under and (b) over 12 months in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38893","38893"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522218","2016-06-06","Ministry of Justice","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much has been paid from the public purse to community rehabilitation companies under the payments-by-results arrangement.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38884","38884"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522219","2016-06-06","Ministry of Justice","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many offenders on probation have been (a) classified in each risk category, (b) moved up a risk category and (c) moved down a risk category in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38881","38881"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522220","2016-06-06","Ministry of Justice","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the effect of his policies on transforming rehabilitation on the performance of the Probation Service.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38883","38883"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522221","2016-06-06","Ministry of Justice","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what response he has made to HM Inspectorate of Probation's Transforming Rehabilitation, Early Implementation 5 report, published in May 2016.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38911","38911"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522222","2016-06-06","Northern Ireland Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, pursuant to the Answer of 25 May 2016 to Question 37198, how many of the leaflets entitled Why the Government believes that voting to remain in the European Union is the best decision for the UK have been returned to her Department; and what the postage cost to the Government has been of such returns.","Biography information for Tom Pursglove","Tom Pursglove","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38777","38777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522223","2016-06-06","Northern Ireland Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, if she will place in the Library copies of all letters, leaflets and other material from her Department circulated to (a) stakeholders and (b) members of the public on the EU referendum; what the costs of the production and distribution of that material has been since 1 January 2016; and what she estimates the cost of any further production and distribution of such material will be between 6 May 2016 and 23 June 2016.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38824","38824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522224","2016-06-06","Cabinet Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will place in the Library copies of all letters, leaflets and other material from 10 Downing Street circulated to (a) stakeholders and (b) members of the public on the EU referendum; what the costs of the production and distribution of that material has been since 1 January 2016; and what he estimates the cost of any further production and distribution of such material will be between 6 May 2016 and 23 June 2016.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38825","38825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522225","2016-06-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether it is the Government's policy that the UK is part of the European Project, as that term is used by the EU Commission and the European Council; and if the Prime Minister will make a statement.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38632","38632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522226","2016-06-06","Scotland Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, if he will place in the Library copies of all letters, leaflets and other material from his Department circulated to (a) stakeholders and (b) members of the public on the EU referendum; what the costs of the production and distribution of that material has been since 1 January 2016; and what he estimates the cost of any further production and distribution of such material will be between 6 May 2016 and 23 June 2016.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38826","38826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522227","2016-06-06","Scotland Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, pursuant to the Answer of 25 May 2016 to Question 37198, how many of the leaflets entitled Why the Government believes that voting to remain in the European Union is the best decision for the UK have been returned to his Department; and what the postage cost to the Government has been of such returns.","Biography information for Tom Pursglove","Tom Pursglove","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38778","38778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522228","2016-06-06","Department for Transport","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 25 May 2016 to Question 37198, how many of the leaflets entitled Why the Government believes that voting to remain in the European Union is the best decision for the UK have been returned to his Department; and what the postage cost to the Government has been of such returns.","Biography information for Tom Pursglove","Tom Pursglove","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38779","38779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522229","2016-06-06","Department for Transport","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will place in the Library copies of all letters, leaflets and other material from his Department circulated to (a) stakeholders and (b) members of the public on the EU referendum; what the costs of the production and distribution of that material has been since 1 January 2016; and what he estimates the cost of any further production and distribution of such material will be between 6 May 2016 and 23 June 2016.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38827","38827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522230","2016-06-06","Department for Transport","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to assess the potential merits of its proposals on drones to be included in the planned Modern Transport Bill; and what assessment he has made of the need for temporary measures to ensure public safety related to drones until such proposals have been enacted.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38744","38744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522231","2016-06-06","Department for Transport","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he, Ministers or officials of his Department have had with Govia Thameslink Railway on indemnifying Govia Thameslink Railway from losses incurred as a result of industrial action; and what the dates and outcomes of those discussions were.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38716","38716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522232","2016-06-06","Department for Transport","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what sanctions his Department can apply on Govia Thameslink Railway for being in breach of its remedial plan.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38731","38731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522233","2016-06-06","Department for Transport","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the most recent Public Performance Measure figures are which have been reported by Govia Thameslink Railway.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38732","38732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522234","2016-06-06","Department for Transport","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he plans to take to improve the rail network and services between London and Stafford.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38841","38841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522235","2016-06-06","Department for Transport","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department has taken to assist local authorities with the maintenance of rural roads.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38842","38842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522236","2016-06-06","Department for Transport","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of whether the most recent Public Performance Measure figures reported by Govia Thameslink Railway put Govia Thameslink Railway in breach of its Remedial Plan.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38784","38784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522237","2016-06-06","Department for Transport","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much information his Department holds on how many electric motorcycles have been sold in the UK in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Sammy Wilson","Sammy Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38783","38783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522238","2016-06-06","Department for Transport","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions his Department has had with Govia Thameslink Railway on extending Driver Only Operation; and what the outcome of those discussions was.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38787","38787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522239","2016-06-06","Department for Transport","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many traffic surveys and counts his Department has conducted in Stafford constituency since 2010.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38838","38838"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522240","2016-06-06","Department for Transport","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many registered car owners there were in Stafford constituency in each year since 2005.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38839","38839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522241","2016-06-06","Department for Transport","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of whether the most recent Public Performance Measure figures reported by Govia Thameslink Railway put that company in breach of its franchise agreement.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38759","38759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522242","2016-06-06","Department for Transport","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to tackle speeding by (a) cars, (b) HGVs and (c) buses.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38855","38855"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522243","2016-06-06","Department for Transport","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what progress his Department is making on the procurement and appointment process for the construction of a new lorry park around junction 11 on the M20.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38752","38752"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522244","2016-06-06","Department for Transport","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking on steps to find a long-term solution for congestion in the South East.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38753","38753"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522245","2016-06-06","Department for Transport","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the proportional real terms change in the cost of travelling by (a) private car, (b) bus, (c) train and (d) aeroplane since (i) 1980, (ii) 1997, (iii) 2010 and (iv) 2015.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38669","38669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522246","2016-06-09","Department for Transport","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, for what reason several cameras are being installed on the A1 north of Colsterworth; how many accidents have occurred on the stretch of road being covered by those cameras in each of the last five years for which figures are available; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38704","38704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522247","2016-06-09","Department for Transport","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what his latest assessment is of the effectiveness of the foreign lorry user charge; whether he has been in discussion with any representatives of the EU concerning the compliance of that charge with EU law; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38705","38705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522248","2016-06-06","Department for Transport","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions his Department has had with Govia Thameslink Railway on the closure of Govia Thameslink Railway ticket offices; and what the dates of those discussions were.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38709","38709"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522249","2016-06-06","Department for Transport","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions his Department has had with Govia Thameslink Railway on the closure of Govia Thameslink Railway ticket offices; and what the outcome of those discussions was.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38710","38710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522250","2016-06-06","Department for Transport","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the definition of ticket office is for the purposes of Schedule 17 ticketing arrangements.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38708","38708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522251","2016-06-06","Department for Transport","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to his Department's press release, Rip-off pedicabs to be driven off the road under new proposals, published 26 May 2016, whether he plans to (a) amend secondary legislation or (b) bring forward legislative proposals to regulate pedicabs in London.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38639","38639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522252","2016-06-06","Department for Transport","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what changes have recently been made to the franchise agreements and ancillary documents for Govia Thameslink Railway Ltd.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38637","38637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522253","2016-06-06","Department for Transport","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what sanctions can be applied in the event of a breach by Govia Thameslink Railway of its remedial plan.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38606","38606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522254","2016-06-06","Department for Transport","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will publish the Govia Thameslink Railway remedial plan.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38607","38607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522255","2016-06-06","Department for Transport","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the potential conflict of interest between being a member of the Rail North board and an elected councillor.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38625","38625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522256","2016-06-06","Department for Transport","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether any officials of his Department have been transferred, disciplined or dismissed in relation to management of the contract for SS Gairsoppa.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38912","38912"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522257","2016-06-06","Department for Transport","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps the Government has taken to recover funds it is owed by Odyssey Marine Exploration from the deduction of salvage expenses from the Government's share of the silver recovered from SS Gairsoppa.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38934","38934"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522258","2016-06-06","Department for Transport","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he was made aware of Volkswagen's decision to delay Jones Day's comprehensive investigation into diesel emissions until the fourth quarter of 2016.","Biography information for Stewart Malcolm McDonald","Stewart Malcolm McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38914","38914"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522259","2016-06-06","Department for Transport","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many meetings he has had with representatives of Volkswagen to discuss diesel emissions in 2016 to date.","Biography information for Stewart Malcolm McDonald","Stewart Malcolm McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38915","38915"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522260","2016-06-06","Department for Transport","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the value was of the salvage expenses deducted by Odyssey Marine Exploration  from the Government's share of the silver recovered from SS Gairsoppa.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38935","38935"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522261","2016-06-06","Department for Transport","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what representations he has (a) received and (b) made to his French counterpart on the effect on road freight of recent strike action in France.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38791","38791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522262","2016-06-06","Wales Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, if he will place in the Library copies of all letters, leaflets and other material from his Department circulated to (a) stakeholders and (b) members of the public on the EU referendum; what the costs of the production and distribution of that material has been since 1 January 2016; and what he estimates the cost of any further production and distribution of such material will be between 6 May 2016 and 23 June 2016.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38829","38829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522263","2016-06-06","Wales Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, pursuant to the Answer of 25 May 2016 to Question 37198, how many of the leaflets entitled Why the Government believes that voting to remain in the European Union is the best decision for the UK have been returned to his Department; and what the postage cost to the Government has been of such returns.","Biography information for Tom Pursglove","Tom Pursglove","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38781","38781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522264","2016-06-06","Women and Equalities","2016-05-26","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, if she will place in the Library copies of all letters, leaflets and other material from the Government Equalities Office circulated to (a) stakeholders and (b) members of the public on the EU referendum; what the costs of the production and distribution of that material has been since 1 January 2016; and what she estimates the cost of any further production and distribution of such material will be between 6 May 2016 and 23 June 2016.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38819","38819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522265","2016-06-06","Women and Equalities","2016-05-26","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, whether she has discussed with the Prison Service and probation services the recommendations of the Women and Equalities Committee in its First Report of Session 2015-16, on Transgender Equality, HC390, relating to the criminal justice system and prisons.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38714","38714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522266","2016-06-06","Women and Equalities","2016-05-26","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, if her will estimate the number of times people with guide dogs have been refused entry to restaurants in each of the last five years; and what steps she is taking to ensure that people with guide dogs are not refused such entry.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38643","38643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522267","2016-06-06","Women and Equalities","2016-05-26","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what discussions she has had with (a) the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland and (b) members of the Northern Ireland Executive about the prosecution of women in Northern Ireland under the Offences against the Person Act 1861.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38930","38930"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522268","2016-06-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when his Department plans to publish its response to its consultation on Section 75 employer debt in non-associated multi-employer defined benefit pension schemes which closed in May 2015.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38923","38923"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522269","2016-06-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what guidance his Department issues to inform people of state pension age of the implications for their surviving civil partner in the event of their death they are not married; and how many civil partners have been denied a claim to their partner's pension following a claimant's death.","Biography information for Owen Thompson","Owen Thompson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38913","38913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522270","2016-06-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many benefit claimants have been given a yellow card warning since the introduction of such a warning; and of those claimants how many were not subsequently sanctioned.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38630","38630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522271","2016-06-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect of the loss of local authorities' access to housing benefit claim data on their ability to target services and support tenants effectively; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38631","38631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522272","2016-06-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people appointed to the taskforce to look at improving accessibility of apprenticeships for people with learning disabilities have learning difficulties.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38747","38747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522273","2016-06-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 25 May 2016 to Question 37198, how many of the leaflets entitled Why the Government believes that voting to remain in the European Union is the best decision for the UK have been returned to his Department; and what the postage cost to the Government has been of such returns.","Biography information for Tom Pursglove","Tom Pursglove","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38782","38782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522274","2016-06-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether his Department has carried out an impact assessment on the effect of removing housing benefit from people aged under 25 on (a) disabled people and (b) care leavers.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38808","38808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522275","2016-06-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will place in the Library copies of all letters, leaflets and other material from his Department circulated to (a) stakeholders and (b) members of the public on the EU referendum; what the costs of the production and distribution of that material has been since 1 January 2016; and what he estimates the cost of any further production and distribution of such material will be between 6 May 2016 and 23 June 2016.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38830","38830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523218","2016-06-08","Northern Ireland Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what further plans the Government has to devolve tax powers to Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Sir Edward Leigh","Sir Edward Leigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 905256","905256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523245","2016-06-07","HM Treasury","2016-05-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of regulation of banking sector.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 905211","905211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523246","2016-06-07","HM Treasury","2016-05-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of corporation tax receipts from the digital economy sector in 2015-16.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 905207","905207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523247","2016-06-07","HM Treasury","2016-05-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to reduce the gender pay gap in the financial services sector.","Biography information for Ben Howlett","Ben Howlett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 905212","905212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523248","2016-06-07","HM Treasury","2016-05-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what guidance he has given to HM Revenue and Customs on the use of powers in the Finance Act 2014 to issue accelerated payment notices for seeking retrospective tax payments.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 905209","905209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523249","2016-06-07","HM Treasury","2016-05-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to increase exports.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 905203","905203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523250","2016-06-07","HM Treasury","2016-05-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to improve tax transparency.","Biography information for Stewart Malcolm McDonald","Stewart Malcolm McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 905205","905205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523251","2016-06-07","HM Treasury","2016-05-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to ensure that disabled people are not disproportionately affected by reductions in government expenditure.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 905206","905206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523252","2016-06-07","HM Treasury","2016-05-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent estimate he has made of the effect of the Government's steps to tackle aggressive tax avoidance on the revenues derived from general taxation.","Biography information for Stephen Phillips","Stephen Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 905208","905208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523253","2016-06-07","HM Treasury","2016-05-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps the Government is taking to reduce the number of personal injury whiplash claims.","Biography information for Chris Philp","Chris Philp","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 905202","905202"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523759","2016-06-08","Northern Ireland Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what discussions she has had with the Northern Ireland Executive on proposals to repeal the Human Rights Act 1998 and the potential effect of such a repeal on the Good Friday Agreement; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 905258","905258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523760","2016-06-08","Northern Ireland Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what recent assessment she has made of the potential effect on the economy in Northern Ireland of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 905261","905261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523761","2016-06-08","Northern Ireland Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what steps she is taking to help strengthen the economy of Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 905260","905260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523762","2016-06-08","Northern Ireland Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what steps the Government is taking to reach an agreement with political parties in Northern Ireland on how to deal with the legacy of Northern Ireland's past.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 905255","905255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523763","2016-06-08","Northern Ireland Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what steps the Government is taking to tackle low pay in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 905257","905257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521505","2016-06-06","Attorney General","2016-05-25","To ask the Attorney General, how many (a) prosecutions and (b) convictions there have been for each category of hate crime since 2010.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38489","38489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521506","2016-06-06","Attorney General","2016-05-25","To ask the Attorney General, what steps the Serious Fraud Office is taking to address fraud by employees in large companies.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38562","38562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521507","2016-06-06","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate the Student Loans Company has provided to his Department of the costs of the preparation, introduction and administration of the amendments to the fees and student support system in England arising from the (a) replacement of maintenance grants by maintenance loans, (b) introduction of the postgraduate loan scheme, (c) extension of maintenance loans to part-time students, (d) extension of advanced learner loans to those aged 19 years and above and (e) Teaching Excellence Framework.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38555","38555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521508","2016-06-06","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many visits (a) by Ministers and (b) officials from his Department were made to Coventry in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38530","38530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521509","2016-06-06","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether lease renewal and rent review will remain trigger points for the market rent only option procedure, as set out in Part 6 of the withdrawn Pubs Code etc. Regulations 2016.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38474","38474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521510","2016-06-06","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, when he plans to lay the revised statutory instruments for the Pubs Code etc. Regulations 2016 and Pubs Code (Fees, Costs and Financial Penalties) Regulations 2016 before the House.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38472","38472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521511","2016-06-06","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate his Department has made of the number and value of arms export licences issued to Saudi Arabia since 19 March 2015; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38585","38585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521512","2016-06-06","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what additional resources have been or will be made available to the Student Loans Company to enable that Company to administer amendments to the fees and student support system in England covering the (a) replacement of maintenance grants by maintenance loans, (b) introduction of the postgraduate loan scheme, (c) extension of maintenance loans to part-time students, (d) extension of advanced learner loans to those aged 19 years and above and (e) Teaching Excellence Framework.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38551","38551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521513","2016-06-06","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to his Department's White Paper, Success as a knowledge economy: teaching excellence, social mobility and student choice, published in May 2016, what discussions he has had with further education colleges and providers on the future role of further education in delivering higher education; and what assessment he has made of the security of employment and the forms of contract likely to be offered to staff by new alternative providers.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38600","38600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521514","2016-06-06","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to paragraph 119 of the Teaching excellence framework: technical consultation for year two, published by his Department on 16 May 2016, how the estimates for the performance metrics were reached; whether there is scope for making adjustments to those estimates in the future; whether those estimates will be used as part of formal guidance for the operation of the teaching excellence framework; and if he will publish the methodological framework and evidence for how those estimates were reached.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38488","38488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521515","2016-06-06","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether he plans to make changes to the procedure of the market rent only option once triggered, as planned in Part 6 of the withdrawn Pubs Code etc. Regulations 2016.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38473","38473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521516","2016-06-06","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the potential effects on recipients of disabled students allowances of transferring responsibility for funding support from Government to universities.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38433","38433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521517","2016-06-06","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether his Department uses government fire statistics to assess the effect of faulty electrical goods on the number of fires.","Biography information for Yvonne Fovargue","Yvonne Fovargue","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38445","38445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521518","2016-06-06","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department is taking to raise awareness of the dangers of purchasing counterfeit electrical goods.","Biography information for Yvonne Fovargue","Yvonne Fovargue","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38446","38446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521519","2016-06-06","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what meetings he has had with (a) Amazon, (b) eBay and (c) other online retailers on the prevention of the sale of counterfeit electrical goods in the UK.","Biography information for Yvonne Fovargue","Yvonne Fovargue","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38447","38447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521520","2016-06-06","Cabinet Office","2016-05-25","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the gender was of each person who has (a) applied and (b) made the shortlist for each Permanent Secretary appointment since January 2015.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38456","38456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521521","2016-06-06","Cabinet Office","2016-05-25","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the average hourly earnings were of his Department's (a) BME and (b) non-BME employees in (i) 2015 and (ii) 2016.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38431","38431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521522","2016-06-06","Cabinet Office","2016-05-25","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment he has made of the implications for the Government's policy on voter registration of the report by the All-Party Parliamentary Group on Democratic Participation, entitled Getting the Missing Millions on to the Electoral Register, published in April 2016.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38458","38458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521523","2016-06-08","Cabinet Office","2016-05-25","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will take steps to allow postal voting ballot papers to be counted separately in order to more easily detect fraud.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38491","38491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521524","2016-06-06","HM Treasury","2016-05-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what studies and research his Department has undertaken or commissioned on the potential benefits of equity release on retirement incomes; and if he will estimate the potential effect on the public purse of a lower take-up rate of means-tested old-age benefits resulting from greater use of equity release.","Biography information for Julian Knight","Julian Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38508","38508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521525","2016-06-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the terms of reference are for the financial modelling work being undertaken by local partnerships into models for devolution in Dorset; and what the estimated cost of such work is to (a) the public purse and (b) the Local Government Association.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38598","38598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521526","2016-06-06","HM Treasury","2016-05-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to his Department's analysis: the long-term economic impact of EU membership and the alternatives, what estimate he has made of the long-term reduction of trade from leaving the EU in each UK region.","Biography information for Nick Herbert","Nick Herbert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38548","38548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521527","2016-06-06","HM Treasury","2016-05-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the average length of time between an application being made for a Venture Capital Trust Scheme and the scheme taking effect was in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38537","38537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521528","2016-06-06","HM Treasury","2016-05-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of trends in the level of banks closing accounts of money service businesses on grounds relating to adherence to money-laundering regulations since July 2013.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38589","38589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521529","2016-06-06","HM Treasury","2016-05-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he plans to increase the scope of the Financial Conduct Authority's terms of reference to include the application of the Treating Customers Fairly policy to banks.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38590","38590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521530","2016-06-06","HM Treasury","2016-05-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what information his Department holds on how many money service businesses had their bank accounts closed in (a) 2013-14, (b) 2014-15 and (c) 2015-16.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38593","38593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521531","2016-06-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he plans to approve the draft selective licensing scheme for landlords for Peterborough City Council; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stewart Jackson","Mr Stewart Jackson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38587","38587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521532","2016-06-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what progress he has made in his review of the effects of the one per cent rent reduction on small almshouse charities.","Biography information for Mr Geoffrey Cox","Mr Geoffrey Cox","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38549","38549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521533","2016-06-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Answer of 25 April 2016 to Question 34913, on planning, if he will publish the analysis of the responses on changes to the National Planning Policy Framework aimed at increasing housing supply in sustainable locations.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38444","38444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521534","2016-06-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Answer of 21 April 2016 to Question 33341, when he plans to publish his Department's analysis of the compliance testing of local authorities with the Local Government Transparency Code 2015.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38442","38442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521535","2016-06-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much he has allocated for housing regeneration in (a) Easington constituency, (b) Country Durham and (c) the North East.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38497","38497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521536","2016-06-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what plans the Government has to provide (a) refuges and (b) other support to family members in rural areas experiencing domestic abuse and other relationship problems; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38492","38492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521537","2016-06-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what guidance his Department issues on housing renewal in former industrial areas and the replacement of dilapidated housing when it no longer meets the needs of the local community.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38496","38496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521538","2016-06-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of his Department's progress on improving municipal statutory notices since his Department's press release, Councils and media invited to bring statutory notices into 21st century, published on 23rd December 2014.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38486","38486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521539","2016-06-06","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to the oral contribution of the Minister for Culture and Digital Economy of 23 May 2016, Official Report, column 371, what estimate his Department has made of the number of households that will not request broadband access under the broadband universal service obligation.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38515","38515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521540","2016-06-09","Ministry of Defence","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether obligations on private owners to preserve scheduled monuments and listed buildings are applicable to government departments; and what his policy is on fulfilling such obligations.","Biography information for Dr Julian Lewis","Dr Julian Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38546","38546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521541","2016-06-09","Ministry of Defence","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the value for money of the investment made by the Portsmouth Naval Base Property Trust from his Department's reverse premium of £6 million on assets previously transferred; and what investment he expects the proposed further reverse premium of £13 million to attract.","Biography information for Dr Julian Lewis","Dr Julian Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38460","38460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521542","2016-06-09","Ministry of Defence","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, for what reason the proposed transfer of land and historic buildings from his Department to Portsmouth Naval Base Property Trust by the end of 2016 has been delayed; and whether it remains his policy to carry out that transfer.","Biography information for Dr Julian Lewis","Dr Julian Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38451","38451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521543","2016-06-09","Ministry of Defence","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent reports he has received on the state of disrepair of (a) the Block Mills, (b) numbers 1, 4, 5 and 6 dry docks, (c) the South Office Block, (d) the Old Naval Academy, (e) the Parade, (f) the former Iron Foundary and (g) other scheduled monuments and Grade I and Grade II* listed buildings at HM Naval Base Portsmouth; and what steps he is taking to prevent further deterioration of those monuments.","Biography information for Dr Julian Lewis","Dr Julian Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38450","38450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521544","2016-06-06","Ministry of Defence","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many new recruits to the infantry were aged (a) 16, (b) 17 and (c) 18 and above on enlistment in each financial year since 2007-08.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38550","38550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521545","2016-06-06","Ministry of Defence","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what information his Department holds on the (a) use and (b) location of UK-manufactured cluster bombs that were produced before the UK signed the Convention of Cluster Munitions.","Biography information for Dr Tania Mathias","Dr Tania Mathias","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38544","38544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521546","2016-06-06","Ministry of Defence","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many new Ajax armoured vehicles will be produced (a) in the UK and (b) abroad.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38571","38571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521547","2016-06-06","Ministry of Defence","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what proportion of steel used in the new Ajax armoured vehicles will be (a) sourced from the UK and (b) imported from abroad.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38572","38572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521548","2016-06-06","Ministry of Defence","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent discussions he has had with NATO allies on the number of troops deployed to the Baltic states; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38539","38539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521549","2016-06-06","Ministry of Defence","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what his Department's policy is on procurement of a British sixth-generation jet fighter.","Biography information for Kate Hollern","Kate Hollern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38535","38535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521550","2016-06-09","Ministry of Defence","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the planned locating of future aircraft carriers at Sheer Jetty and Victory Jetty has resulted in reconsideration of the transfer of nearby land and buildings to the Portsmouth Naval Base Trust; what assessment his Department has made of the merits of preserving such assets; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Julian Lewis","Dr Julian Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38547","38547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521551","2016-06-06","Ministry of Defence","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent assessment he has made of the threats facing the Baltic states; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38538","38538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521552","2016-06-06","Ministry of Defence","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what information his Department holds on whether aircraft manufactured in the UK and granted an export licence to be sold to the Saudi Arabian government have been used by the Saudi Arabian military forces in Yemen since March 2015.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38591","38591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521553","2016-06-06","Ministry of Defence","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which army regiments or corps may be joined by new recruits aged (a) under 16 years and six months and (b) under 16 years and three months; and which such regiments or corps entail (i) combat roles and (ii) non-combat roles.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38553","38553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521554","2016-06-06","Department for Education","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many visits (a) by Ministers and (b) officials from her Department were made to Coventry in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38531","38531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521555","2016-06-06","Department for Education","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many free schools have opened in areas where there are surplus places in the age range covered by the school in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38541","38541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521556","2016-06-06","Department for Education","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the answer of 23 May 2016 to Question 37442, what the (a) budget and (b) spend was for the three Northern Fund competitions for academy sponsors.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38584","38584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521557","2016-06-06","Department for Education","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the role of University Technical Colleges in the Skills Plan which is proposed for inclusion in the forthcoming Bill on education for all.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38601","38601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521558","2016-06-06","Department for Education","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what consultations she has had with trades unions and staff representative organisations on the future of technical and professional recruitment planned for inclusion in the proposed Skills Plan.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38602","38602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521559","2016-06-06","Department for Education","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the timetable is for the publication of the consultation on changes to the School Admissions Code.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38597","38597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521560","2016-06-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the consequences of pollution levels in London; and what steps her Department is taking to reduce pollution in that city.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38565","38565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521561","2016-06-06","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if she will make an assessment of the potential role of the UK in developing usable carbon capture and storage technology.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38426","38426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521562","2016-06-06","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate she has made of the cost of hotel bookings made for (a) Ministers, (b) special advisers and (c) officials in her Department in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38527","38527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521563","2016-06-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much was spent on research by her Department in each of the last five years; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38502","38502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521564","2016-06-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate her Department has made of the funding available to the Waste and Resources Action Programme in each of the next five years; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38501","38501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521565","2016-06-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what ministerial representation there will be at the CITES Conference of the Parties in September 2016.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38425","38425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521566","2016-06-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether Natural England has agreed to the proposal by Christchurch Borough Council for the development of residential beach chalets on Highcliffe clifftop; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38596","38596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521567","2016-06-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to his Answer of 5 January 2016 to Question 20987, what discussions representatives of the British Embassy have had with the Columbian government on the detention of Professor Miguel Angel Beltran; whether they have raised concerns with that government on his current state of health; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Clive Efford","Clive Efford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38586","38586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521568","2016-06-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to his Department's Human Rights and Democracy Report 2015, Cm 9245, what countries his Department is supporting to develop Preventing Violent Extremism action plans to tackle the root causes of extremism and prejudice; and what the support is which his Department is giving in each such case.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38592","38592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521569","2016-06-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has made representations to the Turkish government on the effect of its policies on freedom of speech, the right to a fair trial and the rule of law.","Biography information for Tommy Sheppard","Tommy Sheppard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38579","38579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521570","2016-06-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with the Kenyan government on the closure of the Dadaab refugee camp.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38580","38580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521571","2016-06-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many times the Foreign Secretary's Advisory Group on Human Rights has met in each year since its formation; and how many of those meetings in each such year (a) he or his predecessor and (b) Minister of his Department attended.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38581","38581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521572","2016-06-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many staff of his Department at what grades have received training on the international human rights context for freedom of religion or belief in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38582","38582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521573","2016-06-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received on the number of people unlawfully executed in Libya by Daesh.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38583","38583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521574","2016-06-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many UK citizens currently resident elsewhere in the EU his Department expects to return to the UK in the event of a vote to leave the EU.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38563","38563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521575","2016-06-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many UK nationals were employed at Director level in the European Commission in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38534","38534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521576","2016-06-06","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he plans to take in response to the leaked documents relating to the operations of Mossack Fonseca to ensure that foreign officials and politicians (a) in general and (b) from Pakistan who own property in the UK do not use such property to hide their assets.","Biography information for Julian Knight","Julian Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38507","38507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521577","2016-06-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what (a) direct and (b) other financial support his Department provides to the Afghan Mines Protection Force and (b) local police.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38526","38526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521578","2016-06-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what his Department's policy is on the use by HM Ambassadors of their official Twitter accounts to promote arguments for staying in the EU ahead of the referendum on 23 June.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38536","38536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521579","2016-06-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to encourage UK nationals to take up junior and entry-level positions in the European Commission.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38462","38462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521580","2016-06-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what information his Department holds on how many UK nationals (a) entered the EU Concours examination and (b) passed that examination in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38463","38463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521581","2016-06-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has made representations to the government of Turkey on that government's proposal to remove parliamentary immunity from opposition members of parliament.","Biography information for Tommy Sheppard","Tommy Sheppard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38475","38475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521582","2016-06-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to recommendation 8 of the report of the Foreign Affairs Committee, The UK's role in the war against ISIL following the cessation of hostilities in Syria in February 2016, published on 24 March 2016, what representations he has made to his Turkish counterpart on seeking a negotiated, peaceful and democratic solution to the conflict in predominantly Kurdish areas of Turkey.","Biography information for Tommy Sheppard","Tommy Sheppard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38477","38477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521583","2016-06-06","Department of Health","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his Department's policy is on media appearances of officials of his Department; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38479","38479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521584","2016-06-06","Department of Health","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his Department's policy is on the use of the NHS logo by organisations and people outside the NHS.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38480","38480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521585","2016-06-06","Department of Health","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the NHS logo is a registered trademark; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38481","38481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521586","2016-06-06","Department of Health","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his policy is on conscientious objection for midwives asked to (a) advise on and (b) participate in abortions.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38464","38464"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521587","2016-06-06","Department of Health","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will review the (a) commissioning framework and (b) tariff payment for bereavement care for families who have suffered a stillbirth or neonatal death.","Biography information for Antoinette Sandbach","Antoinette Sandbach","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38493","38493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521588","2016-06-06","Department of Health","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of differences between bereavement support services for families who have suffered a stillbirth or neonatal death commissioned by clinical commissioning groups and such services provided by hospital trusts; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Antoinette Sandbach","Antoinette Sandbach","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38494","38494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521589","2016-06-06","Department of Health","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will request that the Joint Committee on Vaccination and Immunisation undertakes an assessment of the recommendation from the Britain Against Cancer conference held in December 2015 to report its review on extending HPV vaccination to boys in 2016.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38503","38503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521590","2016-06-06","Department of Health","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to improve the recruitment and retention of paramedics employed by the London Ambulance Service.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38487","38487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521591","2016-06-06","Department of Health","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the findings of the King's Fund Quarterly Monitoring Report 19, published in May 2016; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38528","38528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521592","2016-06-06","Department of Health","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the relationship between hand hygiene compliance levels across the NHS and rates of trust-assigned MRSA bacteraemia in 2015.","Biography information for Andrea Jenkyns","Andrea Jenkyns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38529","38529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521593","2016-06-06","Department of Health","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many heart valve replacements have been undertaken in the last five years for which figures are available; and whether those figures are comparable to France and Germany.","Biography information for Fabian Hamilton","Fabian Hamilton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38514","38514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521594","2016-06-06","Department of Health","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of patients who participated in medical research in each year since 2010; and what steps his Department is taking to encourage patient participation in such research.","Biography information for Derek Thomas","Derek Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38468","38468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521595","2016-06-06","Department of Health","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he plans to review the current time limits for abortion.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38524","38524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521596","2016-06-06","Department of Health","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his policy is on the introduction of abortion up to birth.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38469","38469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521597","2016-06-06","Department of Health","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that training in the diagnosis and treatment of ME forms part of medical students' training.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38505","38505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521598","2016-06-06","Department of Health","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the effectiveness of NHS blood donation services.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38504","38504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521599","2016-06-06","Department of Health","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of the availability of (a) special care neonatal and level three cots and (b) transfers between neonatal units and between neonatal intensive care units.","Biography information for Wendy Morton","Wendy Morton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38509","38509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521600","2016-06-06","Department of Health","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many visits by (a) Ministers and (b) officials from his Department were made to Coventry in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38510","38510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521601","2016-06-06","Department of Health","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when NHS England plans to publish its response to its consultation on developing a method to assist investment decisions in specialised services.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38427","38427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521602","2016-06-06","Department of Health","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that NHS England's new prioritisation framework for making decisions on investment in specialised services will be aligned with the recommendations of the accelerated access review.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38428","38428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521603","2016-06-06","Department of Health","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when NHS England plans to publish the (a) agenda for and (b) minutes of the June 2016 meeting of its Commissioning Priorities Advisory Group.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38429","38429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521604","2016-06-06","Department of Health","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the (a) efficiency of existing diagnostic tests and (b) effectiveness of current treatments for Lyme disease.","Biography information for Colleen Fletcher","Colleen Fletcher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38421","38421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521605","2016-06-06","Department of Health","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether healthcare professionals in Greater Manchester expressed support for the introduction of charging for (a) primary care and (b) emergency care in response to his Department's consultation, Making a fair contribution: consultation on the extension of charging overseas visitors and migrants using the NHS in England.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38448","38448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521606","2016-06-06","Department of Health","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Answer of 2 March 2016 to Question 29364, what the grounds are for the Public Health England Office for Data Release denying requests made to it for information collected via the Systemic Anti-Cancer Therapy dataset; what the timescale is for that office to respond to any requests made; and whether there will be a public announcement setting out the date when requests for data may be made to that office.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38457","38457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521607","2016-06-06","Department of Health","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, for what reasons GP practice lists have been closed in East Grinstead; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38453","38453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521608","2016-06-06","Department of Health","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he plans to take to expand health services in Mid Sussex to meet increased housing and population numbers.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38455","38455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521609","2016-06-06","Department of Health","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to page 23 of the final report of the Review on Antimicrobial Resistance, published in May 2016, what steps his Department is taking to address the low level of adherence to proper hand hygiene in hospitals and other care settings.","Biography information for Andrea Jenkyns","Andrea Jenkyns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38542","38542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521610","2016-06-06","Department of Health","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to page 23 of the final report of the Review on Antimicrobial Resistance, published in May 2016, what steps his Department is taking to address the substantial evidence gaps relating to effectiveness and cost-effectiveness of new technologies for improving hygiene.","Biography information for Andrea Jenkyns","Andrea Jenkyns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38543","38543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521611","2016-06-06","Department of Health","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions his Department has had with NHS Supply Chain on that organisation's decision on the choice of urine drainage bags available through the NHS Core List Programme.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38552","38552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521612","2016-06-06","Department of Health","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when his Department plans to implement the National Screening Committee's recommendations on introducing (a) the Faecal Immunochemical Test into the bowel screening programme and (b) HPV as the primary test in the cervical screening programme.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38559","38559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521613","2016-06-06","Department of Health","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the National Screening Committee's recommendations for the bowel and cervical screening programmes; and whether he plans to support those recommendations","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38558","38558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521614","2016-06-06","Department of Health","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department has assessed the effect on (a) patients and (b) patient choice of centralised procurement.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38573","38573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521615","2016-06-06","Department of Health","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many junior doctors were employed by the NHS in (a) London and (b) England in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38595","38595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521616","2016-06-06","Department of Health","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will re-open the consultation on pharmacy dispensing models and displaying prices on medicines that closed on 17 May 2016 in order to allow respondents to take into account revised information on the safety profile of hub and spoke dispensing models.","Biography information for Stephen Pound","Stephen Pound","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38588","38588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521617","2016-06-06","Department of Health","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of whether the NHS Constitution's commitment to provide a comprehensive service available to all, irrespective of gender, is consistent with a policy of not providing an HPV vaccination programme for boys.","Biography information for Mr John Baron","Mr John Baron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38577","38577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521618","2016-06-06","Department of Health","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effects on public health of changes in the number of paramedics employed by the London Ambulance Service.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38578","38578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521619","2016-06-06","Department of Health","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many GP practices in Dorset provide phlebotomy services; and what action his Department is taking to increase the number of practices providing such services.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38599","38599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521620","2016-06-06","Home Office","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Written Statement of 14 January 2016, HCWS70, on immigration detention, when she plans to publish the joint Department of Health, NHS and Home Office mental health plan.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38594","38594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521621","2016-06-06","Home Office","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to safeguard the existing rights under EU treaties of non-UK EU citizens living in the UK in the event of a vote to leave the EU.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38564","38564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521622","2016-06-06","Home Office","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps Border Force has taken to identify and assist potential victims of trafficking and modern slavery at ports across the UK.","Biography information for James Berry","James Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38560","38560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521623","2016-06-06","Home Office","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to improve the timely conclusion of investigations by the Independent Police Complaints Commission; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stewart Jackson","Mr Stewart Jackson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38454","38454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521624","2016-06-06","Home Office","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications to the Disclosure and Barring Service from people living in Croydon have taken more than 60 days to process in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38438","38438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521625","2016-06-06","Home Office","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average time taken to complete a Disclosure and Barring Service check, including the time taken by the Metropolitan Police, was in London for each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38437","38437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521626","2016-06-06","Home Office","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the current average waiting time is for the completion of pre-employment checks by the Disclosure and Barring Service in (a) England and Wales and (b) London.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38435","38435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521627","2016-06-06","Home Office","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of Disclosure and Barring Service checks in London were completed within the 60-day maximum in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38436","38436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521628","2016-06-06","Home Office","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications to the Disclosure and Barring Service from people living in Dulwich and West Norwood constituency have taken more than 60 days to process in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38511","38511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521629","2016-06-06","Home Office","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department has taken to increase the effectiveness of the UK Border Force as a law enforcement organisation since it was established as an independent operational command within her Department in 2012.","Biography information for Edward Argar","Edward Argar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38471","38471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521630","2016-06-06","Home Office","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average conviction rate has been in England and Wales in each of the last three years; and what that rate has been where the offender is someone brought back to the UK under a European Arrest Warrant.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38525","38525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521631","2016-06-06","Home Office","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the oral contribution of the Prime Minister of 11 May 2016, Official Report, column 627, when she plans to decide whether to launch an independent panel hearing into the policing of the miners' strike at Orgreave in 1984.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38449","38449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521632","2016-06-06","Department of Health","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what provisions are in place at detention centres for people suffering with mental health conditions.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38461","38461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521633","2016-06-06","Home Office","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what security checks her Department carries out on EU citizens seeking entry to the UK; how those checks differ from such checks on non-EU citizens seeking entry to the UK; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38465","38465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521634","2016-06-06","Home Office","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what resources her Department has allocated to publicise the Psychoactive Substances Act 2016.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38490","38490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521635","2016-06-06","Department for International Development","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to increase reporting and improve data collection of violence against women and girls in developing countries.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38517","38517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521636","2016-06-06","Department for International Development","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether her Department plans to publish a specific strategy for policy-influencing work relating to violence against women and girls and monitoring of that work.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38516","38516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521637","2016-06-06","Department for International Development","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what training and learning activities her Department undertakes to improve evidence collection for the design and implementation of violence against women and girls programmes.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38523","38523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521638","2016-06-06","Department for International Development","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment her Department has made of potential steps to reduce corruption in Pakistan (a) in general and (b) within the political system.","Biography information for Julian Knight","Julian Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38506","38506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521639","2016-06-06","Department for International Development","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much funding her Department has provided to (a) the UNHCR and (b) other organisations to support Eritrean refugees in Ethiopia in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Dame Caroline Spelman","Mrs Caroline Spelman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38434","38434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521640","2016-06-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his Department records acts of alleged genocide by Daesh reported by refugees who are provided with humanitarian aid by his Department to support future criminal investigations.","Biography information for Derek Thomas","Derek Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38432","38432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521641","2016-06-06","Department for International Development","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if her Department will take steps to increase prevention programmes for violence against women and girls in developing countries.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38518","38518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521642","2016-06-06","Department for International Development","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to encourage donor organisations and partner countries to include action on violence against women and girls in their sectoral programmes.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38570","38570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521643","2016-06-06","Department for International Development","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to (a) create awareness of and (b) encourage access to its research on violence against women and girls for external organisations.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38561","38561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521644","2016-06-06","Department for International Development","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the potential effect of the closure of the Dadaab refugee camp in Kenya on refugees in that region; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38574","38574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521645","2016-06-06","Ministry of Justice","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average fine is for people found guilty of breaking the law by not allowing the transport of blind people and their guide dogs in licensed taxis under the Equality Act 2010.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38556","38556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521646","2016-06-06","Ministry of Justice","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prosecutions each local authority has brought under the provisions governing a blind person's right to travel in licensed taxis with their guide dogs of the Equality Act 2010.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38557","38557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521647","2016-06-06","Ministry of Justice","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many fines were issued for disability discrimination against blind people with guide dogs by licensed taxi drivers in each year for which information is available.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38554","38554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521648","2016-06-06","Ministry of Justice","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the cost of hotel bookings made for (a) Ministers, (b) special advisers and (c) officials in his Department in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38532","38532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521649","2016-06-06","Ministry of Justice","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of reform of access to legal aid in cases of domestic violence on children; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38519","38519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521650","2016-06-06","Ministry of Justice","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment his Department has made of the effect on applicants for legal aid in cases of domestic violence of the requirement that victims provide substantial written evidence; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38521","38521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521651","2016-06-06","Ministry of Justice","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what provision is made within the family justice system to assist victims of domestic abuse in private family law cases who do not have the financial capability to provide documented evidence when applying for legal aid.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38522","38522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521652","2016-06-06","Ministry of Justice","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to his letter to the Chair of the Justice Committee, dated 19 May 2016, how much of the additional £10 million to deal with prison safety has been allocated to each prison.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38533","38533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521653","2016-06-06","Ministry of Justice","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will review charges made by the (a) police and (b) NHS for obtaining official documentation when such papers are required for applications for legal aid in cases of domestic abuse.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38520","38520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521654","2016-06-06","Ministry of Justice","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to reduce the number of women in prison.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38545","38545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521655","2016-06-06","Ministry of Justice","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the size of the prison population in (a) 2020, (b) 2025, (c) 2030 and (d) 2050.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38440","38440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521656","2016-06-06","Ministry of Justice","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent steps he has taken to reduce the number of people serving sentences of imprisonment for public protection after their prison tariff has expired.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38441","38441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521657","2016-06-06","Ministry of Justice","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what plans he has to review the position of people serving sentences of imprisonment for public protection who are significantly over tariff and assessed as low or medium risk.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38512","38512"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521658","2016-06-06","Ministry of Justice","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many appeals were submitted to the Tribunals Service from appellants in (a) Coventry, (b) the West Midlands and (c) England regarding (i) personal independence payment, (ii) employment and support allowance, (iii) income support, (iv) jobseeker's allowance and (v) tax credits in 2015; and how many of those appeals were successful.","Biography information for Colleen Fletcher","Colleen Fletcher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38483","38483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521659","2016-06-06","Ministry of Justice","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many appellants in (a) Coventry, (b) the West Midlands and (c) England are waiting for the Tribunals Service to list their Fist-Tier Tribunal Social Security and Child Support appeal in respect of personal independence payment.","Biography information for Colleen Fletcher","Colleen Fletcher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38484","38484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521660","2016-06-06","Ministry of Justice","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average length of time was for the Tribunals Service to administer a First-Tier Tribunal Social Security and Child Support appeal in respect of (a) personal independence payment, (b) employment and support allowance, (c) income support, (d) jobseeker's allowance and (e) tax credits in (i) Coventry, (ii) the West Midlands and (iii) England in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Colleen Fletcher","Colleen Fletcher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38485","38485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521661","2016-06-06","Cabinet Office","2016-05-25","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the average hourly earnings were of 10 Downing Street's (a) BME and (b) non-BME employees in (i) 2015 and (ii) 2016.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38430","38430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521662","2016-06-06","Department for Transport","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans he has to increase the number of locations with paid toll crossings in England.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38422","38422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521663","2016-06-06","Department for Transport","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the number of uninsured vehicles in the UK; and how many vehicles were seized for unpaid insurance in each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38423","38423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521664","2016-06-06","Department for Transport","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what proportion of (a) tolls and (b) fines related to non-payment of tolls were unpaid on the Dartford Crossing in each of the last three years; and what the cost to the public purse of unpaid fines was in each of those years.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38424","38424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521665","2016-06-06","Department for Transport","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment he has made of the extent of a backlog of driving licence renewal applications for people over 70 years old.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38478","38478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521666","2016-06-08","Department for Transport","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to increase the speed of passenger trains between Doncaster and Hull; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38452","38452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521667","2016-06-06","Department for Transport","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what funding  streams are available for the construction of new rail stations in the North of England.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38499","38499"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521668","2016-06-06","Department for Transport","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the average waiting time for an assessment by the DVLA Drivers Medical Group was for (a) all drivers and (b) drivers requiring re-assessment on a regular basis on medical grounds in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38467","38467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521669","2016-06-06","Department for Transport","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions he has had about funding the construction of a new rail station at Horden.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38498","38498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521670","2016-06-06","Department for Transport","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps (a) his Department and (b) the DVLA is taking to increase the number of seizures of uninsured vehicles.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38466","38466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521671","2016-06-06","Department for Transport","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the average time was for processing driving licence renewal applications for people over 70 years old in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38470","38470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521673","2016-06-06","Department for Transport","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assurances he has received from Vauxhall that all owners of Zafira B models were informed about the changes to the vehicle safety recall relating to those cars.","Biography information for Stewart Malcolm McDonald","Stewart Malcolm McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38568","38568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521674","2016-06-06","Department for Transport","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to help ensure that the independent testing of Vauxhall Zafiras meets the aims set out for that independent testing.","Biography information for Stewart Malcolm McDonald","Stewart Malcolm McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38569","38569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521675","2016-06-06","Department for Transport","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what progress has been made on finalising the route for the second stage of High Speed 2; and when he expects to announce the decision on that route.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38540","38540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521676","2016-06-06","Department for Transport","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he has asked Vauxhall to reclassify the root cause of the risk of fire in Zafira B models that have been subject to vehicle safety recalls to include premature corrosion of the blower motor.","Biography information for Stewart Malcolm McDonald","Stewart Malcolm McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38567","38567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521677","2016-06-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what guidelines his Department issues on continued payment of housing benefit when a person remains in hospital for longer than 52 weeks.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38575","38575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521678","2016-06-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what impact assessment has been conducted on the change in the method of payment of Disability Living Allowance to being solely into a bank account.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38576","38576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521679","2016-06-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if his Department will provide additional financial support to disabled people whose income will be reduced as a result of (a) changes in the employment and support allowance work-related activity group and (b) the universal credit work allowance as a result of provisions in the Welfare Reform and Work Act 2016.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38566","38566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521680","2016-06-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether the Pensions Regulator will now update its rules on defined benefit (DB) schemes to clarify the legal responsibilities of DB trustees.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38500","38500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521681","2016-06-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people who have been reassessed to remain in the support group of employment support allowance have medical conditions that are not expected to improve.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38513","38513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521682","2016-06-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to support people who require a mobility vehicle during a personal independence payment mandatory reconsideration and appeal process.","Biography information for Susan Elan Jones","Susan Elan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38459","38459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521683","2016-06-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, (a) how many and (b) what proportion of work capability assessments were carried out within 13 weeks of submission of a new employment and support allowance claim in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38476","38476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521684","2016-06-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department has taken to allow pensioners to draw down all funds within any public pension schemes that existed before 2016-17.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38495","38495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521685","2016-06-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, (a) how many and (b) what proportion of personal independence payment applications were disallowed in (i) 2015 and (ii) the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Colleen Fletcher","Colleen Fletcher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38482","38482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521686","2016-06-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what guidance his Department issued to Jobcentre Plus offices on the use of letters to jobseekers which combine information about attending a mandatory interview with a work coach and non-mandatory group information sessions.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38418","38418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521687","2016-06-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, which Jobcentre Plus offices he has contacted on the use of their own locally-developed claimant communications rather than using those produced by his Department.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38419","38419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521689","2016-06-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what reports he has received on local Jobcentre Plus offices developing their own claimant communications rather than using those produced by his Department.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38420","38420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521690","2016-06-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people with inflammatory bowel disease as their main disabling condition granted a personal independence payment between April 2013 and October 2015 were (a) new claimants, (b) expiring time-limited claimants and (c) claimants whose circumstances had changed.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38439","38439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521691","2016-06-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-05-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 25 April 2016 to Question 34939, on local housing allowance, when he expects to publish information on the proportion of local authorities that will receive Targeted Affordability Funding.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38443","38443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521046","2016-06-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-05-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when he made his most recent assessment of UK compliance with (a) the Cluster Munitions Convention, (b) the Arms Trade Treaty and (c) the EU Consolidated Arms Export Criteria.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38234","38234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521047","2016-06-06","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-05-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether (a) he and (b) ministers of his Department have met with the new Welsh Government to discuss the steel crisis.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38236","38236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521048","2016-06-06","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-05-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many meetings of the British-Irish Council Ministers of his Department took part in since May 2013.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38265","38265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521049","2016-05-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-05-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department is taking to support businesses in Stafford constituency.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38309","38309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521050","2016-05-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-05-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent steps his Department has taken to increase the level of access to credit for businesses in Stafford constituency in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38310","38310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521051","2016-05-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-05-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to protect children from in-game selling and promotions when playing games online.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38300","38300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521052","2016-05-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-05-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment his Department has made of the effectiveness of legislation for protecting children from in-game selling and promotions when playing games online.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38301","38301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521053","2016-06-06","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-05-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many new businesses have been set up in Manchester, Withington constituency since May 2010.","Biography information for Jeff Smith","Jeff Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38352","38352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521054","2016-06-06","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-05-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate his Department has made of the value of the higher education sector to the economy.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38397","38397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521055","2016-06-06","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-05-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what discussions his Department has had with the Home Office on the effect of existing legislation on overseas students on steps to increase the number of international students studying in the UK.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38398","38398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521056","2016-06-06","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-05-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect of the proposals in his Department's White Paper, Success as a knowledge economy: teaching excellence, social mobility and student choice, published on 16 May 2016, on the number of new providers in the higher education sector by 2020.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38399","38399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521057","2016-05-26","Department for Transport","2016-05-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment the Government has made of the potential effect of expansion at (a) Heathrow and (b) Gatwick Airport on the number of jobs that will be created in the North East by (i) 2030 and (ii) 2050.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38316","38316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521058","2016-05-26","HM Treasury","2016-05-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans his Department has to submit evidence to the independent review of the British Bakers Association Access to Banking Protocol led by Professor Russell Griggs.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38318","38318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521059","2016-05-26","HM Treasury","2016-05-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent discussions his Department has had with the British Bankers' Association Industry Protocol on how effectively banks have applied and implemented the Protocol during its first year and the efficacy of the Protocol in mitigating the effect of branch closures on (a) local businesses and (b) the elderly, disabled and other vulnerable customers.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38320","38320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521060","2016-05-26","HM Treasury","2016-05-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the efficacy of the British Bankers' Association Industry Protocol on Branch Closures in mitigating the effect of branch closures on local businesses and customers.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38319","38319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521061","2016-05-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-05-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with which organisations Ministers of his Department have met to discuss the review of enforcement of the Consumer Protection from Unfair Trading Regulations 2008 in respect of copycat packaging of branded electrical goods in the last three months.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38332","38332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521062","2016-05-26","HM Treasury","2016-05-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of bank branch closures on (a) affected communities, (b) local businesses and (c) customers.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38333","38333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521063","2016-05-26","HM Treasury","2016-05-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the extent to which banks have effectively applied and implemented the British Banker's Association Industry Protocol.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38334","38334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521064","2016-06-06","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-05-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what plans his Department has to promote Scottish exports and businesses at the International Festival for Business 2016.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38123","38123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521065","2016-05-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-05-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, for what reasons the Government is not proceeding with joint auditing or increased tendering in its transposition of EU Regulation No. 537/2014 on statutory auditing of public-interest entities.","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38137","38137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521066","2016-05-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-05-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to the Answer of 10 May 2016 to Question 36447, how much of the £10.3 million of minimum wage arrears recovered in 2015-16 was recovered from the 145 employers who were not issued with a Notice of Underpayment and who did not have to pay a penalty.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38139","38139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521067","2016-05-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-05-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to the Answer of 14 September 2015 to Question 8859, how many employers took advantage of the National Minimum Wage campaign announced on 30 July 2015 to self-report their non-compliance with the National Minimum Wage; how many workers were identified as having been underpaid by those employers; and what the total sum was of arrears recovered for those workers.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38140","38140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521068","2016-05-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-05-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to encourage private investment in laboratories involved in research and science.","Biography information for Chris Green","Chris Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38141","38141"
