"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010587","2018-11-22","Home Office","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps his Department has taken to ensure that asylum seekers accommodated as part of the asylum accommodation and support contracts are not placed in shared bedrooms with non-family members.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193513","193513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010588","2018-11-22","Home Office","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 19 November 2018 to Question 191442 on Diamorphine: Glasgow, what the guidelines are on chronic heroin addiction treatment plans as a condition of his Department permitting a diamorphine prescribing licence to local authorities.","Biography information for Mr Paul Sweeney","Mr Paul Sweeney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193514","193514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010589","2018-11-23","Home Office","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many creative and sporting tier 5 visa applications (a) were subject to an administrative review and (b) had the original decision overturned following an administrative review in each year from 2012 to 2017.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193515","193515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010590","2018-11-23","Home Office","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 19 November 2018 to Question 191442 on Diamorphine: Glasgow, what the timetable is for the decision on whether to grant a diamorphine prescribing licence to Glasgow City Health and Social Care Partnership.","Biography information for Mr Paul Sweeney","Mr Paul Sweeney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193516","193516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010591","2018-11-23","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the number of women employed by his Department in each year since 2000.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193517","193517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010592","2018-11-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he has (a) undertaken and (b) made an assessment of the outcomes of studies produced by other bodies of the effects on (a) air quality and (b) human health of different sized waste incinerators.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193365","193365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010593","2018-11-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he has made an assessment of the effects on human health of waste incinerators situated in urban areas.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193366","193366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010594","2018-11-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he takes to assess the potential effects on human health of proposed waste incinerators.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193367","193367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010595","2018-11-22","Home Office","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessments are undertaken to ensure that decisions to classify immigration cases as complex comply with the Equality Act 2010.","Biography information for Drew Hendry","Drew Hendry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193518","193518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010596","2018-11-23","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he plans to respond to Question 188038, tabled on 5 November 2018, by the hon. Member for East Londonderry.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193391","193391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010597","2018-11-22","Treasury","2018-11-20","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment the Government has made of the potential merits of reducing the VAT rate for goods and services required for the essential repair and maintenance of (a) residential and (b) commercial buildings.","Biography information for Drew Hendry","Drew Hendry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193519","193519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010598","2018-11-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the march-in rights provided by the US Bayh-Dole Act 1980, if he will introduce such rights in Medical Research Council (MRC) contracts, to enable the Government to license a patent to a third party for a MRC-funded medicine.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193426","193426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010599","2018-11-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to Articles 81 and 82 of the Draft Agreement on the withdrawal of the United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland from the European Union and the European Atomic Energy Community, dated 14 November 2018, what bodies external to the UK will verify compliance with UK obligations under the Treaty on the Non-Proliferation of Nuclear Weapons.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193427","193427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010600","2018-11-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to Article 83, paragraphs (1) and (2) of the Draft Agreement on the withdrawal of the UK from the EU and the European Atomic Energy Agency, dated 14 November 2018, who will own fissile materials stored at UK nuclear facilities after the UK withdraws from that agency.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193428","193428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010601","2018-11-22","Department for International Development","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to promote trade for development.","Biography information for Giles Watling","Giles Watling","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193609","193609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010602","2018-11-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many fines have been levied against Scottish limited partnerships for failing to register a person of significant control.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193520","193520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010603","2018-11-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate he has made of the number of Scottish limited partnerships that are qualifying under the terms of the Scottish Partnerships (Register of People with Significant Control) Regulations 2017 and the Companies and Partnerships (Accounts and Audit) Regulations 2013.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193521","193521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010604","2018-11-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when he plans to publish a response to his Department's consultation on the review of limited partnership law.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193522","193522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010605","2018-11-23","Home Office","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the High Court Judgement K & Anor, R (on the application of) v Secretary of State for the Home Department of 8 November 2018, how the back payments to victims of trafficking will be made; who will be responsible for administering the back payments to victims who have left the National Referral Mechanism; whether the back payments will result in any deduction from any other benefits; and what financial literacy support will be put in place to help victims manage large payments.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193523","193523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010606","2018-11-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps are being taken to respond to the recommendations of the UN Fact Finding Mission on Myanmar on referrals to the International Criminal Court.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193392","193392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010607","2018-11-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to collect evidence of sexual violence in Kachin and Shan States in Myanmar.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193393","193393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010608","2018-11-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of progress of the peace process in Myanmar.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193394","193394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010609","2018-11-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to improve treatment for children after surgery.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193429","193429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010610","2018-11-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to prevent African swine fever in wild boar entering the UK.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193430","193430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010611","2018-11-23","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners gave birth in prison without a midwife present in the last year for which information is available.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193395","193395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010612","2018-11-23","Home Office","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will publish the timetable for the (a) drafting of and (b) public consultation on the statutory guidance on victim support as set out under Section 49 of the Modern Slavery Act 2015.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193524","193524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010613","2018-11-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he has made an assessment of the implications for his policies of the November 2018 analysis by the County Councils Network entitled A Fair Future for Counties; and whether his Department has discussed that analysis with the Ministry for Housing, Communities and Local Government.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193431","193431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010614","2018-11-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the November 2018 report by Rethink entitled Right treatment, right time, whether he is taking steps to ensure that NHS England works with NHS Improvement and NHS Digital to develop the Mental Health Dashboard further to include operational data for people treated in secondary and community care under a mental health trust.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193432","193432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010615","2018-11-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how he plans to spend the £4.5 billion announced on 23 July 2018 for social prescribing.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193433","193433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010616","2018-11-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the November 2018 report by Rethink entitled Right treatment, right time, whether he is taking steps to lower the average 14-week wait for assessment and 19-week wait for treatment for people with schizophrenia, bipolar disorder, personality disorder, eating disorders and other severe mental illnesses.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193434","193434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010617","2018-11-22","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the membership of the University Royal Naval Unit in Glasgow in each year from 2008-2018.","Biography information for Andrew Bowie","Andrew Bowie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193525","193525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010618","2018-11-22","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the membership of the University Royal Naval Unit in Liverpool in each year from 2008-2018.","Biography information for Andrew Bowie","Andrew Bowie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193526","193526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010619","2018-11-22","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the membership of the University Royal Naval Unit in Southampton in each year from 2008-2018.","Biography information for Andrew Bowie","Andrew Bowie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193527","193527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010620","2018-11-22","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the membership of the University Royal Naval Unit in Birmingham in each year from 2008-2018.","Biography information for Andrew Bowie","Andrew Bowie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193528","193528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010621","2018-11-22","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the membership of the University Royal Naval Unit in London in each year from 2008-2018.","Biography information for Andrew Bowie","Andrew Bowie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193529","193529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010622","2018-11-22","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the membership of the University Royal Naval Unit in Bristol in each year from 2008-2018.","Biography information for Andrew Bowie","Andrew Bowie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193530","193530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010623","2018-11-22","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the membership of the University Royal Naval Unit in Manchester in each year from 2008-2018.","Biography information for Andrew Bowie","Andrew Bowie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193531","193531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010624","2018-11-22","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the membership of the University Royal Naval Unit in Sussex in each year from 2008-2018.","Biography information for Andrew Bowie","Andrew Bowie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193532","193532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010625","2018-11-22","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the membership of the University Royal Naval Unit in Cambridge in each year from 2008-2018.","Biography information for Andrew Bowie","Andrew Bowie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193533","193533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010626","2018-11-22","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the membership of the University Royal Naval Unit in Northumbria in each year from 2008-2018.","Biography information for Andrew Bowie","Andrew Bowie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193534","193534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010627","2018-11-22","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the membership of the University Royal Naval Unit in Oxford in each year from 2008-2018.","Biography information for Andrew Bowie","Andrew Bowie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193535","193535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010628","2018-11-22","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the membership of the University Royal Naval Unit in Wales in each year from 2008-2018.","Biography information for Andrew Bowie","Andrew Bowie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193536","193536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010629","2018-11-22","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the membership of the University Royal Naval Unit in Yorkshire in each year from 2008-2018.","Biography information for Andrew Bowie","Andrew Bowie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193537","193537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010630","2018-11-23","Wales Office","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales,  pursuant to the Answer of 19 November 2018 to Question 191441 on UK Shared Prosperity Fund: Wales, whether he has made an assessment of the potential effect on the Welsh economy and regional development of a lower level of Shared Prosperity Fund funding than that received under the European Regional Development Fund and European Social Fund in Wales.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193538","193538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010631","2018-11-22","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the membership of the University Royal Naval Unit in Devon in each year from 2008-2018.","Biography information for Andrew Bowie","Andrew Bowie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193539","193539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010632","2018-11-23","Wales Office","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, pursuant to the Answer of 19 November 2018 to Question 191441, whether he has estimated the current level of funding that Wales receives from the European Regional Development Fund, European Social Fund, Horizon 2020, Rural Development Funding and the Wales-Ireland Co-operation scheme.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193540","193540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010633","2018-11-23","Wales Office","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, pursuant to the Answer of 19 November 2018 to Question 191441, whether the Government plans to allocate more or less than £2.1 billion from the Shared Prosperity Fund to Wales between 2021 and 2027.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193541","193541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010634","2018-11-23","Wales Office","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, pursuant to the Answer of 19 November 2018 to Question 191441, whether those specific priorities will differ from the priorities that have informed the allocation of funding from the European Regional Development Fund and European Social Fund in Wales.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193542","193542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010635","2018-11-23","Wales Office","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, pursuant to the Answer of 19 November 2018 to Question 191441, whether those amounts are lower or higher than the amount that those areas have received in the same period from the European Regional Development Fund and European Social Fund.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193543","193543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010636","2018-11-23","Department for International Trade","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether his Department plans to review arms sales to the Government of Cameroon.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193544","193544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010637","2018-11-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether he plans to support employers in the provision of pastoral care programmes.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193545","193545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010638","2018-11-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many health visitors (a) resigned and (b) otherwise left their posts in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193546","193546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010639","2018-11-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will make it her policy to disregard income from an Armed Forces medical pension when calculating universal credit payments.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193435","193435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010640","2018-11-23","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what account he has taken of the interests of the British Overseas Territories, apart from Gibraltar, in preparing the Draft Agreement on the withdrawal of the United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland from the European Union and the European Atomic Energy Community and the Outline Political Declaration on the Future Relationship.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193396","193396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010641","2018-11-23","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what his assessment is of the potential cost to industry of Articles 40-125 of the draft Withdrawal Agreement.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193397","193397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010642","2018-11-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Transport on the costs incurred by the NHS in treating conditions caused by air pollution arising from different forms of transport.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193372","193372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010643","2018-11-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what his assessment is of the potential costs to the pharmaceutical industry of Article 45 of the Draft Agreement on the withdrawal of the United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland from the European Union and the European Atomic Energy Community.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193398","193398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010644","2018-11-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions the Government has had with the Government of Spain on the future of Gibraltar during the negotiations on leaving the EU.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193373","193373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010645","2018-11-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what progress has been made on the oil and gas sector deal.","Biography information for Andrew Bowie","Andrew Bowie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193547","193547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010646","2018-11-23","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the UK leaving the EU on data regulations in the UK.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193374","193374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010647","2018-11-27","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to reduce the number of empty Annington Property Limited dwellings.","Biography information for Sir Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","Sir Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193368","193368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010648","2018-11-27","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to improve the standard of accommodation in Annington Property Limited properties.","Biography information for Sir Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","Sir Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193369","193369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010649","2018-11-23","Department for Transport","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to increase the affordability of electric cars.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193375","193375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010650","2018-11-22","Treasury","2018-11-20","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 7 November 2018 to Questions 185525-8 on Tax Avoidance, whom he defines as (a) employers and (b) individuals.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193399","193399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010651","2018-11-22","Treasury","2018-11-20","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer,  pursuant to the Answer of 7 November 2018 to Questions 185525-8 on Tax Avoidance, (a) how many and (b) what proportion of the scheme users classified as employers are individuals who were paid through their own limited companies.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193400","193400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010652","2018-11-23","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 12 November 2018 to Question 187366, how many places in residential women's centres were funded by the Government in 2016.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193548","193548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010653","2018-11-23","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the real terms change in his Departmental Resource Budgets (a) was in each year since 2010 and (b) is projected to be in each year to 2022.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193549","193549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010654","2018-11-23","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of trends in staffing levels in community rehabilitation centres from their introduction until the end of the 2016-17 financial year.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193550","193550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010655","2018-11-22","Treasury","2018-11-20","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 7 November 2018 to Questions 185525-8 on Tax Avoidance, how many promoters and providers of disguised remuneration schemes have been (a) pursued or investigated and (b) penalised or prosecuted by HMRC.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193401","193401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010656","2018-11-22","Treasury","2018-11-20","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 7 November 2018 to Questions 185525-8 on Tax Avoidance, what estimate he has made of the number of promoters and providers of disguised remuneration schemes he expects to be (a) pursued or investigated and (b) penalised or prosecuted by HMRC.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193402","193402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010657","2018-11-23","Department for Education","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to improve access to universities for students with special educational needs.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193376","193376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010658","2018-11-23","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to his Department's press release entitled Life sentences for killer drivers published on 15 October 2017, what the timetable is for the introduction of changes in sentences for causing death by dangerous or careless driving.","Biography information for Judith Cummins","Judith Cummins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193551","193551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010659","2018-11-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when he plans to publish the Social Care Green Paper.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193552","193552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010660","2018-11-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the effect of the interim report of the Independent Review of the Mental Health Act on the rate of detentions under that Act in the NHS Bolton clinical commissioning group area.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193436","193436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010661","2018-11-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the timetable is for his Department to respond to the recommendations of the Independent Review of the Mental Health Act.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193437","193437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010662","2018-11-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what funding the Government has made available to local authorities to support elderly people who are lonely.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193553","193553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010663","2018-11-22","Treasury","2018-11-20","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the Draft Agreement on the withdrawal of the United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland from the European Union and the European Atomic Energy Community, published in November 2018, what his assessment is of the effect of articles 47-50 of that agreement on UK supply chains.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193403","193403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010664","2018-11-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what funding the Government has made available to local authorities to support older people with a severe disability.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193554","193554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010665","2018-11-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many high-rise blocks owned by local authorities and housing associations will have their cladding removed between 1 November 2018 and 20 March 2019.","Biography information for Emma Dent Coad","Emma Dent Coad","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193610","193610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010666","2018-11-22","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate he has made of the proportion of children who engage in the Chief Medical Officer’s national recommended level of activity.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193555","193555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010667","2018-11-23","Home Office","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the High Court judgment in respect of K & Anor, R (on the application of) v Secretary of State for the Home Department of 8 November 2018; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193377","193377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010668","2018-11-23","Home Office","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the High Court judgment in respect of K & Anor, R (on the application of) v Secretary of State for the Home Department of 8 November 2018, when all victims of trafficking will have their subsistence rates restored to the higher level as required by that judgment.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193378","193378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010669","2018-11-22","Home Office","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the High Court judgment in respect of K & Anor, R (on the application of) v Secretary of State for the Home Department of 8 November 2018, whether all victims of trafficking who had their subsistence rates cut between March and November 2018 and subsequently exited the National Referral Mechanism will receive the full back payment.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193379","193379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010670","2018-11-22","Department for Education","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans he has put in place to ensure that every primary school child is able to undertake at least 60 minutes of moderate to vigorous physical activity a day.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193556","193556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010671","2018-11-23","Home Office","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when he will issue guidance under Section 49 of the Modern Slavery Act 2015; and what plans he has to consult on that guidance.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193380","193380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010672","2018-11-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether an assessment has been made of the potential merits of creating a regulatory body to oversee the pricing of domestic LPG supplies.","Biography information for Bill Grant","Bill Grant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193557","193557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010673","2018-11-22","Cabinet Office","2018-11-20","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will publish the locations of all UK ministerial visits to Kirkcaldy and Cowdenbeath constituency since the 2010 general election.","Biography information for Lesley Laird","Lesley Laird","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193558","193558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010674","2018-11-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what guidance he has issued to local authorities on social care charges for vulnerable people receiving benefits; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193381","193381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010675","2018-11-22","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what plans his Department has put in place for the effect on Scotland of the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Lesley Laird","Lesley Laird","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193559","193559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010676","2018-11-22","Department for Education","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to ensure that the SEND focus group supporting the development of the early career framework for teachers includes an expert in speech, language and communication needs.","Biography information for Emma Hardy","Emma Hardy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193560","193560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010677","2018-11-22","Department for Education","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how his Department defines school readiness in (a) speech, (b) language and (c) communication skills.","Biography information for Emma Hardy","Emma Hardy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193561","193561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010678","2018-11-22","Department for Education","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he has taken to fund What Works and other research centres in (a) storing and (b) sharing evidence of interventions that support speech, language and communication.","Biography information for Emma Hardy","Emma Hardy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193562","193562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010679","2018-11-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will review the level of charges for social care payable by vulnerable people on benefits; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193382","193382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010680","2018-11-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans NHS England has to (a) work with commissioners, provider organisations and patients to identify metrics to indicate progression in children and young people with speech, language and communication needs and (b) support providers to collect and benchmark that data.","Biography information for Emma Hardy","Emma Hardy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193563","193563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010681","2018-11-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps NHS England is taking to ensure that the NHS long-term plan is informed by the findings of the Bercow: Ten Years On report, published on 20 March 2018.","Biography information for Emma Hardy","Emma Hardy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193564","193564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010682","2018-11-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 24 July 2018 to Question 164870 on Incinerators: Health Hazards, when those papers will be published.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193404","193404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010683","2018-11-22","Cabinet Office","2018-11-20","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate his Department has made of the number of children with cancer in the UK.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193438","193438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010684","2018-11-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what guidance his Department provides to patients planning to travel overseas for stem cell treatment.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193565","193565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010685","2018-11-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to encourage children to brush their teeth daily.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193566","193566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010686","2018-11-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to tackle dementia.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193567","193567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010687","2018-11-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what training is delivered to nurses to inform their treatment of pre-eclampsia.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193568","193568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010688","2018-11-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to reduce the number of people experiencing pre-eclampsia.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193569","193569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010689","2018-11-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many autistic children are in solitary confinement in assessment and treatment units.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193570","193570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010690","2018-11-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information his Department holds on the number of people experiencing gum disease in the last 12 months for which information is available.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193571","193571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010691","2018-11-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much has been disbursed by the NHS in relation to medical negligence claims in the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193572","193572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010692","2018-11-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the level of religious freedom and tolerance in Eritrea.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193383","193383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010693","2018-11-23","Home Office","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether he has plans to replace the biometric service at Post Offices with the new UK Visa and Citizenship Application Service centres.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193573","193573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010694","2018-11-22","Department for Education","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to increase the number of children being adopted.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193574","193574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010695","2018-11-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to tackle diabetes experienced by children to help ensure they live long lives.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193575","193575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010696","2018-11-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to reduce cases of melanoma in men.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193576","193576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010697","2018-11-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what estimate he has made of the number of people seeking to leave Eritrea; and what steps the Khartoum Process is taking to reduce this.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193384","193384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010698","2018-11-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to people who are in seasonal self-employment and are also employed, whether the minimum income floor will apply to their self employed income when they are not in employment even if their average income is over the minimum income floor when their employed income is included.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193577","193577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010699","2018-11-23","Home Office","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when he plans to answer Questions 190963 and 190959 tabled on 13 November 2018 by the hon. Member for Manchester, Gorton.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193578","193578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010700","2018-11-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of the provision of support for heating costs provided by local authorities and Housing Associations to social housing tenants while unsafe cladding systems are removed from their homes.","Biography information for Emma Dent Coad","Emma Dent Coad","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193611","193611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010701","2018-11-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of her Department's frontline staff have received training relating to domestic abuse.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193579","193579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010702","2018-11-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to ensure employment support allowance and personal independence payment assessors are (a) informed of and (b) abide by mandates instructing communications via an agreed advocate rather than directly with the client.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193580","193580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010703","2018-11-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many NHS prescription fines have been issued to people in (a) Easington constituency and (b) England in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193439","193439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010704","2018-11-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps she is taking to encourage older people to participate in the workforce.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193581","193581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010705","2018-11-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 15 November 2018 to Question 190427, what information her Department collects on the number of home consultations carried out by the Centre for Health and Disabilities Assessment as part of its universal credit contract.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193440","193440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010706","2018-11-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 22 October to Question 180697, how many NHS patients have received a Freestyle Libre glucose monitoring system to date.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193441","193441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010707","2018-11-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 17 October 2018 to 178277, what support his Department provides to claimants suffering multiple epileptic seizures on a weekly basis to gain and sustain employment; and what guidance his Department provides to employers on ensuring that people with epilepsy are supported in the workplace.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193442","193442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010708","2018-11-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant the Answer of 14 September 2018 to Question 171353; how many universal credit claims were determined on the scrutiny of written information alone in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193443","193443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010709","2018-11-22","Department for Transport","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans his Department has to review the guidelines on installing charging points for electric vehicles; and if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of allowing a charging point to be installed at a place other than the address at which the vehicle is registered.","Biography information for Sandy Martin","Sandy Martin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193612","193612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010710","2018-11-23","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what progress he has made in negotiating a co-operative accord on culture and education with the EU.","Biography information for James Frith","James Frith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193582","193582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010711","2018-11-22","Department for Transport","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 25 July 2018 to Question 164905 on Motorcycles: Noise, when his Department plans to publish the research it has commissioned to support police and highway authorities in combating and enforcing against excessive noise from motorcycles.","Biography information for Sir Hugo Swire","Sir Hugo Swire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193405","193405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010712","2018-11-22","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 20 September 2018 to Question 172598, if she will set a reasonable waiting time target for the hearing of cases by the social security tribunal.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193444","193444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010713","2018-11-22","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 20 September 2018 to Question 172598, what the (a) shortest, (b) longest and (c) average waiting time was for social security tribunal hearings at the Sunderland tribunal venue in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193445","193445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010714","2018-11-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will give universal credit work coaches greater autonomy over whether to apply sanctioning guidelines to a claimant when they consider that a sanction would hinder that person's ability to (a) engage further with Jobcentre Plus and (b) gain employment.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193446","193446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010715","2018-11-23","Home Office","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 19 November 2018 to Question 191448, whether the immigration health surcharge will apply to EU citizens arriving in the UK during the transition period.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193583","193583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010716","2018-11-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will review the (a) purpose, (b) merits and (c) economic and health effects of sanctioning social security claimants in receipt of an out-of-work benefit.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193447","193447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010717","2018-11-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 18 September 2018 to Question 172595, what plans she has for the legacy benefit IT systems when the roll-out of universal credit is completed.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193448","193448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010718","2018-11-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many benefit sanctions have been issued to Easington constituents in receipt of (a) jobseekers allowance, (b) employment and support allowance and (c) universal credit in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193449","193449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010719","2018-11-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 24 October 2018 to Question 183335, if he will make an assessment of the effect on NHS staffing levels of the IR35 tax changes.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193450","193450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010720","2018-11-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 19 October to Questions 178312, what the timetable is for the Regulator of Social Housing to advertise for the appointment of the additional board member; and what steps he is taking to ensure that social housing tenants are made aware of those posts.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193584","193584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010721","2018-11-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many applicants were interviewed for the two new posts as Board Members of the Regulator of Social Housing in January and February 2018.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193585","193585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010722","2018-11-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, by what process were the new Board Members of Homes England recruited.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193586","193586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010723","2018-11-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 19 October 2018 to Question 178310, if he will ensure that as part of its In-Depth Assessment process the Regulator of Social Housing makes inquiries with tenants into their perception of the performance of a downgraded housing association before reaching a decision whether to upgrade that organisation.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193587","193587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010724","2018-11-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 25 January 2018 to Question 123615, what opportunities were given to tenants and leaseholders of social landlords to provide evidence to the Tailored Review of the Homes and Communities Agency in 2016.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193588","193588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010725","2018-11-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps the Regulator of Social Housing has taken since the departure of the chief executive of Clarion Housing Group to ensure that its repairs and housing management services for tenants do not deteriorate.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193589","193589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010726","2018-11-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether the board of the Regulator of Social Housing will have a role in determining the threshold for the serious detriment test used to establish the governance-rating of housing associations.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193590","193590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010727","2018-11-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, who has been a member on the board of the (a) Homes and Communities Agency and (b) Social Housing Regulator and its predecessor regulation committee since May 2010.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193591","193591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010728","2018-11-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what information she holds on the (a) number of past and present employees of Johnston Press who will be affected by its decision to transfer its pension scheme to the Pension Protection Fund and (b) potential proportionate change in the value of the pensions of those employees.","Biography information for Lesley Laird","Lesley Laird","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193592","193592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010729","2018-11-22","Attorney General","2018-11-20","To ask the Attorney General, what guidance he has published on laying criminal charges against people with dementia.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193451","193451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010730","2018-11-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions,what the Pension Protection Fund has determined the value of Johnston Press pension deficit to be.","Biography information for Lesley Laird","Lesley Laird","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193593","193593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010731","2018-11-23","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when the Government plans to issue the call for evidence as part of the review into rogue bailiffs announced on 2 April 2018.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193452","193452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010732","2018-11-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the effect of the abolition of student bursaries on the number of people applying to become nursing students.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193453","193453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010733","2018-11-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what statistics his Department holds of the number of vacancies for (a) nursing staff and (b) doctors in the NHS in England.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193454","193454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010734","2018-11-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to protect children from the health effects  of toxic air.","Biography information for Sir Henry Bellingham","Sir Henry Bellingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193406","193406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010735","2018-11-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what information her Department holds on the steps the JPI Media Board will take to mitigate pension losses and to stabilise the pension scheme for employees of Johnston Press.","Biography information for Lesley Laird","Lesley Laird","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193594","193594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010736","2018-11-23","Cabinet Office","2018-11-20","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate the Government has made of the number of crimes which go unreported.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193455","193455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010737","2018-11-22","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what information his Department holds on the current board members of JPI Media; and of those members, how many served previously on the Johnston Press board.","Biography information for Lesley Laird","Lesley Laird","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193595","193595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010738","2018-11-23","Treasury","2018-11-20","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 19 November 2018 to Question 190861 on Religious Buildings: VAT, whether his Department has plans to remove VAT on the repair and maintenance of places of worship after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham P Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193456","193456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010739","2018-11-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many Health and Safety Executive inspector posts are currently vacant; and what assessment she has made of the effect of those vacancies on the ability of the Health and Safety Executive to attend incidents.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193596","193596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010740","2018-11-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of incidents reported to the Health and Safety Executive (HSE) were attended by an HSE inspector in each of the last three years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193597","193597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010741","2018-11-23","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to incorporate the Government's new loneliness strategy into its policy formulation process.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193407","193407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010742","2018-11-23","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether the Shared Prosperity Fund will fund (a) capital interventions and (b) revenue interventions.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193408","193408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010743","2018-11-23","Wales Office","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what recent bilateral meetings he has had with (a) the Welsh First Minister, (b) other Welsh Cabinet Ministers and (c) UK Government Cabinet Ministers on ensuring that the proposed Shared Prosperity Fund respects devolution settlements.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193409","193409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010744","2018-11-23","Home Office","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what right to work checks employers will have to carry out on EU citizens during the period between March 2019 and December 2020 in the event of the UK leaving the EU (a) with and (b) without a deal.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193613","193613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010745","2018-11-23","Home Office","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what evidence of an EU citizen’s right to work will an employer be required to check during the period between March 2019 and December 2020 in the event of the UK leaving the EU (a) with and (b) without a deal.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193614","193614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010746","2018-11-23","Home Office","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what right to work checks employers will be required to carry out on EU citizens in the event that the transition period is extended; and how employers will be able to distinguish between EU citizens who arrived (a) before the UK left the EU in March 2019, (b) during the originally planned transition period between March 2019 and December 2020 and (c) during the period that the transition is extended for after December 2020.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193615","193615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010747","2018-11-22","Home Office","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what right to rent checks landlords will be required to carry out on EU citizens during the period between March 2019 and December 2020 in the event of the UK leaving the EU (a) with and (b) without a deal.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193616","193616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010748","2018-11-22","Home Office","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether landlords will be required to distinguish between EU citizens who arrived in the UK (a) before March 2019 and (b) during the transition period between March 2019 and December 2020 to check a person's right to rent.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193617","193617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010749","2018-11-22","Department for Education","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 16 October 2018 to Questions 175942, 175943 and 175944, what information his Department (a) holds and (b) records by special educational needs primary need on children educated in settings other than a schools or awaiting a school place.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193385","193385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010750","2018-11-23","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prosecutions there have been under section 76 of the Serious Crime Act 2015.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193457","193457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010751","2018-11-23","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of defences made using section 76(8) of the Serious Crime Act 2015 within criminal trials have been successful.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193458","193458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010752","2018-11-22","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the number of prosecutions made under Section 76 of the Serious Crime Act (2015) which involved a disabled survivor of abuse giving evidence.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193459","193459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010753","2018-11-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of whether UK citizens may continue to seek consular and diplomatic protection from EU member states in countries where the UK is not represented after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193410","193410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010754","2018-11-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether the funding allocated to social housing providers to remove Grenfell-style cladding systems will also cover compensation to tenants who face increased heating costs as a result of the removal of that cladding.","Biography information for Emma Dent Coad","Emma Dent Coad","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193618","193618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010755","2018-11-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what recent assessment he has made of the fire risks posed by non-aluminium composite material cladding systems.","Biography information for Emma Dent Coad","Emma Dent Coad","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193619","193619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010756","2018-11-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether funding for social housing providers to remove Grenfell-style cladding systems includes the cost of the removal of non-aluminium composite material cladding systems.","Biography information for Emma Dent Coad","Emma Dent Coad","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193620","193620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010757","2018-11-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of whether there are financial links between the far-right in the UK and similar groups in the US.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193598","193598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010758","2018-11-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to Answer of 19 November 2018 to Question 190871 on Cancer, what the potential (a) advantages and (b) disadvantages are of implementing the national data guardian opt-out on the quality of the National Cancer Patient Experience Survey data.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193460","193460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010759","2018-11-22","Church Commissioners","2018-11-20","To ask the Right Honourable Member for Meriden, representing the Church Commissioners, what discussions the Church Commissioners have had on maintaining the Christian community in the Middle East.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193461","193461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010760","2018-11-23","Treasury","2018-11-20","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent discussions he has had with the Governor of the Bank of England on the Venezuelan Government's request to withdraw their deposited gold from its reserves.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham P Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193462","193462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010761","2018-11-22","Department for Transport","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the viability of future private funding for (a) road and (b) rail projects as a result of the decision in Budget 2018 to abolish private finance initiatives.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193599","193599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010762","2018-11-22","Treasury","2018-11-20","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he plans to take to ensure that the European Court of Auditors declare EU accounts to be fair and accurate before the Treasury pays the bill for the UK to leave the EU.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193463","193463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010763","2018-11-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he has assessed the economic effect on farmers of articles 40 to 46 and 92 to 97 of the Government's EU withdrawal agreement.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193411","193411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010764","2018-11-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate his Department has made of the number of patients with primary progressive multiple sclerosis who could potentially benefit from treatment with Ocrelizumab.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193600","193600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010765","2018-11-23","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 15 November 2018 to Question 190375, on museums and galleries to which bodies those figures refer.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193412","193412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010766","2018-11-23","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 15 November to Question 190379, what proportion of people on the boards of which (a) broadcasters and (b) galleries sponsored by his Department are (i) BAME and (ii) female.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193413","193413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010767","2018-11-23","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how much of the Life Chances Fund remains to be spent.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193601","193601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010768","2018-11-23","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how much profit has been distributed to investors in social impact bonds since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193602","193602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010769","2018-11-23","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care on the mental health and wellbeing of serving personnel and veterans.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193603","193603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010770","2018-11-23","Home Office","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of whether local authorities have sufficient power to tackle anti-social behaviour.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193604","193604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010771","2018-11-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, for what reasons the (a) finance, (b) human resources and (c) communications functions of the Environment Agency have been moved into the centrally-managed work of his Department; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193464","193464"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010772","2018-11-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many staff have been transferred from the Environment Agency to his Department in each month from July 2016 to October 2018; what the reasons were for each of those transfers; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193465","193465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010773","2018-11-22","Department for Education","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when the Education and Skills Funding Agency regulations for 16-19 education provision on student eligibility for funding in 2019-20 will be published.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193466","193466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010774","2018-11-23","Department for Education","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans he has to introduce a national entitlement to the study of religious education in schools.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193357","193357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010775","2018-11-23","Department for Education","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to ensure that state-funded schools meet the statutory obligation to teach religious education as part of a broad and balanced curriculum.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193359","193359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010776","2018-11-23","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what progress TechCity UK has made in promoting (a) women and (b) BAME people within that organisation.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193467","193467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010777","2018-11-23","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what progress Tech City has made in funding tech start-ups led by (a) women and (b) BAME people.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193468","193468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010778","2018-11-23","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions the Government has had with the Inclusive Tech Alliance in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193469","193469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010779","2018-11-23","Cabinet Office","2018-11-20","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many investigations into Secretary of State resignations there have been in the last five years.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193470","193470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010780","2018-11-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to help raise awareness of Phenylketonuria.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193605","193605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010781","2018-11-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information the Department of Health and Social Care hold on the number of NHS patients currently admitted to assessment and treatment units operated by the private sector.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193471","193471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010782","2018-11-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the cost to NHS England of payments to private companies for the treatment of patients with (a) learning disabilities and (b) autism in in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193472","193472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010783","2018-11-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many dowries have been paid by the NHS to local authorities for patients leaving hospital after five or more years in inpatient care at the point of discharge since 2016.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193473","193473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010784","2018-11-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what proportion of the workforce at the Catapult centres is (a) female, (b) BAME and (c) disabled.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193474","193474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010785","2018-11-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of community mental health teams between 1999 and 2009.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193475","193475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010786","2018-11-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of people found eligible for support from Access to Work do not submit a claim for equipment or support after their award has been approved.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193360","193360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010787","2018-11-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of community mental health teams in each year since 2009.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193476","193476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010788","2018-11-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what support is available to help people challenge employers who do not act on Access to Work recommendations in a timely manner.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193361","193361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010789","2018-11-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 15 November 2018 to Question 188044 on Preventive Medicine, (a) what the definition of community services is and (b) which prevention interventions are covered.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193414","193414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010790","2018-11-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when his Department plans to respond to the Green Paper on modernising consumer markets.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193477","193477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010791","2018-11-23","Department for Education","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Written Statement of 19 November 2018 on TEF reviewer appointment, HLWS1060, what provision will be made for students to give evidence to the review.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193415","193415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010792","2018-11-23","Department for Education","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether he intends to propose to the Teaching Excellence and Student Outcomes Framework (TEF) reviewer that there should be student representation on the advisory group that will be set up for the review of the TEF.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193416","193416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010793","2018-11-23","Department for Education","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions he has had with colleagues in the Department of Health on expanding the number of higher education nursing programmes covering learning disability and mental health nursing.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193417","193417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010794","2018-11-22","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what his policy is on paying to the Government of Iran funds relating to the purchase of Chieftain tanks through International Military Services.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193478","193478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010795","2018-11-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what his policy is on the unconditional release of UK citizens detained as political prisoners overseas.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193479","193479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010796","2018-11-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policy on the unconditional release of UK citizens detained as political prisoners overseas of paying to the Government of Iran funds relating to the purchase of Chieftain tanks through International Military Services.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193480","193480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010797","2018-11-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans she has to visit the Govan Job Centre in December 2018; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193606","193606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010798","2018-11-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he discussed with his Iranian counterpart the release of Nazanin Zaghari-Ratcliffe in relation to the payment to the Government of Iran funds relating to the purchase of Chieftain tanks through International Military Services.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193481","193481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010799","2018-11-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans she has to visit a food bank in the Glasgow South West constituency in December 2018; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193607","193607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010800","2018-11-23","Treasury","2018-11-20","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many basic rate taxpayers in (a) England, (b) Wales and (c) Northern Ireland have contacted HM Revenue and Customs to register their residence in Scotland in the last 12 months; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193608","193608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010153","2018-11-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 16 October 2018 to Question 177617 on Eating disorders, if he will list the 70 new or extended community services providing specialist community-based care for eating disorders that are open or in development by the local authority in which they are based.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192754","192754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010154","2018-11-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the declaration from the recent London Conference on the Illegal Wildlife Trade, what progress his Department has made on implementing the declaration of the previous such conference in 2014.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192755","192755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010155","2018-11-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the implications are for his Department's policy of the US Government's recently stated policy to remain committed to military intervention in Syria as long as Iranian forces retain a presence in that country.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192958","192958"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010156","2018-11-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of progress on negotiations between the Syrian Democratic Council and the Government of Syria.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192756","192756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010157","2018-11-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the validity of recent reports by the Moroccan Association of Human Rights of a recent increase in attacks against sub-Saharan African migrants in Morocco.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192757","192757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010158","2018-11-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his Angolan counterpart on the expulsion of Congolese nationals from that country since 25 September 2018.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192758","192758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010159","2018-11-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what information his Department holds on the number of Congolese nationals expelled from Angola by the Government of that country since 25 September 2018.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192759","192759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010160","2018-11-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received of (a) human rights abuses perpetrated against Congolese nationals and (b) looting and theft of Congolese nationals’ possessions during recent operations by the Angolan authorities to expel Congolese nationals from that country.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192760","192760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010161","2018-11-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his counterpart in the Democratic Republic of Congo on reported recent threats by members of that country’s Government to repatriate refugees from neighbouring countries in response to the recent expulsion of Congolese nations from Angola.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192761","192761"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010162","2018-11-21","Cabinet Office","2018-11-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, at what level and how often does his Department review advisory guidance issued by NCSC and GCHQ.","Biography information for Mr Ian Liddell-Grainger","Mr Ian Liddell-Grainger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192762","192762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010163","2018-11-21","Cabinet Office","2018-11-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the National Cyber Security Centre (NCSC) news story entitled ZTE: NCSC advice to select telecommunications operators with national security concerns, published on 16 April 2018, whether he authorised the NCSC's letter on ZTE dated 13 April 2018.","Biography information for Mr Ian Liddell-Grainger","Mr Ian Liddell-Grainger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192763","192763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010164","2018-11-21","Cabinet Office","2018-11-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the National Cyber Security Centre (NCSC) news story entitled ZTE: NCSC advice to select telecommunications operators with national security concerns, published on 16 April 2018, what his Department's assessment of the reasons NCSC stated in its letter of 13 April 2018 that there was no way to mitigate potential risk from using ZTE technology is.","Biography information for Mr Ian Liddell-Grainger","Mr Ian Liddell-Grainger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192764","192764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010165","2018-11-21","Cabinet Office","2018-11-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the National Cyber Security Centre (NCSC) news story entitled ZTE: NCSC advice to select telecommunications operators with national security concerns, published on 16 April 2018, if his Department conducted an urgent review of NCSC's advice in its letter of 13 April 2018.","Biography information for Mr Ian Liddell-Grainger","Mr Ian Liddell-Grainger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192765","192765"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010166","2018-11-21","Department for International Development","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the potential implications for her Department's policies of the findings of the 5th November report by the Office of the Inspector General at the United States Department of Defense concerning the diversion of USAID funding for humanitarian assistance in Syria to support the activities of the Ha’yat Tahrir Al-Sham militia.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192766","192766"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010167","2018-11-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his counterpart in the Democratic Republic of Congo on the findings of the recent UN report which noted a 35 per cent increase in human rights violations related to restrictions of democratic space before the presidential election on 23 December 2018 in that country.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192767","192767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010168","2018-11-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his Ugandan counterpart on preparations for a national dialogue between political parties in that country.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192768","192768"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010169","2018-11-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government plans to take to help ensure that the parliamentary election on 20 December 2018 in Togo is conducted in a free and fair manner.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192769","192769"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010170","2018-11-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the parliamentary election in Togo on 20 December 2018 on efforts to resolve the political crisis in that country.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192817","192817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010171","2018-11-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the progress of talks on reaching agreement on the formation of a unity government in Lebanon.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192818","192818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010172","2018-11-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his Iraqi counterpart on the integration of members of the popular mobilisation units into that country’s national armed forces.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192819","192819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010173","2018-11-22","Home Office","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the suitability criterion for Settled Status that the applicant must not be subject to a removal decision under the EEA Regulations on the grounds of their non-exercise or misuse of rights under Directive 2004/38/EC, whether his Department will check whether (a) each applicant for Settled Status is exercising their rights under Directive 2004/38/EC or (b) it is those subject to a removal decision before they make their application for Settled Status who will be refused on suitability grounds.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192820","192820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010174","2018-11-22","Department for International Development","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what estimate she has made of the cost in cash terms of maintaining Official Development Assistance at 0.7 per cent of gross national income in the next financial year.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192770","192770"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010175","2018-11-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to the Kyrgyzstan authorities on ensuring the promotion of freedom of religion by that country's State Commission for Religious Affairs.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192771","192771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010176","2018-11-22","Cabinet Office","2018-11-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office,  what the five most common cancer diagnoses were among (a) men and (b) women in (i) 2007 and (ii) 2017.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192772","192772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010177","2018-11-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment his Department has made of the implications for his policies on (a) green energy subsidies and (b) taxes on fossil fuel emissions of the findings of the UN Intergovernmental Panel on Climate Change's special report, Global warming of 1.5 degrees, published in October 2018.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192821","192821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010178","2018-11-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what plans his Department has to ensure that proposed new permitted development rights do not undermine local affordable housing targets.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192822","192822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010179","2018-11-22","Department for Education","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of the SEND budgets of local authorities.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192823","192823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010180","2018-11-22","Department for Education","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what information his Department holds on how many local authorities have overspent on special education needs and disability budgets in each year since 2014.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192824","192824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010181","2018-11-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment his Department has made of the global rate of biodiversity loss; and what effect that assessment has had on the formulation of his Department's policies.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192825","192825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010182","2018-11-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make it his policy to reform the Mental Health Act 1983 better to protect the rights of those who are in receipt of mental health treatment.","Biography information for Janet Daby","Janet Daby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192945","192945"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010183","2018-11-21","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the Government plans to introduce further measures to support veterans of Operation Herrick.","Biography information for Adam Holloway","Adam Holloway","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192773","192773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010184","2018-11-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what technology and innovation projects have been supported by Innovate UK in Northern Ireland in the last two years.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192774","192774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010185","2018-11-22","Department for International Trade","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what progress he has made on securing trade deals with third countries after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Mike Amesbury","Mike Amesbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192826","192826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010186","2018-11-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to his Department’s consultation entitled NICE recommendations: charging and appeal panels which closed on 14 September 2018, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect on the sustainability of the smallest businesses of (a) charging for NICE appraisals and (b) charging for NICE appraisals at a discounted rate.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192827","192827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010187","2018-11-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to his Department’s consultation entitled NICE recommendations: charging and appeal panels which closed on 14 September 2018, what discussions his Department has had with NICE on exempting the smallest companies from the proposed appraisal charges.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192828","192828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010188","2018-11-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the European Medicines Verification Organisation’s report, NMVO’s Fee Models Status, published on 21 August 2018, what discussions his Department has had with the UK's National Medicines Verification Organisation on reducing the entrance fees for small companies in line with those of other European countries.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192829","192829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010189","2018-11-21","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to ensure that small and medium sized UK business and manufacturing is protected from eviction by large international firms.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192722","192722"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010190","2018-11-22","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 15 November 2018 to Question 190539 on Army: Young People, for what were the reasons for under-18s applicants not starting basic training in each of the three years for which information is provided.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192830","192830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010191","2018-11-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate his Department has made of the number of jobs that have been lost as a result of commercial evictions arising from land acquisition by Lidl.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192723","192723"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010192","2018-11-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the outcomes of projects reducing children’s exposure to air pollution in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Christine Jardine","Christine Jardine","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192831","192831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010193","2018-11-21","Department for International Development","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, with reference to the absence in the UN Global Compact for Migration of the UK’s three main objectives as set out in the Prime Minister’s addresses to the UN General Assembly in 2016 and 2017, whether the Government plans to decline to sign that compact at the forthcoming UN meeting in Morocco.","Biography information for Sir John Hayes","Mr John Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192724","192724"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010194","2018-11-22","Home Office","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether people who have been granted leave to land will have to apply for settled status once the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192832","192832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010195","2018-11-22","Cabinet Office","2018-11-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to his oral Answer of 14 November 2018, Official Report, column 298, on the Infected Blood Inquiry, whether his reference to compensation relates to acceptance of Government liability or ex-gratia payments.","Biography information for Mr Paul Sweeney","Mr Paul Sweeney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192833","192833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010196","2018-11-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 15 November 2018 to Question 186941 on Offshore Industry: Oil, and with reference to the October 2018 IPCC report recommendations on the reduction in emissions required by 2030, what his Department's definition is of the time frame medium term.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192706","192706"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010197","2018-11-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 15 November 2018 to Question 189542, on Carbon Budgets: Climate Change, and with reference to the Committee on Climate Change’s assessment of the cost-effectiveness of the UK’s decarbonisation pathway, whether it is mandatory that the committee includes an assessment of the costs incurred by continued high carbon emissions.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192707","192707"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010198","2018-11-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many occupational therapists have been employed in NHS mental health services in each month since March 2017.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192834","192834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010199","2018-11-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many professionally qualified staff have been employed in NHS mental health services in each month since March 2017.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192835","192835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010200","2018-11-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many clinical support staff have been employed in NHS mental health services in each month since March 2017.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192836","192836"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010201","2018-11-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many administrative and infrastructure staff have been employed in NHS mental health services in each month since March 2017.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192837","192837"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010202","2018-11-22","Department for Education","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions (a) he and (b) the Minister of State for Apprenticeships and Skills has had with M&C Saatchi on their contract to relaunch the marketing campaign promoting apprenticeships.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192725","192725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010203","2018-11-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many allied health professionals and scientific, therapeutic and technical staff have been employed in NHS mental health services in each month since March 2017.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192838","192838"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010204","2018-11-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent estimate she has made of the number and proportion of unemployed people who are entitled to claim (a) jobseeker's allowance and (b) universal credit but are not doing so.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192726","192726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010205","2018-11-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate she has made of the number of people who have ceased to claim income-related benefits in the most recent 12 months for which data is available; and for what reasons those people ceased to make such claims.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192727","192727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010206","2018-11-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of new claims for (a) jobseeker's allowance and (b) employment and support allowance were processed within (i) five days and (ii) 10 days or longer within the most recent 12 months for which data are available.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192728","192728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010207","2018-11-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of new claims for universal credit were processed (a) within five weeks, (b) between five and ten weeks and (c) in ten weeks or longer in the most recent 12 months for which data are available.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192729","192729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010208","2018-11-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people applied (a) successfully and (b) unsuccessfully for short term benefit advance or advance payments in the most recent 12 months for which data are available.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192730","192730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010209","2018-11-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many universal credit claimants each month are having more than 40 per cent of their monthly award deducted to repay debt.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192731","192731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010210","2018-11-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many members of staff directly employed by her Department or contracted to work for her Department have been available to answer incoming calls to each benefit telephone line in each of the last 18 months for which data are available.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192732","192732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010211","2018-11-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many calls have been made to each of her Department's benefit telephone lines in each of the last 18 months for which data are available.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192733","192733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010212","2018-11-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the (a) shortest, (b) longest and (c) average waiting times for calls to each of her Department's benefit telephone lines were in each of the last 18 months for which data are available.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192734","192734"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010213","2018-11-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate she has made of the number of households in Northern Ireland that will receive the winter fuel payment in 2018-19.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192775","192775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010214","2018-11-22","Department for International Trade","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, pursuant to the Answer of 14 November 2018 to Question 189652 on Department for International Trade: Staff, how many of his Department's staff were employed in (a) non-EU countries, (b) EU countries, (c) Greece and (d) Italy in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192839","192839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010215","2018-11-22","Department for Education","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what information he holds on the amount that Gloucestershire County Council has spent on legal activity regarding education, health and care plans in each of the last three years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192698","192698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010216","2018-11-21","Department for Education","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate his Department has made of the number of education, health and care (EHC) plans produced by Gloucestershire County Council in each of the last three years; and on how many occasions that Council did (a) not proceed with an EHC Needs Assessment, (b) not produce an EHC plan when one had been requested and (c) receive an appeal against the support included in the plan in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192708","192708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010217","2018-11-21","Department for Education","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many new special schools have opened since the introduction of free schools in 2010.","Biography information for Marsha De Cordova","Marsha De Cordova","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192946","192946"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010218","2018-11-22","Department for International Trade","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what progress he has made on securing a trade agreement with the US.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192776","192776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010219","2018-11-22","Department for International Trade","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what his timetable is for agreeing a trade deal with the US.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192777","192777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010220","2018-11-22","Department for International Trade","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, on what dates the UK-US trade and investment working group has met.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192778","192778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010221","2018-11-22","Department for International Trade","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, who the members are of the UK-US trade and investment working group.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192779","192779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010222","2018-11-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many trained psychiatrists have (a) joined and (b) left NHS-employment every year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192709","192709"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010223","2018-11-22","Cabinet Office","2018-11-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what recent estimate he has made of the number of young people moving from small towns and villages to large towns and cities; and what assessment he has made of the effect of that movement on the long-term sustainability of small towns and villages.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192710","192710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010224","2018-11-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the percentage change in the amount of people diagnosed with mental health conditions has been in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192735","192735"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010225","2018-11-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the percentage change in Government spending on mental health conditions has been in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192736","192736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010226","2018-11-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care,  what recent research he has (a) commissioned and (b) considered of the effects on human health of municipal waste incinerators on people living within (i) 0.5 kilometre, (ii) 0.9 kilometre, (iii) 1 kilometre, (iv) 2 kilometres and (v) 5 kilometres of those incinerators.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192711","192711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010227","2018-11-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 8 November 2018 to Question 186415 on Buildings: Insulation, what assessment his Department has made of the risk posed by non-ACM building materials on the external walls of buildings.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192840","192840"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010228","2018-11-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent evidence his Department has considered on the effects of waste incinerators on the health of people living downwind of such incinerators.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192712","192712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010229","2018-11-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the security situation in Central African Republic.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192737","192737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010230","2018-11-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to ensure UK citizens overseas are able to register at UK embassies in order to receive consular support and information.","Biography information for Derek Thomas","Derek Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192841","192841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010231","2018-11-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 8 November 2018 to Question 186415 on Buildings: Insulation, what assessment his Department has made of the ability of high-rise building owners to identify combustible insulation and cladding other than ACM cladding on their external walls.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192842","192842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010232","2018-11-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what comparative assessment his Department has made of the effect on public health of municipal waste incinerators and anaerobic digestion of waste.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192713","192713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010233","2018-11-21","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when the decision was taken to close the University Royal Navy Unit attached to Aberdeen University.","Biography information for Andrew Bowie","Andrew Bowie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192843","192843"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010234","2018-11-22","Home Office","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether he plans to bring forward legislative proposals to implement the provisions of the draft Regulation of the European Parliament and of the Council on preventing the dissemination of terrorist content online.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192780","192780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010235","2018-11-21","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Royal Navy (a) officers and (b) sailors recruited in each year between 2008 and 2018 are or were (i) graduates and (ii) undergraduates of the University of Aberdeen.","Biography information for Andrew Bowie","Andrew Bowie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192844","192844"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010236","2018-11-21","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many applications there were to join the Royal Navy in each year between 2008 and 2018; and how many of those applications in each of those years were successful.","Biography information for Andrew Bowie","Andrew Bowie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192845","192845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010237","2018-11-21","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how the size of an area’s catchment group for University Royal Navy Unit recruitment is calculated.","Biography information for Andrew Bowie","Andrew Bowie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192846","192846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010238","2018-11-21","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans there are to relocate the Aberdeen University Officer Training Corps.","Biography information for Andrew Bowie","Andrew Bowie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192847","192847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010239","2018-11-21","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the annual cost of running the University Royal Naval Unit in Aberdeen was in each year between 2008 and 2012.","Biography information for Andrew Bowie","Andrew Bowie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192848","192848"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010240","2018-11-21","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the annual cost of running the University Royal Naval Unit in Edinburgh was in each year between 2012 and 2018.","Biography information for Andrew Bowie","Andrew Bowie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192849","192849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010241","2018-11-21","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the annual cost of running the University Royal Naval Unit in Glasgow was in each year between 2008 and 2018.","Biography information for Andrew Bowie","Andrew Bowie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192850","192850"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010242","2018-11-21","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the annual cost of running the University Royal Naval Unit in Liverpool was in each year between 2008 and 2018.","Biography information for Andrew Bowie","Andrew Bowie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192851","192851"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010243","2018-11-21","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the annual cost of running the University Royal Naval Unit in Southampton was in each year between 2008 and 2018.","Biography information for Andrew Bowie","Andrew Bowie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192852","192852"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010244","2018-11-21","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the annual cost of running the University Royal Naval Unit in Birmingham was in each year between 2008 and 2018.","Biography information for Andrew Bowie","Andrew Bowie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192853","192853"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010245","2018-11-21","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the annual cost of running the University Royal Naval Unit in London was in each year between 2008 and 2018.","Biography information for Andrew Bowie","Andrew Bowie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192854","192854"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010246","2018-11-21","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the annual cost of running the University Royal Naval Unit in Bristol was in each year between 2008 and 2018.","Biography information for Andrew Bowie","Andrew Bowie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192855","192855"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010247","2018-11-21","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the annual cost of running the University Royal Naval Unit in Manchester was in each year between 2008 and 2018.","Biography information for Andrew Bowie","Andrew Bowie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192856","192856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010248","2018-11-21","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the annual cost of running the University Royal Naval Unit in Sussex was in each year between 2008 and 2018.","Biography information for Andrew Bowie","Andrew Bowie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192857","192857"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010249","2018-11-21","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the annual cost of running the University Royal Naval Unit in Cambridge was in each year between 2008 and 2018.","Biography information for Andrew Bowie","Andrew Bowie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192858","192858"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010250","2018-11-21","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the annual cost of running the University Royal Naval Unit in Northumbria was in each year between 2008 and 2018.","Biography information for Andrew Bowie","Andrew Bowie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192859","192859"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010251","2018-11-21","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the annual cost of running the University Royal Naval Unit in Devon was in each year between 2008 and 2018.","Biography information for Andrew Bowie","Andrew Bowie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192860","192860"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010252","2018-11-21","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the membership of the University Royal Naval Unit in Aberdeen was in each year between 2008 and 2012.","Biography information for Andrew Bowie","Andrew Bowie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192861","192861"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010253","2018-11-21","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the membership of the University Royal Naval Unit in Edinburgh was in each year between 2012 and 2018.","Biography information for Andrew Bowie","Andrew Bowie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192862","192862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010254","2018-11-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, on what date subsequent to the murder of Jamal Khashoggi (a) officials and (b) Ministers in his Department were made aware of the existence of evidence that Saudi officials had been seeking to take Mr Khashoggi to Riyadh.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192863","192863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010255","2018-11-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, on what date subsequent to the murder of Jamal Khashoggi (a) officials and (b) Ministers in his Department were made aware of the existence of evidence that Saudi officials had been involved in Mr Khashoggi's death.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192864","192864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010256","2018-11-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, on what date (a) officials and (b) Ministers in his Department heard a copy of the audio recording from Turkish authorities of the murder of Jamal Khashoggi.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192865","192865"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010257","2018-11-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether any of the 17 Saudi officials and agents subjected to Magnitsky sanctions by the United States on 15 November 2018 were among the entourage who accompanied Crown Prince Mohammed Bin Salman on his visit to the UK in April 2018.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192866","192866"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010258","2018-11-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his US counterpart on the US State Department’s latest assessment of the involvement of Crown Prince Mohammed Bin Salman in ordering the murder of Jamal Khashoggi.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192867","192867"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010259","2018-11-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, to which schemes and projects with the specific purpose of reducing children’s exposure to air pollution his Department has allocated funding to local authorities from the air quality grant in (a) 2018- 19, (b) 2017-18, (c) 2016-17 and (d) 2015-16; and how much such funding was allocated to each of those schemes and projects in each of those years.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192868","192868"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010260","2018-11-21","Treasury","2018-11-19","To ask the ,Chancellor of the Exchequer  what estimate he has made of the contribution to the public purse from sales of (a) digital versatile discs and (b) photographs of the presentation of official honours at Buckingham Palace in the financial years (i) 2015-16, (ii) 2016-17, (iii) 2017-18 and (iv) 2018-19 to date.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192869","192869"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010261","2018-11-21","Treasury","2018-11-19","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what net profit has accrued to the public purse from (a) the filming and sale of digital versatile discs and (b) the capture and sale of photographs whose images were taken during the presentation of official honours at Buckingham Palace in the financial years (i) 2015-16, (ii) 2016-17, (iii) 2017-18 and (iv) 2018-19 to date.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192870","192870"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010262","2018-11-22","Cabinet Office","2018-11-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much has been spent from the public purse on promoting social media posts relating to the UK leaving the EU on (a) the @10DowningStreet Twitter account and (b) other online platforms for which her office is responsible in the last three months; and if she will place details of the content of those posts in the Library.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192871","192871"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010263","2018-11-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of the recommendations of the Academic Health Science Networks report of 5 November 2018 on Understanding the Performance and Potential of Specialist Hospitals.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192781","192781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010264","2018-11-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he plans to refer to the role of specialist hospitals in research, innovation and training in future NHS planning.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192782","192782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010265","2018-11-22","Department for International Development","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, with reference to her Department's Memorandum of Understanding with the Palestinian Authority, what discussions her Department has had with the PA on a video posted on social media on 2 November 2018 by PA Education Minister Sabri Saidam which included the line, it was said that the old continent was sick of the behaviour of the Jews at the time and therefore it planned to get rid of them.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192699","192699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010266","2018-11-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps her Department is taking to reduce the number of personal independence payment applications that go to appeal.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192872","192872"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010267","2018-11-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many people were employed by his Department on 19 November 2018.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192873","192873"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010268","2018-11-21","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how much the Government has spent on preparing for the UK leaving the EU without a deal in each of the last 24 months for which figures are available.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192874","192874"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010269","2018-11-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what checks his Department takes to ensure that no insects or pesticides are brought into the UK through food imports.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192875","192875"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010270","2018-11-21","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how much the Government has spent on preparing for the UK leaving the EU without a deal in the last 12 months for which figures are available.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192876","192876"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010271","2018-11-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what his Department's policy will be on time limits for farmers to spread fertiliser after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192877","192877"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010272","2018-11-21","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how much his Department plans to spend on preparations for the UK leaving the EU without a deal between now and March 2020.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192878","192878"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010273","2018-11-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what his Department's policy is on financial support for farmers affected by heavy flooding.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192879","192879"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010274","2018-11-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the mortality rate was for game bird farms in each year from 2010 to 2018.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192783","192783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010275","2018-11-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that employees have access to good toilet facilities in the workplace.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192880","192880"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010276","2018-11-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many game bird farms have more than (a) 20,000 and (b) 50,000 birds.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192784","192784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010277","2018-11-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will commission research comparing the welfare of caged game birds with those that are not caged.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192785","192785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010278","2018-11-21","Department for Education","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to encourage large businesses to offer work placements to school leavers.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192881","192881"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010279","2018-11-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department is taking to support high street retailers increase footfall.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192882","192882"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010280","2018-11-21","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what discussions he has had with local councils in Northern Ireland on business rates.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192883","192883"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010281","2018-11-21","Department for Education","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent discussions he has had with the Permanent Secretary in the Department of Education in Northern Ireland on the financial situation of schools in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192884","192884"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010282","2018-11-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how much (a) PM2.5, (b) ammonia, (c) nitrogen oxides, (d) sulphur dioxide, (e) benzene, (f) formaldhyde, (g) acrolein and (h) polycyclic aromatic hydrocarbons is emitted annually by sources supported financially by the (i) domestic and (ii) non-domestic Renewable Heat Incentive.","Biography information for Graham Stringer","Graham Stringer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192738","192738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010283","2018-11-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with fishermen in Northern Ireland on the UK's withdrawal from the EU.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192885","192885"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010284","2018-11-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent assessment he has made of the effect of the use of biomass boilers supported financially by the (a) domestic and (b) non-domestic renewable heat incentive on (i) air quality and (ii) levels of (A) particulate emissions, (B) morbidity and (C) mortality.","Biography information for Graham Stringer","Graham Stringer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192739","192739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010285","2018-11-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent assessment he has made of the effect of the use of biomass boilers supported financially by the (a) domestic and (b) non-domestic renewable heat incentive on (i) air quality and (ii) levels of (A) morbidity and (B) mortality in (1) urban and (2) rural areas.","Biography information for Graham Stringer","Graham Stringer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192740","192740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010286","2018-11-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average processing time for income-related employment support allowance claims where a claimant has a DS1500 medical condition report is.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192886","192886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010287","2018-11-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, for what reasons MPs offices have implicit consent arrangements for universal credit applications and advice services require explicit consent to support claimants.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192887","192887"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010288","2018-11-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many smoke control areas cover (a) urban areas and (b) rural areas; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192888","192888"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010289","2018-11-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many electricity suppliers offer power purchase agreements for the procurement of power from solar generators on domestic homes.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192692","192692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010290","2018-11-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the average cost is of raising a second export meter point administration number in domestic homes for the purposes of metered export; and on which parties such costs fall.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192693","192693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010291","2018-11-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether he has made a recent assessment of the effectiveness with which local authorities undertake their duty to provide independent advocacy services to people subject to the Mental Health Act 1983; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192714","192714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010292","2018-11-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the effect of the interim report of the Independent Review of the Mental Health Act on the rate of detentions under that Act in (a) England and (b) the Oxfordshire clinical commissioning group area.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192889","192889"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010293","2018-11-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he has made an assessment of the implications for the provisions of the Mental Capacity (Amendments) Bill of the forthcoming final report of the Independent Review of the Mental Health Act.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192715","192715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010294","2018-11-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the timetable is for his Department to respond to the forthcoming final report of the Independent Review of the Mental Health Act.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192890","192890"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010295","2018-11-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the forthcoming final report of the Independent Review of the Mental Health Act, if he will reform that Act better to protect the rights of people who are subject to it; and whether there is a timescale for bringing forward such legislative proposals.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192891","192891"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010296","2018-11-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the timetable is for the decision by the Cambridge and Peterborough Clinical Commissioning Group on the options for an NHS and social care hub in Royston; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Oliver Heald","Sir Oliver Heald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192694","192694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010297","2018-11-21","Department for Education","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when he plans to publish the allocation of funding for schools for the current academic year.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192892","192892"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010298","2018-11-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the effect of the independent review of the Mental Health Act on the rate of detentions under that Act in NHS Hartlepool and Stockton-on-Tees CCG.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192893","192893"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010299","2018-11-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will reform the Mental Health Act to better protect the rights of people with mental health needs.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192894","192894"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010300","2018-11-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the timetable for his Department to respond to the recommendations of the independent review of the Mental Health Act is.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192895","192895"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010301","2018-11-21","Treasury","2018-11-19","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many child tax credit and working tax credit cases are waiting over 30 days for a mandatory reconsideration.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192741","192741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010302","2018-11-21","Treasury","2018-11-19","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many child tax credit and working tax credit cases are waiting over 40 days for a mandatory reconsideration.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192742","192742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010303","2018-11-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure that children with life-limiting conditions and their families have access to children's palliative care in the community out-of-hours and at weekends.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192786","192786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010304","2018-11-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether NHS England has put forward the inclusion of a maternal six-week postnatal check in negotiations on the General Medical Services contract; and what recent progress has been made in those negotiations.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192896","192896"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010305","2018-11-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure that a maternal six-week postnatal check is included in the General Medical Services contract; and what funding he plans to allocate for the provision of those checks.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192897","192897"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010306","2018-11-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the shortage of EpiPen 0.3mg Auto-Injectors in (a) Yorkshire and the Humber and (b) England; and what steps he is taking to address that shortage.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192898","192898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010307","2018-11-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the effect on the health of children under 16 of the national shortage of EpiPen 0.3mg Auto-Injectors; and what plans he has in place to reduce that shortage.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192899","192899"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010308","2018-11-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether pregnant asylum seekers with no leave to remain are charged different amounts for maternity services in different parts of the UK.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192900","192900"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010309","2018-11-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many pregnant failed asylum seekers have been charged for maternity care between January and November 2018; and what the average amount of that charge was.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192901","192901"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010310","2018-11-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the cost to the public purse of invoicing pregnant asylum seekers with no leave to remain for maternity care in 2017-2018 was.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192902","192902"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010311","2018-11-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care,  what the proportion was of pregnant asylum seekers who paid in full their invoices for maternity care in (a) 2016 and (b) 2017.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192903","192903"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010312","2018-11-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether her Department seeks to recover remaining payments on an advance payment for universal credit from the estate of a deceased person.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192904","192904"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010313","2018-11-21","Department for Transport","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 13 September 2018 to Question 172553 on Railways: Bicycles,(a) what constitutes a specific need for cycle storage space on trains and (b) how may passengers communicate their need for cycle storage space to the his Department.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192905","192905"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010314","2018-11-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people with Parkinson’s who were awarded 10 points or lower for the moving around activity of personal independence payment were previously in receipt of the highest rate of the mobility component of disability living allowance.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192787","192787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010315","2018-11-21","Home Office","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what information his Department holds on the number of people who attempted to make reports of fraud to Action Fraud over the latest 12-month period for which data is available; of those who attempted to make such reports how many were successful over that period; how much enforcement activity was undertaken as a result of those reports; by which police authorities such action was undertaken; how many telephone calls were made to Action Fraud over that period; and, of those calls, how many were answered by Action Fraud.","Biography information for Andrew Selous","Andrew Selous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192788","192788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010316","2018-11-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 24 October 2018 to Question 183314 on Children: Death, if he will make an estimate of how many child death reviews which identified trauma or external factors as the cause of death related to gang violence for each local authority area in England in each of the last five years; and how many of those child death reviews led to a Serious Case Review.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192906","192906"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010317","2018-11-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the efficacy of the UN peacekeeping mission MINUSCA in protecting civilian security, life, and rights in the Central African Republic, and what assessment he has made of the effect of (a) troop levels, (b) resourcing levels, and (c) the temporary nature of the mandate, in determining that level of efficacy in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192907","192907"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010318","2018-11-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the effect of Israel’s Regional Tracks for Peace project on the viability of a future Palestinian state.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192908","192908"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010319","2018-11-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to support the ceasefire agreed between the Israeli Government and Hamas on Tuesday 13 November 2018.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192909","192909"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010320","2018-11-21","House of Commons Commission","2018-11-19","To ask the right hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington, representing the House of Commons Commission, how many certificates of exemption have been issued pursuant to section 34 of the Freedom of Information Act 2000 in each of the last 10 years for which records are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192910","192910"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010321","2018-11-22","Department for Transport","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 16 October 2018 to Question 177630 on Shipping: Minimum wage, when the meeting with the responsible Minister in the Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy took place; what progress has been made in discussions between officials in his Department and their counterparts in BEIS; and on what date he plans to formally publish the recommendations of the legal working group.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192789","192789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010322","2018-11-21","Department for Transport","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much of the Highways England Air Quality Fund was spent up to November 2018; and how much is planned to be spent in (a) 2018-19 and (b) 2019-20.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192790","192790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010323","2018-11-21","Department for Transport","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the report entitled Highways England’s approach to delivering schemes through its ring-fenced funds, published in February 2018, whether the overall performance of the Highways England Air Quality Fund remains rated as red.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192791","192791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010324","2018-11-22","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 9 November 2018 to Question 186964 on Prisons: Crimes of Violence and Self-harm, if he will place a copy of those tables in the Library.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192743","192743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010325","2018-11-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of claimants undergoing work capability assessments have had their assessments audio-recorded since 2012.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192744","192744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010326","2018-11-21","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what support UK troops in Afghanistan are providing for the protection of civilian Hazaras.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192792","192792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010327","2018-11-22","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of the Information Commissioner's proposed code of practice to protect democratic institutions in the United Kingdom.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192793","192793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010328","2018-11-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether local housing allowance rates for tenants in the private rented sector will be set at the 30th percentile of local market rents at the end of the freeze of those rates in March 2020.","Biography information for Emma Dent Coad","Emma Dent Coad","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192947","192947"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010329","2018-11-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether her Department has made an estimate of the cost to the public purse of reducing the age limit for the Shared Accommodation rate of Local Housing Allowance from 35 to 30 years old; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Emma Dent Coad","Emma Dent Coad","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192948","192948"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010330","2018-11-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate her Department has made of the effect of delaying managed migration of existing social security claimants to universal credit on the cost to the public purse of universal credit transitional protection; and whether those estimates constitute a saving to the public purse.","Biography information for Emma Dent Coad","Emma Dent Coad","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192949","192949"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010331","2018-11-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 17 October 2018, to Question 176689 on Employment Support Allowance, what written evidence her Department holds on the British Medical Association and Royal College of General Practitioners agreement to the revised wording of the ESA65B letters sent to claimants’ GPs when they fail the work capability assessment.","Biography information for Emma Dent Coad","Emma Dent Coad","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192950","192950"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010332","2018-11-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many recipients of universal credit are self-employed.","Biography information for Emma Dent Coad","Emma Dent Coad","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192951","192951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010333","2018-11-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 19 November to Question 191275 on Offshore Industry: Carbon Emissions, if he will assess the (a) compatibility of the Oil and Gas Authority's remit to maximise the economic recovery of petroleum from the UK continental shelf with the UK’s decarbonisation commitments as a signatory to the Paris agreement and (b) potential merits of changing that remit to support the winding down of the petroleum industry over the next 30 years.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192716","192716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010334","2018-11-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what representations she has received on the effect of the universal credit minimum income floor on the amount of housing element support self-employed claimants are entitled to compared with their housing benefit entitlement under the legacy benefit system.","Biography information for Emma Dent Coad","Emma Dent Coad","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192952","192952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010335","2018-11-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 16 October 2018 to Question 176686 on Independent Case Examiner, how much additional funding the Independent Case Examiner received in 2017-18 to reduce the waiting time for a decision.","Biography information for Emma Dent Coad","Emma Dent Coad","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192953","192953"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010336","2018-11-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many complaints to the Independent Case Examiner were concluded by (a) the early resolution process, (b) settlement following a review of the evidence and (c) a full investigation in each month from January 2017 to October 2018 inclusive.","Biography information for Emma Dent Coad","Emma Dent Coad","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192954","192954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010337","2018-11-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether complaints to the Independent Case Examiner that have been considered under the early resolution process can be referred directly to the Parliamentary Ombudsman.","Biography information for Emma Dent Coad","Emma Dent Coad","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192955","192955"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010338","2018-11-21","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to his Answers of 27 June 2018 to Questions 155404 and 155405, when he will begin recruitment to the post of permanent Chair of the Board of the Regulator of Social Housing; and when he plans to place copies of the revised job description and person specification in the Library.","Biography information for Emma Dent Coad","Emma Dent Coad","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192956","192956"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010339","2018-11-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to protect children from the effect of toxic air on their health in (a) Oxford West and Abingdon constituency and (b) England.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192911","192911"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010340","2018-11-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what evaluations his Department has conducted of any measures and schemes specifically designed to reduce children’s exposure to air pollution in each of the last three years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Geraint Davies","Geraint Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192695","192695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010341","2018-11-21","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 1 November 2018 to Question 183892 on High Rise Flats: Insulation, how many student accommodation blocks over 18 metres with non-ACM combustible cladding have been identified.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192794","192794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010342","2018-11-21","Department for Education","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 1 November 2018 to Question 183891 on Schools: Insulation, how many school fires occurred in 2017-2018.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192795","192795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010343","2018-11-21","Department for Education","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 1 November 2018 to Question 183891 on Schools: Insulation, how many school fires resulted in the relocation of pupils to separate premises in 2017-18.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192796","192796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010344","2018-11-21","Department for Education","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 1 November 2018 to Question 183891 on Schools: Insulation, how many days of operation have been lost as a result of fires in schools in 2017-2018.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192797","192797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010345","2018-11-21","Department for Education","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 1 November 2018 to Question 183891 on Schools: Insulation, what the cost has been to (a) central Government and (b) local authorities of fires in schools in 2017-18.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192798","192798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010346","2018-11-21","Department for Education","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 1 November 2018 to Question 183891 on Schools: Insulation, whether the Government has measured the effect on children’s education of fires which have destroyed school buildings.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192799","192799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010347","2018-11-22","Treasury","2018-11-19","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether (a) he and (b) the Financial Conduct Authority plan to investigate the alleged unlicensed selling of insurance products in EU countries to UK investors by UK companies using Isle of Man subsidiaries.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192912","192912"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010348","2018-11-22","Treasury","2018-11-19","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will hold discussions with his Isle of Man counterpart on strengthening consumer rights and protections for UK investors who purchase (a) insurance and (b) other financial products in the (i) UK and (ii) EU from companies based in that jurisdiction; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192913","192913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010349","2018-11-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his Bahraini counterpart on the detention of former Bahraini MP Ali Rashed Al Asheeri.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192800","192800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010350","2018-11-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has made representations to his Bahraini counterpart on reports of acts of reprisal against Ali Hajji and Naji Fateel in Jau Prison, Bahrain since those cases were highlighted by British Parliamentarians.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192801","192801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010351","2018-11-21","Wales Office","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, which trade unions he has met in the last 12 months; and on what dates those meetings took place.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192802","192802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010352","2018-11-21","Wales Office","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what products featuring (a) departmental and (b) Government branding his Department has procured in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192803","192803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010353","2018-11-22","Home Office","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many cases of breaches of the Hunting Act 2004 were referred to the Crown Prosecution Service by Durham constabulary in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192914","192914"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010354","2018-11-21","Wales Office","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how much funding he allocated to Welsh lessons for staff in his Department in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192804","192804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010355","2018-11-22","Wales Office","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what steps he is taking to incorporate the Prime Minister's cross-governmental loneliness strategy into the policy-formulation and decision-making processes of his Department.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192805","192805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010356","2018-11-22","Home Office","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have been arrested by Durham constabulary for breaches of the Hunting Act 2004 in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192915","192915"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010357","2018-11-22","Home Office","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps he is taking to improve the (a) detection and (b) policing of illegal fox hunting activities in County Durham.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192916","192916"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010358","2018-11-21","Wales Office","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what estimate he has made of his Department's spending on (a) departmental Christmas cards and (b) postage for Christmas 2018.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192806","192806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010359","2018-11-22","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many cases have (a) gone to trial and (b) been successfully prosecuted for breaches of the Hunting Act 2004 in County Durham in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192917","192917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010361","2018-11-21","Wales Office","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how many letters he has received from Members of the House of (a) Commons and (b) Lords in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192807","192807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010362","2018-11-22","Department for Education","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment he has made of the risk of university closures due to financial pressures.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192918","192918"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010363","2018-11-22","Department for Education","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the oral contribution of the Minister for School Standards of 9 October 2018, Official Report column 65WH, what his planned timescale is for putting guidance on school uniform prices on a statutory footing.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192919","192919"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010364","2018-11-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment the Government has made of the effect of palm oil production on the orangutan population in Malaysia.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192920","192920"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010365","2018-11-22","Department for Transport","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of the EU decision to phase out the use of palm oil in transport fuels by 2030.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192921","192921"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010366","2018-11-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps she is taking to ensure that the calculation of universal credit for self-employed people (a) accurately reflects (i) the amount that they allocate to expenses to maintain their business and (ii) their take-home earnings and (b) leaves those people in a better financial position as a result of being in work.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192922","192922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010367","2018-11-22","Cabinet Office","2018-11-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether his Department has commissioned the Department of Health and Social Care to review Government policy on the reform of nursing higher education.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192923","192923"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010368","2018-11-22","Cabinet Office","2018-11-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what his most recent estimate is of the number of economically inactive young people.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192696","192696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010369","2018-11-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he has made an assessment of the potential effect on public health of reducing (a) household, (b) commercial and (c) industrial waste; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192717","192717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010370","2018-11-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether NHS England plans to approve an app to support patients in managing hearing loss; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192697","192697"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010371","2018-11-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much the Government spent on Access to Work in the last year for which figures are available; and of that amount how much was spent on (a) equipment and (b) services.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192700","192700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010372","2018-11-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he has made an assessment of the potential effect on public health of increasing the amount of waste that is recycled; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192718","192718"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010373","2018-11-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment he has made of the (a) adequacy and (b) accessibility to prisoners of mental health services in prisons.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192745","192745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010374","2018-11-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of (a) the extent of employer compliance and (b) how long it takes employers to comply with the recommendations made by Access to Work.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192701","192701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010375","2018-11-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether equipment purchased under the Access to Work scheme belongs to (a) the employer, (b) the employee or (c) her Department; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192702","192702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010376","2018-11-22","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent assessment he has made of trends in the level of waiting times for personal independence payment appeals to be heard in (a) St. Helens, (b) Liverpool and (c) Wigan county courts; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192746","192746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010377","2018-11-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the effect on the level of indebtedness of people in Warrington of waiting times for personal independence payment appeal hearings in local county courts.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192747","192747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010378","2018-11-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how her Department assesses child maintenance liabilities in cases where HMRC has not received updated PAYE or self-assessment records at the end of the financial year.","Biography information for Angela Crawley","Angela Crawley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192924","192924"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010379","2018-11-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps can be taken by the child maintenance service against non-resident parents when they have failed to report any changes to their income of greater than 25 per cent.","Biography information for Angela Crawley","Angela Crawley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192925","192925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010380","2018-11-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his Department recognises Taiwan’s efforts and contribution on combating climate change; and if his Department will support Taiwan’s participation as an observer in the 24th Session of the Conference of the Parties under the United Nations Framework Convention on Climate Change which will take place in Poland in December 2018.","Biography information for Scott Mann","Scott Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192926","192926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010381","2018-11-22","Home Office","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent discussions he has had with Police and Crime Commissioners on the effect on police budgets of additional pension costs.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192719","192719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010382","2018-11-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the timetable is for the Government’s response to its consultations on (a) Employment status (b) Increasing transparency in the labour market (c) Agency workers and (d) Enforcement of employment rights.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192927","192927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010383","2018-11-21","Department for Transport","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he has had discussions with the Cross Country train-operating company on overcrowding on its services; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Martin Whitfield","Martin Whitfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192928","192928"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010384","2018-11-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether the Government plans to use money from the public purse for (a) redundancy and (b) compensation payments as a result of the upcoming franchising of post office branches to WHSmith; and what estimate has been made of those payments.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192720","192720"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010385","2018-11-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether the Government has (a) sought and (b) obtained guarantees from WH Smith that post office staff will not be (i) made redundant and (ii) moved to roles with (A) poorer working conditions and (B) lower pay after their branches are franchised.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192721","192721"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010386","2018-11-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of claimants receiving the housing element of universal credit are women.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192808","192808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010387","2018-11-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of claimants receiving the housing element of universal credit are disabled.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192809","192809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010388","2018-11-21","Department for International Trade","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what responsibilities his Department will have after 29 March 2019 in the event that the House agrees to the EU-UK withdrawal deal.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192929","192929"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010389","2018-11-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of claimants receiving the housing element of universal credit are from black, Asian or minority ethnic backgrounds.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192810","192810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010390","2018-11-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of claimants receiving the housing element of universal credit are also claiming the state pension.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192811","192811"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010391","2018-11-22","Department for Education","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 19 November 2018 to Question 191474, which 13 local authorities have been granted the ability to move funding from the schools block to the high needs block.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192930","192930"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010392","2018-11-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what discussions his Department has had with (a) the Wales Office and (b) the Welsh Government on the level of funding from the European Regional Development Fund and the European Social Fund in Wales that the Shared Prosperity Fund is intended to replace.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192931","192931"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010393","2018-11-22","Home Office","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate he has made of the number of people investigated under Prevent for (a) Islamic extremism and (b) far-right extremism in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192932","192932"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010394","2018-11-22","Home Office","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what progress he has made on the review commissioned by his Department earlier this year into the possible introduction of statutory time limits on immigration detention.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192933","192933"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010395","2018-11-22","Home Office","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what constitutes a reasonable period of time for a person to be detained at an immigration removal centre.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192934","192934"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010396","2018-11-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many universal credit cases have been closed in error in the most recent 12 months for which data are available; and what the time taken was for each of those cases to be rebuilt.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192748","192748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010397","2018-11-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he plans to include provisions for achieving World Health Organisation limits on (a) nitrogen dioxide, (b) PM2.5 and (c) PM10 emissions by 2030 in his forthcoming Environment Bill.","Biography information for Jeff Smith","Jeff Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192935","192935"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010398","2018-11-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the World Health Organisation conclusion that there is no safe level of PM2.5 or PM10.","Biography information for Jeff Smith","Jeff Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192936","192936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010399","2018-11-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether he is taking steps to ensure that generating stations which qualify for Feed-in-Tariffs continue to receive equipment breakdown support after the closure of the scheme in April 2019.","Biography information for Jeff Smith","Jeff Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192937","192937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010400","2018-11-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he has made an assessment of the implications for his policies of the recent Rethink Mental Illness survey which found that patients with severe mental illness wait on average 14 weeks for an assessment; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jeff Smith","Jeff Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192938","192938"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010401","2018-11-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to page 36 of the Five Year Forward View for Mental Health, whether each access to treatment pathway will (a) be published according to the timetable set out in that document and (b) include waiting time targets.","Biography information for Jeff Smith","Jeff Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192939","192939"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010402","2018-11-21","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the (a) median and (b) mean times were for private landlords to progress from a claim to possession of a property by a county court bailiff for the most recent period for which figures are available (i) across England and (ii) by each court circuit.","Biography information for Kevin Hollinrake","Kevin Hollinrake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192940","192940"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010403","2018-11-22","Home Office","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what is the longest period spent in immigration detention by a detainee who left an Immigration Removal Centre between June 2017 and October 2018.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192941","192941"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010404","2018-11-21","Cabinet Office","2018-11-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the Government’s Response to the Call for Evidence on Access to Elections published 30 August 2018, whether he can provide an update on the progress of the Accessibility Working Group's consideration of the viability of sending out electoral information by electronic means to blind and partially-sighted people.","Biography information for Marsha De Cordova","Marsha De Cordova","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192957","192957"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010405","2018-11-22","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of the proposal by President Macron to create a European army.","Biography information for Mr Peter Bone","Mr Peter Bone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192942","192942"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010406","2018-11-22","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the UK would allow British service personnel to become part of a European army in the event that such an army is established.","Biography information for Mr Peter Bone","Mr Peter Bone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192943","192943"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010407","2018-11-22","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the draft withdrawal agreement for the UK leaving the EU on the UK's armed forces.","Biography information for Mr Peter Bone","Mr Peter Bone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192944","192944"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010408","2018-11-22","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, pursuant to the Prime Minister's oral contribution of 15 November 2018, Official Report column 454, what the meaning is of the legal term best endeavours.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Sir Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192703","192703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010409","2018-11-22","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union,  pursuant to the Prime Minister's oral contribution of 15 November 2018, Official Report column 454, what process there will be for resolution of any dispute as to whether best endeavours have been used.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Sir Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192704","192704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010410","2018-11-22","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, pursuant to the Prime Minister's oral contribution of 15 November 2018, Official Report column 454, what the sanction or other mode of enforcement will be for a failure to comply with the legal requirement to use best endeavours.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Sir Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192705","192705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010411","2018-11-21","Cabinet Office","2018-11-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate his Department has made of the number of people in Northern Ireland affected by the contaminated blood scandal; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192812","192812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010412","2018-11-21","Northern Ireland Office","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, if her Department will (a) respond to feedback received by the Northern Ireland Executive Office's consultation on Historical Institutional Abuse and (b) take steps to implement the recommendations of the Hart Report in the absence of a functioning Northern Ireland Assembly; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192813","192813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010413","2018-11-21","Cabinet Office","2018-11-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, in what locations in Northern Ireland will hearings in the contaminated blood inquiry take place; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192814","192814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010414","2018-11-21","Northern Ireland Office","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, if she will meet families of cystic fibrosis sufferers in Northern Ireland who are seeking to secure the availability of Orkambi on the NHS; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192815","192815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010415","2018-11-21","Northern Ireland Office","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what assessment she has made of the effect on local and regional newspapers in Northern Ireland of the pre-pack rescue of Johnston Press; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192816","192816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010416","2018-11-22","Department for Education","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Written Statement of 19 November 2018, TEF reviewer appointment, HCWS 1089, whether the independent review of the TEF and its reviewer will be able to have access to the deliberations of Philip Aurgar's Review of Post-18 Education and Funding relating to matters pertaining to the Teaching Excellence and Student Outcomes Framework.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192749","192749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010417","2018-11-22","Department for Education","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Written Statement of 19 November 2018, TEF reviewer appointment, HCWS 1089, whether the reviewer will have autonomy in the establishment and composition of the advisory group charged in the review's terms of reference with providing advice and helping inform her review.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192750","192750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010418","2018-11-22","Department for Education","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Written Statement of 19 November 2018, TEF reviewer appointment, HCWS 1089, whether the reviewer will report to (a) the House and (b) the Education Committee.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192751","192751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010419","2018-11-21","Department for Education","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Written Statement of 19 November 2018, TEF reviewer appointment, HCWS 1089, what ability the independent reviewer will have to (a) receive written submissions and (b) commission open hearings.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192752","192752"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1010420","2018-11-22","Department for Education","2018-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Written Statement of 19 November 2018, TEF reviewer appointment, HCWS 1089, what ability the independent reviewer will have to share access to speak to (a) providers who are taking part in pilots for the subject-level teaching excellence framework (b) his Department's officials involved in those pilots.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192753","192753"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1008447","2018-11-21","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to the Government's press release entitled PM launches Government’s first loneliness strategy, published on 15 October 2018, whether his Department has conducted a loneliness policy test on Budget 2018.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192092","192092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1008448","2018-11-20","Department for Education","2018-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment he has made of the effect of the practice of contested adoption on the well-being of the child.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192088","192088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1008449","2018-11-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the total value of the properties managed by NHS Property Services.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192093","192093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1008450","2018-11-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when the procedure for dealing with complaints to NHS Property Services was last changed.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192094","192094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1008451","2018-11-21","Department for International Development","2018-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment her Department has made of whether the global polio eradication initiative will be completed by September 2019.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192100","192100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1008452","2018-11-21","Treasury","2018-11-16","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the level of foreign direct investment was in the 12 months from July 2017.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192101","192101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1008453","2018-11-21","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what liaison arrangements exist between the multi-agency public protection arrangements (MAPPA) framework in England and Wales and the MAPPA frameworks in (a) Scotland and (b) Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192102","192102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1008454","2018-11-21","Department for Transport","2018-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the annual targets of his Department are for reducing transport emissions in the next 15 years.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192103","192103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1008455","2018-11-20","Treasury","2018-11-16","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 23 October 2018 to Question 179286, whether the Government plans to make back payments of child benefit to those parents who have mistakenly omitted to claim that benefit and as a result lost out on national insurance state pension credits.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192115","192115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1008456","2018-11-21","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether he has made representations to the Premier League on the £5 million bonus being paid to its outgoing executive chairman Richard Scudamore; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192104","192104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1008457","2018-11-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure the supply of statins after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192116","192116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1008458","2018-11-21","Cabinet Office","2018-11-16","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when he plans to publish the results of the Civil Service People Survey 2018.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192117","192117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1008459","2018-11-21","Department for Education","2018-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the value is of his Department's contract with M&C Saatchi to relaunch the marketing campaign promoting apprenticeships.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192118","192118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1008460","2018-11-21","Department for Education","2018-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 4 September 2018 to Question 168016, when he plans to place a copy of the report of the multi-academy trust review of Wakefield City Academies Trust carried out by the Education and Skills Funding Agency in the Libraries of both Houses.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192119","192119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1008461","2018-11-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will hold meetings with representatives of the oil industry on the recent reduction in the crude oil price that is not reflected in retail fuel prices.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192105","192105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1008462","2018-11-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of potential job losses in the renewable energy sector after the closure of the feed-in-tariff scheme in March 2019.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192120","192120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1008463","2018-11-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how much funding from the EU is proposed to be allocated to (a) improve the energy efficiency of the housing stock and (b) to reduce fuel poverty in England in the next (i) five years and (ii) ten years; and whether that funding from the EU will still be available in the event that the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192087","192087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1008464","2018-11-21","Home Office","2018-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when the booking system for the new Sopra Steria visa premium service centres is planned to go live.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192121","192121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1008465","2018-11-21","Home Office","2018-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, for what reason the opening of the new booking system for the Sopra Streia Visa Premium Service Centre appointments has been delayed.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192122","192122"
