"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105135","2019-04-01","Department for Education","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of trends in the level of demand for children’s social care services in the timeframe of the next Spending Review.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237048","237048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105136","2019-04-01","Department for Education","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to monitor the outcomes of spending on early interventions for nursery and reception children in (a) York and (b) Yorkshire.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237114","237114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105137","2019-04-01","Department for Education","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of spending on early interventions for nursery and reception children on the attainment gap; and what steps his Department is taking to measure that effect.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237115","237115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105138","2019-03-28","Home Office","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the oral contribution of the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for the Home Department of 22 March 2019, Official Report, column 1404, how much of the £100 million in funding will be allocated to the police, by each police force.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237008","237008"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105139","2019-03-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many times a request for a Statement of Reasons pertaining to the allocation of universal credit (limited capability to work) has not been delivered within the statutory time limit of 14 days in each of the last three years for which data are available.","Biography information for Martin Whitfield","Martin Whitfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237116","237116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105140","2019-04-01","Department for Transport","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 28 February 2019 to Question 225461 on Aviation Licensing, how many initial issues for each category of licence were made to people aged (a) 16 to 30, (b) 30 to 45 and (c) over 45.","Biography information for Mr Peter Bone","Mr Peter Bone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237049","237049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105141","2019-03-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when she plans to respond to the letter of 10 January 2019 from the hon. Member for Glasgow Central on behalf of her constituent Mr Neil Rothnie.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237117","237117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105142","2019-04-01","Department for Education","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which schools in Birkenhead have expanded their intake without undertaking a public consultation in the last five years.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237009","237009"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105143","2019-03-28","Home Office","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the 18 per cent reduction in the number of National Insurance registrations in Scotland by overseas workers between 2015 and 2018, what steps his Department is taking to encourage overseas workers to Scotland.","Biography information for Angela Crawley","Angela Crawley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237118","237118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105144","2019-04-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he has made an assessment of the implications for his policies of the recommendations in the Red Cross report entitled Home to the Unknown: Getting hospital discharge right; and whether he is taking steps to introduce an independence check prior to discharge or within 72 hours of going home, as recommended by the Red Cross.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237050","237050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105146","2019-04-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 8 February 2019 to Question 216920, what plans she has to publish Youth Obligation outcome data; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236984","236984"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105147","2019-04-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people have joined the Youth Obligation programme since 1 January 2019.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236985","236985"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105148","2019-04-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many Youth Obligation participants have secured (a) employment, (b) traineeships, (c) work placements and (d) apprenticeships since 1 January 2019.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236986","236986"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105150","2019-04-01","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people working on developing HM Courts & Tribunals Service Reform are (a) contingent labour, (b) supplier resource and (c) civil servants.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236991","236991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105151","2019-04-01","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people working on developing Criminal Justice System Common Platform are (a) contingent labour, (b) supplier resource and (c) civil servants.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236992","236992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105152","2019-03-28","Home Office","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people working on developing NCA Transformation Programme are (a) contingent labour, (b) supplier resource and (c) civil servants.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236993","236993"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105153","2019-03-28","Home Office","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people working on developing the IT Transformation Programme are (a) contingent labour, (b) supplier resource and (c) civil servants.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236994","236994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105154","2019-03-28","Home Office","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps he is taking to support convenience retailers in Warrington South that have lost an estimated £133,145 due to shop theft.","Biography information for Faisal Rashid","Faisal Rashid","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237119","237119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105155","2019-03-28","Cabinet Office","2019-03-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people working on developing the Office for National Statistics Census Transformation Programme are (a) contingent labour, (b) supplier resource and (c) civil servants.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236995","236995"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105156","2019-04-01","Home Office","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether his Department will continue to provide funding to the National Business Crime Centre; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Rosie Duffield","Rosie Duffield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237120","237120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105157","2019-04-01","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the European Commission report entitled Energy prices and costs in Europe 2018, what assessment he has made of the implications for (a) his policies and (b) the Government's 25 Year Environment Plan of that report's conclusion that the UK offers the biggest fuel subsidies in the EU.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237051","237051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105158","2019-04-01","Home Office","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps his Department is taking to tackle (a) retail crime and (b) violence against shopworkers; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Rosie Duffield","Rosie Duffield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237121","237121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105159","2019-04-01","Home Office","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department,  what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of Association of Convenience Stores Crime Report 2019 findings that (a) the total cost of crime for the convenience sector was £246 million, (b) there were 9,782 incidents of violence against people working in local shops and (c) that convenience retailers had invested £4,080 per store in crime prevention equipment; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237010","237010"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105160","2019-04-02","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will (a) take steps to ensure that vegan meals are offered to inpatients diagnosed with eating disorders and (b) encourage drug companies to develop vegan-friendly prescription (i) medications, (ii) supplement drinks and (iii) feeds.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237052","237052"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105161","2019-04-01","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps are being taken to develop a systemic approach to safe management of agricultural animal waste.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237053","237053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105162","2019-04-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will ensure that dog attacks on cats are recorded by police forces when he meets with the National Police Chiefs’ Council to discuss a new approach to tackling dog attacks.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237054","237054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105164","2019-04-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs how many community protection notices were issued for dog attacks on cats in each of the last three years; and what plans his Department has to review the effectiveness of community protection notices in protecting cats from dog attacks.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237055","237055"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105165","2019-04-01","Treasury","2019-03-26","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the final report of the Access to cash review published on 6 March 2019; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ged Killen","Ged Killen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237122","237122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105166","2019-04-01","Department for Education","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 15 March 2019 to Question 229154 on Department for Education: Public Expenditure, how much of the (a) £23 billion his Department has allocated to the school estate and (b) £7 billion his Department has allocated for the creation of new school places between 2015 and 2021 will be spent in the fiscal year (i) 2016-17, (ii) 2017-18, (iii) 2018-19, (iv) 2019-20 and (v) 2020-21.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237123","237123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105167","2019-04-01","Department for Education","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what measure of performance his Department uses to monitor the outcomes of early years spending from the public purse in (a) Leigh constituency (b) Greater Manchester and (c) the North West.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237124","237124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105168","2019-03-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps will be taken under the pilot scheme to co-locate mental health advisors in job centres to ensure that claimants enter into psychological therapy voluntarily.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237125","237125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105169","2019-03-28","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what proportion of Innovate UK grant funding has been awarded to (a) SMEs and (b) large companies since 2004; and what the amount awarded has been by sector over that period.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237126","237126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105170","2019-03-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to ensure claimants’ privacy is upheld when receiving mental health treatment in job centre settings; and whether future mental health referrals will offer claimants alternative community-based treatment in non-job centre settings.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237127","237127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105171","2019-03-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what level of training mental health advisors will receive prior to their appointment as part of the upcoming pilot scheme to co-locate mental health advisors in job centres.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237128","237128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105172","2019-04-01","Department for Education","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he took in response to the letter of September 2018 from experts and organisations on his Department's myth-busting document.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237129","237129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105173","2019-04-01","Department for Education","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, for what reason his Department did not hold meetings with concerned charities when it received the letter of September 2018 on his Department's myth-busting document from experts and organisations.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237130","237130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105174","2019-04-01","Home Office","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps he is taking to support convenience retailers in Ealing, Southall following shop thefts; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237056","237056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105175","2019-04-01","Department for Education","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what internal checks his Department made prior to publishing the myth-busting document on that document.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237131","237131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105176","2019-04-01","Home Office","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of introducing tougher sentences for people attacking shopworkers; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237057","237057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105177","2019-04-01","Home Office","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the salary exemption for nurses under Tier 2 visa rules will apply to EEA citizens after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237011","237011"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105178","2019-04-01","Home Office","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps his Department is taking to tackle (a) retail crime and (b) violence against shopworkers; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237132","237132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105179","2019-04-01","Home Office","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps he is taking to ensure that care assistants will continue to be able to come and work in the UK after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237058","237058"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105180","2019-04-01","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 20 March 2019 to Question 232574 on Buildings: Insulation, whether his Department consulted the Local Government Association on the design of the test.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237133","237133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105181","2019-04-01","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 20 March 2019 to Question 232020 on Buildings: Insulation, if the test with high-pressure laminate B and stonewool results in a failure whether the Government will advise that combinations with high-pressure laminate and combustible insulation should be removed from buildings.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237134","237134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105182","2019-04-01","Home Office","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the time taken was for each emergency travel document application to be secured for a person in immigration detention in 2018.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237135","237135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105183","2019-04-01","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions he  has had with (a) management and (b) staff at Tate Galleries in (a) Liverpool, (b) London and (c) St Ives on the 2018 pay award and ballots of PCS and Prospect members for strike action.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237059","237059"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105184","2019-03-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the UK’s diplomatic relations with Belarus.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237136","237136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105185","2019-03-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent steps his Department has taken to promote (a) human rights and (b) press freedom in Belarus.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237137","237137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105186","2019-03-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking with his overseas counterparts to tackle the distribution of disinformation in (a) Ukraine, (b) Belarus and (c) the Baltic States.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237138","237138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105187","2019-03-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the his Department's Integrated Activity Fund in Bahrain .","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237139","237139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105188","2019-04-01","Department for Education","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what data his Department collects to monitor the effectiveness of money allocated from the public purse to early years early intervention strategies in (a) Kirklees and (b) Yorkshire.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237140","237140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105189","2019-04-01","Home Office","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps his Department is taking to support convenience store retailers that have experienced shop theft, verbal abuse and violence.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236996","236996"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105190","2019-04-01","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of Out of Court Disposals for shop theft.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236997","236997"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105191","2019-04-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that all children with epilepsy have access to effective epilepsy services.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236998","236998"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105192","2019-04-01","Department for Education","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children are currently eligible for 15 hours of free childcare for disadvantaged two-year olds; and what proportion of eligible children are in receipt of that childcare.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237141","237141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105193","2019-04-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Thai counterpart on the conduct of the recent elections in Thailand.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236999","236999"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105194","2019-04-01","Department for Education","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the average cost to the public purse is of providing 15 hours of free childcare for a disadvantaged two-year old.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237142","237142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105195","2019-04-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the 2018 finding of the National Autistic Society that half of autistic people report not leaving the house because they are worried about society's reaction to them, what steps the Government is taking to increase awareness of autism.","Biography information for Mr Paul Sweeney","Mr Paul Sweeney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237143","237143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105196","2019-04-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps the Government is taking to reduce the time that people have to wait for a diagnosis of autism.","Biography information for Mr Paul Sweeney","Mr Paul Sweeney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237144","237144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105197","2019-04-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether all PIP assessors have undertaken training on understanding the (a) nature and (b) impact of fluctuating medical conditions.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237000","237000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105198","2019-04-01","Department for Education","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of disadvantaged children are eligible for 30 hours of free childcare.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237145","237145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105199","2019-04-01","Cabinet Office","2019-03-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the Government's budget is for advertising on (a) social and (b) other media to increase people's awareness of voter registration deadlines for forthcoming local elections.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237012","237012"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105200","2019-03-28","Home Office","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what representations he has received on the increases in the per person visa fees for Commonwealth UK Armed Forces personnel applying for Indefinite Leave to Remain.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237146","237146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105201","2019-04-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the Government of (a) the United States and (b) Israel on sovereignty of the Golan Heights.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236977","236977"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105202","2019-04-01","Department for Education","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what data his Department collects to monitor the effectiveness of money allocated from the public purse to early years early intervention strategies in (a) Kirklees and (b) Yorkshire and the Humber.","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237147","237147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105203","2019-03-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people with epilepsy have been helped into employment through (a) the Work and Health Programme, (b) Personal Support Package and (c) Access to Work.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237013","237013"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105204","2019-03-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps she is taking to encourage SMEs to sign up to the Disability Confident scheme.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237014","237014"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105205","2019-03-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to ensure the effectiveness of the personal independence payment assessment process for individuals with (a) fluctuating conditions, and (b) neurological conditions that don’t consistently present with physical symptoms.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237015","237015"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105206","2019-03-28","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps the Government is taking to maintain levels of funding for epilepsy (a) research and (b) treatment after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237016","237016"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105207","2019-03-28","Home Office","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps he is taking to support convenience retailers in Woking that lost an estimated £125,763 due to shop theft, according to estimates of Association of Convenience Stores; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Mr Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237148","237148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105208","2019-03-28","Home Office","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of implications for his policies of the findings of the Association of Convenience Stores Crime Report 2019 that (a) the total cost of crime for the convenience sector was £246 million, (b) there were 9,782 incidents of violence against people working in local shops and (c) convenience retailers had invested £4,080 per store in crime prevention equipment; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Mr Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237149","237149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105209","2019-03-28","Home Office","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps his department is taking to tackle (a) retail crime and (b) violence against shop-workers; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Mr Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237150","237150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105210","2019-03-28","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department has taken to review the use of Out Of Court Disposals for shop theft; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Mr Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237151","237151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105211","2019-03-28","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department is taking to implement simplified Out of Court Disposals following the 2014 pilot on Adult Out of Court Disposals; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Mr Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237152","237152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105212","2019-03-28","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of introducing tougher sanctions for people attacking shop-workers; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Mr Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237153","237153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105213","2019-03-28","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment his Department has made of the potential benefits of commencing section 151 of the Criminal Justice Act 2003 to allow courts to issue community orders rather than fines for minor offences by repeat offenders; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Mr Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237154","237154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105214","2019-04-01","Home Office","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the salary exemption announced for nurses under Tier 2 visas will be (a) maintained after the UK leaves the EU and (b) extended to EEA citizens; and what further steps the Government is taking to ensure effective recruitment from EU and non-EU countries to meet demand for NHS and social care staff after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236987","236987"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105215","2019-04-01","Home Office","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will publish a list of attendees to the Prime Minister's knife crime summit.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237155","237155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105216","2019-04-01","Prime Minister","2019-03-26","To ask the Prime Minister, when she plans to name a new Minister for Disabled People, Health and Work.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237017","237017"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105217","2019-04-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he will make to the Chinese Government on the protection of minorities in light of the recent allegations of forced organ harvesting in China.","Biography information for Mr Paul Sweeney","Mr Paul Sweeney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237156","237156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105219","2019-04-01","Home Office","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether his Department holds data on the change in the number of schools-based police officers since 2010.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237158","237158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105220","2019-04-01","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, which of his Department's arm's-length bodies have seconded staff to his Department (a) since June 2016, (b) in the last 12 months and (c) in the last month.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237159","237159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105221","2019-04-01","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many staff of his Department's arm's-length bodies have been seconded to his Department (a) since June 2016, (b) in the 12 months and (c) in the last month.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237160","237160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105222","2019-04-01","Department for International Trade","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, pursuant to Answer of 8 March 2019 to Question 227160, how many staff have been employed by his Department in each month since 31 January 2019.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237161","237161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105223","2019-04-01","Home Office","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 12 March 2019 to Question 227161 on Home Office: Staff, how many staff have been employed by his Department in each month since 31 January 2019.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237162","237162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105224","2019-03-28","Department for Education","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what data his Department collects in relation to the effectiveness of early years early intervention strategies in (a) Hull, (b) East Riding of Yorkshire and (c) Yorkshire and Humber.","Biography information for Emma Hardy","Emma Hardy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237163","237163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105225","2019-04-01","Department for Education","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will publish (a) which local authorities underspent their early years block allocations, (b) the amount of each such underspend and (c) the amount and proportion of each such underspend which was transferred to the High Needs block in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237164","237164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105226","2019-04-01","Home Office","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether representatives from the (a) Department of Health and (b) Department of Education have been to each meeting of the serious violence taskforce.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237165","237165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105227","2019-04-01","Home Office","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will publish the (a) agendas and (b) attendees of each meeting of the serious violence taskforce from its inception to date.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237166","237166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105228","2019-04-01","Home Office","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, from which programmes will the £20 million re-prioritised from the Home Office towards the £100 million knife crime contingency fund be drawn.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237167","237167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105229","2019-03-28","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the report entitled, Deaths associated with neurological conditions in England 2001 to 2014, published by Public Health England, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the conclusion that people with epilepsy are three times more likely to die from their condition if they live in a deprived area.","Biography information for Mr Edward Vaizey","Mr Edward Vaizey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237060","237060"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105230","2019-04-01","Department for Education","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what data his Department collects to monitor the effectiveness of early years early intervention strategies in (a) Birmingham Edgbaston, (b) Birmingham City and (c) the West Midlands.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237168","237168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105231","2019-03-28","Home Office","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps he is taking to support convenience retailers in Crawley that lost an estimated £160,211 from shop theft; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237061","237061"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105232","2019-03-28","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to ensure the adequacy of funding for a national network of support services for women in the criminal justice system.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237018","237018"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105233","2019-04-01","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to page 45 of the Government's Civil Society Strategy, published in August 2018, what steps his Department has taken to establish a national Young Commissioners and Inspectors Group to involve young people directly and meaningfully in the commissioning, monitoring and evaluation of national programmes affecting young people.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237169","237169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105234","2019-04-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 22 March 2019 to Question 234069, whether his Department has updated its advice to UK citizens travelling to the United Arab Emirates since the arrest of Matthew Hedges and Ali Issa Ahmad.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236988","236988"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105235","2019-04-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether UK citizens living in the European Union and utilising S1 form certificates to access medication for existing chronic conditions will be able to do so in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237170","237170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105236","2019-03-28","Home Office","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions he has had with social media organisations on age verification on their platforms.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237062","237062"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105237","2019-04-01","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 21 March 2019 to Question 233511 on Citizens' Juries, what the timeframe is for the announcement of the successful pilot locations.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237171","237171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105238","2019-04-01","Department for Education","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of trends in the level of homophobic abuse of pupils in schools.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237172","237172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105239","2019-04-01","Department for Education","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many violent incidents directed at teachers at schools there were in each of the last five academic years.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237173","237173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105240","2019-04-01","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how officials in his Department have (a) retired, (b) transferred it to a different Department and (c) left the civil service in each year since the Department’s creation.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237174","237174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105241","2019-03-28","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when he plans to make Cerliponase alfa, marketed as Brineura, available on the NHS for the treatment of ceroid lipofuscinosis type 2.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237175","237175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105242","2019-03-28","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what recent steps he has taken to ensure the adequacy support for the housing market in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237001","237001"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105243","2019-04-01","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many officials in his Department were on long term paid sick leave as of 1 March 2019.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237176","237176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105244","2019-04-01","Home Office","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will list the commercial airlines with which his Department currently has contracts for the purposes of carrying out enforced returns.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237177","237177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105245","2019-04-01","Home Office","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many times his Department has used each commercial airline it currently holds contracts with for the purposes of enforced returns in the last two years.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237178","237178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105246","2019-04-01","Home Office","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will publish the financial value of each contract his Department holds with commercial airlines for the purposes of enforced returns.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237179","237179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105247","2019-04-01","Home Office","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether his Department has ever given direction, pursuant to Schedule 3 of the Immigration Act 1971, to an airline to carry out enforced returns.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237180","237180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105248","2019-04-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of personal independence payment claimants with mental health conditions have had their application granted in (a) Camberwell and Peckham constituency, (b) Southwark, and (c) London in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236978","236978"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105249","2019-03-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to prioritise respect for human rights and the rights of minorities when working in partnership with countries of the Sahel.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237063","237063"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105250","2019-04-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of personal independence payment claimants with physical health conditions have their application granted in (a) Camberwell and Peckham constituency, (b) Southwark, and (c) London in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236979","236979"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105251","2019-04-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of personal independence payment assessment meetings are carried out (a) at the claimant’s home and (b) in assessment centres.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236980","236980"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105252","2019-03-28","Home Office","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department,  what steps the Government is taking to ensure that the UK is not perceived as a safe haven for people suspected of committing international crimes.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Mitchell","Mr Andrew Mitchell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237019","237019"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105253","2019-03-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to strengthen UK co-operation with international partners to ensure the (a) prosecution and (b) extradition of people who commit international crimes.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Mitchell","Mr Andrew Mitchell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237020","237020"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105254","2019-04-01","Home Office","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people were stopped and searched by the Metropolitan Police in each of the last five years; and for how many of those people was there no further action.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236981","236981"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105255","2019-03-28","Home Office","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of the resources of the (a) Metropolitan Police and (b) CPS to (i) investigate and (ii) prosecute people residing in the UK who are suspected of committing international crimes; and if he will ensure that the investigation and prosecution of such individuals is prioritised.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Mitchell","Mr Andrew Mitchell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237021","237021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105256","2019-04-01","Home Office","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of the impact of Stop and Search on the relationship between police officers and young BAME people.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236982","236982"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105257","2019-03-28","Home Office","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the High Court decision not to extradite to Rwanda persons suspected of involvement in the 1994 genocide against the Tutsis, what steps the (a) Metropolitan Police and (b) CPS have taken to comply with the Government's obligations under national and international law to investigate and prosecute acts of genocide.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Mitchell","Mr Andrew Mitchell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237022","237022"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105258","2019-04-01","Northern Ireland Office","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, on what date the next British Irish Intergovernmental Conference is scheduled to take place.","Biography information for Tony Lloyd","Tony Lloyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237023","237023"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105259","2019-03-28","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how many people working on the broadband delivery programme are (a) contingent labour, (b) supplier resource and (c) civil servants.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237002","237002"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105260","2019-04-01","Northern Ireland Office","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, when she plans to lay before the House the relevant measures to extend the period under which the duty to call an Assembly election is removed as outlined in the Northern Ireland (Executive Formation and Exercise of Functions) Act 2018.","Biography information for Tony Lloyd","Tony Lloyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237024","237024"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105261","2019-04-01","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the findings of the May 2018 report by the Institute for European Environmental Policy, what steps his Department is taking to tackle micro-plastic contamination on land; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237064","237064"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105262","2019-04-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether health professionals and other experts in the health sector outside of the appointed national workforce group will be consulted and able to feed into the forthcoming workforce implementation plan.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237025","237025"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105263","2019-04-01","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 13 February 2019 to Question 217065 on Prisons: Drugs, how many ambulances attended each prison as a result of (a) injuries due to exposure to psychoactive substance and (b) all injuries in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237181","237181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105264","2019-03-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of the regulations governing the use of the whip in horse racing.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237026","237026"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105265","2019-03-28","Department for Education","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether the upcoming Comprehensive Spending Review will prioritise funding services for disabled children and implement the Disabled Children's Partnership's proposal for an early intervention and family resilience scheme.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237065","237065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105266","2019-03-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many bovine tuberculosis (a) new herd incidents and (b) officially free status withdrawn cases there were in the Nottingham-shire badger cull areas in each calendar year from 2010 to 2018.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237182","237182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105267","2019-03-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate his Department has made of the number of deaths that can be attributed to poor air quality in Nottinghamshire in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237183","237183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105268","2019-03-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment the Government has made of the feasibility of banning the use of non-recyclable plastics in Nottinghamshire.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237184","237184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105269","2019-03-28","Home Office","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans he has for immigration policy to ensure the effective recruitment NHS and care workers from EU and non-EU countries after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Mr Robert Goodwill","Mr Robert Goodwill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237066","237066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105270","2019-03-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent steps his Department has taken to support the food and beverage sector in Nottinghamshire.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237185","237185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105271","2019-03-28","Home Office","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the salary exemption for nurses under Tier 2 visa rules will (a) remain in place and (b) be extended to EEA citizens after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Mr Robert Goodwill","Mr Robert Goodwill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237067","237067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105272","2019-03-28","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how many people working on the 700 MHz Clearance Programme are (a) contingent labour, (b) supplier resource and (c) civil servants.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237003","237003"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105273","2019-03-28","Home Office","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps he is taking to ensure care workers can come and work in the UK.","Biography information for Mr Robert Goodwill","Mr Robert Goodwill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237068","237068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105274","2019-03-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many people working on the Defra Unity Programme are (a) contingent labour, (b) supplier resource and (c) civil servants.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237004","237004"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105275","2019-04-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to his oral contribution of 26 March 2019, what assessment he has made of the effect on Ealing Hospital of the Government ceasing to support the Shaping a healthier future project.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237069","237069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105276","2019-04-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the contribution of the Minister for Health in the Seventh Delegated Legislation Committee on 25 March 2019, columns 11-12, if he will place in the Library a copy of the communication from the Permanent Secretary of the Department of Health for Northern Ireland confirming the assent of the Northern Ireland Civil Service to the draft Health Services (Cross-Border Health Care and Miscellaneous Amendments) (Northern Ireland) (EU Exit) Regulations 2019.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237070","237070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105277","2019-03-28","Department for Transport","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many people working on the airport capacity programme are (a) contingent labour, (b) supplier resource and (c) civil servants.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237005","237005"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105278","2019-03-28","Home Office","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions he has had with Cabinet colleagues on the increase in right-wing extremism.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237186","237186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105279","2019-03-28","Department for International Trade","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on UK oil refining from the unilateral application of zero import tariffs on 87 per cent of goods entering the UK in the event of the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Stephen Crabb","Stephen Crabb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237071","237071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105280","2019-03-28","Department for International Trade","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of imposing reciprocal tariffs for petroleum products in the event of the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Stephen Crabb","Stephen Crabb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237072","237072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105281","2019-03-28","Department for Transport","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment he has made of the effectiveness of enforcement mechanisms to ensure legal compliance of car manufacturers with emissions targets.","Biography information for Nick Smith","Nick Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237073","237073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105282","2019-03-28","Department for Transport","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the need for UK Government investment in transport infrastructure in South Wales after the UK leaves the European Union; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Nick Smith","Nick Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237074","237074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105284","2019-03-28","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the merits of raising the current clinical age limits for screening for (a) breast and (b) cervical cancer.","Biography information for Nick Smith","Nick Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237076","237076"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105285","2019-03-28","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the merits of extending the National Child Measurement Programme to other primary school age groups.","Biography information for Nick Smith","Nick Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237077","237077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105286","2019-03-28","Treasury","2019-03-26","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of current (a) legal (b) administrative and (c) financial penalties for the provision of poor pension transfer advice.","Biography information for Nick Smith","Nick Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237078","237078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105287","2019-03-28","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the number of people in the UK who suffer with mental health as a consequence of alopecia.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237079","237079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105288","2019-03-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the level of coordination between the Pensions Regulator and the Financial Conduct Authority in relation to defined benefit pension transfer advice.","Biography information for Nick Smith","Nick Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237080","237080"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105289","2019-04-01","Department for Transport","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many ministerial directions have been issued by Ministers in his Department in each of the last eight years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237027","237027"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105290","2019-03-28","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the number of people who have been diagnosed with alopecia in the UK.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237081","237081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105291","2019-03-28","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much the NHS has spent on providing wigs to patients diagnosed with alopecia in each of the last three years for which information is available.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237082","237082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105292","2019-03-28","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much money from the public purse has been spent on approving suppliers to the NHS in each of the last three years for which information is available.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237083","237083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105293","2019-03-28","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the number of CCGs that are using suppliers that have not been officially approved by the NHS.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237084","237084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105294","2019-03-28","Department for Transport","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the letter of 20 March 2019 from the Prime Minister to Midland Connect, whether the potential changes to phase 2b of the High Speed Two route will affect the (a) eastern leg and (b) western leg of that route.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237006","237006"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105295","2019-03-28","Department for Transport","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the letter of 20 March 2019 from the Prime Minister to Midland Connect, what are the potential changes to phase 2b of the High Speed Two route.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237028","237028"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105296","2019-03-28","Department for Transport","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the letter of 20 March 2019 from the Prime Minister to Midland Connect, whether the potential changes to phase b of the High Speed Two route will affect (a) residents, (b) property, (c) business and (d) transport links in Hemsworth constituency.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237029","237029"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105297","2019-03-28","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 22 February 2019 to Question 220837 on Local Plans, whether his Department has no plans to set a deadline for local authorities to have a local plan.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237085","237085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105298","2019-03-28","Department for Transport","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the letter of 20 March 2019 from the Prime Minister to Midland Connect, whether details of the potential changes to phase 2b of the High Speed Two route are publicly available.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237030","237030"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105299","2019-03-28","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 20 February 2019 to Question 220835 on Housing: Construction, when his Department will be setting out space standards for new homes.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237086","237086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105300","2019-03-28","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 22 February 2019 to Question 220834, what progress his Department has made since 2017 in increasing transparency on who owns land privately held and the options held over it.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237087","237087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105301","2019-03-28","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 22 February 2019 to Question 220826 on Housing: Construction, whether his Department has made an estimate of the amount of Section 106 funding lost to local authorities when new homes are created under permitted development rather than through granted planning permission.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237088","237088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105302","2019-04-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will publish details of his assessment that The Health Services (Cross-Border Health Care And Miscellaneous Amendments)(Northern Ireland) (EU Exit) Regulations 2019 was required in order to secure legal certainty in Northern Ireland; and on what date that decision was made.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237089","237089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105303","2019-03-28","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 22 February 2019 to Question 220840 on Housing: Construction, whether his Department has made no assessment of the suitability of the location of housing created under permitted development.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237090","237090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105304","2019-04-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will publish a list of the officials he consulted with from the Department of Health in Northern Ireland and the Northern Ireland Office who gave consent to the Health Services (Cross-Border Health Care and Miscellaneous Amendments) (Northern Ireland) (EU Exit) Regulations 2019.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237091","237091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105305","2019-04-01","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to ensure that out-of-country appeals from Ghana are conducted fairly and without prejudice to an appellant’s case; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236989","236989"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105306","2019-03-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 18 March 2019 to Question 232052 on Social Security Benefits: Medical Examinations, if she will make an assessment of the average waiting time at assessment centres; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237187","237187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105307","2019-03-28","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people working on the CSC Local Service Provider Delivery Programme are (a) contingent labour, (b) supplier resource and (c) civil servants.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237031","237031"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105308","2019-03-28","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people working on the NHSmail 2 programme are (a) contingent labour, (b) supplier resource and (c) civil servants.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237032","237032"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105309","2019-03-28","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether the Government has made an assessment of the effect on levels of nuisance calls of companies requiring consumers to provide their phone numbers when purchasing products or signing up for services.","Biography information for Alex Chalk","Alex Chalk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237188","237188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105310","2019-03-28","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people working on the National Data Services Development Programme are (a) contingent labour, (b) supplier resource and (c) civil servants.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237033","237033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105311","2019-03-28","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people working on the Health and Social Care Network are (a) contingent labour, (b) supplier resource and (c) civil servants.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237034","237034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105312","2019-03-28","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of holding classes in local schools to teach parents how to cook quick, nutritious and affordable meals.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237189","237189"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105313","2019-03-28","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people working on the Procurement Transformation Programme are (a) contingent labour, (b) supplier resource and (c) civil servants.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237035","237035"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105314","2019-03-28","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions he has had with his devolved Assembly counterparts on health inequalities throughout the UK.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237190","237190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105315","2019-03-28","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of people being able to self-refer for a smear test in a local sexual health clinic.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237191","237191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105316","2019-03-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 21 March 2019 to Question 231976, what the capacity assessment of the Expert Committee on Pesticides concluded with respect to whether the (a) annual budget and (b) staff capacity of the Committee and its secretariat would need to be increased in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237092","237092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105317","2019-03-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he his making to his Bahraini counterpart on the welfare of female human rights defenders detained in Isa Town Prison.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237192","237192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105318","2019-04-01","Northern Ireland Office","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, with reference to her oral contribution to the Women and Equalities Committee inquiry into abortion in Northern Ireland on 27 February 2019, what plans she has to bring forward legislative proposals to give legal standing to the Northern Ireland Human Rights Committee.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237193","237193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105319","2019-03-28","Department for Transport","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what his policy is on proposals for new stations within the greenbelt.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237036","237036"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105320","2019-03-28","Department for Transport","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what his policy is on dealing with proposals from transport authorities for new stations which do not fall within that authority's area.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237037","237037"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105321","2019-04-01","Home Office","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans he has to tackle (a) retail crime and (b) violence against shopworkers; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236990","236990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105322","2019-03-28","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the average waiting time for a non-emergency GP appointment was in Warrington at the last date for which figures are available.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237038","237038"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105323","2019-03-28","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the 2019 voluntary scheme for branded medicines pricing and access affordability mechanism, whether his Department has conducted an impact assessment on the exemption of smaller companies from the rebate scheme.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237093","237093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105324","2019-04-01","Department for Education","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much his Department spent on (a) the universal 15 hours of free childcare for three to four-year olds, (b) the extended entitlement for eligible three to four-year old children of working parents and (c) free childcare for two year olds in 2016-17.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237194","237194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105325","2019-04-01","Treasury","2019-03-26","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much was spent on (a) tax-free childcare, (b) employer-supported childcare and (c) the childcare element of working tax credit in 2017-18.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237195","237195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105326","2019-04-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he has taken to ensure there is an independent and transparent investigation into killings on the Gaza border in 2018.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237094","237094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105327","2019-03-28","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the 2019 voluntary scheme for branded medicines pricing and access affordability mechanism, whether his Department has conducted an impact assessment on how the 36-month exemption of new medicines from contributing to the rebate scheme will effect the NHS's drug procurement Bill.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237095","237095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105328","2019-03-28","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to encourage organ donation.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237096","237096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105329","2019-03-28","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to improve services for people with autism.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237097","237097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105330","2019-03-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what progress has been made in implementing an EU sanctions regime on the use of chemical weapons.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237098","237098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105331","2019-03-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many active universal credit (work capability) decisions, which have been appealed to Her Majesty's Courts and Tribunals Service, are now subject to an order of the tribunal asking her Department to respond within 21 days.","Biography information for Martin Whitfield","Martin Whitfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237196","237196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105332","2019-04-01","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to row 12 of the table on page 35 of his Department's 2018-19 Main Estimate Memorandum, if he will publish a breakdown of spending under the heading Low Pay Commission.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237197","237197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105333","2019-04-01","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to rows 25,26 and 27 of the table on page 36 of the his Department's 2018-19 Main Estimate Memorandum, if he will publish a breakdown of spending under the heading Capability: Core and Agency Admin, Centrally held/unallocated and Other Programmes.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237198","237198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105334","2019-03-28","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to row 8 of the table on page 37 of his Department's 2018-19 Main Estimate Memorandum, if he will publish a breakdown of spending under the heading Government as a Shareholder: Other Programmes.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237199","237199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105335","2019-03-28","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to row 16 of the table on page 37 of his Department's 2018-19 Main Estimate Memorandum, if he will publish a breakdown of spending under the heading Financial Reporting Council Admin.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237200","237200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105336","2019-03-28","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to row 15 of the table on page 37 of his Department's 2018-19 Main Estimate Memorandum, if he will publish a breakdown of spending under the heading Competition Service Programme.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237201","237201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105337","2019-04-01","Department for International Trade","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what plans his Department has for imposing a ban on the importation of fur products.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237099","237099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105338","2019-03-28","Cabinet Office","2019-03-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will list the suicide rates in the UK in each of the last five years by local authority area.","Biography information for Tracey Crouch","Tracey Crouch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237100","237100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105339","2019-04-01","Department for Education","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of eligible children are receiving 15 hours of free childcare for disadvantaged two-year olds in each local authority.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237202","237202"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105340","2019-03-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent steps the Government is taking to help tackle the persecution of Christians overseas.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237101","237101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105341","2019-03-28","Ministry of Defence","2019-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to support defence industry jobs.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237102","237102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105342","2019-03-28","Treasury","2019-03-26","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many sites HMRC have vacated since 15 November 2015.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237203","237203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105343","2019-04-01","Treasury","2019-03-26","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate the Department has made of the number of sites that it has vacated since 15 November 2015 for which HMRC has paid rent to (a) any freeholder and (b)  Mapeley after it had vacated those sites.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237204","237204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105344","2019-04-01","Treasury","2019-03-26","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether HMRC is paying rent on sites that have (a) been vacated by its staff and (b) where there is no active HMRC work being carried out.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237205","237205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105345","2019-03-28","Treasury","2019-03-26","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many sites vacated by HMRC since 15 November 2015 were sites managed under the STEPS contract.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237206","237206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105346","2019-04-01","Treasury","2019-03-26","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to Mortgage customers: proposed changes to responsible lending rules and guidance CP19/14 published by the Financial Conduct Authority on 26 March 2019, what estimate his Department has made of the number of mortgage customers currently unable to switch their mortgage product who will not be able to benefit from modified affordability assessment proposals.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237207","237207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105347","2019-03-28","Treasury","2019-03-26","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many sites that HMRC has vacated since 15 November 2015 were sites (a) not under the STEPS contract and (b) where the freeholder was not Mapeley.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237208","237208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105348","2019-04-01","Treasury","2019-03-26","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with the Financial Conduct Authority on the development of the cost benefit analysis used to assess the potential impact of the its proposals in Mortgage customers: proposed changes to responsible lending rules and guidance CP19/14 published on 26 March 2019.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237209","237209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1105349","2019-04-01","Treasury","2019-03-26","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to correspondence from the Economic Secretary to the Treasury to the Chair of the Treasury Committee on 30 January 2019 on how the Standard Variable Rate will be set; what the identity is of the regulatory active lenders in the mechanism referred to on page 3; what the current level of Standard Variable Rate being charged by those lenders is; and what formula was used by UK Asset Resolution to link its Standard Variable Rate to the rate charged by those lenders.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237210","237210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104477","2019-03-25","Ministry of Defence","2019-03-25","What recent assessment he has made of trends in the level of morale in the armed forces.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 910007","910007"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104478","2019-03-25","Ministry of Defence","2019-03-25","What steps his Department is taking to ensure that veterans are honoured for their service; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Charlie Elphicke","Charlie Elphicke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 910008","910008"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104691","2019-03-28","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what research his Department has (a) conducted or (b) commissioned on whether the correct legal procedures are being followed in relation to adjudications in prisons.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236493","236493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104692","2019-03-27","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many oncology patients have been registered to receive treatment through the NHS in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236365","236365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104693","2019-03-27","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many (a) nurses and (b) doctors are specifically employed within the oncology speciality.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236366","236366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104694","2019-03-27","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much the NHS spent on providing oncological treatment in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236367","236367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104695","2019-03-27","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the estimated cost of inefficiency in the NHS has been in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236368","236368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104696","2019-03-27","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many IT systems are used within oncological treatment in the NHS.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236369","236369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104697","2019-03-27","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what the outcomes were from the meetings of the Sports Business Council held between June 2017 and April 2018; and when the council next plans to meet.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236370","236370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104698","2019-03-27","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what plans the Government has to maintain the Inter-Ministerial Group for Healthy Living and the Sports Business Council.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236371","236371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104699","2019-03-28","Department for Transport","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the target for all franchises to stop discharging effluent onto tracks will be met by the end of the calendar year; and whether any franchises will be allowed exemptions.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236494","236494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104700","2019-03-27","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent progress his Department has made in ensuring the UK meets its 2.4% GDP target for R&D funding.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236372","236372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104701","2019-03-27","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent steps his Department has taken in ensuring continuity of funding for research projects with EU funding in the event of the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236373","236373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104702","2019-03-27","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether the £7 billion of additional spending for research and development will be in addition to replacing EU funding lost after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236374","236374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104703","2019-03-27","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will support a targeted capacity building approach to his Department’s funding of research and development.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236375","236375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104704","2019-03-27","Department for Education","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to tackle the skills gap in STEM subjects.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236376","236376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104705","2019-03-27","Northern Ireland Office","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what estimate she has made of the number of people with obesity in (a) Northern Ireland and (b) each Clinical Commissioning Group in Northern Ireland by (i) age and (ii) gender in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236377","236377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104706","2019-03-27","Northern Ireland Office","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what steps her Department is taking to tackle regional differences in (a) adult and (b) childhood obesity in Northern Ireland; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236378","236378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104707","2019-03-27","Northern Ireland Office","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, which Clinical Commissioning Groups in Northern Ireland provide a (a) tier three and (b) tier four weight management service.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236379","236379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104708","2019-03-27","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether NHS England plans to continue to fund the NICE commissioning support programme until the capacity of the NICE appraisal programme is increased to enable the routine assessment of all new medicines.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236380","236380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104709","2019-03-27","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, which clinical policies awaiting review by the Clinical Priorities Advisory Group involve the use of the NICE commissioning support programme.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236381","236381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104710","2019-03-27","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many adults started eating disorder treatment in (a) 2016-17 and (b) 2017-18.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236495","236495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104711","2019-03-27","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many adults were referred for assessment of a suspected eating disorder in (a) 2016-17 and (b) 2017-18; and what proportion of those referrals were made to an eating disorders service.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236496","236496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104712","2019-03-27","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the size of the workforce was in working time equivalent of (a) community eating disorders services for children and young people and (b) adult community eating disorders services, on 31 March 2017.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236497","236497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104713","2019-03-27","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what revised training is being provided to existing prison officers to ensure that they are equipped to support a rehabilitative approach for offenders in custody; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236498","236498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104714","2019-03-28","Attorney General","2019-03-25","To ask the Attorney General, what the timetable is for the Serious Fraud Office investigation into London Capital & Finance.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236382","236382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104715","2019-03-27","Attorney General","2019-03-25","To ask the The Attorney General, for what reasons three former Credit Suisse employees, Andrew James Pearse, Surjan Singh and Detelina Vaneva Subeva who are subject to an extradition request from US authorities, have not been charged under UK law.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236253","236253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104716","2019-03-28","Northern Ireland Office","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, if she will publish who (a) she and (b) Ministers of her Department have met in meetings and engagements over the last 14 months; and if she will also publish on what dates those meetings were held.","Biography information for Tony Lloyd","Tony Lloyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236301","236301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104717","2019-03-28","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether he discussed with Mark Zuckerberg at their meeting in week commencing 18 February 2019 the January 2019 Facebook data breach in which the passwords of up to 600 million users were made available to Facebook employees.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236302","236302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104718","2019-03-28","Home Office","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions he has had with his counterparts in (a) Turkey, (b) Bulgaria and (c) Greece on supporting their investigations into the movement of the suspect in the recent shootings in mosques in Christchurch, New Zealand.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236383","236383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104719","2019-03-28","Department for International Development","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much financial aid her Department plans to provide to (a) Mozambique and (b) Malawi to tackle the destruction of Cyclone Idai; and which organisations will receive that funding.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236384","236384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104720","2019-03-28","Department for International Development","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what plans the Government has to support Italy’s draft resolution on improving the transparency of markets for drugs, vaccines and other health-related technologies at the World Health Assembly.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236385","236385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104721","2019-03-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent estimate she has made of the number of universal credit claimants in (a) Cardiff South and Penarth, (b) the Vale of Glamorgan and (c) Wales who have (ii) had their housing benefit stopped without notice and (ii) are in rent arrears.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236386","236386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104722","2019-03-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent estimate she has made of the number of people in (a) Cardiff South and Penarth, (b) the Vale of Glamorgan and (c) Wales that have waited more than 6 weeks to receive benefit payments in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236387","236387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104723","2019-03-27","Home Office","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of bringing the funding for the  protection for mosques in line with that provided for the protection of synagogues via the grant administered by the Community Security Trust.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236388","236388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104724","2019-03-28","Cabinet Office","2019-03-25","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will publish the social media policy for HM Government accounts.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236499","236499"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104725","2019-03-28","Home Office","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps his Department is taking to support young EU nationals apply to the EU Settlement Scheme who may have difficulty in providing documentation proving their residency in the UK.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236500","236500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104726","2019-03-28","Home Office","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Coram Children’s Legal Centre's report entitled Making Brexit work for children, what assessment he has made of the potential merits for his policies of that report's recommendations on settlement status of EU national children in the UK.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236501","236501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104727","2019-03-28","Department for Education","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to figures published by the Higher Education Statistics Agency for 2017-18, what assessment he has made of the reasons for the increase in the number of higher education institutions in deficit.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236303","236303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104728","2019-03-28","Department for Education","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent discussions he has had with the Home Secretary on reintroducing post-study work visas for overseas students.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236304","236304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104729","2019-03-28","Home Office","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which local authorities have had the highest incidence of knife-related (a) deaths and (b) injuries in each of the last eight years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236305","236305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104730","2019-03-28","Department for Education","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many exclusions per head of population there have been in each local authority area in each of the last nine years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236306","236306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104731","2019-03-28","Department for Education","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether it is his policy to allow existing selective schools to open new sites; and whether the Selective School Expansion Fund can be used to fund school expansion onto new sites.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236389","236389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104732","2019-03-28","Department for Education","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether his Department has received legal advice on whether expansion of existing grammar schools to new sites or campuses is lawful.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236390","236390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104733","2019-03-28","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the average waiting time for patients to see their GP in the Blackpool NHS Clinical Commissioning Group has been for non-emergency appointments (a) between June and September 2018, (b) between October and December 2018, (c) in January 2019 and (d) in February 2019.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236307","236307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104734","2019-03-28","Department for Education","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what criteria his Department uses to define a new school.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236391","236391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104735","2019-03-28","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the number of people attending (a) A&E facilities at the Blackpool Acute Hospitals Trust and (b) Walk-in facilities in Blackpool between June 2018 and January 2019 who could have been seen as a non-emergency appointment.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236308","236308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104736","2019-03-28","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the effect has been on levels of nurse recruitment of the removal of the nursing bursary.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236245","236245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104737","2019-03-27","Ministry of Defence","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department has taken to (a) protect (i) military personnel and (ii) their spouses and children in relation to domestic abuse and (b) ensure the protection of people reporting that abuse.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236392","236392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104738","2019-03-27","Ministry of Defence","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what monitoring his Department undertakes on reports of domestic abuse in (a) his Department and (b) each of the armed services.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236393","236393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104739","2019-03-27","Ministry of Defence","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what (a) charities and (b) other support services his Department engages with in order to provide support to military personnel and their families affected by domestic abuse.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236394","236394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104740","2019-03-27","Ministry of Defence","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what monitoring his Department undertakes of incidents of domestic abuse throughout the military estate (a) in the UK and (b) overseas.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236395","236395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104741","2019-03-27","Ministry of Defence","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he has taken to ensure the adequacy of the (a) recording of domestic abuse and (b) the provision of that information to support services on each military base.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236396","236396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104742","2019-03-27","Ministry of Defence","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many service personnel have been suspended or reprimanded as a result of incidents and alleged incidents of domestic abuse in each year for which information is available.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236502","236502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104743","2019-03-27","Ministry of Defence","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many service personnel have been prosecuted for domestic abuse in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236503","236503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104744","2019-03-28","Home Office","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many places in the seasonal workers pilot scheme have been ring-fenced for Scotland.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236504","236504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104745","2019-03-28","Home Office","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what criteria his Department used to determine the figure of 2,500 for non-EU workers for the seasonal workers pilot scheme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236505","236505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104746","2019-03-27","Home Office","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps he is taking to ensure that the number of (a) NHS and (b) care workers recruited from (i) EEA and (ii) non-EEA countries is adequate for (A) current requirements and (B) requirements in the short term.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236397","236397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104747","2019-03-27","Home Office","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of establishing identity scanner locations to process applications for the EU settlement scheme.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236269","236269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104748","2019-03-28","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many assaults took place in each prison in the 12 months to September 2018.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236506","236506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104749","2019-03-27","Department for Education","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which (a) individuals and (b) organisations were sent copies of the Relationships Education, Relationships and Sex Education and Health Education draft statutory guidance for governing bodies, proprietors, head teachers, principals, senior leadership teams, teachers prior to its publication; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236239","236239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104750","2019-03-27","Home Office","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether he plans to extend the Tier 2 visa salary exemption for nurses to EEA nationals in the event that the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236398","236398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104751","2019-03-28","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average population was in each prison in the 12 months to September 2018.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236507","236507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104752","2019-03-27","Home Office","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many identity scanner locations (a) have been and (b) are planned to be opened for the EU settlement scheme.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236270","236270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104753","2019-03-27","Home Office","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when it is planned to open the EU settlement scheme in full in the event that the UK’s departure from the EU is delayed.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236271","236271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104754","2019-03-27","Home Office","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans his Department has to open new e-passport gates at UK airports.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236272","236272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104755","2019-03-27","Home Office","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which nationalities were able to use e-passport gates in (a) 2016, (b) 2017, (c) 2018 and (d) to date in 2019; and which nationalities are planned to be able to access e-passport gates in 2020.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236273","236273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104756","2019-03-28","Home Office","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps he is taking to ensure the recruitment of NHS and care workers from (a) EU and (b) non-EU countries to meet levels of demand after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236399","236399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104757","2019-03-28","Home Office","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether he holds information on the average time a person released under investigation went without contact from an investigating officer in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236508","236508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104758","2019-03-28","Home Office","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether he plans to (a) retain and (b) extend to EEA citizens the Tier 2 visa salary exemption for nurses after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236400","236400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104759","2019-03-28","Home Office","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether he plans to ensure that overseas care workers are exempt from the Tier 2 visa £30,000 salary cap and able to work in the UK; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236401","236401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104760","2019-03-27","Department for Education","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whom his Department consulted before drafting the Relationships Education, Relationships and Sex Education and Health Education draft statutory guidance for governing bodies, proprietors, head teachers, principals, senior leadership teams, teachers; what research was evaluated; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236240","236240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104761","2019-03-28","Attorney General","2019-03-25","To ask the Attorney General, what steps he is taking to address failures relating to disclosure of evidence through the encouragement of early engagement between prosecution and defence in criminal cases.","Biography information for Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236509","236509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104762","2019-03-28","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the current number of vacancies is in each community rehabilitation company.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236510","236510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104763","2019-03-28","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many Serious Further Offence reviews have been reopened in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236511","236511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104764","2019-03-27","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, in how many cases Serious Further Offence reviews have cited excessive workload as a contributory factor to that offence.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236512","236512"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104765","2019-03-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 19 March 2019 to Question 230785, whether the Commissioner for the British Indian Ocean Territory plans to be accompanied by Mauritian Government officials on future visits to the Chagos Archipelago.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236513","236513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104766","2019-03-27","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, in how many cases Serious Further Offence reviews have cited inadequate management supervision as factor contributing to the further serious offence.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236514","236514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104767","2019-03-28","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average caseload is per probation officer in each community rehabilitation company.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236515","236515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104768","2019-03-27","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many probation officers worked at over 110% capacity at some point during 2018 in each community rehabilitation company.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236516","236516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104769","2019-03-27","Home Office","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people working on the Smarter Working Programme are (a) contingent labour, (b) supplier resource and (c) civil servants.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236274","236274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104770","2019-03-28","Home Office","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people working on developing the Disclosure and Barring Service are (a) contingent labour, (b) supplier resource and (c) civil servants.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236275","236275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104771","2019-03-27","Home Office","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people working on developing Digital Services at the Border are (a) contingent labour, (b) supplier resource and (c) civil servants.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236276","236276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104772","2019-03-28","Home Office","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people working on developing the Emergency Services Mobile Communications Programme are (a) contingent labour, (b) supplier resource and (c) civil servants.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236277","236277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104773","2019-03-27","Department for Education","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what requests for information relating to (a) abortion and (b) sex and relationships education were made to his Department and its predecessor under the provisions of the Freedom of Information Act 2000 in each year since 2010; whether each request was (i) agreed to and (ii) refused; if he will place in the Library a copy of the information provided in response to each request; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236241","236241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104774","2019-03-28","Ministry of Defence","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many people working on developing the Wildcat Programme are (a) contingent labour, (b) supplier resource and (c) civil servants.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236278","236278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104775","2019-03-27","Department for Education","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what information is provided to parents on the content of sex education being taught in their child's primary school; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236242","236242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104776","2019-03-28","Ministry of Defence","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many people working on developing MODnet Evolve are (a) contingent labour, (b) supplier resource (c) civil servants.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236279","236279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104777","2019-03-28","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how many consultants his Department has hired in each year since 2016; and what the cost has been to the public purse.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236402","236402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104778","2019-03-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many consultants his Department has hired in each year since 2016; and what the cost has been to the public purse.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236403","236403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104779","2019-03-27","Ministry of Defence","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many people working on developing New Style of Information Technology Deployed are (a) contingent labour, (b) supplier resource and (c) civil servants.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236280","236280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104780","2019-03-28","Attorney General","2019-03-25","To ask the Attorney General, how many consultants his Department has hired in each year since 2016; and what the cost has been to the public purse.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236404","236404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104781","2019-03-28","Wales Office","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how many consultants his Department has hired in each year since 2016; and what the cost has been to the public purse.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236405","236405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104782","2019-03-27","Ministry of Defence","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many people working on New Style of Information Technology (Base) are (a) contingent labour, (b) supplier resource and (c) civil servants.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236281","236281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104783","2019-03-28","Scotland Office","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how many consultants his Department has hired in each year since 2016; and what the cost has been to the public purse.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236406","236406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104784","2019-03-27","Ministry of Defence","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many people working on developing Contracting, Purchasing and Finance are (a) contingent labour, (b) supplier resource and (c) civil servants.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236282","236282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104785","2019-03-27","Ministry of Defence","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many people working on developing the Future IT Sourcing Programme are (a) contingent labour, (b) supplier resource and (c) civil servants.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236283","236283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104786","2019-03-27","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people working on developing the Future IT Sourcing Programme are (a) contingent labour, (b) supplier resource and (c) civil servants.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236284","236284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104787","2019-03-28","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people working on developing the NOMS Digital Transformation Programme are (a) contingent labour, (b) supplier resource and (c) civil servants.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236285","236285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104788","2019-03-27","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people working on developing the Criminal Justice System Exchange Re-provisioning programme are (a) contingent labour, (b) supplier resource and (c) civil servants.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236286","236286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104789","2019-03-27","Department for Education","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will place in the Library copies of the Memorandum of Understanding and any other data-sharing agreement for pupil, student and workforce data between his Department and the Home Office.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236407","236407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104790","2019-03-27","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people working on developing HM Courts & Tribunals Service Reform Re-provisioning are (a) contingent labour, (b) supplier resource and (c) civil servants.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236287","236287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104791","2019-03-27","Department for Education","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 19 December 2018 to Question 201097 on Pupils: Personal Records,  what methods schools have as available to them as joint data controllers to withdraw (a) nationality and (b) country-of-birth data that they collected in the school census since 2016 and which parents now wish to retract as a result of the ongoing use of pupil data for immigration enforcement purposes.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236408","236408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104792","2019-03-28","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will ask the Competition and Markets Authority to investigate the level and effectiveness of competition in online hotel booking.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236409","236409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104793","2019-03-28","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the effect of AirB&B on tourism in the North East.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236410","236410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104794","2019-03-28","Treasury","2019-03-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the taxation rate for online accommodation booking businesses.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236411","236411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104795","2019-03-28","Treasury","2019-03-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will publish in full the results from any local economic impact assessment ahead of the decision to close the HMRC office in Portsmouth.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236517","236517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104796","2019-03-28","Treasury","2019-03-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what is the cumulative length of service of all HMRC staff (a) employed at and (b) at risk of redundancy from the closure of the Portsmouth office.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236518","236518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104797","2019-03-27","Treasury","2019-03-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the cumulative years of experience lost through staff redundancy by HMRC in south coast offices in 2018.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236519","236519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104798","2019-03-28","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans the Government and NHS England have to ensure that CCGs use the funding allocated nationally to prescribe Flash Glucose Monitoring from 1 April 2019 using central NHS criteria.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236412","236412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104799","2019-03-28","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps NHS England is taking to encourage CCGs which do not prescribe Flash Glucose Monitoring technology to do so as soon as possible when new guidance comes into effect from 1 April 2019.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236413","236413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104800","2019-03-28","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, which CCGs do not currently prescribe Flash Glucose Monitoring kits.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236414","236414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104801","2019-03-28","Northern Ireland Office","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, whether the decision on the legislative consent motions required for clauses 1 to 4 of the Offensive Weapons Bill will be made solely by the Department of Justice in Northern Ireland and the Northern Ireland Office.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236415","236415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104802","2019-03-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to progress trade opportunities with China in poultry meat and breeding stock.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236416","236416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104803","2019-03-28","Department for International Trade","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that the carcass balance of poultry meat is maintained as part of trade negotiations with China after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236417","236417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104804","2019-03-27","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to ensure that standards of poultry welfare are maintained in a potential future trade agreement with the US.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236418","236418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104805","2019-03-27","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, if he will provide a costed list of central government grants made to the National Trust in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Dr Andrew Murrison","Dr Andrew Murrison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236309","236309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104806","2019-03-28","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what guidance he has provided to Ofgem on how it checks that energy companies approach customers and other householders in an appropriate manner on the installation of smart meters; and whether there is a protocol to ensure that companies have clear guidelines on that process.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236254","236254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104807","2019-03-28","House of Commons Commission","2019-03-25","To ask the right hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington, representing the House of Commons Commission, what training and support is available to hon. Members' staff on suicide awareness.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236255","236255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104808","2019-03-27","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the level of access to superfast fibre broadband for (a) businesses and (b) members of the public in Mansfield; and what steps he is taking to improve such access.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236520","236520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104809","2019-03-27","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many Drug Rehabilitation Requirements have been granted by courts in England in each of the last two years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236521","236521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104810","2019-03-28","Department for Transport","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to his Department's consultation Bus Services Act 2017: accessible information which closed on 16 September 2018, when he plans to bring forward legislative proposals on the requirement for all buses to have audio visual next stop and final destination announcements; and whether he plans to publish guidance on that matter.","Biography information for Teresa Pearce","Teresa Pearce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236419","236419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104811","2019-03-28","Department for Transport","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether (a) his Department has completed its evaluation of bids and (b) he has completed his consent relating to the tender for the Southeastern franchise; and whether his Department currently has credible live bids for that tender.","Biography information for Teresa Pearce","Teresa Pearce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236420","236420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104812","2019-03-28","Treasury","2019-03-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 5 February 2019 to Question 215222 on Brexit: Festivals and Special Occasions, on what date The Royal Mint plans for the 50 pence coin commemorating the UK’s departure from the EU to go into circulation.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236421","236421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104813","2019-03-28","Treasury","2019-03-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, on what date The Royal Mint began or plans to begin production of the 50 pence coin commemorating the UK’s departure from the EU.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236422","236422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104814","2019-03-28","Treasury","2019-03-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what costs The Royal Mint has incurred for the (a) design and (b) production of the 50 pence coin commemorating the UK’s departure from the EU.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236423","236423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104815","2019-03-27","Home Office","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the decision for Tata to replace Capita as IT providers for the Decision Barring Service, whether his Department has met with the Information Commissioner's Office to ensure that data is kept securely by Tata.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236522","236522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104816","2019-03-27","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if his Department will make an assessment of the potential merits of banning the import of polar bear trophies into the UK.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236523","236523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104817","2019-03-27","Home Office","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of a £30,000 annual salary threshold for  intermediate and high-skilled migrant workers on small towns that rely upon skilled migrant workers in the Yorkshire and the Humber; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236524","236524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104818","2019-03-27","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to secure a deal with Vertex on access for patients to the drug Orkambi on the NHS.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236525","236525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104819","2019-03-28","Department for Education","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans his Department has to ensure that relationship and sex education is LGBT-inclusive in all types of school in Yorkshire.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236526","236526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104820","2019-03-27","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the article entitled From power stations to solar panels, the future is local, by the Minister of State for Energy and Clean Growth on 8 January 2019, what steps he is taking to assist communities in Yorkshire transition to smarter energy systems.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236527","236527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104821","2019-03-27","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent steps his Department has taken to reduce waiting times (a) for NHS operations and (b) between admission and treatment at A&E in Yorkshire and the Humber.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236528","236528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104822","2019-03-28","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to make Brineura accessible to sufferers of Batten disease.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236529","236529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104823","2019-03-28","Home Office","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if his Department will allocate additional funding for the security and protection of mosques and Muslim faith schools.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236530","236530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104824","2019-03-28","Home Office","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps he is taking to protect people whose partners fraudulently take out debts in their name without their knowledge.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236531","236531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104825","2019-03-28","Department for International Trade","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether the UK ban on exports of sodium thiopental to the US will be maintained after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236532","236532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104826","2019-03-27","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, if the Government will make it its policy to extend mobile coverage with 4G technology to 95 per cent of the UK by the end of 2022.","Biography information for Chris Elmore","Chris Elmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236533","236533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104827","2019-03-27","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether the Government's policy to extend geographic mobile coverage to 95 per cent of the UK by the end of 2022 relates to 4G technology.","Biography information for Chris Elmore","Chris Elmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236534","236534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104828","2019-03-27","Department for Education","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of (a) all children and (b) children eligible for free school meals reached a Good Level of Development at age five in North Norfolk in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236310","236310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104829","2019-03-27","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to establish a diagnostic and care pathway for Ehlers-Danlos syndrome.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236424","236424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104830","2019-03-27","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people have been diagnosed with Ehlers-Danlos syndrome in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236425","236425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104831","2019-03-27","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of testing expectant mothers for hypermobility.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236426","236426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104832","2019-03-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many advance benefit payments have been made to people in Glasgow South West in each month since September 2018.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236535","236535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104833","2019-03-28","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he has made an assessment of the implications for his policies on staffing of the March 2019 King's Fund report entitled Closing the gap: Key areas of action for the health and care workforce; and whether he is taking urgent steps to ensure an adequate level of staffing for the delivery of high-quality health and social care over the next 10 years.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236311","236311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104834","2019-03-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the take-up rate has been of each income-based pensioner benefit in each of the last five years for which data are available.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236312","236312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104835","2019-03-28","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what support his Department is providing to entrepreneurs with family care responsibilities.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236313","236313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104836","2019-03-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent estimate she has made of the number of people who cannot claim universal credit online because they cannot access (a) a computer or (b) the internet.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236314","236314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104837","2019-03-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent estimate she has made of the number of universal credit claimants who do not have access to a computer or the internet.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236315","236315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104838","2019-03-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many sanctions applied to universal credit claimants result from a matter relating to the Online Journal system.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236316","236316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104839","2019-03-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent estimate he has made of the amount of surplus food produced in the UK; what the (a) sources and (b) destinations were of those surplus stocks; and how that estimate was calculated.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236317","236317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104840","2019-03-28","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department is taking to encourage UK-based institutional and private investors to invest in female entrepreneurs.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236318","236318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104841","2019-03-27","Department for Transport","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what progress his Department has made on awarding spaceport licences for horizontal satellite launch in the United Kingdom.","Biography information for Bill Grant","Bill Grant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236536","236536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104842","2019-03-28","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many times that Secretaries of State for his Department have used Chevening House for (a) departmental and (b) personal use during their respective times in office since the Department's establishment in 2016; and what the duration was of each of those occasions.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236537","236537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104843","2019-03-27","Treasury","2019-03-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many Economic Operator Registration and Identification numbers have been issued by HMRC to (a) VAT-registered and (b) non-VAT-registered UK exporters to EU countries in preparation for the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236246","236246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104844","2019-03-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment the Government has made of options for the return of UK nationals detained in North East Syria to be charged and prosecuted in the UK.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236247","236247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104845","2019-03-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what his policy is on (a) the transfer of detainees to the US detention facility in Guantanamo Bay and (b) the closure of that detention facility.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236248","236248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104846","2019-03-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the Government's policy is on the transfer of detainees in North East Syria for prosecution to authorities in (a) Assad-controlled Syria and (b) Iraq for prosecution in Iraqi domestic courts.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236249","236249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104847","2019-03-28","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether the core of Aluminium Composite Material cladding is filler material as the term is to be understood in the Government published guidance Fire safety: Approved Document B2, published in 2006, 2010, 2013, paragraph 12.7 and Approved Document B2, published 2018, Amendments paragraph 12.6.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236427","236427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104848","2019-03-28","House of Commons Commission","2019-03-25","To ask the right hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington, representing the House of Commons Commission, what assessment has been made of the success of the roll-out of updated IT equipment for Members and their staff, to enable them to work as efficiently as possible in responding to, and resolving, constituents’ cases.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236428","236428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104849","2019-03-27","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the cost to the public purse has been of  requiring medical professionals to disclose payments and gifts from medical and other suppliers; and what benefits have been derived from the implementing that requirement.","Biography information for Stephen Kerr","Stephen Kerr","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236538","236538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104850","2019-03-27","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many people working on the Local Land Charges Programme are (a) contingent labour, (b) supplier resource and (c) civil servants.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236288","236288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104851","2019-03-27","Cabinet Office","2019-03-25","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people working on the FOXHOUND Programme are (a) contingent labour, (b) supplier resource and (c) civil servants.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236289","236289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104852","2019-03-27","Cabinet Office","2019-03-25","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people working on GOV UK Verify are (a) contingent labour, (b) supplier resource and (c) civil servants.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236319","236319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104853","2019-03-27","Cabinet Office","2019-03-25","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people working on the ISSC2 are (a) contingent labour, (b) supplier resource and (c) civil servants.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236320","236320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104854","2019-03-27","Cabinet Office","2019-03-25","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people working on the Government as a platform programme are (a) contingent labour, (b) supplier resource and (c) civil servants.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236321","236321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104855","2019-03-27","Cabinet Office","2019-03-25","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people are on the Common Technology Services Programme are (a) contingent labour, (b) supplier resource and (c) civil servants.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236322","236322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104856","2019-03-27","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans his Department has for changes to sheep ageing methods to control transmissible spongiform encephalopathies.","Biography information for Angela Crawley","Angela Crawley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236539","236539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104857","2019-03-27","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to encourage new entrants to the (a) farming and (b) crofting sectors.","Biography information for Angela Crawley","Angela Crawley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236540","236540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104858","2019-03-27","Department for Education","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Edge Foundation's report entitled Our Plan for Apprenticeships, published on 2 March,  what assessment he made of the implications for his policies of that report's finding that the number of apprenticeship starts has dropped from 521,000 in 2011-12 to 376,000 in 2017-18; and what steps he is taking to meet the Government’s target of three million apprenticeship starts by 2020.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236323","236323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104859","2019-03-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his international counterparts on alleged human rights violations of Muslims in Xinjiang province.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236429","236429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104860","2019-03-28","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of leaving the EU without an agreement on the UK’s ability to access (a) radioactive isotopes to diagnose and treat breast cancer and (b) other such medical materials.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236430","236430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104861","2019-03-27","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department will take to ensure that standards on food safety, animal welfare and environmental protection are not lowered in future trade deals.","Biography information for Angela Crawley","Angela Crawley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236541","236541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104862","2019-03-27","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, for what reason his Department has not published the transparency data entitled BEIS: Spending over £25,000 since 8 February 2018; and when they plan to next update that data.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236431","236431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104863","2019-03-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claimants who applied for (a) attendance allowance, (b) employment support allowance and (c) universal credit have died within six months of having those applications rejected.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236324","236324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104864","2019-03-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claimants of (a) attendance allowance, (b) employment support allowance and (c) universal credit have died after registering those claims but prior to her Department making a decision on those claims; and how many of those claimants applied for those social security benefits under (i) normal and (ii) special rules.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236325","236325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104865","2019-03-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the level of human rights abuses against indigenous people in West Papua; and what recent representations he has made to his Indonesian counterpart on that assessment.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236542","236542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104866","2019-03-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many employment support allowance claimants who have had their application rejected under normal rules have subsequently reapplied for that social security benefit under the special rules for terminal illness process; and what medical conditions those claimants had.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236326","236326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104867","2019-03-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many universal credit claimants who have had their application rejected under normal rules have subsequently reapplied for that social security benefit under the special rules for terminal illness process; and what medical conditions those claimants had.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236327","236327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104868","2019-03-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many attendance allowance claimants who have had their application rejected under normal rules have subsequently reapplied for that social security benefit under the special rules for terminal illness process; and what medical conditions those claimants had.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236328","236328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104869","2019-03-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 1 Feb 2019 to Question 209781 on Personal Independence Payment, how many personal independence payments claimants died within six months of their claim being disallowed at initial decision under normal rules.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236329","236329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104870","2019-03-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 1 Feb 2019 to Question 209781 on Personal Independence Payment, what the average length of time was between a claimant receiving an award under special rules for terminal illness and initially registering that claim under normal rules.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236330","236330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104871","2019-03-28","Home Office","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if his Department will make an assessment of the potential merits of removing visa charges for Commonwealth armed forces personnel applying for indefinite leave to remain.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236432","236432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104872","2019-03-28","Department for Education","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether his Department has made an estimate of the number of school buildings below 18 metres in height that have aluminium composite material cladding.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236433","236433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104873","2019-03-28","Home Office","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps his Department is taking to reduce youth-related violence in (a) Barnsley and (b) Sheffield City Region.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236434","236434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104874","2019-03-28","Department for Education","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether his Department has made an estimate of the number of school buildings (a) below and (b) above 18 metres in height that have high pressure laminate cladding.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236435","236435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104875","2019-03-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made in the last six months to (a) the Belarus Ambassador in London and (b) his counterpart in Belarus on recent amendments to media law, the criminal prosecution of journalists and editors and the persecution of journalists who co-operate with foreign media without accreditation.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236331","236331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104876","2019-03-28","Home Office","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many incidents of knife crime there were in (a) Barnsley and (b) Sheffield City Region in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236436","236436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104877","2019-03-28","Ministry of Defence","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department plans to deploy troops to Northern Ireland in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Tony Lloyd","Tony Lloyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236332","236332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104878","2019-03-28","Department for Education","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether he has made an assessment of the implications for his policies of the February 2019 Sutton Trust report which found that disadvantaged young people are more likely to be taught by teachers with less experience and lower qualifications; and whether he is taking steps to improve teacher recruitment in disadvantaged areas.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236437","236437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104879","2019-03-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps she is taking to ensure that arrears are not discarded without the permission of the parent to whom the arrears are owed when cases are migrated from the Child Support Agency to the Child Maintenance Service.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236438","236438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104880","2019-03-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether she plans to ensure the use of previous tribunal decisions in the event of (a) new assessments or (b) re-assessments.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236439","236439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104881","2019-03-28","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure effective recruitment from EU and non-EU countries to meet demand for (a) NHS and (b) care workers after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236440","236440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104882","2019-03-28","Home Office","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the Tier 2 visa salary exemption for nurses will (a) remain his policy after the UK leaves the EU and (b) be extended to EEA citizens.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236441","236441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104883","2019-03-28","Home Office","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps he is taking to ensure that care workers from EU Member States can work in the UK after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236442","236442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104884","2019-03-28","Department for International Trade","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, pursuant to the Answer of 22 March 2019 to Question 234238 on Exports: Saudi Arabia, how many applications for (a) SIELs, (b) OIELs, (c) SITLs, (d) OITCLs and (e) SITCLs for exports to Saudi Arabia were referred to ministers in each Government Department since March 2015.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236543","236543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104885","2019-03-27","Home Office","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps he is taking to ensure effective recruitment from EU and non-EU countries to meet demand for (a) NHS and (b) care workers after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236333","236333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104886","2019-03-27","Cabinet Office","2019-03-25","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment he has made of the prevalence of domestic abuse against (a) men and boys and (b) women and girls.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236443","236443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104887","2019-03-27","Cabinet Office","2019-03-25","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many men were killed by their current or former partner in the last 12 months for which information is available.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236444","236444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104888","2019-03-27","Department for Education","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what his policy is on the provision of education to girls on domestic violence against men and boys.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236445","236445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104889","2019-03-27","Home Office","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the salary exemption for nurses under Tier 2 visas will remain in force after the UK leaves the EU; and whether that exemption will be extended to EEA citizens.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236334","236334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104890","2019-03-28","Home Office","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent discussions he has had with the Lord Chancellor on the effectiveness of short custodial sentences for people convicted of knife offences in reducing levels of knife crime.","Biography information for Mr Ranil Jayawardena","Mr Ranil Jayawardena","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236544","236544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104891","2019-03-28","Home Office","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps he is taking to increase the (a) amount and (b) quality of modern slavery training provided to police officers.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236256","236256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104892","2019-03-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make it his policy to suspend arms sales to Saudi Arabia.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236290","236290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104893","2019-03-28","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment his Department has made of the feasibility of the use of brownfield sites as potential locations to build new homes.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236291","236291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104894","2019-03-28","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent estimate his Department has made of the number of businesses that have paid workers below the national minimum wage.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236292","236292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104895","2019-03-27","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans he has for fisheries policy after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236293","236293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104896","2019-03-27","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure that the NHS is adequately staffed after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236294","236294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104897","2019-03-27","Ministry of Defence","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to ensure the financial viability of the defence industry in Yorkshire and the Humber.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236295","236295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104898","2019-03-27","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to tackle the increase in anti-microbial resistance.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236296","236296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104899","2019-03-27","Treasury","2019-03-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to improve productivity in Yorkshire and the Humber.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236297","236297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104900","2019-03-27","Treasury","2019-03-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he has taken to promote the grants available to small businesses in relation to new customs requirements after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236298","236298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104901","2019-03-27","Department for Transport","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what economic impact assessment has been carried out on the electrification of the rail network in the north of England.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236299","236299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104902","2019-03-28","Home Office","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the salary exemption for nurses under Tier 2 visas will be extended to EEA citizens.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236257","236257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104903","2019-03-28","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the effectiveness of support for people suffering from myalgic encephalomyelitis in (a) South Shields and (b) the North East.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236446","236446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104905","2019-03-28","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent steps his Department is taking to improve access to cervical cancer screenings.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236300","236300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104906","2019-03-28","Home Office","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether he plans to (a) retain and (b) extend to EEA citizens the Tier 2 visa salary exemption for nurses after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Mr Paul Sweeney","Mr Paul Sweeney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236545","236545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104907","2019-03-27","Home Office","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps he is taking to ensure care workers can continue to come and work in the UK after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Mr Paul Sweeney","Mr Paul Sweeney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236546","236546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104908","2019-03-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with (a) Cabinet colleagues, (b) his Cuban counterpart and (c) his counterpart in the US Administration on banking measures to support British businesses in Cuba.","Biography information for Mr Paul Sweeney","Mr Paul Sweeney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236547","236547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104909","2019-03-28","Home Office","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether he plans to ensure that overseas care workers are exempt from the Tier 2 visa £30,000 salary cap and able to work in the UK; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Paul Sweeney","Mr Paul Sweeney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236548","236548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104910","2019-03-27","Department for Transport","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect on the route operator's (a) revenue and (b) service level provision of the decision to delay improvement work on the East Coast mainline between Bawtry and Edinburgh.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236447","236447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104911","2019-03-27","Department for Transport","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the capacity of his Department to (a) develop, (b) evaluate and (c) award market-led proposals to enhance the railway; and how many of his Department's officials have been allocated to work relating to those proposals.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236448","236448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104912","2019-03-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the Prosperity Fund project entitled Promoting best practice sharing in Deepwater oil and gas exploration and development in Mexico, reference GB-GOV-PPF-MEX-000041, what (a) the total amount of funding for that project is and (b) proportion of that funding is from the Official Development Assistance budget.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236549","236549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104913","2019-03-27","Department for Transport","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect on the incumbent East Coast route operator's (a) revenue and (b) service level provision in the event that additional open access services are implemented on the East Coast mainline from 2021.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236449","236449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104914","2019-03-27","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether his Department has made an estimate of the economic effect of an outbreak of African swine flu in the UK; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236258","236258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104915","2019-03-27","Department for Transport","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when his Department plans to publish its response to its consultation, Bus Services Act 2017: accessible information.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236336","236336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104916","2019-03-28","Treasury","2019-03-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 25 March 2019 to Question 233582 on Children: Day Care, how much funding his Department plans to allocate to (a) tax free childcare, (b) employer supported childcare and (c) the childcare element of Working Tax Credit in 2019-20.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236450","236450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104917","2019-03-28","Department for Education","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 25 March 2019 to Question 233582 on Children: Day Care, what estimate he has made of the funding that will be allocated to (a) 15 hours free childcare for all three and four year olds, (b) the additional 15 hours free childcare for eligible working parents of three and four year olds and (c) 15 hours free childcare for the most disadvantaged two year olds in 2019-20.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236451","236451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104918","2019-03-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what sanctions her Department have put in place under the Child Maintenance Service for receiving parents who do not keep the service informed of changes in circumstance that result in a child being no longer eligible for maintenance.","Biography information for Angela Crawley","Angela Crawley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236550","236550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104919","2019-03-28","Cabinet Office","2019-03-25","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what proportion of public sector buyers utilise the Digital Marketplace.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236551","236551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104920","2019-03-27","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of trends in the level of population growth in Cambridgeshire on local health services.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236452","236452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104921","2019-03-27","Department for Transport","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the Bus Services Act in 2017, when he plans to bring forward legislative proposals for audio visual next stop and final destination announcements for buses.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236337","236337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104922","2019-03-27","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will publish a response to EDM 2177 on UK-wide climate emergency.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236453","236453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104923","2019-03-28","Treasury","2019-03-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what criteria his Department used to calculate the estimated revenue from the digital services tax proposed in 2018 Budget.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236552","236552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104924","2019-03-28","Treasury","2019-03-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of how the anti-treaty-shopping provisions within the Digital Services Tax proposed in the 2018 Budget would be used; and what modelling his Department has has undertaken on that subject.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236553","236553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104925","2019-03-28","Treasury","2019-03-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions his Department has had with its counterparts in other countries on the application of the digital services tax proposed in Budget 2018.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236554","236554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104926","2019-03-27","Church Commissioners","2019-03-25","To ask the right hon. Member for Meriden, representing the Church Commissioners, whether the Church of England has a financial interest in (a) Tidemill Green and (b) the site of Old Tidemill School in Deptford.","Biography information for Hugh Gaffney","Hugh Gaffney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236555","236555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104927","2019-03-27","Department for International Trade","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what discussions he has had with his counterpart in the US Administration on confectionery trade between US and UK after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236454","236454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104928","2019-03-27","Department for International Trade","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what recent discussions he has had with his Japanese counterpart on a potential trade agreement after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236455","236455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104929","2019-03-27","Department for International Trade","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what his Department's trade policy will be if the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236456","236456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104930","2019-03-27","Department for International Trade","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many countries in the Commonwealth have not agreed a trade deal with the UK for when the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236457","236457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104931","2019-03-27","Department for International Trade","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps his Department is taking ensure that the maintenance of food of comparable quality from overseas without tariffs after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236458","236458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104932","2019-03-27","Department for Education","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether his Department has plans to allocate funding from the public purse to the procurement of defibrillators by schools.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236459","236459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104933","2019-03-27","Treasury","2019-03-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much money was accrued to the public purse from Air Passenger Duty in Northern Ireland in each of the last three years.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236460","236460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104934","2019-03-27","Treasury","2019-03-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent discussions has he had with the Governor of the Bank of England on the level of interest rates.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236461","236461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104935","2019-03-27","Treasury","2019-03-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department is taking to support economic growth in Northern Ireland in the event of the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236462","236462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104936","2019-03-27","Treasury","2019-03-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent discussions has he had with representatives from banks on branch closures.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236463","236463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104937","2019-03-28","Cabinet Office","2019-03-25","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what relationship the Government plans to have with the eIDAS scheme after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236556","236556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104938","2019-03-27","Home Office","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care on ensuring the effective recruitment of care workers from EU and non-EU countries to meet demand in the UK in the event that the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Wera Hobhouse","Wera Hobhouse","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236557","236557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104939","2019-03-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the effect of the bedroom tax on payments to universal credit claimants.","Biography information for Hugh Gaffney","Hugh Gaffney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236558","236558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104940","2019-03-27","Department for Education","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which Pupil Referral Units (a) employ speech and language therapists or (b) have access to speech and language therapy services.","Biography information for Geraint Davies","Geraint Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236250","236250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104941","2019-03-27","Department for Education","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans he has to consult experts in speech, language and communication on the development of the early career framework for teachers' curricula and training materials.","Biography information for Geraint Davies","Geraint Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236251","236251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104942","2019-03-27","Department for Education","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 13 February 2019 to Question 216909 on Children in Care: Health Services, what discussions the consortium of partners delivering the mental health assessment pilots for looked after children has had with the Royal College of Speech and Language Therapists.","Biography information for Geraint Davies","Geraint Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236252","236252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104943","2019-03-27","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that all workers on trial periods are paid.","Biography information for Hugh Gaffney","Hugh Gaffney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236559","236559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104944","2019-03-27","Department for Education","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when his Department plans to respond to the letter to the Parliamentary Under Secretary of State for Children and Families of 19 November 2018 on his speech to the All-Party Parliamentary Group on Speech and Language Difficulties on 23 October 2018.","Biography information for Geraint Davies","Geraint Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236259","236259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104945","2019-03-27","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans NHS England has to ensure that every child and adolescent mental health service includes speech and language therapists.","Biography information for Geraint Davies","Geraint Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236260","236260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104946","2019-03-27","Treasury","2019-03-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 27 November 2018 to Question 192869 on Buckingham Palace: Honours, which organisations hold the contracts with the Royal Household to create and sell the items referred to in that Question.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236338","236338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104947","2019-03-27","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans Public Health England has to align the Healthy Child Programme service specification with the Speech, Language and Communication pathway for children under five.","Biography information for Geraint Davies","Geraint Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236261","236261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104948","2019-03-27","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many children and young people in contact with liaison and diversion services have speech, language and communication needs.","Biography information for Geraint Davies","Geraint Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236262","236262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104949","2019-03-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of alleged human rights abuses committed in (a) Saudi Arabia and (b) other countries by the Saudi Rapid Intervention Group.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236339","236339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104950","2019-03-27","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what criteria will be used to determine which professionals can train to become an Approved Mental Capacity Professional; and whether those criteria will be made public.","Biography information for Geraint Davies","Geraint Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236263","236263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104951","2019-03-28","Home Office","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when Saudi nationals (a) Saud al-Qahtani, (b) Maher Abdulaziz Mutreb, and (c) Thaar Ghaleb al-Harbi last visited the UK.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236464","236464"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104952","2019-03-27","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what speech and language therapy representation there is on the group working on revision of the Mental Capacity Act 2005 Code of Practice.","Biography information for Geraint Davies","Geraint Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236264","236264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104953","2019-03-28","Home Office","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether Saudi nationals (a) Saud al-Qahtani, (b) Maher Abdulaziz Mutreb and (c) Thaar Ghaleb al-Harbi are currently permitted to visit the UK.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236465","236465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104954","2019-03-27","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what progress has he made on implementing the recommendations contained in A Voice for the Voiceless: The Victims’ Commissioner’s Review into the Provision of Registered Intermediaries for Children and Vulnerable Victims and Witnesses, published in January 2018.","Biography information for Geraint Davies","Geraint Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236265","236265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104955","2019-03-28","Home Office","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether Saudi nationals (a) Saud al-Qahtani, (b) Maher Abdulaziz Mutreb, and (c) Thaar Ghaleb al-Harbi are currently permitted to hold assets in the UK.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236466","236466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104956","2019-03-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the United Nations plans to relocate Rohingya refugees from the Cox’s Bazar camps in Bangladesh to the island of Bhasan Char.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236467","236467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104957","2019-03-27","Department for International Development","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what estimate he has made of the level of investment necessary for (a) the provision of clean water and sanitation and (b) flood protection to make the island of Bhasan Char habitable by Rohingya refugees.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236468","236468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104958","2019-03-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his counterpart in Myanmar on the appeal against the conviction of Reuters reporters Kyaw Soe Oo and Wa Lone.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236469","236469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104959","2019-03-27","Department for International Development","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what discussions he has had with his counterpart in Mozambique on that country’s humanitarian needs as a result of Cyclone Idai.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236470","236470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104960","2019-03-27","Department for International Development","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what discussions he has had with his counterpart in Zimbabwe on that country’s humanitarian needs as a result of Cyclone Idai.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236471","236471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104961","2019-03-28","Treasury","2019-03-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 19 April 2018 to Question 135229 on Public Sector: Pensions, what progress has been made by responsible Departments in implementing the necessary regulatory changes arising from the Walker v. Innospec Limited judgement.","Biography information for Hannah Bardell","Hannah Bardell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236560","236560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104962","2019-03-27","Department for International Development","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what discussions she has had with her counterpart in Malawi on that country’s humanitarian needs after Cyclone Idai.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236472","236472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104963","2019-03-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what his Department's guidance is on responding to the (a) death, (b) torture and (c) imprisonment of British citizens abroad.","Biography information for Hannah Bardell","Hannah Bardell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236561","236561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104964","2019-03-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what criteria his Department uses to assess whether consular assistance is provided after the (a) death, (b) torture and (c) imprisonment of a British citizen abroad.","Biography information for Hannah Bardell","Hannah Bardell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236562","236562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104965","2019-03-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 3 December 2018 to Question 196148 on Foreign and Commonwealth Office: Private Education, what the current maximum level of financial subsidy per child is that can be claimed by staff in his Department to support the private education of their children at UK schools.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236473","236473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104966","2019-03-27","Scotland Office","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what recent discussions he has had with the Scottish Government on reducing child poverty levels in Scotland.","Biography information for Hugh Gaffney","Hugh Gaffney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236563","236563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104967","2019-03-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the corrected Answer of 18 March 2019 to Question 196150 on Foreign and Commonwealth Office: Private Education, how many of the 541 children whose private education in UK schools was supported by his Department in 2016-17 received the maximum level of financial subsidy available per child.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236474","236474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104968","2019-03-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what definition the Government has of the high degree of autonomy that Hong Kong is supposed to exercise under the terms of Article 2 of the Basic Law that came into effect in 1997;  and what assessment he has made of whether Hong Kong enjoys that high degree of autonomy.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236475","236475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104969","2019-03-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what definition his Department has of executive, legislative and independent judicial power that Hong Kong is supposed to enjoy under the terms of Article 2 of the Basic Law that came into effect in 1997; and what assessment he has made of whether Hong Kong currently holds those powers.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236476","236476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104970","2019-03-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will set out the criteria used to assess whether diplomatic protection is provided following the torture or imprisonment of a British citizen whilst overseas.","Biography information for Hannah Bardell","Hannah Bardell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236564","236564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104971","2019-03-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his counterparts in South Sudan and Kenya on the detention of human rights activists Dong Samuel Luak and Aggrey Ezbon Idri.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236477","236477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104972","2019-03-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his counterpart in Mozambique on the detention of journalist Amade Abubacar.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236478","236478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104973","2019-03-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his counterpart in Ghana on (a) the murder of journalist Ahmed Hussein-Suale Divela and (b) the beating and detention of journalist Malik Sullemana in that country.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236479","236479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104974","2019-03-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his counterpart in Cameroon on the recent sentencing of 26 people for illegal gathering and demonstration in that country; and what assessment he has made of whether those convictions are consistent with the terms of the Commonwealth Charter.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236480","236480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104975","2019-03-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Chinese counterpart on the recent jail sentences given to (a) journalist and human rights activist Liu Feiyue and (b) human rights lawyer Wang Quanzhang.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236481","236481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104976","2019-03-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what criteria is applied to a decision on whether a British citizen receives consular assistance or diplomatic protection.","Biography information for Hannah Bardell","Hannah Bardell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236565","236565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104977","2019-03-27","Department for Education","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to improve air quality outside schools.","Biography information for Hugh Gaffney","Hugh Gaffney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236566","236566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104978","2019-03-27","Home Office","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what progress his Department has made on the (a) production and (b) rollout of compulsory training on religion or belief claims for all asylum assessors, announced in October 2018.","Biography information for Crispin Blunt","Crispin Blunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236243","236243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1104979","2019-03-27","Department for Education","2019-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, for what reasons he has withdrawn his Department's myth-busting guide for local authorities on their obligations on children's care; and what plans he has to issue a revised guide.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236482","236482"
