"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141624","2019-09-03","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of benefits appeals resulted in a decision being overturned in each Government region in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Edward Miliband","Edward Miliband","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281664","281664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141625","2019-09-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of benefits decisions in Doncaster have been appealed in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Edward Miliband","Edward Miliband","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281665","281665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141626","2019-09-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of benefits decisions have been appealed in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Edward Miliband","Edward Miliband","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281666","281666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141627","2019-09-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of benefits decisions have been appealed in each Government region in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Edward Miliband","Edward Miliband","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281667","281667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141628","2019-09-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he has had discussions with the Scottish Government on the Scottish Government's targets relating to the ending of biodegradable municipal waste being sent to landfill by 2021.","Biography information for Kirstene Hair","Kirstene Hair","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281771","281771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141629","2019-09-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he plans to attend the next World Health Organization World Conference on Tobacco or Health in the Irish Republic.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281639","281639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141630","2019-09-03","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the Amending the Private Rented Sector Energy Efficiency Regulations, Final Stage Impact Assessment figures that only 48 per cent of Energy Performance Certificate F- and G-rated privately rented homes will be improved to Band E under the current landlord cost cap of £3,500, if he will use the forthcoming consultation on a trajectory for tightening the Minimum Energy Efficiency Standard for the Domestic Private Rented Sector to ensure that a higher proportion of homes will meet any future standard.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281753","281753"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141631","2019-09-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his international counterparts on tackling the illegal trade in human organs; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281598","281598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141632","2019-09-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the rate of mental illness is of (a) males in the richest decile and (b) females in the poorest decile.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281619","281619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141633","2019-09-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment he has made of the effects of (a) unemployment and (b) poverty on levels of mental illness.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281620","281620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141634","2019-09-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment he has made of the effect of living in (a) an urban and (b) a rural environment on levels of mental illness.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281621","281621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141635","2019-09-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent discussions he has had with representatives of universities on research into mindfulness-based therapies; and what research projects his Department has funded into mindfulness-based therapies in the last three years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281622","281622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141636","2019-09-03","Department for Education","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment he has made of Roots of Empathy classroom practices as a means of promoting social and emotional learning.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281623","281623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141637","2019-09-03","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will take steps to ensure a child psychologist is in place in every youth offending team.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281624","281624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141638","2019-09-03","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the effect of frequent house moves on the well-being of (a) adults and (b) children.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281625","281625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141639","2019-09-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the (a) efficacy and (b) cost of mindfulness-based therapies in treating (i) attention deficit disorder, (ii) hyperactivity and (iii) other mental health conditions.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281626","281626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141640","2019-09-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information he holds on the incidence of (a) self harming, (b) eating disorders and (c) mental illness among (i) boys and (ii) girls in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281627","281627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141641","2019-09-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will estimate the average cost to the public purse of treating repeated episodes of depression by (a) drugs, (b) individual counselling and (c) mindfulness-based therapy in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281628","281628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141642","2019-09-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what proportion of expenditure by his Department on the NHS was spent on mental health services in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281629","281629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141643","2019-09-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what public awareness campaigns his Department initiated on food and drink that poses a threat to public health in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281630","281630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141644","2019-09-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what public health campaigns his Department has funded in each of the last 10 years; and how much his Department spent on each of those campaigns.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281631","281631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141645","2019-09-03","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many applications for research into mindfulness-based therapies were (a) accepted and (b) rejected by the Medical Research Council in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281632","281632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141646","2019-09-03","Department for Education","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Written Statement of 22 July 2019, HCWS1766 on Teachers update, whether the £105 million is additional funding from the public purse.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281772","281772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141647","2019-09-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether the Joint Air Quality Unit vehicle checking software will be ready by February 2020.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281575","281575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141648","2019-09-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the ability of his Department to support Birmingham City Council in implementing a system to collect payments from the proposed Clean Air Zone.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281576","281576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141649","2019-09-03","Home Office","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of the (a) quality and (b) value for money of services provided by Sopra Steria for HM Passports Office; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281609","281609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141650","2019-09-03","Home Office","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment his Department has made of the potential savings to the public purse of producing an in-house bid for HM Passport Office work.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281610","281610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141651","2019-09-03","Home Office","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the options analysis for HM Passports Office produced by his Department assessed the merits of returning outsourced work to in-house.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281611","281611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141652","2019-09-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information his Department holds on how many consultant-led NHS acute mental-health beds there were in each year since 2009.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr Dan Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281697","281697"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141653","2019-09-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information his Department holds on how many consultant-led NHS working age adult acute mental-health beds there were in each year since 2009.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr Dan Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281698","281698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141654","2019-09-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many and what proportion of mental-health bed admissions there were under the Mental Health Act 1983 in each year since 2009.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr Dan Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281699","281699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141655","2019-09-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many and what proportion of working-age adult mental-health bed admissions took place under the Mental Health Act 1983 in each year since 2009.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr Dan Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281700","281700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141656","2019-09-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the average length of occupancy was of consultant-led NHS acute mental-health beds in each year since 2009.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr Dan Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281701","281701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141657","2019-09-03","Treasury","2019-07-24","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the financial effect on the bingo industry of the change to bingo duty in 2014.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281720","281720"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141658","2019-09-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to his oral contribution of 22 July 2019, column 1121, on the situation in the Gulf, on what date the US Authorities first communicated with the UK Government on the detention of the Grace 1 Iranian oil tanker by the Gibraltarian authorities.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281690","281690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141659","2019-09-03","Treasury","2019-07-24","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent estimate he has made of the rate of gross profit tax levied from (a) the Football Pools and (b) bookmakers; what the rationale is for applying the same rate of duty to the Football Pools and bookmakers; and what recent assessment he has made of reducing the reducing the rate of the Pools Betting Duty to 10 per cent.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281721","281721"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141660","2019-09-03","Home Office","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, for what reason the UK has not opted into EU Directive 2018/1673 on combating money laundering by criminal law.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281754","281754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141661","2019-09-03","Home Office","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the equivalence of  the UK's corporate liability regime achieve with article 7 (the liability of legal persons) of EU Directive 2018/1673 on combating money laundering by criminal law.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281755","281755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141662","2019-09-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of trends in the level of risk to health of pregnant women in (a) Northamptonshire, (b) Oxfordshire and (c) Warwickshire as a result of the closure of obstetrics at the Horton Hospital.","Biography information for Andrea Leadsom","Andrea Leadsom","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281746","281746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141663","2019-09-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent discussions his Department has had with (a) local Clinical Commissioning Groups, (b) local healthcare trusts, (c) local authorities, and (d) other stakeholders on the effect on maternity services in (i) Northamptonshire, (ii) Oxfordshire and (iii) Warwickshire as a result of the ongoing closure of obstetrics at the Horton Hospital.","Biography information for Andrea Leadsom","Andrea Leadsom","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281747","281747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141664","2019-09-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to support the Oxfordshire Joint Health Overview and Scrutiny Committee in that Committee's consideration of the reconfiguration of local maternity services.","Biography information for Andrea Leadsom","Andrea Leadsom","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281748","281748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141665","2019-09-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of the availability of (a) autism and (b) ADHD assessments in South Northamptonshire constituency.","Biography information for Andrea Leadsom","Andrea Leadsom","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281749","281749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141666","2019-09-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the (a) extent to which patients in the south of Northamptonshire are being refused out-of-hours access to treatment at the Horton hospital and (b) risk to patients in the south of Northamptonshire having to travel to Daventry or Northampton to seek treatment due to cross-boundary healthcare problems between Oxfordshire and Northamptonshire.","Biography information for Andrea Leadsom","Andrea Leadsom","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281750","281750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141667","2019-09-03","Treasury","2019-07-24","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the findings of the John Lewis Partnership Working Well report, published on 11 June 2019 on the benefits to public services of greater workplace health prevention and early intervention; and what steps he plans to take ensure that taxation incentivises early intervention from employers.","Biography information for Jack Lopresti","Jack Lopresti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281709","281709"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141668","2019-09-03","Treasury","2019-07-24","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the potential benefit to the public purse of workers receiving workplace medical treatment at work instead of after 28 consecutive days of absence.","Biography information for Jack Lopresti","Jack Lopresti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281710","281710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141669","2019-09-03","Treasury","2019-07-24","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of the taxation of employees with occupational health support on the take-up of those services by low paid workers.","Biography information for Jack Lopresti","Jack Lopresti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281711","281711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141670","2019-09-03","Treasury","2019-07-24","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies on (a) health prevention and (b) early intervention of the (a) conditions in relation to 28 day consecutive absence and (b)requirement that a health condition must be a direct result of work in the exemption for employer-funded recommended medical treatment under section 320C of the Income Tax (Earnings and Pensions) Act 2003.","Biography information for Jack Lopresti","Jack Lopresti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281712","281712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141671","2019-09-03","Treasury","2019-07-24","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the compatibility of the conditions on tax reliefs for workplace health services with his Department's principles of tax simplification.","Biography information for Jack Lopresti","Jack Lopresti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281713","281713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141672","2019-09-03","Treasury","2019-07-24","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect on number of additional workers that would be eligible for the exemption under section 320C of the Income Tax (Earnings and Pensions) Act 2003 of removing the requirement for a 28 consecutive day absence.","Biography information for Jack Lopresti","Jack Lopresti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281714","281714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141673","2019-09-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 10 July to Question 272107, what his Department’s express freight service is planned to deliver; by what form of transport that service will be delivered; over what time period that service will run; and what estimate he has made of the cost of that service to the public purse.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281549","281549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141674","2019-09-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 10 July 2019 to Question 272107 on Department of Health and Social Care: Brexit, what medicines will be in the small medical supply consignment referred to in that answer.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281550","281550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141675","2019-09-03","Department for Transport","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, on how many occasions there was significant disruption to East Coast Main Line services as a result of damage to overhead wires in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281756","281756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141676","2019-09-03","Treasury","2019-07-24","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 10 July 2019 to Question 272107 on Department of Heath and Social Care: Brexit, when his Department plans to publish details of the new customs procedures.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281551","281551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141677","2019-09-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 10 July to Question 272107 on Department of Health and Social Care: Brexit, whether his Department has assessed the average additional costs facing companies transferring medicines and medical equipment in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281552","281552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141678","2019-09-03","Department for Transport","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions his Department has held with Network Rail on future priorities for investment in the East Coast Main Line for Control Period 7 (CP7) 2024–2029.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281757","281757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141679","2019-09-03","Treasury","2019-07-24","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the cost to the Exchequer of removing the requirement for a 28 consecutive day absence and £500 cap per tax year from the s320C ITEPA 2003 (EIM21774) exemption for employer-funded recommended medical treatment.","Biography information for Jack Lopresti","Jack Lopresti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281715","281715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141680","2019-09-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 10 July 2019 to Question 272107 on Department of Health and Social Care: Brexit, how many regulatory requirements still need to be changed.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281553","281553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141681","2019-09-03","Department for Transport","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what enhancement projects on the East Coast Main Line have been identified to progress through the Rail Network Enhancement Pipeline process.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281758","281758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141682","2019-09-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 10 July 2019 to Question 272107 on Department of Health and Social Care: Brexit, how many citizens with existing healthcare conditions the Government has contacted to help ensure that they have the correct travel insurance.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281554","281554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141683","2019-09-03","Department for Transport","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment he has made of the key constraints on each section of the East Coast Main Line.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281759","281759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141684","2019-09-03","Department for Transport","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps the Government plans to take to remove key constraints on the East Coast Main Line.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281760","281760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141685","2019-09-03","Department for Transport","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps the Government is taking to increase capacity for (a) rail freight and (b) passenger services on the East Coast Main Line.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281761","281761"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141686","2019-09-03","Department for Transport","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what options the Partnership Board have developed for delivering the East Coast Partnership.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281762","281762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141687","2019-09-03","Home Office","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many staff have been employed in the programme team to deliver the Emergency Services Network, in each month since that Network was established.","Biography information for Douglas Ross","Douglas Ross","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281773","281773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141688","2019-09-03","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment his Department has made of the effect on (a) the safety of prisoners and (b) the levels of staffing in prisons in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281562","281562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141689","2019-09-03","Treasury","2019-07-24","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many and what proportion of people in the UK have private medical insurance.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281774","281774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141690","2019-09-03","Treasury","2019-07-24","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much was spent on private medical health cover in the UK in 2018.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281775","281775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141691","2019-09-03","Home Office","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what criteria his Department plans to use to allow police forces to assess the comparative performance of Emergency Services Network and Airwave.","Biography information for Douglas Ross","Douglas Ross","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281776","281776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141692","2019-09-03","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when he plans to answer named day Question 274532, on Probation, tabled on 8 July 2019.","Biography information for Andrea Leadsom","Andrea Leadsom","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281751","281751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141693","2019-09-03","Department for Education","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 23 July 2019 to Question 279134, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of setting up an independent body to run a student complaints scheme for (a) Level three and (b) Level two qualifications.","Biography information for Rosie Duffield","Rosie Duffield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281777","281777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141694","2019-09-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment he has made of the potential merits of lifting the freeze on local housing allowance to ensure that it covers at least the cheapest third of rents to improve housing security.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281640","281640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141695","2019-09-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 23 July 2019 to Question 278471, what estimate he has made of the number of cubic metres of cold meat storage that will be available to store sheep meat on 1 November 2019 in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Jenny Chapman","Jenny Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281703","281703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141696","2019-09-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 23 July to Question 278955, what the economic basis is for an increase in the availability of lamb on the domestic market potentially leading to an increase in international demand for UK sheep meat products.","Biography information for Jenny Chapman","Jenny Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281704","281704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141697","2019-09-03","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what progress his Department has made on using social prescribing interventions to help tackle loneliness among young people as part of the Government's loneliness strategy.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281778","281778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141698","2019-09-03","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what refitting and retrofitting has been performed on the 14 C-130J/C-130J-30 Hercules transport aircraft to allow OSD to be extended for a further five years.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281650","281650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141699","2019-09-03","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans her Department has to remove Armoured Infantry 2025 project to upgrade Warrior vehicles from the IPA's red classification.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281651","281651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141700","2019-09-03","Home Office","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many asylum seekers resident in Scotland have been required to attend Home Office appointments in England as part of their asylum application in each of the last five calendar years; how many of those appointments did applicants fail to attend in each of the last five calendar years; how many asylum seekers who failed to attend a Home Office appointment in England when they were resident in Scotland had their asylum application refused in each of the last five calendar years.","Biography information for Tommy Sheppard","Tommy Sheppard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281779","281779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141701","2019-09-03","Home Office","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of the financial and practical barriers experienced by asylum seekers who are resident in Scotland being required to attend Home Office appointments in England as part of their asylum application.","Biography information for Tommy Sheppard","Tommy Sheppard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281780","281780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141702","2019-09-03","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment she has made of the UK's airlift capability since the sale of five UK-surplus Lockheed Martin C-130J Hercules transport aircraft to Bangladesh.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281652","281652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141703","2019-09-03","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what price the UK has attained for the sale of five UK-surplus Lockheed Martin C-130J Hercules transport aircraft to Bangladesh.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281653","281653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141704","2019-09-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much each clinical commissioning group has spent on child and adolescent mental health services in each year since 2013.","Biography information for Neil O'Brien","Neil O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281781","281781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141705","2019-09-03","Home Office","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps his Department is taking to provide mental health support to immigration removal centre staff.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281599","281599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141706","2019-09-03","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans she has to collaborate with Sweden on combat air systems as a result of the signing of a Memorandum of Understanding on that matter with that country on 18 July 2019.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281654","281654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141707","2019-09-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the number of children and adolescents with mental health problems who required treatment in each year since 2013; and what assessment he has made of the levels of severity of those problems.","Biography information for Neil O'Brien","Neil O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281782","281782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141708","2019-09-03","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what support the Government provides to tackle loneliness among young people.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281783","281783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141709","2019-09-03","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the of Answer 23 July 2019 to Question 279062 on Buildings: Insulation, if he will publish the full test report for the test which was planned to take place in June 2019 but which was aborted due to procedural issues.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281764","281764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141710","2019-09-03","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the of Answer 23 July 2019 to Question 279062 on Buildings: Insulation, whether changes were made to the BS 8414 test on high pressure laminate cladding and stonewool insulation as a result of the test planned to take place in June 2019.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281765","281765"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141711","2019-09-03","Department for Education","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what progress his Department has made in improving access to adequate support for young carers to tackle loneliness and social isolation.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281784","281784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141712","2019-09-03","Treasury","2019-07-24","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment the Government has made of the potential merits of reinstating tax relief for investors in community energy schemes.","Biography information for Dr Rupa Huq","Dr Rupa Huq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281785","281785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141713","2019-09-03","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 23 May 2019 to Question 255690 on OnSide Youth Zones, how much Government funding is being provided to the new Onside Youth Zone in Croydon.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281766","281766"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141714","2019-09-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the Government's timescale is for bringing forward legislative proposals to implement its commitment to achieving WHO guideline limits on air pollution by 2030.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281641","281641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141715","2019-09-03","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to the review his Department has launched into statutory guidance for local authorities on providing youth services, whether his Department has undertaken an impact assessment on funding for youth services.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281767","281767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141716","2019-09-03","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to the review his Department has launched into statutory guidance for local authorities on providing youth services, whether he plans to (a) allocate funding and (b) issue guidance as a result of that review.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281786","281786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141717","2019-09-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Control of Noise at Work Regulations 2005, what steps she is taking to ensure that employers protect employees' hearing.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281642","281642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141718","2019-09-03","Department for Education","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that degree apprenticeships support (a) social mobility and (b) lifelong learning among underrepresented groups.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281643","281643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141719","2019-09-03","Department for Education","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department and the Education and Skills Funding Agency are taking to support universities to work closely with non-levy-paying small and medium-sized enterprises.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281644","281644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141720","2019-09-03","Department for Education","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the importance of transparency on setting and lowering funding bands for degree apprenticeships.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281645","281645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141721","2019-09-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many residential drugs treatment services have been made available for (a) men and (b) women in the North East in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281705","281705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141722","2019-09-03","Scotland Office","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what discussions his Department has had with representatives of the Scottish Government on future support for the oil and gas sector.","Biography information for Andrew Bowie","Andrew Bowie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281787","281787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141723","2019-09-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will commission an urgent review of maternal care in response to the findings of the MBRRACE-UK maternal deaths and morbidity statistics 2014-16 relating to increased maternal mortality rates for women from BAME communities.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281788","281788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141724","2019-09-03","Department for Transport","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of automatically awarding season ticket rail passengers with compensation in respect of a delay to their travel.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281646","281646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141725","2019-09-03","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what progress his Department has made on implementing an oil and gas sector deal; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Bowie","Andrew Bowie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281789","281789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141726","2019-09-03","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, when he next plans to meet with his Scottish Government counterpart to discuss increasing the availability of superfast broadband in the north east of Scotland.","Biography information for Andrew Bowie","Andrew Bowie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281790","281790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141727","2019-09-03","Department for Education","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will make an assessment of the implications for his Department's policies of the findings of the Children’s Commissioner’s 2019 childhood vulnerability report published in July 2019.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281791","281791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141728","2019-09-03","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether his Department has met with (a) the Scottish Government and (b) representatives of the oil and gas industry in Scotland to discuss (i) domestic skills, (ii) training and (iii) recruitment in that industry in Scotland.","Biography information for Andrew Bowie","Andrew Bowie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281792","281792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141729","2019-09-03","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent steps he has taken to support businesses in the West Aberdeenshire and Kincardine constituency.","Biography information for Andrew Bowie","Andrew Bowie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281793","281793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141730","2019-09-03","Department for International Trade","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps she is taking to encourage investment in the oil and gas industry in the (a) UK and (b) north east of Scotland.","Biography information for Andrew Bowie","Andrew Bowie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281794","281794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141731","2019-09-03","Treasury","2019-07-24","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people have benefited from the Help to Buy ISA in (a) north east Scotland and (b) West Aberdeenshire and Kincardine; and what the cost to the public purse was of that policy in those areas since the introduction of that scheme.","Biography information for Andrew Bowie","Andrew Bowie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281795","281795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141732","2019-09-03","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps she is taking to increase recruitment to the armed forces from communities in West Aberdeenshire and Kincardine.","Biography information for Andrew Bowie","Andrew Bowie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281796","281796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141733","2019-09-03","Department for Transport","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to support Scottish civil aviation.","Biography information for Andrew Bowie","Andrew Bowie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281797","281797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141734","2019-09-03","Department for Transport","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the contribution of Aberdeen City airport to the UK economy.","Biography information for Andrew Bowie","Andrew Bowie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281798","281798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141735","2019-09-03","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prosecutions under the Malicious Communications Act 1988 were made in Scotland in the last five years.","Biography information for Andrew Bowie","Andrew Bowie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281799","281799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141736","2019-09-03","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the annual cost was of running the University Officer Training Corps unit in Aberdeen in each year between 2008 and 2018.","Biography information for Andrew Bowie","Andrew Bowie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281800","281800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141737","2019-09-03","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the annual cost was of running the University Officer Training Corps unit in Birmingham in each year between 2008 and 2018.","Biography information for Andrew Bowie","Andrew Bowie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281801","281801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141738","2019-09-03","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the annual cost was of running the University Officer Training Corps unit in Bristol in each year between 2008 and 2018.","Biography information for Andrew Bowie","Andrew Bowie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281802","281802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141739","2019-09-03","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the annual cost was of running the University Officer Training Corps unit in Cambridge in each year between 2008 and 2018.","Biography information for Andrew Bowie","Andrew Bowie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281803","281803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141740","2019-09-03","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the annual cost was of running the University Officer Training Corps unit in Edinburgh in each year between 2008 and 2018.","Biography information for Andrew Bowie","Andrew Bowie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281804","281804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141741","2019-09-03","Church Commissioners","2019-07-24","To ask the right hon. Member for Meriden, representing the Church Commissioners, whether the Church of England has plans to adopt the approach of the Global Anglican Future Conference as a model for the (a) growth and (b) development of the Anglican Communion.","Biography information for Sir John Hayes","Sir John Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281578","281578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141742","2019-09-03","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the annual cost was of running the University Officer Training Corps unit in the East Midlands in each year between 2008 and 2018.","Biography information for Andrew Bowie","Andrew Bowie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281805","281805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141743","2019-09-03","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the annual cost of running the University Officer Training Corps unit in Exeter was in each year between 2008 and 2018.","Biography information for Andrew Bowie","Andrew Bowie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281806","281806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141744","2019-09-03","Church Commissioners","2019-07-24","To ask the right hon. Member for Meriden, representing the Church Commissioners, whether the Archbishop of Canterbury plans to attend the 2020 Global Anglican Future Conference in Kigali, Rwanda.","Biography information for Sir John Hayes","Sir John Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281579","281579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141745","2019-09-03","Church Commissioners","2019-07-24","To ask the right hon. Member for Meriden, representing the Church Commissioners, if the Church of England will clarify its interpretation of biblical teaching on sex and gender in relation to transgender issues.","Biography information for Sir John Hayes","Sir John Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281580","281580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141746","2019-09-03","Church Commissioners","2019-07-24","To ask the right hon. Member for Meriden, representing the Church Commissioners, what proportion of Church of England employees are practising Christians.","Biography information for Sir John Hayes","Sir John Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281581","281581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141747","2019-09-03","Church Commissioners","2019-07-24","To ask the right hon. Member for Meriden, representing the Church Commissioners, what steps the Church of England is taking to help ensure that its theology is founded on the 39 articles.","Biography information for Sir John Hayes","Sir John Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281582","281582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141748","2019-09-03","Church Commissioners","2019-07-24","To ask the right hon. Member for Meriden, representing the Church Commissioners, whether the Archbishop of Canterbury will pledge his commitment to the Jerusalem Statement of 2008.","Biography information for Sir John Hayes","Sir John Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281583","281583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141749","2019-09-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure the adequacy of allergen labelling on pre-packaged food.","Biography information for Sir John Hayes","Sir John Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281584","281584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141750","2019-09-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he has taken to increase the number of trees planted in (a) Lincolnshire and (b) the UK.","Biography information for Sir John Hayes","Sir John Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281585","281585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141751","2019-09-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans he has to promote the sale of milk in reusable glass bottles.","Biography information for Sir John Hayes","Sir John Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281586","281586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141752","2019-09-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to improve the detection of cancer in its early stages.","Biography information for Sir John Hayes","Sir John Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281587","281587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141753","2019-09-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to improve care for people with learning difficulties.","Biography information for Sir John Hayes","Sir John Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281588","281588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141754","2019-09-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to improve and upgrade NHS facilities in (a) Lincolnshire and (b) the UK.","Biography information for Sir John Hayes","Sir John Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281589","281589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141755","2019-09-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps the Government is taking to increase the number of apprenticeships in social care in (a) Lincolnshire and (b) the UK.","Biography information for Sir John Hayes","Sir John Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281590","281590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141756","2019-09-03","Women and Equalities","2019-07-24","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what plans the Government has to encourage more candidates with disabilities to stand for elected office.","Biography information for Sir John Hayes","Sir John Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281591","281591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141757","2019-09-03","Cabinet Office","2019-07-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps he is taking to ensure Government (a) suppliers and (b) subcontractors are paid on time.","Biography information for Sir John Hayes","Sir John Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281592","281592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141758","2019-09-03","Cabinet Office","2019-07-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what recent discussions he has had with the Scottish Government on further devolution of power to devolved authorities.","Biography information for Sir John Hayes","Sir John Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281593","281593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141759","2019-09-03","Treasury","2019-07-24","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to ensure people are able to access cash.","Biography information for Sir John Hayes","Sir John Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281594","281594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141760","2019-09-03","Treasury","2019-07-24","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to narrow wealth differentials between the richest and poorest (a) individuals, (b) regions, (c) counties and (d) constituencies.","Biography information for Sir John Hayes","Sir John Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281595","281595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141761","2019-09-03","Treasury","2019-07-24","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department has taken to cap large bonuses paid to bankers.","Biography information for Sir John Hayes","Sir John Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281596","281596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141762","2019-09-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to help tackle the persecution of Christians in (a) Pakistan and (b) Nigeria.","Biography information for Sir John Hayes","Sir John Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281597","281597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141763","2019-09-03","Home Office","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps his Department is taking to provide support to individuals employed in immigration removal centres who are suffering from post-traumatic stress disorder.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281600","281600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141764","2019-09-03","Home Office","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people employed in immigration removal centres were signed off work as a result of mental health illnesses in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281601","281601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141765","2019-09-03","Home Office","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people employed in immigration removal centres took early retirement as a result of ill health in each of the last ten years.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281602","281602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141766","2019-09-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care,  which clinical trials are currently being monitored by NHS England’s national specialised commissioning team to assess the evidence base for the use of Stereotactic Ablative Radiotherapy to treat early non-small cell lung cancer.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281686","281686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141767","2019-09-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate his Department has made of the potential savings accrued to the public purse of establishing a rolling replacement programme for radiotherapy machines.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281687","281687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141768","2019-09-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the NHS Long-Term Plan, what the (a) timeframe and (b) terms of reference are for the review of the national tariff.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281688","281688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141769","2019-09-03","Home Office","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people employed in immigration removal centres were signed off work as a result of post-traumatic stress disorder in each of the last ten years.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281603","281603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141770","2019-09-03","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he is taking to encourage (a) UK and (b) overseas citizens to take holidays in UK (i) seaside towns and (b) coastal communities.","Biography information for Gordon Henderson","Gordon Henderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281738","281738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141771","2019-09-03","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what plans he has to encourage  the development of tourism in seaside towns and coastal communities.","Biography information for Gordon Henderson","Gordon Henderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281739","281739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141772","2019-09-03","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of overtime for staff responding to IT problems in January 2019; and whether his Department has changed IT suppliers as a result of those problems.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281689","281689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141773","2019-09-03","Home Office","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will publish the service specification, including key performance indicators, agreed with Sopra Steria Limited (SSL) in respect of the contract for UK Visa and Citizenship Application Services.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281733","281733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141774","2019-09-03","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what mental health support his Department provides to people employed in the justice and custodial sector.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281604","281604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141775","2019-09-03","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what support his Department provides to people employed in the justice and custodial sector who are suffering from post-traumatic stress disorder.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281605","281605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141776","2019-09-03","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prison officers were signed off work for mental health reasons in (a) publicly-managed and (b) privately-managed prisons in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281606","281606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141777","2019-09-03","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prison officers were signed off work with post-traumatic stress disorder in (a) publicly-managed and (b) privately-managed prisons in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281607","281607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141778","2019-09-03","Home Office","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, for what reasons visa applicants are unable to access a local rate 0330 number to contact UK Visa and Citizenship Application Services until they have succeeded in making such an application; what estimate his Department has made of the number of people who have had to use the premium rate telephone number; and how much revenue was received in revenue from that premium rate number in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281734","281734"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141779","2019-09-03","Home Office","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when his Department has had meetings with Sopra Steria Ltd on the UK Visa and Citizenship Application Services in the last 12 months; and what was discussed at those meetings.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281735","281735"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141780","2019-09-03","Home Office","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will undertake a full review of the service and performance of Sopra Steria Ltd regarding the UK Visa and Citizenship Application Services.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281736","281736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141781","2019-09-03","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prison officers took early retirement due to ill health in (a) publicly-managed and (b) privately-managed prisons in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281608","281608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141782","2019-09-03","Home Office","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which organisations his Department has advertised information to outlining that visa applicants wishing to extend their leave to remain will not be penalised in cases where they have had to wait for an appointment at a UK Visa and Citizenship Application Services service point; and how that information has been publicised.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281737","281737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141783","2019-09-03","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether his Department plans to develop deep-water turbines as a means of producing clean energy in the UK.","Biography information for Susan Elan Jones","Susan Elan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281702","281702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141784","2019-09-03","Department for Transport","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of trends in the number of cloned vehicles in the UK in the last five years.","Biography information for Stephen Crabb","Stephen Crabb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281670","281670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141785","2019-09-03","Home Office","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many motoring offences have been committed by drivers of cloned vehicles in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Stephen Crabb","Stephen Crabb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281671","281671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141786","2019-09-03","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if she will place in the Library a copy of her Department's recent report entitled the TIN 2.101 Defence Inclusivity Phase 2: The Lived Experience: Final Report and its summary.","Biography information for Gerald Jones","Gerald Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281807","281807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141787","2019-09-03","Department for Transport","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps are being taken by (a) his Department and (b) the DVLA to tackle vehicle cloning.","Biography information for Stephen Crabb","Stephen Crabb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281672","281672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141788","2019-09-03","Department for Transport","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much per capita funding has been allocated from the public purse to cycling in each local authority in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Andrew Selous","Andrew Selous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281656","281656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141789","2019-09-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether a Minister of his Department attended the Trondheim conference on biodiversity in July 2019.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281659","281659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141790","2019-09-03","Department for International Development","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, with reference to the Green Finance Strategy: Transforming Finance for a Greener Future, published in July 2019, under what circumstances and using what criteria the Government will determine that Official Development Assistance spent on investment support for fossil fuels is in line with the Paris Agreement temperature goals and transition plans.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281691","281691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141791","2019-09-03","Department for Transport","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, on how many occasions there has been significant disruption to the East Coast Main Line as a result of points failures in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281763","281763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141792","2019-09-03","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if she will make an assessment of the potential for pre-packaged administrations to be open to abuse as a way of passing on pension liabilities to the Pension Protection Fund.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281706","281706"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141793","2019-09-03","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if she will make an assessment of (a) the reasons for the collapse of Johnston Press and (b) whether additional powers for the Pension Regulator would help to safeguard pension funds and mitigate the potential financial loss to employees.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281707","281707"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141794","2019-09-03","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if she will review pre-packaged administration deals and make an assessment of the potential merits of preventing directors of a failed company becoming directors of the new company in cases where pension liabilities are passed onto the Pension Protection Fund.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281708","281708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141795","2019-09-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 10 July 2019 to Question 273727, whether her Department consulted (a) advice agencies and (b) disability charities on the wording of the revised ESA65B letters to employment and support allowance claimants’ GPs before authorising the use of that letter from 3 June 2019 onwards.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281555","281555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141796","2019-09-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 10 July 2019 to Question 273727, whether her Department has written to the GPs of all those employment and support allowance claimants whom her Department sent an ESA65B letter between August 2017 and 3 June 2019 to correct the advice that they no longer need to provide fit notes for patients.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281556","281556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141797","2019-09-03","Department for Education","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will make it his policy to provide free transport to and from schools for school pupils of compulsory education age; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281561","281561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141798","2019-09-03","Department for Education","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans he has to change regulations relating to schools so that they receive national funding formula per pupil de minimis levels in full.","Biography information for Mrs Kemi Badenoch","Mrs Kemi Badenoch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281808","281808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141799","2019-09-03","Department for Transport","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many staff HS2 Limited made redundant in (a) 2015, (b) 2016, (c) 2017, (d) 2018 and (e) 2019.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281612","281612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141800","2019-09-03","Department for Education","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what representations he has received from (a) Harrow council and (b) other stakeholders on the financial costs incurred by Harrow Council as a result of the need to urgently move the location of Pinner Wood Primary School; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281559","281559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141801","2019-09-03","Department for Transport","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many staff made redundant by HS2 Limited in (a) 2015, (b) 2016, (c) 2017, (d) 2018 and (e) 2019 had non-disclosure requirements included in their redundancy settlements.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281613","281613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141802","2019-09-03","Department for Transport","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many section 16 orders were issued by HS2 Ltd in (a) 2015, (b) 2016, (c) 2017, (d) 2018 and (e) 2019.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281614","281614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141803","2019-09-03","Department for Transport","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the cost has been of the use of section 16 by HS2 Ltd in (a) 2015, (b) 2016, (c) 2017, (d) 2018 and (e) 2019.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281615","281615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141804","2019-09-03","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether he plans to support the implementation of locally based development programmes in seaside towns.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281617","281617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141805","2019-09-03","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether tourism zones will include (a) seaside towns and (b) capital funds to allow local authorities to support projects to improve (i) the public realm and (ii) cultural and heritage assets.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281618","281618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141806","2019-09-03","Home Office","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 22 July 2019 to Question 278478 on Immigration: EU Nationals, what mechanisms his Department has established to enable statistics users can make views known.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281741","281741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141807","2019-09-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the scale of the problem of primates being kept and traded as pets in the UK.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281683","281683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141808","2019-09-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of further restricting the keeping of primates as pets beyond that set out in section 4 and section 9 the Animal Welfare Act 2006.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281684","281684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141809","2019-09-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the implications for his policies of the claims in the July 2019 report by the Australian Strategic Policy Institute entitled Mapping Conditions in Rakhine State that (a) minimal preparations have been made for any return of Rohingya refugees from Bangladesh, (b) 320 of the settlements damaged or destroyed during the genocide of 2017 show no signs of reconstruction, (c) 58 remaining settlements were damaged or destroyed after the crisis during 2018 and (d) six suspected military facilities have been built on the sites of destroyed settlements.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281685","281685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141810","2019-09-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of updating his Department's Protection of Civilians in Conflict strategy.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281730","281730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141811","2019-09-03","Department for Transport","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what progress his Department has made on the introduction of (a) flexible rail season tickets and (b) rail season tickets targeted at part-time workers on the Govia Thameslink Railway franchise.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281809","281809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141812","2019-09-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 22 July 2019 to Question 278405 on Universal Credit: Terminal Illnesses and with reference to the absence of a Northern Ireland Executive, if she will extend the review of the universal credit six month rule on terminal illness to Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281647","281647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141813","2019-09-03","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the Tackling Racial Disparity in the Criminal Justice System: October 2018 Update, how many FTE employees work within the dedicated team in his Department coordinating work on ethnic and racial disparity in the criminal justice system.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281810","281810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141814","2019-09-03","Northern Ireland Office","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, with reference to the absence of a Northern Ireland Executive, what steps her Office is taking with the Northern Ireland Department for Communities to reform liquor licensing to support the hospitality and tourism sectors in Northern Ireland; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281648","281648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141815","2019-09-03","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the Tackling Racial Disparity in the Criminal Justice System: October 2018 Update report, what the total spend has been on the dedicated team in his Department coordinating work on ethnic and racial disparity in the criminal justice system.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281811","281811"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141816","2019-09-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of claimants over 65 have (a) been unsuccessful in their application for personal independence payment, (b) received benefit at a lower rate and (c) received benefit at a higher rate when transferring from disability living allowance.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281692","281692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141817","2019-09-03","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the Tackling Racial Disparity in the Criminal Justice System: October 2018 Update, how many full-time equivalent employees worked within the dedicated team in the Department co-ordinating work on ethnic and racial disparity in the criminal justice system when it was first set up.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281812","281812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141818","2019-09-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many adults born after 8 April 1948 are awaiting a decision in their application to transfer from disability living allowance to personal independence payment; and how many of those people are (a) aged 66 to 69 and (b) aged 70 or older.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281693","281693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141819","2019-09-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many adults born after 8 April 1948 are in receipt of disability living allowance and waiting to be invited to claim personal independence payment; and how many of those adults are aged (a) 66 to 69 and (b) 70 or older.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281694","281694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141820","2019-09-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many pensioners claiming disability living allowance the Department has (a) invited and (b) still to invite to apply for personal independence payment; and by what date all pensioners claiming disability living allowance will have been invited to apply for personal independence payment.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281695","281695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141821","2019-09-03","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average waiting time is for a decision in the appeal stage of a personal independence payment application for those transferring from disability living allowance.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281696","281696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141822","2019-09-03","Treasury","2019-07-24","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 15 October 2018 to Question 174781 on Infrastructure, when the Government plans to publish its full response to the National Infrastructure Commission’s report of July 2018 entitled National Infrastructure Assessment.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281813","281813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141823","2019-09-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether she has made an assessment of the appropriateness of requiring claimants with mental health conditions to attend face-to-face interviews as part of the social security benefits assessment process.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281655","281655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141824","2019-09-03","Department for Education","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the number of school staff members who are paid more than £150,000 a year.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281577","281577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141825","2019-09-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that parents and carers are provided with accurate information on the benefits and risks of the MMR vaccine.","Biography information for Adam Holloway","Adam Holloway","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281668","281668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141826","2019-09-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the answer of 22 July 2019 to Question 278344 on universal credit: fraud, what recourse is available to people, particularly vulnerable people, who have benefited financially but who were unaware that a universal credit advance was the source of the money.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281563","281563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141827","2019-09-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 22 July 2019 to Question 278344, on Universal Credit: Fraud, over what period of time the 52 pages were shut down.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281564","281564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141828","2019-09-03","Home Office","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps his Department has taken with the Loneliness Action Group to share learning on loneliness and ensure effective implementation of the loneliness strategy.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281732","281732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141829","2019-09-03","Treasury","2019-07-24","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what information his Department (a) collects and (b) publishes on (i) tobacco sales, (ii) profits, (iii) marketing and (iv) research.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281814","281814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141830","2019-09-03","Treasury","2019-07-24","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if his Department will collect data on illicit tobacco seizures of less than 100,000 cigarettes.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281815","281815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141832","2019-09-03","Treasury","2019-07-24","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department is taking to assess the extent of the illicit tobacco trade in the UK.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281816","281816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141833","2019-09-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether it is his Department's policy to fulfil the UK's obligations under the 1984 Sino-British Joint Declaration.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281731","281731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141834","2019-09-03","Treasury","2019-07-24","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer,what processes his Department uses to (a) audit its track and trace contract arrangements with De La Rue and (b) ensure that De La Rue's subcontractors are independent from the tobacco industry.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281817","281817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141835","2019-09-03","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps is he taking to improve the regulation of Approved Inspectors in the building industry.","Biography information for Gordon Henderson","Gordon Henderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281740","281740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141836","2019-09-03","Northern Ireland Office","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, pursuant to the Answer of 23 July 2019 to Question 278925 and with reference to the absence of a Northern Ireland Executive, how much funding was allocated to Tourism Ireland in each of the last three years; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281649","281649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141837","2019-09-03","Department for Education","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans he has to issue guidance to schools on the need to include spoken language in schools’ special educational needs information reports.","Biography information for Geraint Davies","Geraint Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281557","281557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141838","2019-09-03","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 22 July 2019 to Question 278349 on Private Rented Housing: Pensioners, what assessment he has made of the effect of the ban on letting fees on monthly rental prices.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281565","281565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141839","2019-09-03","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of the 22 July 2019 to Question 278349 on Private Rented Housing: Pensioners, what assessment his Department has made of trends in the level of landlords that allow older renters to make modifications to their rented property to accommodate for mobility issues.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281566","281566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141840","2019-09-03","Department for Education","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what progress he has made on implementing the recommendations of the United Nations General Assembly of 17 December 2018 on the Rights of the Child; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ann Coffey","Ann Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281616","281616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141841","2019-09-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, which representatives of the UK Government attended the Second Global Rehabilitation 2030 Meeting in Geneva on 8 and 9 July 2019.","Biography information for Geraint Davies","Geraint Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281558","281558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141842","2019-09-03","Department for Education","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 23 July 2019 to Question 278350 on Children: Day Care, what additional support his Department provides to low income households that require childcare during the summer holidays.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281567","281567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141843","2019-09-03","Department for Education","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 23 July 2019 to Question 278350 on Children: Day Care, what support is available for parents of a child with (a) special educational needs and (b) a disability whose childcare costs exceed £4,000 each year.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281568","281568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141845","2019-09-03","Department for Education","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 23 July 2019 to Question 278350 on Children: Day Care, what support is available for parents of a child with (a) special educational needs and  (b) a disability who live in a local authority area which is unable to provide sufficient childcare to meet their needs during the school summer holidays.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281569","281569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141846","2019-09-03","Department for Education","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment his Department has made of the ability of local authorities to provide sufficient childcare to meet the needs of children with special educational needs and disabilities in their local authority areas.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281570","281570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141847","2019-09-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make a comparative assessment of the proportion of parents in low income families who are (a) out of work and (b) in part-time work (i) during the school summer holidays and (ii) at all other times in the school year.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281571","281571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141848","2019-09-03","Department for Education","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 17 July 2019 to Question 278353, how the 0.7 per cent of funding from donations is distributed across all schools.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281572","281572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141849","2019-09-03","Department for Education","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 21 June 2019 to Question 263684, what assessment his Department has made of the overall compliance of schools in England with equalities law and the schools admission code in their admittance and treatment of children with SEND.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281573","281573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141850","2019-09-03","Department for Education","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 21 June 2019 to Question 263684, what assessment his Department has made of the merits of the reported practice of parents and reviewing bodies of schools seeking to avoid compliance with equalities law and the schools admission code in their admittance and treatment of children with SEND.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281574","281574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141851","2019-09-03","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to section 5.1 of the consultation Local Government Pension Scheme (LGPS): Changes to the local valuation cycle and the management of employer risk, what information his Department holds on demographic composition of (a) teaching staff and (b) non-teaching staff in England by (i) gender and (ii) age.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281818","281818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141852","2019-09-03","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to section 5.1 of the consultation Local Government Pension Scheme (LGPS): Changes to the local valuation cycle and the management of employer risk, what the average income of people classed as (a) teaching staff and (b) non-teaching staff is.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281819","281819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141853","2019-09-03","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to section 5.1 of the consultation Local Government Pension Scheme (LGPS): Changes to the local valuation cycle and the management of employer risk,  what assessment he has made of which alternative pension schemes those non-teaching staff that are not offered the LGPS would be eligible for.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281820","281820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141854","2019-09-03","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to section 5.1 of the consultation Local Government Pension Scheme (LGPS): Changes to the local valuation cycle and the management of employer risk, what assessment he has made of the potential economic effect on non-teaching staff of joining pension schemes other than the LGPS.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281821","281821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141855","2019-09-03","Department for Transport","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect of the construction of High Speed Two on (a) badger populations along the line of route and (b) the risk to cattle populations from bovine TB due to badger displacement.","Biography information for Andrea Leadsom","Andrea Leadsom","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281752","281752"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141856","2019-09-03","Treasury","2019-07-24","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that UK banks fulfuil their obligations under the EU Payment Accounts Directive; and whether he plans to retain the consumer protections in that directive after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281633","281633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141857","2019-09-03","Treasury","2019-07-24","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent estimate he has made of the percentage of adults in the UK who do not have a UK bank account.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281634","281634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141858","2019-09-03","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the number of Lasting Powers of Attorneys which were registered with the Office of Public Guardian in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281635","281635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141859","2019-09-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the timeline is for the implementation of personalised cancer care interventions for all patients, including those with secondary cancers, including access to a clinical nurse specialist or other support worker.","Biography information for Craig Tracey","Craig Tracey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281822","281822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141860","2019-09-03","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many people are members of the Local Government Pension Scheme in (a) Barnsley, (b) South Yorkshire and (c) Yorkshire and Humber.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281823","281823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141861","2019-09-03","Treasury","2019-07-24","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of making protecting access to cash a statutory duty of the Payment Systems Regulator.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281636","281636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141862","2019-09-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the NHS Long Term Plan, what steps he (a) is taking and (b) plans to take to meet the target that 50 per cent of people taking part in clinical trials are teenagers and young adults by 2025.","Biography information for Craig Tracey","Craig Tracey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281824","281824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141863","2019-09-03","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect on members of the local government pension scheme of changing local fund valuations from a triennial to a quadrennial cycle by (a) region and (b) local authority.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281825","281825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141864","2019-09-03","Treasury","2019-07-24","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the economic effectiveness of the no-interest loan scheme pilot announced in Budget 2018.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281637","281637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141865","2019-09-03","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, when he plans to publish the results of his Department's consultation on changes to the Local Government Pension Scheme.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281826","281826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141866","2019-09-03","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether his Department has conducted a risk assessment of the proposed move from a triennial to a quadrennial cycle for local fund valuations of the Local Government Pension Scheme.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281827","281827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141867","2019-09-03","Cabinet Office","2019-07-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will publish in table format (a) a list of the ministerial redundancy payments issued since August 2010 and (b) which former ministers accepted those payments.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham P Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281716","281716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141868","2019-09-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps her Department is taking to protect people on benefits or low incomes who would be most vulnerable to rising food prices or food supply disruption in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Ruth Smeeth","Ruth Smeeth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281828","281828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141869","2019-09-03","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment she has made of the presence of asbestos at Ashchurch military depot.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281669","281669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141870","2019-09-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans his Department has to review the effectiveness of NHS (a) diagnoses and (b) treatment of pineal cysts.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281742","281742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141871","2019-09-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to ensure that imported liquid and powdered egg products are compliant with UK food standards after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Mr David Jones","Mr David Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281660","281660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141872","2019-09-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with the British Egg Industry Council on food safety standards for imported egg products after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Mr David Jones","Mr David Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281661","281661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141873","2019-09-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what funding the Government is providing for research into the treatment of pineal cysts.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281743","281743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141874","2019-09-03","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 11 June 2019 to Question 261159 on Internet: Cryptography, when (a) he, (b) Ministers in his Department and (c) officials in his Department met with representatives of browser providers on the forthcoming protocol to deploy DNS over HTTP.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281657","281657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141875","2019-09-03","Treasury","2019-07-24","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 22 July 2019 to Question 277102 on Aviation: Alternative Fuels, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of introducing tax (a) incentives and (b) disincentives to accelerate the switch to alternative aviation fuels.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281560","281560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141876","2019-09-03","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 11 June 2019 to Question 261159 on Internet: Cryptography, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of bringing forward legislative proposals to ensure that the switch to DNS from HTTP protocol does not weaken (a) existing child online safety provisions and (b) ISP blocking.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281658","281658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141877","2019-09-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans his Department has to develop new guidelines for the diagnosis and treatment of pineal cysts.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281744","281744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141878","2019-09-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if his Department will take steps to increase the availability of regular follow up MRI scans for people with pineal cysts.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281745","281745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141879","2019-09-03","Home Office","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 13 March 2019 to Question 230087, whether local Common Travel Area journeys across the Irish land border will not be subject to the proposed future requirement to obtain Electronic Travel Authorisation.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281829","281829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141880","2019-09-03","Northern Ireland Office","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, pursuant to the Answer of 13 March 2019 to Question 230086 on Brexit: Northern Ireland, whether it is the Government's position that only Irish citizens living in Northern Ireland who are also British citizens will be permitted to vote in the event of a border poll conducted under Schedule 1 of the Northern Ireland Act 1998.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281830","281830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141881","2019-09-03","Department for Transport","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the Government supports the reinstatement of the rail link between Skipton and Colne.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham P Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281717","281717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141882","2019-09-03","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what plans the Government has for the formation of a Pennine Lancashire unitary authority.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham P Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281718","281718"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141883","2019-09-03","Women and Equalities","2019-07-24","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, how much the Government spent on celebrations for International Women's day in each year since 2015.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281673","281673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141884","2019-09-03","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how much his Department has spent on purchasing (a) national newspapers and (b) newspaper online subscriptions since 2016; and how many copies of each national newspaper were purchased in that time period.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281674","281674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141885","2019-09-03","Department for Transport","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he plans to allocate additional funding to Transport for the North to implement the One North Strategic Transport Plan ahead of schedule.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham P Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281719","281719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141886","2019-09-03","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how much his Department has spent on purchasing (a) national newspapers and (b) newspaper online subscriptions since 2016; and how many copies of each national newspaper were purchased in that time period.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281675","281675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141887","2019-09-03","Department for International Development","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much his Department has spent on purchasing (a) national newspapers and (b) newspaper online subscriptions since 2016; and how many copies of each national newspaper were purchased in that time period.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281676","281676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141888","2019-09-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how much his Department has spent on purchasing (a) national newspapers and (b) newspaper online subscriptions since 2016; and how many copies of each national newspaper were purchased in that time period.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281677","281677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141889","2019-09-03","Department for International Trade","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how much his Department has spent on purchasing (a) national newspapers and (b) newspaper online subscriptions since 2016; and how many copies of each national newspaper were purchased in that time period.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281678","281678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141890","2019-09-03","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 17 May 2019 to Question 252665 on Prison Officers, what assessment he has made of the effect on levels of prison violence of the loss of over 80,000 years of prison officers' cumulative length of service.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281831","281831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141891","2019-09-03","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to Written Statement of 22 July 2019 on Prisons and Probation, HCWS1783, what assessment he has made of how partnering with the private sector to operate prisons offers value for money.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281832","281832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141892","2019-09-03","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the effect of (a) prison violence and (b) exposure to new psychoactive substances on the (i) physical and (ii) mental health of prison staff.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281833","281833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141893","2019-09-03","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the physical ability of prison officers to work in front-line roles above the age of 60.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281834","281834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141894","2019-09-03","Department for Transport","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much his Department has spent on schemes to encourage staff of his Department to cycle to work since 2015; and how much his Department has spent on (a) installing bicycle racks and (b) bonus schemes for bicycle use in that time period.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281679","281679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141895","2019-09-03","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how much his Department has spent on schemes to encourage staff of his Department to cycle to work since 2015; and how much his Department has spent on (a) installing bicycle racks and (b) bonus schemes for bicycle use in that time period.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281680","281680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141896","2019-09-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much his Department has spent on schemes to encourage staff of his Department to cycle to work since 2015; and how much his Department has spent on (a) installing bicycle racks and (b) bonus schemes for bicycle use in that time period.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281681","281681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141897","2019-09-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much his Department has spent on schemes to encourage staff of his Department to cycle to work since 2015; and how much his Department has spent on (a) installing bicycle racks and (b) bonus schemes for bicycle use in that time period.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281682","281682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140799","2019-07-25","Department for Education","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the effect of the cost of learning BSL on take up of those courses.","Biography information for Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280364","280364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140954","2019-07-24","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2019-07-23","To ask the hon. Member for Houghton and Sunderland South, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, if he will make an assessment of the ability of the Electoral Commission to monitor the performance of electoral registration officers in dealing with electors who (a) have low reading and writing skills, (b) are visually impaired and (c) have learning difficulties.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280147","280147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141139","2019-07-24","Home Office","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps his Department is taking to help councils (a) accommodate and (b) process asylum seekers.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280223","280223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141245","2019-09-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his counterpart in Mauritania on tackling slavery in that country.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280958","280958"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141246","2019-09-03","Women and Equalities","2019-07-23","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what steps the Government is taking to promote the values of equality and diversity in UK society.","Biography information for Andrea Leadsom","Andrea Leadsom","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280959","280959"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141247","2019-09-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the Government plans to recognise the Ottoman Empire's killing of 1.5 million Armenians between 1915 and 1917 as genocide.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280960","280960"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141248","2019-09-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what progress his Department has made on the commitment made in the loneliness strategy to launch an online social prescribing platform for commissioners and practitioners.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280961","280961"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141249","2019-09-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what progress his Department has made on the commitment made in the loneliness strategy to pilot accredited learning programmes for social prescribing link workers.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280962","280962"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141250","2019-09-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what progress his Department has made on the commitment in the loneliness strategy to undertake work to assess how a variety of organisations and services currently refer individuals into social prescribing schemes and local provision.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280963","280963"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141251","2019-07-25","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when a long-term workforce plan which sets out the number of staff required to meet the current and future needs of cancer patients will be published.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280964","280964"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141252","2019-09-03","Department for Transport","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of increased (a) car ownership in Towcester and (b) vehicle movements on the (i) A5 and (ii) A43 in the event that the Towcester Relief Road is not built.","Biography information for Andrea Leadsom","Andrea Leadsom","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280965","280965"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141253","2019-07-25","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment he has made of the potential effect of the UK leaving the EU on the supply of drugs to the NHS.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281022","281022"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141254","2019-09-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent steps his Department is taking to increase collaboration between the Animal and Plant Health Agency and veterinary regulatory authorities in other countries to tackle provision of fake pet passports and veterinary certificates for dogs being imported into the UK.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280926","280926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141255","2019-07-25","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what legal duties govern the administering of dermal fillers to people under the age of 18 by non-regulated practitioners.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280927","280927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141256","2019-07-25","Department for Transport","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the distance is via rail to the relevant London terminal from each station outside London; and what the price per mile is of a peak time return ticket to London from each of those stations.","Biography information for Neil O'Brien","Neil O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281023","281023"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141257","2019-07-25","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2019-07-23","To ask the hon. Member for Houghton and Sunderland South, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what recent assessment the Electoral Commission has made of electoral registration rates of attainers in (a) Scotland, (b) Northern Ireland, (c) Wales and (d) England.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280928","280928"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141258","2019-07-25","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2019-07-23","To ask the hon. Member for Houghton and Sunderland South, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, which local authorities have achieved the highest increase in levels of voter registration in the last two years; and what steps have been taken to ensure that the practices leading to such increases are adopted in other local authorities.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280929","280929"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141259","2019-07-25","Cabinet Office","2019-07-23","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will commission research on the effect of levels of functional illiteracy on electoral registration rates.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280930","280930"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141260","2019-07-25","Cabinet Office","2019-07-23","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what his most recent estimate is of the electoral registration rate for each region of the UK.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280931","280931"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141261","2019-07-25","Cabinet Office","2019-07-23","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the electoral registration rate was in each year since 1997 in the 100 parliamentary constituencies which have had the largest decrease in the number of electors on the register from the date of the local boundary review to July 2019.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280932","280932"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141262","2019-09-03","Cabinet Office","2019-07-23","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps his Department has taken to increase registration rates and voter turnout of (a) visually impaired voters and (b) voters with learning difficulties.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280933","280933"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141263","2019-07-25","Cabinet Office","2019-07-23","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what (a) central Government and (b) local government databases electoral registration officers may use in undertaking their registration functions.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280934","280934"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141264","2019-07-25","Cabinet Office","2019-07-23","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many electoral registration officers have been convicted of an offence related to failure to take sufficient steps to register electors under section 9A of the Electoral Registration Act 2006.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280935","280935"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141265","2019-07-25","Cabinet Office","2019-07-23","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the Answer of 20 July 2010, Official Report, column 298W, on Electoral Register, how many electoral registration officers have been convicted of an offence related to failure to take sufficient steps to register electors under section 9A of the Electoral Registration Act 2006.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280936","280936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141266","2019-09-03","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2019-07-23","To ask the hon. Member for Houghton and Sunderland South, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what training has been given to electoral registration officers on the implementation of fixed penalty notices for non-registration.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280937","280937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141267","2019-07-25","Cabinet Office","2019-07-23","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what additional central Government funding was made available to electoral registration officers for electoral registration in each of the last five years; and which local authorities were successful in bidding for that funding.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280938","280938"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141268","2019-09-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of reports that people who are paid on the last day of the month are incorrectly showing on the HMRC database as having been paid on the first working day of the month on the ability of her Department to correctly assess an individual’s entitlement to benefits; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281024","281024"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141269","2019-09-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what representations his Department has received following recommendations from NICE on NHS England adopting a commissioning policy for MR-guided focused ultrasound for essential tremor; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280966","280966"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141270","2019-09-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment has been made by his Department's agencies and public bodies of the potential clinical benefits of MR-guided focused ultrasound as a treatment for essential tremor; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280967","280967"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141271","2019-09-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment has been made by his Department's agencies and public bodies of the potential value for money of MR-guided focused ultrasound as a treatment for essential tremor; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280968","280968"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141272","2019-09-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate his Department has made of the number of people who would potentially benefit from MR-guided focused ultrasound as a treatment for essential tremor each year; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280969","280969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141273","2019-09-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if his Department will provide interim funding for NHS patients to access MR-guided focused ultrasound as a treatment for essential tremor at St Mary’s Hospital, Imperial College Healthcare Trust; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280970","280970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141274","2019-09-03","Department for International Trade","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, with reference to the 20 June 2019 Court of Appeal judgment on arms sales to Saudi Arabia, how many (a) standard individual export licences, (b) open individual and (c) open general export licences his Department is reviewing.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281025","281025"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141275","2019-07-25","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Written Statement of 18 July 2019, Building safety update, HCWS 1757, what his Department's definition is of the exceptional circumstances that would provide justification for private sector building owners not completing remediation of buildings with unsafe ACM cladding by June 2020.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281026","281026"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141277","2019-07-25","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Written Statement of 18 July 2019, Building safety update, HCWS 1757, how leaseholders will be notified whether the owners of the private sector buildings to which they hold a leasehold will be required to complete remediation of those buildings with unsafe ACM cladding by June 2020.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281027","281027"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141278","2019-07-25","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Written Statement of 18 July 2019, Building safety update, HCWS 1757, what steps he is taking to expedite remedial works on buildings with unsafe ACM cladding in cases where private sector building owners have given a clear commitment to that remediation and a plan has been agreed but the proposed finish date for those works is after June 2020.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281028","281028"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141279","2019-07-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the proportion of universal credit claimants that have had a deduction as a result of arrears to their (a) first, (b) second, (c) third, (d) fourth, (e) fifth and (f) sixth universal credit payment in the most recent period for which data is available.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280971","280971"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141280","2019-09-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his Israeli counterpart on the recent shooting of the unarmed child, Abd el-Rahman Shatawi, in Kafr Qaddum; and what information he has received on that shooting.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281029","281029"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141281","2019-07-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 15 May 2019 to Question 224493, how much has been deducted from universal credit claimants' standard allowance in (a) the London Borough of Tower Hamlets and (b) Poplar and Limehouse constituency in each month since April 2017.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280902","280902"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141282","2019-07-25","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the effect of the increased numbers of people vaping on (a) nicotine addiction, (b) incidences of increased blood pressure and (c) heart attack rates.","Biography information for Mr Ranil Jayawardena","Mr Ranil Jayawardena","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281030","281030"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141283","2019-07-25","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to ban e-cigarettes wherever the smoking ban is in place. .","Biography information for Mr Ranil Jayawardena","Mr Ranil Jayawardena","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281031","281031"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141284","2019-07-25","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to ban (a) e-cigarette shops and (b) smoking on NHS hospital property.","Biography information for Mr Ranil Jayawardena","Mr Ranil Jayawardena","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281032","281032"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141285","2019-07-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will raise with his German counterpart the decision by the City of Koblenz to ban the burqa at public swimming pools.","Biography information for Ruth Jones","Ruth Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281033","281033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141286","2019-07-25","Department for Transport","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what criteria his Department used to calculate the £950,000 cost of the annual upgrade of the UK Drone Registration Scheme.","Biography information for Lee Rowley","Lee Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281034","281034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141287","2019-07-25","Department for Transport","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, on what evidence his Department based its estimate of the predicted registration of 170,000 drone users within the first 18 months of the UK Drone Registration Scheme.","Biography information for Lee Rowley","Lee Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281035","281035"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141288","2019-07-25","Department for Transport","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of using British Model Flying Association drone registration data to avoid duplicate registrations in the UK Drone Registration Scheme.","Biography information for Lee Rowley","Lee Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281036","281036"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141289","2019-07-25","Department for Transport","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans his Department has to publicise the UK Drone Registration Scheme to (a) new and (b) drone owners.","Biography information for Lee Rowley","Lee Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281037","281037"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141290","2019-07-25","Department for Transport","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect of the UK Drone Registration Scheme on levels of criminal activity involving drones.","Biography information for Lee Rowley","Lee Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281038","281038"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141291","2019-07-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if his Department will meet with representatives of the Shuhuh 6 to discuss the human rights situation in Oman.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281039","281039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141292","2019-07-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department has taken to verify assurances given by the Government of Oman that (a) there is no discrimination against the Shuhuh 6 and (b) the arrest of the Shuhuh 6 was conducted with respect for human rights.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281040","281040"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141293","2019-07-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether Ministers of his Department have seen the Amnesty International statement of 22 May 2019 entitled, Oman: Life Sentence for Prisoner of Conscious on the imprisonment of Mohammed Abdullah al-Shahi.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281041","281041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141294","2019-07-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if his Department will support the call by Amnesty International for the Government of Oman to unconditionally release (a) Mohammed Abdullah al-Shahi and (b) other prisoners of conscience in that country.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281042","281042"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141295","2019-07-25","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2019-07-23","To ask the hon. Member for Houghton and Sunderland South, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, how many successful prosecutions for (a) postal vote fraud, excluding by proxy voting, and (b) electoral registration fraud there have been in each of the last 15 years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280939","280939"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141296","2019-09-03","Home Office","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she has taken to support female refugees to access English language lessons as set out in the Integrated Communities Strategy 2018.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280972","280972"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141297","2019-09-03","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the European-led maritime protection mission to be deployed in the strait of Hormuz will operate under the framework of the Common Security and Defence Policy.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280973","280973"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141298","2019-09-03","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when she plans to respond to the letter of 17 June from the hon. Member for Llanelli on Afghan interpreters.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280974","280974"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141299","2019-09-03","Treasury","2019-07-23","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he has plans to undertake a review of the level of taxation on (a) beer and (b) pubs.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham P Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280975","280975"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141300","2019-07-25","Cabinet Office","2019-07-23","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what (a) national and (b) local authority databases may be inspected by electoral registration officers.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280940","280940"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141301","2019-09-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the threat posed by the oil tanker anchored off the coast of Yemen to the environment.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280903","280903"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141302","2019-07-25","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2019-07-23","To ask the hon. Member for Houghton and Sunderland South, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what the cost to the public purse was of registering each overseas voter in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280941","280941"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141303","2019-09-03","Department for Transport","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the available capacity for additional train paths on the West Coast Main Line; and when the last study of network capacity on the West Coast Main Line was undertaken.","Biography information for Andrea Leadsom","Andrea Leadsom","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280976","280976"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141304","2019-09-03","Department for Transport","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what priority his Department gives on the West Coast Main Line to (a) passenger train and (b) freight train paths.","Biography information for Andrea Leadsom","Andrea Leadsom","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280977","280977"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141305","2019-09-03","Department for Transport","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect of (a) existing and (b) future projected demands on access to the West Coast Main Line on the operation of that line.","Biography information for Andrea Leadsom","Andrea Leadsom","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280978","280978"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141306","2019-09-03","Department for Transport","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect of two or more competing Nationally Significant Infrastructure Projects on the physical and mental well-being of affected communities.","Biography information for Andrea Leadsom","Andrea Leadsom","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280979","280979"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141307","2019-07-25","Treasury","2019-07-23","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 1 July 2019 to Question 268968 on Tax Avoidance and with reference to his Department’s report on Time limits and the charge on disguised remuneration loans published in March 2019, what steps HMRC has taken to increase mental health support for people subject to the 2019 Loan Charge.","Biography information for Andrea Leadsom","Andrea Leadsom","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281043","281043"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141308","2019-07-25","Treasury","2019-07-23","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 1 July 2019 to Question 268968 on Tax Avoidance and with reference to his Department’s report on Time limits and the charge on disguised remuneration loans published in March 2019, whether people subject to the 2019 Loan Charge are at risk of losing their homes.","Biography information for Andrea Leadsom","Andrea Leadsom","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281044","281044"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141309","2019-07-25","Department for Education","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, for what reason apprentices studying for a National Vocational Qualification alongside their in-work training prior to applying to university do not accrue UCAS points for that NVQ.","Biography information for Andrea Leadsom","Andrea Leadsom","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281045","281045"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141310","2019-07-25","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions officials in his Department have had with their counterparts in the Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government on the proposed pilot scheme merger of the provision of social care and health care in Northamptonshire under a single new organisation.","Biography information for Andrea Leadsom","Andrea Leadsom","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281046","281046"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141311","2019-07-25","Department for Education","2019-07-23","To Ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 15 July 2019 to Question 273801 on Child Exploitation, how many children-in-need assessments were undertaken in which criminal exploitation through county lines was identified as a potential risk to the child’s life in each year since 2015.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281047","281047"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141312","2019-07-25","Home Office","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether it is his policy that consistency of police force systems and processes nationally should be mandated while maintaining links and accountability locally for service delivery.","Biography information for Andrea Leadsom","Andrea Leadsom","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281048","281048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141313","2019-07-25","Home Office","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps he is taking to ensure that the next review of the policing funding formula provides an equitable settlement for Northamptonshire Police.","Biography information for Andrea Leadsom","Andrea Leadsom","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281049","281049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141314","2019-07-25","Home Office","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will take steps to help police forces answer freedom of information requests.","Biography information for Andrea Leadsom","Andrea Leadsom","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281050","281050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141315","2019-07-25","Home Office","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether he has made an assessment of the potential merits of (a) giving PCCs direct responsibility for a number of statutory functions in the police complaints system and (b) other reforms to that system as set out in the Policing and Crime Act 2017; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrea Leadsom","Andrea Leadsom","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281051","281051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141316","2019-09-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment he has made of trends in the level of waiting times at A&E at the Royal Blackburn Hospital.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham P Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280980","280980"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141317","2019-07-25","Home Office","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of (a) Police, Fire and Crime Commissioners more easily pooling buildings and other assets and (b) other forms of collaboration between emergency services.","Biography information for Andrea Leadsom","Andrea Leadsom","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281052","281052"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141318","2019-07-25","Department for Transport","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that the future West Coast Partnership will not prioritise its train paths over those of other train operating companies; and if he will make an assessment of the effect of the West Coast Partnership franchise on timetabling of trains on the West Coast Main Line.","Biography information for Andrea Leadsom","Andrea Leadsom","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281053","281053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141319","2019-07-25","Department for Transport","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the (a) level of available capacity on the North London Line for additional (i) freight and (ii) passenger services and (b) the potential for additional freight paths from (iii) existing and (iv) proposed strategic rail freight interchanges in the Midlands to (A) Felixstowe and (B) the London Ports via the North London Line.","Biography information for Andrea Leadsom","Andrea Leadsom","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281054","281054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141320","2019-09-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what resources his Department has allocated to raise awareness of his green paper and open consultation entitled Advancing our health: prevention in the 2020s.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280942","280942"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141321","2019-09-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to de-escalate tensions with Iran.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280904","280904"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141322","2019-09-03","House of Commons Commission","2019-07-23","To ask the right hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington, representing the House of Commons Commission, what discussions the Commission has had on establishing in-house BSL interpretation service for deaf visitors.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham P Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280981","280981"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141323","2019-07-25","House of Commons Commission","2019-07-23","To ask the right hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington, representing the House of Commons Commission, what progress the Commission has made on expanding the Independent Complaints and Grievance Scheme to resolving cases dating back to before June 2017.","Biography information for Andrea Leadsom","Andrea Leadsom","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281055","281055"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141324","2019-07-25","Department for Education","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 15 July 2019 to Question 273801 on Child Exploitation, what plans his Department has to ensure that local authorities monitor the risk of criminal exploitation to children within their area.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281056","281056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141325","2019-09-03","Department for Transport","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many and what proportion of settlement agreements entered into by HS2 Ltd with former staff included non-disclosure provisions.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280910","280910"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141326","2019-09-03","Department for Transport","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many compromise agreements entered into by HS2 Ltd with former staff included non-disclosure provisions.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280911","280911"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141327","2019-09-03","Department for Transport","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the total cost of redundancy payments to former HS2 Ltd staff is.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280912","280912"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141328","2019-09-03","Department for Transport","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, under what authorised scheme redundancy payments were made to former HS2 Ltd staff.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280913","280913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141329","2019-09-03","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the finding of the Royal Institute of British Architects report Space Standards for Homes that the level of administration and red tape involved when local authorities seek to adopt the Nationally Described Space Standard (NDSS) means that in many cases it takes several years to adopt, whether he plans to adopt RIBA’s recommendation that the NDSS should be universally applied through building regulations.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280982","280982"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141330","2019-09-03","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the finding of the Royal Institute of British Architects' report Space Standards for Homes that half of all new homes remain too small when measured against the minimum standards of the Nationally Described Space Standard.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280983","280983"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141331","2019-09-03","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether she has plans to bring all houses in multiple occupation within the scope of the minimum energy efficiency standard for the domestic private rented sector.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280984","280984"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141332","2019-09-03","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the BRE Code for Sustainable Homes data that 107,000 homes have been built in England to the zero carbon homes standard, if he will include in the forthcoming review of Building Regulations a proposal to reinstate that standard from 2020.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280985","280985"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141333","2019-07-25","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the implications for her policies of the findings of the February 2019 Energy & Climate Intelligence Unit Zero Carbon Homes report that had the Zero Carbon Homes policy not been cancelled, occupants of new homes built since the intended policy start date of 2016 would be saving more than £200 per year on their energy bills, and that the total extra cumulative energy costs paid by those homeowners to date is more than £120 million.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280986","280986"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141334","2019-07-25","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to recent English Housing Survey statistics which show that four per cent of local authority housing and 13 per cent of social housing fail to meet the Decent Homes Standard, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of restoring central Government funding for housing providers to enable the remaining non-decent homes to be improved.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280987","280987"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141335","2019-07-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent discussions his Department has had with (a) the Forestry Commission, (b) Forest Enterprise England and (c) other agencies on the closure of Tree Top Way in Salcey forest, south Northamptonshire; and if his Department will provide financial support to help Tree Top Way reopen as soon as possible.","Biography information for Andrea Leadsom","Andrea Leadsom","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281057","281057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141336","2019-07-25","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to increase the number of community pharmacies.","Biography information for Neil O'Brien","Neil O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281058","281058"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141337","2019-09-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps are being taken to ensure breast cancer screening is a prioritised by the NHS.","Biography information for Mike Amesbury","Mike Amesbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281059","281059"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141338","2019-07-25","Department for Education","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 15 July 2019 to Question 273801 on Child Exploitation, what plans his Department has to ensure that services can safeguard children at the earliest opportunity.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281060","281060"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141339","2019-09-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Bangladeshi counterpart on the safety of Bhasan Char for Rohingya refugees.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280905","280905"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141340","2019-07-25","Department for Education","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the need for a contextual safeguarding framework to be used alongside other safeguarding models within the child protection system in order to more effectively identify and support children who are being exploited.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281061","281061"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141341","2019-09-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to prevent the export of (a) hazardous and (b) medical UK waste to Sri Lanka as recycling.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280906","280906"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141342","2019-07-25","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he plans to take to better integrate healthcare and social care throughout the UK.","Biography information for Andrea Leadsom","Andrea Leadsom","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281062","281062"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141343","2019-07-25","Scotland Office","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what steps he is taking to ensure that Scotland maintains its position as a global leader in offshore wind.","Biography information for Andrea Leadsom","Andrea Leadsom","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281063","281063"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141344","2019-09-03","Department for Education","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to ensure that people with learning disabilities are adequately supported to pursue further education and lifelong learning opportunities.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280988","280988"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141345","2019-09-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure that people with learning disabilities receive specialist support to help them engage effectively with the NHS.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280989","280989"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141346","2019-09-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to reduce waiting times for patients to see their GP.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280990","280990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141347","2019-07-25","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what proportion of the latest round of funding from the UK Research Partnership Investment Fund will be allocated to projects in Scotland; and how much private investment will be leveraged for those projects.","Biography information for Kirstene Hair","Kirstene Hair","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281064","281064"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141348","2019-07-25","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what proportion of funding from all rounds of the UK Research Partnership Investment Fund has been allocated to projects in Scotland; and how much private investment has been committed to those projects.","Biography information for Kirstene Hair","Kirstene Hair","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281065","281065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141349","2019-07-25","Department for International Trade","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what support is being provided to businesses in Angus to access new foreign markets and increase export volumes.","Biography information for Kirstene Hair","Kirstene Hair","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281066","281066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141350","2019-07-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many local authorities in England have submitted data for 2019 on the number of licences they have issued under the Animal Welfare (Licensing of Activities Involving Animals) (England) Regulations 2018.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280991","280991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141351","2019-07-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the Animal Welfare (Licensing of Activities Involving Animals) (England) Regulations 2018, how many licences have been issued under those regulations in 2019 for (a) breeding dogs, (b) providing or arranging for the provision of boarding for cats, (c) providing or arranging for the provision of boarding for dogs in kennels, (d) providing or arranging for the provision of day care for dogs, (e) hiring out horses, (f) selling animals as pets and (g) keeping or training animals for exhibition.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280992","280992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141352","2019-07-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to The Animal Welfare (Licensing of Activities Involving Animals) (England) Regulations 2018, what the (a) average fee and (b) lowest and highest charges for licences issued in England in 2019 to date across all local authorities was for (i) breeding dogs, (ii) providing or arranging for the provision of boarding for cats, (iii) providing or arranging for the provision of boarding for dogs in kennels, (iv) providing or arranging for the provision of day care for dogs, (v) hiring out horses, (vi) selling animals as pets and (vii) keeping or training animals for exhibition.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280993","280993"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141353","2019-09-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has made representations to his Israeli counterpart on the demolition of Palestinian buildings in the Sur Baher neighbourhood in East Jerusalem; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281067","281067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141354","2019-09-03","Department for Transport","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will bring forward legislative proposals on the regulatory reform of the taxi and private hire industry.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281068","281068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141355","2019-07-25","Department for Transport","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what proportion of services leaving each railway station were (a) cancelled or significantly late and (b) met the public performance measure in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Neil O'Brien","Neil O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281069","281069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141356","2019-07-25","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of whether Kuvan should be assessed through NICE's highly-specialised technology appraisal.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280943","280943"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141357","2019-09-03","Department for Education","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Loneliness Strategy, published in October 2018, what progress his Department has made on publishing guidance on schools maximising the use of their premises, as well as other forms of income generation that can be beneficial to the community.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281070","281070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141358","2019-09-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, which public body is responsible for providing support to cancer patients to access radiotherapy when those people live long distances from radiotherapy centres.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280994","280994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141359","2019-09-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how much funding the Government has allocated to the Great Britain China Centre; and what the (a) terms and (b) objectives were for that funding.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280896","280896"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141360","2019-09-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many (a) discussions and (b) meetings there have been between Ministers of his Department and representatives of the Great Britain China Centre in the last five years.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280897","280897"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141361","2019-09-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has received on a referral of the Chinese Government to the United Nations Special Committee on Decolonisation  in relation to human rights abuses in Tibet.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280898","280898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141362","2019-07-25","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what guidance his Department has published on distinguishing between rashes caused by the measles vaccine and those arising from the wild strain of measles.","Biography information for Adam Holloway","Adam Holloway","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280995","280995"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141363","2019-07-25","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure that statistics on the infection rate for measles do not include people who have received the live measles vaccine and contracted a measles-like rash and fever.","Biography information for Adam Holloway","Adam Holloway","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280996","280996"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141364","2019-07-25","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure that (a) body inclusion encephalitis and (b) other adverse events experienced after a measles vaccine are identified in a timely way by healthcare professionals.","Biography information for Adam Holloway","Adam Holloway","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280997","280997"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141365","2019-09-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when he plans to publish the next Serious Incident Framework.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281071","281071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141366","2019-07-25","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how much funding has been disbursed for disabled facilities grants by (a) central Government and (b) Oxford County Council in 2019-20.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281072","281072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141367","2019-07-25","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how much funding was disbursed for disabled facilities grants by (a) central Government and (b) local authorities in Oxfordshire in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281073","281073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141368","2019-09-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to reduce instances of (a) breast cancer among women and (b) prostate cancer.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280944","280944"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141369","2019-07-25","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how much funding was disbursed for disabled facilities grants by (a) central Government and (b) Oxford County Council in each year from 2000 to 2009.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281074","281074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141370","2019-07-25","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the number of applications for disabled facilities grants in (a) 2010-2019 and (b) 2000-2009.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281075","281075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141371","2019-07-25","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what proportion of applications from (a) council tenants, (b) housing association tenants, (c) private tenants and (d) homeowners for disabled facilities grants were successful in each (i) constituent part and (ii) region of the UK in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281076","281076"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141372","2019-07-25","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, when his Department plans to publish its response to the independent report if published on 10 December 2018 entitled Disabled Facilities Grant and other adaptations: external review.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281077","281077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141373","2019-07-25","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what plans his Department has for public consultation during the development of local industrial strategies.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281078","281078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141374","2019-07-25","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what guidance his Department will give to Local Enterprise Partnerships on the development of local industrial strategies.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281079","281079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141375","2019-09-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of extending the use of medicinal cannabis to people living with CHD2 myoclonic encephalopathy.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281080","281080"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141376","2019-09-03","Northern Ireland Office","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, whether she plans to increase police numbers in Northern Ireland in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281081","281081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141377","2019-09-03","Northern Ireland Office","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what assessment she has made of the potential financial effect on farmers in Northern Ireland of the UK leaving the EU without a deal; and whether she plans to provide farmers in Northern Ireland with financial support in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281082","281082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141378","2019-09-03","Northern Ireland Office","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what assessment she has made of the effect on the economic viability of farmers who graze livestock on both sides of the border in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281083","281083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141379","2019-09-03","Northern Ireland Office","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, whether farmers in Northern Ireland will be able to graze livestock on land in the Republic of Ireland in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281084","281084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141380","2019-07-25","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to maintain and improve pharmacovigilance in relation to the MMR vaccine.","Biography information for Adam Holloway","Adam Holloway","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280998","280998"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141381","2019-07-25","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to help ensure (a) transparency and (b) accountability in the process of manufacturing the MMR vaccine.","Biography information for Adam Holloway","Adam Holloway","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280999","280999"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141382","2019-07-25","Home Office","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many non-UK professional male rugby players sponsored by (a) the Rugby Football Union and (b) rugby clubs issued governing body endorsements to become a sponsor have received Tier 2 and Tier 5 migrant visas in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281085","281085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141383","2019-07-25","Home Office","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the requirements are for an organisation to qualify to sponsor Tier 2 and Tier 5 visas; and how many organisations meet those qualifications.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281086","281086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141384","2019-07-25","Home Office","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of the effect of the level of funding for women's rugby clubs in English women’s rugby championships and premierships on the ability of non-UK professional women rugby players to receive Tier 2 and Tier 5 migrant visas; and what other options are available for non-UK women rugby players to remain in the UK.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281087","281087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141385","2019-07-25","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate he has made of the number of women playing professional rugby in the UK that are (a) UK and (b) non-UK citizens; and what the (i) immigration and (b) visa status is of those non-UK citizen rugby players.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281088","281088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141386","2019-07-25","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will make an estimate of the proportion of lightbulbs in use in households that are LED.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281089","281089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141387","2019-07-25","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate he has made of the average savings accrued to households of using LED instead of conventional lightbulbs.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281090","281090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141388","2019-09-03","Department for International Trade","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of his Department's Export Toolkit; and how much funding he has allocated to the (a) promotion and (b) printing and distribution of that toolkit.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281091","281091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141389","2019-07-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on food (a) supply and (b) disruption in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal on 31 October 2019.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281000","281000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141390","2019-07-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to ensure adequacy of the provision of food for (a) hospitals, (b) schools and (c) care settings in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal on 31 October 2019.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281001","281001"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141391","2019-07-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to ensure the maintenance of food suppliers in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281002","281002"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141392","2019-07-25","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps the Government has taken to ensure diversity of renewable energy sources as part of its goal to achieve zero carbon emissions by 2050.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280899","280899"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141393","2019-07-25","Department for Education","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the timetable is for the conclusion of the final stage of contract negotiations on the formation of the South West Institute of Technology.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281092","281092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141394","2019-07-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to support the provision of emergency medical to Syrian civilians in Idlib.","Biography information for Carol Monaghan","Carol Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281093","281093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141395","2019-09-03","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to define the standard of competency required for landlords meeting their electrical safety obligation to tenants.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281003","281003"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141396","2019-09-03","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will bring forward legislative proposals (a) to improve and regulate qualifications for PAT testing and (b) to ensure those qualifications cannot be gained through online only courses.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281004","281004"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141397","2019-09-03","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will bring forward legislative proposals for the certification of electricians with a specialism in the repair of white goods and small appliances.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281005","281005"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141398","2019-09-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans he has to extend the pathway that Public Health England is developing for children aged 0-5 to children and young people aged 5-25 with speech, language and communication needs.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281094","281094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141399","2019-07-25","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the report of the Children's Commissioner entitled, We need to talk: Access to speech and language therapy, published in June 2019, what plans he has to ensure that expenditure data is collected on the support local areas provide for children and young people with speech, language and communication needs.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281095","281095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141400","2019-07-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what guidance his Department has issued to consumers on the supply of food in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281006","281006"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141401","2019-09-03","Department for Education","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the press release, National mental health programme between schools and NHS, published on 12 July 2019, what plans he has to ensure that the Link Programme of training for each school, college and alternative provision setting includes awareness of the links between mental health and speech, language and communication needs.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281096","281096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141402","2019-07-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will publish his Department's guidance issued to (a) Resilience Forums, (b) local authorities (c) other bodies with responsibilities to prepare for crises under the Civil Contingencies Act 2004 and (d) representatives from the agriculture industry on the worst-case scenario in relation to food preparations in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281007","281007"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141403","2019-07-25","Department for Education","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans he has to increase the support provided to children and young people in secondary schools that have speech, language and communication needs.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281097","281097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141404","2019-07-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment the Government has made of the worse-case effects of the UK leaving the EU without a deal on (a) the proportion of food trucks not being able to have smooth border transit, (b) waiting times at borders, (c) the length of time of disruption to food supplies, (d) potential food price rises and (e) the finances of vulnerable people.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281008","281008"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141405","2019-09-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the timeframe is for patent foraman ovale closure, for the prevention of recurrent cerebral embolic stroke in adults, to be available on the NHS.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280945","280945"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141406","2019-07-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what representations the Government has received from representatives of (a) food companies and (b) food bank organisers on the worst-case effect on food supplies of the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281009","281009"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141407","2019-07-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether the legal responsibility of local authorities to provide food in a time of crisis extends to (a) children, (b) people on a low income, (c) elderly people, (d) disabled people and (e) housebound people.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281010","281010"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141408","2019-07-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps the Government has taken to involve (a) food surplus re-distributors and (b) frontline charities that feed vulnerable groups including (i) homeless shelters, (ii) domestic violence refuges, (iii) mental health groups in supply chain conversations and planning in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281011","281011"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141409","2019-07-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans the Government has to undertake a public awareness campaign on the effect on food (a) supply and (b) prices of the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281012","281012"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141410","2019-09-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many Primary Care Networks are being established; where those networks will be located; how many patients those networks will be responsible for; and what assessment he has made of the effect of those networks on the commissioning of bladder, bowel and continence care services.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281013","281013"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141411","2019-09-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether Primary Care Networks will have responsibility for the implementation of the NHS England Excellence in Continence Care guidelines.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281014","281014"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141412","2019-09-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether Primary Care Networks will be allocated a (a) physiotherapist responsible for pelvic floor health, (b) social prescriber and (c) continence nurse.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281015","281015"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141413","2019-09-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what progress has been made on the NHS England Excellence in Continence Care Board's work with the supply chain on the National Bladder and Bowel Health Project.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281016","281016"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141414","2019-07-25","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 20 June 2019 to Question 263865 on permitted development rights, what assessment he has made of the implications for the quality of new homes of the lack of minimum standards in Building Regulations for (a) space and (b) daylight; and if he will undertake to review those regulations.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281098","281098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141415","2019-07-25","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of (a) incentivising or requiring housebuilders to monitor and collect data on the performance of homes post-occupancy and (b) requiring housebuilders to publish that information.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281099","281099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141416","2019-07-25","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to research by the Local Government Association showing that prosecutions under building regulations have fallen by approximately 75 per cent in the last 10 years what plans he has (a) to increase sanctions and penalties for non-compliance with building regulations and (b) to ensure that local authorities are awarded full costs for such cases.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281100","281100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141417","2019-07-25","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of bringing forward legislative proposals to ensure that planning permission is time limited to prevent completions being built to superceded building regulations.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281101","281101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141418","2019-07-25","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to implement the policy recommendations made by the Committee on Climate Change in its report entitled UK housing: Fit for the future on adapting the UK’s housing stock to the impacts of climate change.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281102","281102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141419","2019-09-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he plans to expand NHS provision of screenings for new-born babies.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280946","280946"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141420","2019-09-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many residents in the London Borough of Sutton are aged 75 or over; and what proportion of those people are (a) eligible for and (b) claiming pension credit.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280900","280900"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141421","2019-07-25","Department for Education","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions he has had with universities on the effect of higher education funding on the sustainability of STEM courses in (a) Portsmouth and (b) the UK.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281103","281103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141422","2019-07-25","Department for Education","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the effect on funding for STEM subjects at higher education institutions of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281104","281104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141423","2019-07-25","Department for Education","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the gender pay gap in higher education (a) at Portsmouth University and (b) in the UK.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281105","281105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141424","2019-07-25","Department for Education","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the effect on jobs of the decision not to support higher education institutions with increased pension costs (a) at Portsmouth University and (b) in the UK.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281106","281106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141425","2019-09-03","Treasury","2019-07-23","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what information the Treasury holds on the number of (a) free-to-use and (b) fee-charging ATMs in the London Borough of Sutton in each year since 2015.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280901","280901"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141426","2019-09-03","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate she has made of the number of households in the London Borough of Sutton in fuel poverty in each year since 2015.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280907","280907"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141427","2019-07-25","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 4 July 2019 to Question 270269 on the National Holocaust Memorial Centre and Learning Service, which operating models the United Kingdom Holocaust Memorial Foundation is considering to cover the running costs of the Holocaust Memorial and Learning Centre.","Biography information for Sir Edward Leigh","Sir Edward Leigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280914","280914"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141428","2019-07-25","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 4 July 2019 to Question 270272 on the National Holocaust Memorial Centre and Learning Service, what further studies commissioned by the Government are under way or planned to establish the extent of the tree roots which will be affected by the construction of the Holocaust Memorial and Learning Centre.","Biography information for Sir Edward Leigh","Sir Edward Leigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280915","280915"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141429","2019-07-25","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 4 July 2019 to Question 270274 on the National Holocaust Memorial Centre and Learning Service, if he will define the green space referred to in the calculation that around 85 per cent of the green space in Victoria Tower Gardens will be retained after the construction of the Holocaust Memorial and Learning Centre.","Biography information for Sir Edward Leigh","Sir Edward Leigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280916","280916"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141430","2019-07-25","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 4 July 2019 to Question 270267 on the National Holocaust Memorial Centre and Learning Service, if he will list the elements in the search for potential sites for the Holocaust Memorial and Learning Centre other than that conducted by the CBRE; and for what reason separate searches were undertaken for potential sites.","Biography information for Sir Edward Leigh","Sir Edward Leigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280917","280917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141431","2019-07-25","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 14 March 2019 to Question 229625 on the National Holocaust Memorial Centre and Learning Service, how many of the 24 possible sites for the Holocaust Memorial and Learning Centre reported by the CBRE to the board of the UK Holocaust Memorial Foundation on 11 January 2016 were not among the almost 50 possible sites identified between 7 September and 30 October 2015.","Biography information for Sir Edward Leigh","Sir Edward Leigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280918","280918"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141432","2019-07-25","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 4 July 2019 to Question 270268 on the National Holocaust Memorial Centre and Learning Service, which Ministers authorised representatives of the UK Holocaust Memorial Foundation to engage with Royal Parks on 2 December 2015 about the possible use of Victoria Tower Gardens for the Holocaust Memorial and Learning Centre.","Biography information for Sir Edward Leigh","Sir Edward Leigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280919","280919"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141433","2019-07-25","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, for what reason Royal Parks was not informed in January 2016 that the Government planned to build the Holocaust Learning Centre and the Memorial in Victoria Tower Gardens subject to constraints being overcome.","Biography information for Sir Edward Leigh","Sir Edward Leigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280920","280920"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141434","2019-07-25","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 15 July 2019 to Question 274442 on the National Holocaust Memorial Centre and Learning Service, what the membership was of the property sub-committee of the UK Holocaust Memorial Foundation from November 2015 to January 2016.","Biography information for Sir Edward Leigh","Sir Edward Leigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280921","280921"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141435","2019-07-25","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 15 July 2019 to Question 274442 on the National Holocaust Memorial Centre and Learning Service, on what date in November 2015 the property sub-committee of the UK Holocaust Memorial Foundation was asked to undertake a search of Government sites.","Biography information for Sir Edward Leigh","Sir Edward Leigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280922","280922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141436","2019-07-25","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 21 December 2018 to Question 203300 on the National Holocaust Memorial Centre and Learning Service, if he will require the UK Holocaust Memorial Foundation to publish the minutes of its meetings as a condition of receiving public funds and support.","Biography information for Sir Edward Leigh","Sir Edward Leigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280923","280923"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141437","2019-07-25","Department for Transport","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the implications for his maritime policies of the decision by international shipping company CMA CGM to reflag 40 vessels away from the UK Ship Register between February and April 2019.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281107","281107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141438","2019-07-25","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make an assessment of the implications for his policies of the recommendations of the All-Party Parliamentary Group on Sepsis Annual Report 2019; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281108","281108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141439","2019-07-25","Department for Transport","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the implications for his maritime policies of the figures published by Lloyds List Intelligence in June 2019 which showed that the UK Ship Register lost a third of its tonnage in the past 12 months.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281109","281109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141440","2019-07-25","Department for Transport","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions he has had with the Maritime and Coastguard Agency on changes to the UK Ship Register.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281110","281110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141441","2019-07-25","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure better use of data interoperability to identify patients most at risk of sepsis.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281111","281111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141442","2019-07-25","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the recommendations of the All-Party Parliamentary Group on Sepsis Annual Report 2019, if he will commit to commissioning a public awareness campaign on sepsis to (a) make more people aware of and (b) improve survival rates for people experiencing that condition.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281112","281112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141443","2019-09-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much her Department has collected through the Child Maintenance Service's (a) four per cent and (b) twenty per cent collection fees under Collect and Pay in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281113","281113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141444","2019-09-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much revenue her Department has collected through the Child Maintenance Service's £20 application fee in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281114","281114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141445","2019-07-25","Department for Transport","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 17 July 2019 to Question 275760, what assessment he has made of the effect of delaying the reassessment of the star rating of the strategic road network for the planning and resource allocation for major risk areas in Road Investment Strategy 2 between 2020 and 2025.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281115","281115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141446","2019-09-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the statement entitled Health and harmony: the future for food, farming and the environment in a green Brexit, published in September 2018, what steps his Department is taking to limit the costs for small land owners of the future environmental land management scheme.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281017","281017"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141447","2019-09-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps the Government has taken to reduce the complexity of environmental schemes for land holders.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281018","281018"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141448","2019-07-25","Department for Education","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 15 July 2019 to Question 273801 on Child Exploitation, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of implementing a contextual safeguarding framework to be used alongside other safeguarding models within the child protection system in order to better identify and support children being exploited.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281116","281116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141449","2019-07-25","Department for Education","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 15 July 2019 to Question 273801 on Child Exploitation, if his Department will take steps to ensure that (a) local authorities and (b) police forces collect data on children at risk of criminal exploitation within their areas.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281117","281117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141450","2019-09-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the evidential base is for the Government's proposal to apply zero rate tariffs for eggs and egg products.","Biography information for Jenny Chapman","Jenny Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281019","281019"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141451","2019-07-25","Department for Education","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans he has to maintain food supplies for school dinners in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281020","281020"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141452","2019-09-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the removal of student bursaries on differences in trends of the number of (a) students, (b) mature students and (c) part-time students on nursing courses in England.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281118","281118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141453","2019-09-03","Department for Education","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps the Office for Students has taken since its establishment to assess the adequacy of provision of mental health services and student support at universities.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281119","281119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141454","2019-09-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the gross amount was of funding made available for footpath maintenance in England in the 2018-19 financial year.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281120","281120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141455","2019-09-03","Department for Transport","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the number of instances where a driver’s details have been released to a controlled third party by the DVLA in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281121","281121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141456","2019-09-03","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if his Department will conduct an impact assessment of the potential effects of extending statutory maternity and paternity leave for parents with ill or premature babies.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281122","281122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141457","2019-09-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent steps his Department has taken to improve patient accessibility to medical cannabis.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280947","280947"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141458","2019-09-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with the Chinese Government on the alleged practice of forced organ harvesting in that country; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280924","280924"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141459","2019-09-03","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the Written Statement of 22 July 2019, Enforcement Update, HCWS 1776, what barriers in the current complaints system may deter people from making a complaint.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281123","281123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141460","2019-07-25","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to encourage health and wellbeing boards to measure and monitor children's subjective well-being as a key outcome in their local area.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280948","280948"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141461","2019-09-03","Department for Education","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many organisations are Investors in People accredited.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280949","280949"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141462","2019-07-25","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many (a) male adults, (b) female adults, (c) male children and (d) female children were diagnosed with a mental illness in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280950","280950"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141463","2019-09-03","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to Written Statement of 22 July 2019 on Enforcement Update, HCWS 1776, whether he has plans to increase the regulation of enforcement agents before work performed by civilian enforcement officers is put out to tender.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281124","281124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141464","2019-09-03","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the Written Statement of 22 July 2019 on Enforcement Update, HCWS 1776, whether he plans to consult staff trades unions before strengthening the regulation of enforcement agents.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281125","281125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141465","2019-09-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to ensure the delivery of the software required for the implementation of the Birmingham Clean Air Zone by February 2020.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280951","280951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141466","2019-09-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he plans to provide support to Birmingham City Council to implement a system to collect payment for the Clean Air Zone.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280952","280952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141467","2019-09-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his international counterparts on the (a) forced harvesting of and (b) trade in human organs; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280925","280925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141468","2019-09-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether the Government plans to pass on any fines Birmingham City Council may incur as a result of breaches in air quality attributable to the late implementation of the charging Clean Air Zone.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280953","280953"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141469","2019-09-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether he plans to bring forward legislative proposals to require employers to provide sun cream for employees that predominantly work outdoors.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280954","280954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141470","2019-07-25","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what progress has been made in restoring shooting to the range of sports in the Commonwealth Games.","Biography information for Stephen Kerr","Stephen Kerr","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281126","281126"
