"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45184","2014-03-31","HM Treasury","2014-03-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the costs to the public purse of the introduction of the pensioner bond in each of the next 20 financial years.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193912","193912"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45185","2014-03-31","HM Treasury","2014-03-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much income tax relief was payable in respect of personal pension contributions for income taxed at (a) 40 per cent and (b) 20 per cent in 2012-13; and how many people in each category received such relief.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193743","193743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45186","2014-03-31","HM Treasury","2014-03-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much gift aid was reclaimed by charities in (a) 2009 and (b) 2013.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193744","193744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45187","2014-03-31","Cabinet Office","2014-03-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the average personal savings in each year from 2010 to 2013.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193745","193745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45188","2014-03-31","HM Treasury","2014-03-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he has taken to ensure that free and impartial guidance will be available to (a) drawing down their pensions at 55 and (b) taking partial retirement.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193747","193747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45189","2014-03-31","HM Treasury","2014-03-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he expects personal current account customers to be able to access transactional data on their account in a standardised and downloadable format for use as a comparison tool.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193797","193797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45190","2014-03-31","HM Treasury","2014-03-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when the Prudential Regulation Authority and the Financial Conduct Authority will publish a review of their work on removing barriers to entry and expansion in retail banking.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193798","193798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45191","2014-03-31","HM Treasury","2014-03-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when the Payment Systems Regulator will launch its market study into the ownership of payment systems by the largest banks.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193799","193799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45192","2014-03-31","HM Treasury","2014-03-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what impact assessment he has made of his plans to introduce electronic Vehicle Excise Duty on (a) companies that trade cars and (b) the sale of second-hand cars; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193786","193786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45193","2014-03-31","HM Treasury","2014-03-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether flats will be liable for the possible introduction of a levy on higher value homes.","Biography information for Mr James Clappison","Mr James Clappison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193787","193787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45194","2014-03-31","HM Treasury","2014-03-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when the Financial Conduct Authority will publish the results of its review into the effectiveness of the Current Account Switching Service.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193796","193796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45195","2014-03-31","HM Treasury","2014-03-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 24 March 2014, Official Report, column 12W, on individual savings accounts and with reference to HM Revenue and Custom's policy paper published on the new ISA and changes to Junior ISA and the Child Trust Fund, what assessment he has made of the consequences for (a) the economy, (b) capital markets and (c) business of a shift in savings portfolio composition away from securities towards cash.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193987","193987"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45196","2014-03-31","HM Treasury","2014-03-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps the Government has taken to ensure that investment trusts are excluded from legislation on packaged retail investment products presently being considered by the European Parliament.","Biography information for Mr John Baron","Mr John Baron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193988","193988"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45197","2014-03-31","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to paragraph 025 of the section entitled Viability in his Department's online National Planning Policy Guidance, what the different funding mechanisms available are.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193998","193998"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45198","2014-03-31","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what progress he has made on measures to allow town and parish councils to send agendas electronically.","Biography information for Andy Sawford","Andy Sawford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193805","193805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45199","2014-03-31","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many deaths in fires in domestic properties in England there were in each year since 1999.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193770","193770"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45200","2014-03-31","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will review the effectiveness of the regulations covering the installation of carbon monoxide detectors in homes.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193742","193742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45201","2014-03-31","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 26 February 2014, Official Report, column 358W, on land drainage, for what reasons responsibility for maintaining balancing tanks and sustainable urban development systems is to be given to county or unitary authorities rather than to local planning authorities; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193910","193910"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45202","2014-03-31","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the likely effect of the Community Infrastructure Levy (Amendment) Regulations 2014 on the amount of Community Infrastructure Levy collected.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193888","193888"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45203","2014-03-31","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what his most recent assessment is of the success of the zero carbon homes policy; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193886","193886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45204","2014-03-31","Home Office","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent steps she has taken to help local authorities control the sale of legal highs.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193902","193902"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45205","2014-03-31","Cabinet Office","2014-03-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 25 November 2013, Official Report, columns 80-1W, on Electoral Register, if his Department will use information gathered on the amount spent by local authorities on voter registration to inform policy on registration levels.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193857","193857"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45206","2014-03-31","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the prevalence of wind turbine developers using the Community Right to Build scheme to circumvent the local planning process.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193840","193840"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45207","2014-03-31","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what guidance his Department provides on how much funding from the Local Government Finance Settlement local authorities should allocate to virtual headteachers.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193878","193878"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45208","2014-03-31","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what proportion of employees in his Department of each (a) Civil Service pay grade and (b) gender work (i) reduced hours, (ii) flexi-time, (iii) from home, (iv) a compressed working week, (v) job share, (vi) term-time only and (vii) part-time.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193958","193958"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45209","2014-03-31","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 26 February 2014, Official Report, column 558W, on land drainage, what funding will be made available to SuDS Approving Bodies to enable them to maintain balancing tanks and sustainable urban drainage systems; who will be responsible for providing that funding; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193909","193909"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45210","2014-03-31","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Government Response to Lord Heseltine's report No Stone Unturned: in Pursuit of Growth, when he expects to publish a draft legislative reform order to ensure that the current legislation on combined authorities is fit for purpose.","Biography information for Andy Sawford","Andy Sawford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193920","193920"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45211","2014-03-31","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what proportion of employees in her Department of each (a) Civil Service pay grade and (b) gender work (i) reduced hours, (ii) flexi-time, (iii) from home, (iv) a compressed working week, (v) job share, (vi) term-time only and (vii) part-time.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193959","193959"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45212","2014-03-31","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions she has had with representatives of boxing in Northern Ireland on the choice of which country they represent at international competitions level.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193858","193858"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45213","2014-03-31","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how long betting shops are given by the Gambling Commission to comply with the requirements surrounding their primary gambling activity.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193829","193829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45214","2014-03-31","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many betting shops have had their licences revoked in each year since 2005; and what the reasons were in each such case.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193830","193830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45215","2014-03-31","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to her Answer of 25 March 2014, Official Report, columns 165-6W, on art: finance, what proportion of the total funding given by her Department's public bodies was used to support creative industries in (a) London and (b) Greater Manchester in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193877","193877"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45216","2014-03-31","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what action the Gambling Commission takes with licensed operators where provision of betting facilities appears non-compliant with primary gambling activity measures.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193884","193884"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45217","2014-03-31","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if she will define primary gambling activity criteria to identify the extent to which betting shops rely on non-betting activities.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193882","193882"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45218","2014-03-31","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what meetings officials in her Department have had with officials from the Department for Business, Innovations and Skills on the implications of the Consumer Rights Bill for (a) licence fee payers and (b) the BBC; and what the Civil Service grades of officials present were.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193794","193794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45219","2014-03-31","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with which small and medium-sized companies in Wales his Department has contracted in each year since 2010; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193776","193776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45220","2014-03-31","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 13 March 2014 to the hon. Member for Crawley, Official Report, column 219W, on War Memorials: World War II, what the reasons are for the disparities between the income per visitor from grant-in-aid and LIBOR fines allocated to the (a) Royal Navy Museum, (b) National Army Museum, (c) Royal Air Force Museum and (d) National Memorial Arboretum; if he will take steps to reduce such disparities in future; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Michael Fabricant","Michael Fabricant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193763","193763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45221","2014-03-31","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the origins are of the NATO target for allies to spend two per cent of gross domestic product on defence; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lord Arbuthnot of Edrom","Mr James Arbuthnot","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193766","193766"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45222","2014-03-31","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Chancellor of the Exchequer's Budget Statement on 19 March 2014, Official Report, column 784, what effect making departmental underspends permanent and locked-in will have on his Department's budgetary assumptions in relation to his Department's (a) revenue and (b) capital budget until 2015-16.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193911","193911"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45223","2014-03-31","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to his Answer of 17 March 2014, Official Report, column 534, what the date and location is of his planned small and medium-sized enterprise meeting in Wales; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193802","193802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45224","2014-03-31","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will introduce an online pension calculator for use by those who have left the armed forces.","Biography information for John Glen","John Glen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193844","193844"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45225","2014-03-31","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what proportion of employees in his Department of each (a) Civil Service pay grade and (b) gender work (i) reduced hours, (ii) flexi-time, (iii) from home, (iv) a compressed working week, (v) job share, (vi) term-time only and (vii) part-time.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193960","193960"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45226","2014-03-31","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-03-26","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, pursuant to the Answer of 20 May 2013, Official Report, column 443W, on electoral register, what progress he has made with private sector credit reference agencies on ensuring the completeness and accuracy of the electoral register.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193919","193919"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45227","2014-03-31","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-03-26","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, pursuant to the Answer of 28 January 2014, Official Report, columns 509-10W, on the Electoral Register, with which national organisations his Department is working to encourage people to register to vote.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193837","193837"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45228","2014-03-31","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-03-26","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, pursuant to the Answer of 28 January 2014, Official Report, column 510W, on the electoral register: young people, how the £4.2 million funding to maximise the rate of voter registration ahead of the transition to individual electoral registration has been spent; and what measures are in place to monitor the effectiveness of this spending.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193839","193839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45229","2014-03-31","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-03-26","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, pursuant to the Answer of 27 January 2014, Official Report, column 386W, on the Electoral Register, what is the (a) earliest and (b) latest age a person is allocated their National Insurance number; and what the earliest date is that an attainer can be registered to vote.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193836","193836"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45230","2014-03-31","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-03-26","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, pursuant to the Answer of 22 January 2014, Official Report, column 189W, on the electoral register: Northern Ireland, if he will discuss the lessons from the registration for schools programme in Northern Ireland with the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193838","193838"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45231","2014-03-31","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-03-26","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, with reference to the Answer of 3 September 2012, Official Report, columns 93-4W, on electoral register: fraud, what assessment he has made of the reasons there have been no successful prosecutions for postal vote fraud since 2011.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193880","193880"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45232","2014-03-31","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-03-26","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, pursuant to the Answer of 24 January 2013, Official Report, column 392W, on the Electoral Register if he will place in the Library a copy of the guidelines for the issuing of fixed penalty notices for non-registration.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193800","193800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45233","2014-03-31","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-03-26","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, pursuant to the Answer of 12 June 2012, Official Report, column 444W, on constituencies, what comparative assessment he has made of the accuracy of the (a) electoral register and (b) census.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193801","193801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45234","2014-03-31","Department for Education","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what meetings officials in his Department have had with officials from the Department for Business, Innovation and Skills on the implications of the Consumer Rights Bill for (a) childcare voucher users and (b) providers of childcare services; and what the Civil Service grades of officials present were.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193793","193793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45235","2014-03-31","Department for Education","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when (a) he and (b) Ministers in his Department last visited a private, voluntary or independent sector childcare setting in an official capacity.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193816","193816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45236","2014-03-31","Department for Education","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will list all academy sponsors with 10 or more academies. [R]","Biography information for Nick Gibb","Mr Nick Gibb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193818","193818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45237","2014-03-31","Department for Education","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of education standards in primary schools in Surrey. [R]","Biography information for Nick Gibb","Mr Nick Gibb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193815","193815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45238","2014-03-31","Department for Education","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the functional literacy rates were in each (a) local authority area and (b) region in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193804","193804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45239","2014-03-31","Department for Education","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what conclusions he has drawn from the 3D Printer Project Report for enriching teaching across STEM and Design subjects in schools.","Biography information for Neil Carmichael","Neil Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193768","193768"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45240","2014-03-31","Department for Education","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 24 March 2014, Official Report, columns 83-4W, on the School Information (England) (Amendment) Regulations 2012, if he will make an assessment of the level of compliance with those regulations among state-funded schools and academies.","Biography information for Nick Gibb","Mr Nick Gibb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193749","193749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45241","2014-03-31","Department for Education","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the number of children who are home-schooled in (a) Yorkshire and the Humber and (b) Brigg and Goole constituency.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193905","193905"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45242","2014-03-31","Department for Education","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when he will announce (a) additional funding for and (b) a help and advice service to schools on universal free school meals.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193900","193900"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45243","2014-03-31","Department for Education","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 12 March 2014, Official Report, columns 250-1W, on special educational needs, when he expects to make an announcement on the effect of reforms on funding for special educational needs.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193842","193842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45244","2014-03-31","Department for Education","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 18 March 2014, Official Report, columns 556-7W, on children in care, if he will place in the Library (a) the results of the virtual school head pilots conducted between September 2007 and August 2009 and (b) all training materials produced by his Department.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193843","193843"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45245","2014-03-31","Department for Education","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children received A* to C grades in GCSE (a) mathematics, (b) English, (c) geography and (d) sciences in Brigg and Goole constituency in each year since May 2010.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193906","193906"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45246","2014-03-31","Department for Education","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of employees in his Department of each (a) Civil Service pay grade and (b) gender work (i) reduced hours, (ii) flexi-time, (iii) from home, (iv) a compressed working week, (v) job share, (vi) term-time only and (vii) part-time.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193961","193961"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45247","2014-03-31","Department for Education","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the statement of 13 March 2014, Official Report, columns 427-9, on school funding, what the (a) total and (b) per-pupil funding for each local authority area will be for 2015-16.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193989","193989"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45248","2014-03-31","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what proportion of employees in his Department of each (a) Civil Service pay grade and (b) gender work (i) reduced hours, (ii) flexi-time, (iii) from home, (iv) a compressed working week, (v) job share, (vi) term-time only and (vii) part-time.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193962","193962"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45249","2014-03-31","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate he has made of the number of properties in (a) Brigg and Goole constituency and (b) Yorkshire and the Humber which do not have mains gas access and which use domestic heating oil.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193904","193904"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45250","2014-03-31","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate he has made of the number of houses in the UK that have solar panels.","Biography information for Iain McKenzie","Iain McKenzie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193737","193737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45251","2014-03-31","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate he has made of how many houses in the UK have an energy efficiency certificate.","Biography information for Iain McKenzie","Iain McKenzie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193738","193738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45252","2014-03-31","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate he has made of the average time it takes for householders who have installed energy efficient products in their property to recover their costs; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Iain McKenzie","Iain McKenzie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193739","193739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45253","2014-03-31","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what sanctions or remedies are available if energy suppliers do not end automatic run-overs of contracts for supplying energy to small businesses.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193790","193790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45254","2014-03-31","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many properties built after January 2009 were flooded in winter 2013-14; and what guidance his Department issues to homeowners who are declined insurance by their provider because of risk of flooding. [R]","Biography information for Nigel Adams","Nigel Adams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193817","193817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45255","2014-03-31","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what proportion of energy generation was produced through anaerobic digestion in each of the last three years; and what steps his Department is taking to increase the levels of energy production through that source.","Biography information for Mr Bob Ainsworth","Mr Bob Ainsworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193780","193780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45256","2014-03-31","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions he has had with his counterparts in African countries about numbers of (a) elephants, (b) rhinoceroses and (c) lions in those countries.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193755","193755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45257","2014-03-31","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will commission a study on measures to accurately record incidences of mis-stunning in abattoirs.","Biography information for Mike Freer","Mike Freer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193828","193828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45258","2014-03-31","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what proportion of employees in his Department of what (a) Civil Service pay grade and (b) gender work (i) reduced hours, (ii) flexi-time, (iii) from home, (iv) a compressed working week, (v) job share, (vi) term-time only and (vii) part-time.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193963","193963"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45259","2014-03-31","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what proportion of employees in his Department of each (a) Civil Service pay grade and (b) gender work (i) reduced hours, (ii) flexi-time, (iii) from home, (iv) a compressed working week, (v) job share, (vi) term-time only and (vii) part-time.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193964","193964"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45260","2014-03-31","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent reports he has received on the level of medical support given to victims of torture in Bahrain; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193848","193848"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45261","2014-03-31","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent reports he has received of reprisals against individuals who raise complaints with the Office of the Police Ombudsman in Bahrain; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193852","193852"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45262","2014-03-31","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent reports he has received of confessions obtained through torture being used as evidence in terrorism cases in Bahrain; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193849","193849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45263","2014-03-31","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received on the work and methods of the Special Investigation Unit in Bahrain; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193850","193850"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45264","2014-03-31","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assistance his Department has provided to (a) the Office of the Police Ombudsman and (b) the Special Investigation Unit in Bahrain since May 2010; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193851","193851"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45265","2014-03-31","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent reports his Department has received on breaches of medical neutrality and the supply of medical care for people injured by security forces in Bahrain; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193845","193845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45266","2014-03-31","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent reports he has received on the death in custody of Jaffar al Durazi in Bahrain; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193846","193846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45267","2014-03-31","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of progress by the government of Bahrain towards ending torture and abuse of detainees since 2011; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193847","193847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45268","2014-03-31","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent reports he has received of rocket fire by Islamic Jihad into Israel from Gaza.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193874","193874"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45269","2014-03-31","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the Palestinian Authority on recent comments by the senior Fatah official Ahmed Assaf on Dalal Mughrabi.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193873","193873"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45270","2014-03-31","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the Palestinian Authority on the publication on Fatah's Facebook page of maps depicting geographic Israel replaced by Palestine.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193872","193872"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45271","2014-03-31","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of which countries in Africa (a) have the highest incidence of illegal killing of wildlife and (b) have the largest illegal trade in wildlife with China.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193756","193756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45272","2014-03-31","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to the Palestinian Authority about reports that cultural and sporting events in the Palestinian Territories are named after Palestinian terrorists.","Biography information for Mr David Burrowes","Mr David Burrowes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193767","193767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45273","2014-03-31","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 25 March 2014, Official Report, column 189W, on the Nuclear Security Summit, which organisations made what suggestions to the UK's contribution to that Summit.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193807","193807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45274","2014-03-31","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Chinese counterpart on ending the illegal wildlife trade.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193754","193754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45275","2014-03-31","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment his Department has made of Iran's financial and material support for terrorist groups in the Middle East.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193773","193773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45276","2014-03-31","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the implications on regional security of the announcement by the Israeli Defence Force of the discovery of a tunnel extending 700 metres into Israel from Gaza.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193772","193772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45277","2014-03-31","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the commitment in the EU-Ukraine Association Agreement signed by the EU and the interim Ukraine administration on 21 March 2014 to a political dialogue designed to promote gradual convergence on foreign and security matters with the aim of Ukraine's ever-deeper involvement in the European security area reflects an EU policy objective of Ukraine eventually joining NATO; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193782","193782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45278","2014-03-31","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with the government of Mozambique on efforts to end violence against women; and what representations he has made on that country's draft criminal code which may allow those accused of sexual violence to avoid prosecution if they marry the victim.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193990","193990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45279","2014-03-31","Department of Health","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people were added to the organ donor register in Brigg and Goole constituency in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193907","193907"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45280","2014-03-31","Department of Health","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what refurbishments have been carried out by his Department since May 2010; what the cost of such refurbishment was by category of expenditure; what refurbishments are planned; and what the estimated cost is of such future refurbishments.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193985","193985"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45281","2014-03-31","Department of Health","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to ensure that the Medical and Healthcare Products Regulatory Agency does not destroy clinical trial data on drugs licensed over 15 years ago; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193986","193986"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45282","2014-03-31","Department of Health","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the statement in the NHS Confederation's 2015 Challenge, that it is very possible that the current basis of the NHS, free for all at the point of need, will become unsustainable in the future; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193982","193982"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45283","2014-03-31","Department of Health","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, on how many occasions the National Institute for Health and Care Excellence has not recommended a licensed treatment where an unlicensed comparator was used in the relevant health technology appraisal.","Biography information for Sir Kevin Barron","Kevin Barron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194018","194018"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45284","2014-03-31","Department of Health","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people (a) are and (b) are not registered with a dentist in (i) Cumbria and (ii) South Lakeland.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193992","193992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45285","2014-03-31","Department of Health","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what further steps he is taking to encourage the use of Fairtrade goods in catering in hospitals; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193993","193993"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45286","2014-03-31","Department of Health","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department has taken to raise public awareness of juvenile idiopathic arthritis among (a) GPs, (b) the general public, (c) school teachers and (d) schoolchildren in England.","Biography information for Mrs Linda Riordan","Mrs Linda Riordan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193819","193819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45287","2014-03-31","Department of Health","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the quality and geographical provision of health services provided to patients with juvenile idiopathic arthritis in England.","Biography information for Mrs Linda Riordan","Mrs Linda Riordan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193820","193820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45288","2014-03-31","Department of Health","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Answer of 4 March 2011, Official Report, column 663W, on health professionals, if he will publish the robust evidence-based cost-benefit risk analysis of the regulation of unregulated healthcare professionals.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193771","193771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45289","2014-03-31","Department of Health","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what meetings officials in his Department have had with officials from the Department for Business, Innovation and Skills on the implications of the Consumer Rights Bill for (a) users of personal care budgets and (b) providers of personal care budgets; and what the Civil Service grades of officials present were.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193791","193791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45290","2014-03-31","Department of Health","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what research his Department has commissioned into Leber's Hereditary Optic Neuropathy in the last five years.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193777","193777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45291","2014-03-31","Department of Health","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment has been made of the effectiveness of the drug Idebonen in treating Leber's Hereditary Optic Neuropathy.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193778","193778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45292","2014-03-31","Department of Health","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to advance and promote transparency in the pharmaceutical industry in publishing data on drugs over 15 years old.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193813","193813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45293","2014-03-31","Department of Health","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many NHS staff in (a) Warrington, (b) the North West and (c) England who have been made redundant since 2010 have since been re-employed by the NHS on (i) a permament basis, (ii) on a fixed-term contract and (iii) as consultants.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193814","193814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45294","2014-03-31","Department of Health","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what account he has taken of the decision by the Belgian government not to pursue a policy of standard packaging of tobacco.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193769","193769"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45295","2014-03-31","Department of Health","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to prevent incidents of self-harm in the under-18 years old age group.","Biography information for Gavin Williamson","Gavin Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193752","193752"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45296","2014-03-31","Department of Health","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he plans to take to ensure that clinical data from pharmaceutical companies on drugs over 15 years old is made available to clinical researchers.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193812","193812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45297","2014-03-31","Department of Health","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the current arrangements for donor lung allocation for people with cystic fibrosis.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193764","193764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45298","2014-03-31","Department of Health","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions he has had with (a) the British Medical Association and (b) GPs' representatives about over prescription of antibiotics.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193759","193759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45299","2014-03-31","Department of Health","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people were diagnosed with sepsis in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193760","193760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45300","2014-03-31","Department of Health","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what consideration he has given to holding surgeries and awareness events on men's health at sports clubs and public houses.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193761","193761"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45301","2014-03-31","Department of Health","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many babies were born with Group B streptococcus in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193775","193775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45302","2014-03-31","Department of Health","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Statement of 18 July 2013, Official Report, columns 125-6WS, on NHS modernisation (costs and benefits), if he will publish a detailed breakdown of the (a) gross savings over the transition period and (b) long-term annual savings.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193748","193748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45303","2014-03-31","Department of Health","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to improve respite care provision in (a) Peterborough and (b) England; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stewart Jackson","Mr Stewart Jackson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193860","193860"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45304","2014-03-31","Department of Health","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress has been made on the Distressed Economy Strategic Review in the NHS in North Staffordshire; when that review will report; and what the terms of reference of that review are.","Biography information for Joan Walley","Joan Walley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193889","193889"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45305","2014-03-31","Department of Health","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what representations he intends to make to the National Institute for Health and Care Excellence on the use of ipilimumab as a first line treatment for advanced melanoma.","Biography information for Mrs Pauline Latham","Pauline Latham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193885","193885"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45306","2014-03-31","Department of Health","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidance his Department offers to clinical commissioning groups on how they should best use the NICE breast cancer quality standard.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193853","193853"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45307","2014-04-01","Department of Health","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the views of the National Institute for Health and Care Excellence on the survival benefit of dacabazine as a first line treatment for advanced melanoma; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Pauline Latham","Pauline Latham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193951","193951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45308","2014-03-31","Department of Health","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of employees in his Department of what (a) Civil Service pay grade and (b) gender work (i) reduced hours, (ii) flexi-time, (iii) from home, (iv) a compressed working week, (v) job share, (vi) term-time only and (vii) part-time.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193966","193966"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45309","2014-03-31","Home Office","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of employees in her Department of what (a) Civil Service pay grade and (b) gender work (i) reduced hours, (ii) flexi-time, (iii) from home, (iv) a compressed working week, (v) job share, (vi) term-time only and (vii) part-time.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193967","193967"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45310","2014-03-31","Home Office","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will redraft the code governing detention of teenagers under the Police and Criminal Evidence Act 1984 to ensure that 17 year olds in custody are treated as teenagers by the police.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193901","193901"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45311","2014-03-31","Home Office","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many maximum fines have been levied under the Immigration (Employment of Adults, Subject to Immigration Control) (Maximum Penalty) Order 2008 in each year since it was enacted.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193753","193753"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45312","2014-03-31","Home Office","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what information her Department holds on the number of specialist refuge places for women from black and minority ethnic communities.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193806","193806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45313","2014-03-31","Home Office","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many deportation orders were issued to foreign national offenders in each year since 2010.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193808","193808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45314","2014-03-31","Home Office","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people held in immigration removal centres and who refused food or fluids have been transferred to prisons since May 2013.","Biography information for Sarah Teather","Sarah Teather","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193784","193784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45315","2014-03-31","Home Office","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what measures her Department has introduced in the last year to reduce the number of businesses employing illegal immigrants.","Biography information for Mr Bob Ainsworth","Mr Bob Ainsworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193823","193823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45316","2014-03-31","Home Office","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many contracts with her Department are held by Airwave; what the value is of each such contract; and when each such contract is due for renewal.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194012","194012"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45317","2014-03-31","Home Office","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent representations she has received about the use of water cannon in London.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194013","194013"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45318","2014-03-31","Home Office","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she has taken to ensure the Emergency Services Mobile Communications Programme delivers a cost effective network that meets the standards of security and resilience essential for mission-critical communications.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194001","194001"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45319","2014-03-31","Home Office","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assurances she has received from operators of commercially available mobile networks that the emergency services will be able to over-ride commercial or public traffic during emergencies.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194000","194000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45320","2014-03-31","Home Office","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions she has had with the Association of Chief Police Officers about proposals for the emergency services communications network to be operated on a commercially available network.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193999","193999"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45321","2014-03-31","Department for International Development","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether any Palestinian Authority civil servant has been refused UK aid payments on the grounds of links with terrorist organisations.","Biography information for Guto Bebb","Guto Bebb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193984","193984"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45322","2014-03-31","Department for International Development","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many portable kits for diagnosis of (a) HIV and (b) hepatitis her Department has delivered to Africa in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193757","193757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45323","2014-03-31","Department for International Development","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what funds her Department has allocated to each country in Africa to tackle wildlife crime.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193758","193758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45324","2014-03-31","Department for International Development","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what proportion of employees in her Department of what (a) Civil Service pay grade and (b) gender work (i) reduced hours, (ii) flexi-time, (iii) from home, (iv) a compressed working week, (v) job share, (vi) term-time only and (vii) part-time.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193968","193968"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45325","2014-03-31","Department for International Development","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what processes are in place to ensure that (a) individuals and (b) non-governmental organisations in the Palestinian Territories receiving UK aid payments are not associated with terrorist organisations.","Biography information for Guto Bebb","Guto Bebb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193825","193825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45326","2014-03-31","Department for International Development","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what processes are in place to ensure Palestinian Authority civil servants in receipt of UK aid payments are not associated with terrorist organisations and have no previous record of terror offences.","Biography information for Guto Bebb","Guto Bebb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193826","193826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45327","2014-03-31","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the target time is for a decision on an application for compensation.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193876","193876"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45328","2014-03-31","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of employees in his Department of what (a) Civil Service pay grade and (b) gender work (i) reduced hours, (ii) flexi-time, (iii) from home, (iv) a compressed working week, (v) job share, (vi) term-time only and (vii) part-time.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193969","193969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45329","2014-03-31","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many staff were employed by the Criminal Injuries Compensation Authority on (a) 31 March 2011, (b) 31 March 2012 and (c) 31 March 2013.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193899","193899"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45330","2014-03-31","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he has taken to ensure that the probation contracts in England and Wales are let without risk to the public or waste of public money.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193895","193895"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45331","2014-03-31","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been convicted of an offence under section 72 of the Sexual Offences Act 2003 where the offence committed corresponds to an offence which would lead to automatic inclusion in the children's barred list, with the right to make representations, under the Safeguarding Vulnerable Groups Act 2006 in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193918","193918"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45332","2014-03-31","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many people have been convicted of an offence contrary to section 42 of the Armed Forces Act 2006 which corresponds to an offence contrary to any provision specified in the table in paragraph 3 of the Schedule of the Safeguarding Vulnerable Groups Act 2006 (Prescribed Criteria and Miscellaneous Provisions) Regulations 2009 in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193734","193734"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45333","2014-03-31","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many senior decision makers were employed by the Criminal Injuries Compensation Authority in each region on (a) 31 March 2011, (b) 31 March 2012 and (c) 31 March 2013.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193735","193735"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45334","2014-03-31","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been convicted of an offence contrary to articles 43 to 54 of the Sexual Offences (Northern Ireland) Order 2008, in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193779","193779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45335","2014-03-31","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to his article published in the Daily Mail on 6 September 2013, what the evidential basis was for his statement that countless left-wing campaigners are using the judicial review system as a promotional tool.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193822","193822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45336","2014-04-01","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been convicted of an offence contrary to Articles 122 (1)(a) and 123 of the Mental Health (Northern Ireland) Order 1986, in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193809","193809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45337","2014-04-01","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been convicted of an offence contrary to sections 30 to 41 of the Sexual Offences Act 2003 in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193810","193810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45338","2014-03-31","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when he plans to Answer question number 191341, submitted by the hon. Member for Hyndburn on 10 March 2014 for Answer on 13 March 2014.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193788","193788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45339","2014-03-31","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many decision makers were employed for work in each region by the Criminal Injuries Compensation Authority on 31 March (a) 2011, (b) 2012 and (c) 2013.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193781","193781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45340","2014-03-31","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been convicted of an offence contrary to sections 142 or 143 of the Criminal Justice and Public Order Act 1994, where the offence was committed against a child, in each of the last four years, broken down by year.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193983","193983"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45341","2014-03-31","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been convicted of an offence contrary to section 4 of the Criminal Law Amendment Act 1885, in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193981","193981"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45342","2014-03-31","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been convicted of an offence contrary to sections 35 or 37 of the Sexual Offences Act 2003, where the person induced, threatened or received was a child in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194008","194008"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45343","2014-03-31","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been convicted of an offence contrary to sections 30, 34 or 38 of the Sexual Offences Act 2003, where the offence was committed against a child in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194009","194009"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45344","2014-03-31","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been convicted of an offence contrary to section 8 of the Sexual Offences Act 2003 in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194010","194010"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45345","2014-03-31","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been convicted of an offence contrary to sections 33 or 41 of the Sexual Offences Act 2003, where the person caused to watch the sexual activity in question was a child, in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194004","194004"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45346","2014-03-31","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been convicted of an offence contrary to sections 31 or 39 of the Sexual Offences Act 2003, where the person caused or incited to engage in sexual activity was a child, in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194005","194005"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45347","2014-03-31","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been convicted of an offence contrary to sections 32 or 40 of the Sexual Offences Act 2003, where the person who was present or in a place from which the person committing the offence could be seen was a child, in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194007","194007"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45348","2014-03-31","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the prison population was, by prison, on 19 March 2014; how many prisoners each prison was built for; and how many foreign national prisoners there are in each prison, by country.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194014","194014"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45349","2014-03-31","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent assessment he has made of the availability of books to prisoners; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193995","193995"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45350","2014-03-31","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been convicted of an offence contrary to section 36 of the Sexual Offences Act 2003, where the person who agreed to be present or in a place from which the person committing the offence could be observed was a child, in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194006","194006"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45351","2014-03-31","Leader of the House","2014-03-26","To ask the Leader of the House, how many e-Petitions have led to debates being arranged in the House since their introduction.","Biography information for Jake Berry","Jake Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193795","193795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45352","2014-03-31","HM Treasury","2014-03-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will ensure that HM Revenue and Customs refunds unnecessary payments of VAT on ISAs.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193774","193774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45353","2014-03-31","Northern Ireland Office","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what proportion of employees in her Department of what (a) Civil Service pay grade and (b) gender work (i) reduced hours, (ii) flexi-time, (iii) from home, (iv) a compressed working week, (v) job share, (vi) term-time only and (vii) part-time.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193970","193970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45354","2014-03-31","Home Office","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment has been made of the effect on Northern Ireland of recent changes to immigration rules in respect of Romania and Bulgaria.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193859","193859"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45355","2014-03-31","Cabinet Office","2014-03-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what proportion of employees in No. 10 Downing Street of what (a) Civil Service pay grade and (b) gender work (i) reduced hours, (ii) flexi-time, (iii) from home, (iv) a compressed working week, (v) job share, (vi) term-time only and (vii) part-time.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193971","193971"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45356","2014-03-31","Scotland Office","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what proportion of employees in his Department of what (a) Civil Service pay grade and (b) gender work (i) reduced hours, (ii) flexi-time, (iii) from home, (iv) a compressed working week, (v) job share, (vi) term-time only and (vii) part-time.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193972","193972"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45357","2014-03-31","Scotland Office","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what discussions the Government has had with the Scottish Government on the introduction of a Right to Move scheme for social tenants.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193789","193789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45358","2014-03-31","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2014-03-26","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, pursuant to the Answer of 29 January 2014, Official Report, columns 622-3W, on the Electoral Register: fraud, if the Electoral Commission will make an assessment of (a) the effect of the views of politicians and (b) statements by the Electoral Commission on public perception of electoral registration.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193832","193832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45359","2014-03-31","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2014-03-26","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, pursuant to the Answer of 29 November 2013, Official Report, columns 455-6W, on the Electoral Register, for what reasons the electoral commission has no plans to undertake a direct assessment of registration rates in specific university towns and cities.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193834","193834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45360","2014-03-31","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2014-03-26","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, pursuant to the Answer of 29 January 2014, Official Report, columns 622-3W, on the Electoral Register: fraud, what comparative assessment he has made of the level of concern about electoral fraud in the UK and other EU countries.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193833","193833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45361","2014-03-31","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2014-03-26","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, pursuant to the Answer of 29 November 2013, Official Report, columns 455-6W, on the Electoral Register, if he will place in the Library a copy of the Electoral Commission's review of public engagement strategies.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193835","193835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45362","2014-03-31","Department for Transport","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the expanded Air Development Fund announced in the Budget Statement 2014 will apply throughout the UK: and how that fund will operate in the devolved jurisdictions.","Biography information for Lord McCrea of Magherafelt and Cookstown","Dr William McCrea","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193868","193868"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45363","2014-03-31","Department for Transport","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what representations he has received from the Welsh Government or the Official Opposition on Barnett consequentials for Wales resulting from future High Speed 2 expenditure.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193879","193879"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45364","2014-03-31","Department for Transport","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much money has been spent on repairing potholes in (a) Harlow and (b) Essex since 2004.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193871","193871"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45365","2014-03-31","Department for Transport","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the proposed service pattern is for classic-compatible High Speed 2 trains serving Carlisle when (a) High Speed 2 phase 1 and (b) High Speed 2 phase 2 opens.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193890","193890"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45366","2014-03-31","Department for Transport","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what proportion of employees in his Department of what (a) Civil Service pay grade and (b) gender work (i) reduced hours, (ii) flexi-time, (iii) from home, (iv) a compressed working week, (v) job share, (vi) term-time only and (vii) part-time.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193973","193973"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45367","2014-03-31","Department for Transport","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans he has for Penrith North Lakes, Oxenholme Lake District and Lancaster to be served by classic-compatible High Speed 2 trains.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193891","193891"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45368","2014-03-31","Department for Transport","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will publish and place in the Library all correspondence sent in the last five years between the Welsh and UK Governments on electrification of the mainline between Swansea and London.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193785","193785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45369","2014-03-31","Department for Transport","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will take steps to ensure people who are currently employed by the Driver and Vehicle Agency receive training to enable them to take up local posts in other Government departments and public bodies..","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193762","193762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45370","2014-03-31","Department for Transport","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he plans to announce the findings of the Green Paper on improving the safety and reducing risks to young drivers.","Biography information for Andrea Leadsom","Andrea Leadsom","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193736","193736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45371","2014-03-31","Department for Transport","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department and the Highways Agency are taking to reduce the risk of death or serious injury to road workers on the motorway network.","Biography information for Lord McCrea of Magherafelt and Cookstown","Dr William McCrea","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193978","193978"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45372","2014-03-31","Department for Transport","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what commercial products his Department or the Highways Agency has mandated for use in road traffic management on the motorway network in the last 10 years.","Biography information for Lord McCrea of Magherafelt and Cookstown","Dr William McCrea","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193979","193979"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45373","2014-03-31","Department for Transport","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what progress his Department and the Highways Agency have made in delivering the Government's small and medium-sized enterprise procurement policy in road traffic management on the motorway network since 2010; what goods and services have been procured from which companies; at what cost; and what processes were used for the procurement of those goods and services.","Biography information for Lord McCrea of Magherafelt and Cookstown","Dr William McCrea","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193980","193980"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45374","2014-03-31","Wales Office","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what proportion of employees in his Department of what (a) Civil Service pay grade and (b) gender work (i) reduced hours, (ii) flexi-time, (iii) from home, (iv) a compressed working week, (v) job share, (vi) term-time only and (vii) part-time.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193975","193975"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45375","2014-03-31","Women and Equalities","2014-03-26","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what proportion of employees in the Government Equalities Office of what (a) Civil Service pay grade and (b) gender work (i) reduced hours, (ii) flexi-time, (iii) from home, (iv) a compressed working week, (v) job share, (vi) term-time only and (vii) part-time.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193965","193965"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45376","2014-03-31","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps the Health and Safety Executive has taken to enforce the Health and Safety at Work Act 1974 in respect of employees in the traffic management industry in the last 10 years for which information is available.","Biography information for Lord McCrea of Magherafelt and Cookstown","Dr William McCrea","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193976","193976"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45377","2014-03-31","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people received face to face guidance from the Pension Advisory Service in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193944","193944"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45378","2014-03-31","HM Treasury","2014-03-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of the planned changes to pensions for low and middle pensioner income.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193949","193949"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45379","2014-03-31","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effect of the planned changes to pensions on the investment strategy of the National Employment Savings Trust.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193950","193950"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45380","2014-03-31","HM Treasury","2014-03-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans the Government has to ensure that a range of good value financial options are available for those approaching retirement.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193934","193934"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45381","2014-03-31","HM Treasury","2014-03-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people received face-to-face guidance from the Money Advice Service in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193943","193943"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45382","2014-03-31","HM Treasury","2014-03-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate has been made of the total amount of pensions savings which will be withdrawn from pension schemes in each of the 15 financial years from April 2015.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193935","193935"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45383","2014-03-31","HM Treasury","2014-03-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of the planned changes to pensions on the operating budget of (a) the Money Advice Service and (b) the Pensions Advisory Service.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193945","193945"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45384","2014-03-31","HM Treasury","2014-03-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the capacity of the financial services sector to provide face-to-face guidance to 500,000 people a year.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193946","193946"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45385","2014-03-31","HM Treasury","2014-03-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of the planned changes to pensions on average returns from annuities.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193947","193947"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45386","2014-03-31","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effect of the planned changes to pensions on opt-out rates of auto enrolment.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193948","193948"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45387","2014-03-31","HM Treasury","2014-03-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of the planned changes to pensions on the costs of social care in old age.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193927","193927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45388","2014-03-31","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people who have been given a prognosis that engagement in work is unlikely in the longer term have been placed in the work-related activity group for employment and support allowance since October 2008.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193893","193893"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45389","2014-03-31","HM Treasury","2014-03-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of the planned changes to pensions on the housing market.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193929","193929"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45390","2014-03-31","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what measures he has in place to establish the extent to which work programme providers have assisted participants to improve their literacy and numeracy skills.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193894","193894"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45391","2014-03-31","HM Treasury","2014-03-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of the planned changes to pensions on opportunities for tax evasion by higher rate tax payers.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193928","193928"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45392","2014-03-31","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he made of the effect of the option for people to top up their state pension on state pensions expenditure.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193926","193926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45393","2014-03-31","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people on incapacity benefit who have been given a prognosis that engagement in work is unlikely in the longer term have been placed in the work-related activity group since October 2010.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193896","193896"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45394","2014-03-31","HM Treasury","2014-03-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the costs of providing free financial guidance to people at the point of retirement.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193930","193930"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45395","2014-03-31","HM Treasury","2014-03-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with the Financial Conduct Authority about changes in regulation of the financial services market to protect people accessing their pension savings at the age of 55.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193936","193936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45396","2014-03-31","HM Treasury","2014-03-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the change in the number of people who will rely wholly on the single tier state pension as a result of the planned changes to pensions from April 2015.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193921","193921"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45397","2014-03-31","HM Treasury","2014-03-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of the planned changes to pensions from April 2015 on the availability of long-term investment funds for infrastructure projects.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193922","193922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45398","2014-03-31","HM Treasury","2014-03-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the impact of the planned changes to pensions on the number of people relying on (a) housing benefit, (b) pensioner credit and (c) other means-tested pensioner support.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193937","193937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45399","2014-03-31","HM Treasury","2014-03-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what provision he has made for financial guidance for individuals on the planned changes to pensions.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193923","193923"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45400","2014-03-31","HM Treasury","2014-03-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of the planned changes to pensions on the need to reform pensions tax relief.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193938","193938"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45401","2014-03-31","HM Treasury","2014-03-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, who will provide face-to-face financial guidance introduced as a result of the planned changes to pensions.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193924","193924"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45402","2014-03-31","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effect of the planned changes to pensions on retirement incomes from private and workplace pensions.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193939","193939"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45403","2014-03-31","HM Treasury","2014-03-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the guidance which the Government is proposing for those who access their pension savings at age 55 will be available at the point at which they (a) withdraw from their pensions savings or (b) enter full retirement.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193931","193931"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45404","2014-03-31","HM Treasury","2014-03-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of the planned changes to pensions on (a) low, (b) middle and (c) higher income earners.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193925","193925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45405","2014-03-31","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of whether the unavailability of child benefit for 18 year olds in receipt of jobseeker's allowance is discouraging the take-up of traineeships.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193897","193897"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45406","2014-03-31","HM Treasury","2014-03-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of allowing people to withdraw pension savings at the age of 55 at a marginal rate of tax on the level of such savings.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193940","193940"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45407","2014-03-31","HM Treasury","2014-03-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to ensure that the guidance that people receive as they approach the point of drawing down their pension will be both sufficient and independent.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193932","193932"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45408","2014-03-31","HM Treasury","2014-03-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what provisions will be in place to ensure people retain assets to support them in very old age.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193933","193933"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45409","2014-03-31","HM Treasury","2014-03-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of the planned changes to pensions on the average cost of independent financial advice.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193941","193941"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45410","2014-03-31","HM Treasury","2014-03-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of the planned changes to pensions on the average cost of face-to-face financial guidance.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193942","193942"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45411","2014-03-31","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will extend the Welsh model of assistance offered to former Remploy employees setting up a business and not subject to TUPE provisions to England and Scotland.","Biography information for Teresa Pearce","Teresa Pearce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193917","193917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45412","2014-03-31","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many fixed-length sanctions of (a) high, (b) medium and (c) low level were imposed on jobseeker's allowance claimants in Scotland in each month from March 2013 to March 2014.","Biography information for Dr Eilidh Whiteford","Dr Eilidh Whiteford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193867","193867"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45413","2014-03-31","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, for what reasons his Department paid the majority of the support package for former Remploy workers to Job Centre Plus for a rapid response team; what that rapid response did to assist former Remploy employees; and what the outcome of that assistance was.","Biography information for Teresa Pearce","Teresa Pearce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193887","193887"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45414","2014-03-31","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, for what reasons the Community Support Fund for former Remploy employees was only accessible through a third party and what estimate he has made of how many eligible former Remploy employees did not make a claim because they were unable to do so themselves.","Biography information for Teresa Pearce","Teresa Pearce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193881","193881"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45415","2014-03-31","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, for what reasons the three year wage subsidy for former Remploy disabled employees transferring to a new employer was not available for new businesses set up for the purpose of employing disabled people formerly employed by Remploy.","Biography information for Teresa Pearce","Teresa Pearce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193870","193870"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45416","2014-03-31","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of sanctions imposed on jobseeker's allowance claimants in Scotland resulted from the recommendations of Work Programme providers between March 2013 and March 2014.","Biography information for Dr Eilidh Whiteford","Dr Eilidh Whiteford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193864","193864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45417","2014-03-31","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in Scotland applied for a hardship payment after being subject to benefit sanctions in each month from March 2013 to March 2014.","Biography information for Dr Eilidh Whiteford","Dr Eilidh Whiteford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193865","193865"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45418","2014-03-31","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of jobseeker's allowance claimants in Scotland were referred to the benefit sanctions regime introduced in October 2012 in each month from March 2013 to March 2014.","Biography information for Dr Eilidh Whiteford","Dr Eilidh Whiteford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193866","193866"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45419","2014-03-31","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what funding his Department has agreed to provide in future years for former Remploy Employment Services; and until what year such funding will continue.","Biography information for Teresa Pearce","Teresa Pearce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193869","193869"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45420","2014-03-31","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average waiting time for a work capability assessment is for claimants in (a) Torbay local authority area, (b) the South West region and (c) England.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193856","193856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45421","2014-03-31","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on the number of tenant evictions resulting from the decision to pay housing benefit direct to claimants rather than landlords.","Biography information for Mr Bob Ainsworth","Mr Bob Ainsworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193827","193827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45422","2014-03-31","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people who were temporarily exempt from the benefit cap due to their housing benefit being reduced were in temporary accommodation between April 2013 and January 2014.","Biography information for Stephen Gilbert","Stephen Gilbert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193740","193740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45423","2014-03-31","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many benefit claimants have been sanctioned for (a) four weeks, (b) three months and (c) three years (i) nationally and (ii) in Oldham in the last year.","Biography information for Mr Michael Meacher","Mr Michael Meacher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193750","193750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45424","2014-03-31","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many additional households in temporary accommodation became subject to the benefit cap on flow in each month between May 2013 and January 2014.","Biography information for Stephen Gilbert","Stephen Gilbert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193746","193746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45425","2014-03-31","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many households in temporary accommodation were subject to the benefit cap between 1 April 2013 and 31 January 2014.","Biography information for Stephen Gilbert","Stephen Gilbert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193731","193731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45426","2014-03-31","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many households in receipt of (a) income support, (b) jobseeker's allowance and (c) employment and support allowance were subject to the benefit cap between 1 April 2013 and 31 January 2014.","Biography information for Stephen Gilbert","Stephen Gilbert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193732","193732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45427","2014-03-31","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many single parents with a child under the age of five years old were subject to the benefit cap between 1 April 2013 and 31 January 2014.","Biography information for Stephen Gilbert","Stephen Gilbert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193733","193733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45428","2014-03-31","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment he has made of the capability of the Work Programme to provide adequate support to jobseekers with long-term medical conditions.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193765","193765"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45429","2014-03-31","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer to the hon. Member for Edinburgh West of 10 February 2014, Official Report, column 515W, on Remploy: Edinburgh, how many former Remploy employees from the Edinburgh site are working (a) less than 16 hours per week in paid employment, (b) less than 30 hours per week in paid employment and (c) in voluntary and unpaid positions.","Biography information for Teresa Pearce","Teresa Pearce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193821","193821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45430","2014-03-31","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many refuges are not classed as supported exempt accommodation for the purposes of housing benefit.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193783","193783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45431","2014-03-31","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 25 March 2014, Official Report, column 233W, on vacancies: internet, what additional checks and safeguards for jobseekers have been introduced in each year since the launch of Universal Jobmatch.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193824","193824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45432","2014-03-31","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps the Health and Safety Executive has taken to recommend or mandate the use of automated traffic management technology to lift and lay cones on the motorway network in the last 10 years for which information is available.","Biography information for Lord McCrea of Magherafelt and Cookstown","Dr William McCrea","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193977","193977"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45433","2014-03-31","Attorney General","2014-03-26","To ask the Attorney General, pursuant to the Answer of 24 March 2014, Official Report, column 40W, how many offences charged under section 14(1) and 22 of the Forgery and Counterfeiting Act 1981 reached a first hearing in magistrates' court in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194028","194028"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45434","2014-03-31","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether his Department is (a) undertaking or (b) plans to undertake a review of the check-off union subscription provision.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194032","194032"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45435","2014-03-31","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-03-26","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, with reference to the Answer of 19 June 2012, Official Report, columns 923-4W, on electoral register: fraud, how many successful prosecutions for electoral registration fraud there were in (a) 2012, (b) 2013 and (c) 2014 to date.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194030","194030"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45436","2014-03-31","Cabinet Office","2014-03-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether his Department is (a) undertaking or (b) plans to undertake a review of the check-off union subscription provision.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194033","194033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45437","2014-03-31","HM Treasury","2014-03-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether his Department is (a) undertaking or (b) plans to undertake a review of the check-off union subscription provision.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194048","194048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45438","2014-03-31","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether his Department is (a) undertaking or (b) plans to undertake a review of the check-off union subscription provision.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194034","194034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45439","2014-03-31","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what recent assessment he has made of the effect of reductions in local government spending on the effectiveness of fire brigades.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193997","193997"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45440","2014-03-31","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether he plans to change the contribution rates to the Firefighters Pension Scheme.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194054","194054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45441","2014-03-31","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what recent assessment he has made of the appropriateness of the current recommended age of retirement for firefighters.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194055","194055"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45442","2014-03-31","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the role of firefighters in responding to the recent floods.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194056","194056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45443","2014-03-31","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will bring forward proposals to impose on fire and rescue services a statutory duty to respond to flooding.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194057","194057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45444","2014-03-31","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether her Department is (a) undertaking or (b) plans to undertake a review of the check-off union subscription provision.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194035","194035"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45445","2014-03-31","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department is (a) undertaking or (b) plans to undertake a review of the check-off union subscription provision.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194036","194036"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45446","2014-03-31","Department for Education","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether his Department is (a) undertaking or (b) plans to undertake a review of the check-off union subscription provision.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194037","194037"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45447","2014-03-31","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if he will urge energy providers to offer unconditional price freezes.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194025","194025"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45448","2014-03-31","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether his Department is (a) undertaking or (b) plans to undertake a review of the check-off union subscription provision.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194038","194038"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45449","2014-03-31","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether his Department is (a) undertaking or (b) plans to undertake a review of the check-off union subscription provision.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194039","194039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45450","2014-03-31","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his Department is (a) undertaking or (b) plans to undertake a review of the check-off union subscription provision.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194040","194040"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45451","2014-03-31","Department of Health","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department is (a) undertaking or (b) plans to undertake a review of the check-off union subscription provision.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194041","194041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45452","2014-03-31","Department of Health","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, on how many occasions his Department has requested the National Institute for Health and Care Excellence to perform a technology appraisal on an unlicensed medicine; and on what basis such a request was made in each case.","Biography information for Sir Kevin Barron","Kevin Barron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194017","194017"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45453","2014-03-31","Department of Health","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of people in (a) Redcar and Cleveland, (b) Middlesbrough, (c) the North East and (d) England are registered organ donors.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194023","194023"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45454","2014-03-31","Department of Health","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what criteria are used by the National Institute for Health and Care Excellence to determine whether an unlicensed medicine is in established use within the NHS.","Biography information for Sir Kevin Barron","Kevin Barron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194019","194019"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45455","2014-03-31","Department of Health","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the timescales are for delivering the commitment in the 2014 Pharmaceutical Price Regulation Scheme for his Department to work with industry and the National Institute for Health and Care Excellence to support further consideration of issues and potential resolutions around the use of unlicensed comparators.","Biography information for Sir Kevin Barron","Kevin Barron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194016","194016"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45456","2014-03-31","Department of Health","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much his Department spent on works and refurbishments to offices allocated to Ministers in his Department in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193996","193996"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45457","2014-03-31","Department of Health","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the use by the National Institute for Health and Care Excellence of unlicensed comparators in technology appraisals on the regulatory incentives for the development of licensed (a) paediatric medicines and (b) medicines for rare diseases.","Biography information for Sir Kevin Barron","Kevin Barron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194020","194020"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45458","2014-03-31","Department of Health","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his Department's policy is on the use of unlicensed medicines in the NHS where licensed medicines exist.","Biography information for Sir Kevin Barron","Kevin Barron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194015","194015"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45459","2014-03-31","Department of Health","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many children (a) are and (b) are not registered with a dentist in (i) Cumbria and (ii) South Lakeland.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194021","194021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45460","2014-03-31","Home Office","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department is (a) undertaking or (b) plans to undertake a review of the check-off union subscription provision.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194042","194042"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45461","2014-03-31","Home Office","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussion she has had with Ministers in the Scottish Government on transitional arrangements to cover the potential gap between the UK Government opting out of EU justice measures and negotiating its re-entry into specific measures.","Biography information for Pete Wishart","Pete Wishart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194026","194026"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45462","2014-03-31","Home Office","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the potential effect on Scotland's justice system of the UK Government opting out of EU justice measures and then negotiating its re-entry into specific measures.","Biography information for Pete Wishart","Pete Wishart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194027","194027"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45463","2014-03-31","Department for International Development","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether her Department is (a) undertaking or (b) plans to undertake a review of the check-off union subscription provision.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194043","194043"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45464","2014-03-31","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether his Department is (a) undertaking or (b) plans to undertake a review of the check-off union subscription provision.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194044","194044"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45465","2014-03-31","Northern Ireland Office","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, if she will place in the Library a list of the members of the IRA who have been beneficiaries of the use of the Royal Prerogative of Mercy.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194053","194053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45466","2014-03-31","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been convicted of an offence under section 128 of the Mental Health Act 1959 where the offence was committed against a child in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194031","194031"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45467","2014-03-31","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been convicted of an offence contrary to section 72 of the Sexual Offences Act 2003, where the offence committed corresponds to an offence which would lead to automatic inclusion in the adults' barred list, with the right to make representations, under the Safeguarding Vulnerable Groups Act 2006, in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194024","194024"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45468","2014-03-31","Northern Ireland Office","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, who took the decision not to announce the use of the Royal Prerogative of Mercy in respect of members of the IRA in the London Gazette or the Belfast Gazette.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194052","194052"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45469","2014-03-31","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been convicted of an offence under sections 1, 2 or 3 of the Female Genital Mutilation Act 2003 where the offence was committed against a child in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194022","194022"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45470","2014-03-31","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many people have been convicted of an offence contrary to section 42 of the Armed Forces Act 2006 which (a) corresponds to an offence contrary to any provision specified in part 1 of the table in paragraph 1 of the Schedule  to the Safeguarding Vulnerable Groups Act 2006 (Prescribed Criteria and Miscellaneous Provisions) Regulations 2009 and was committed in circumstances specified in the entry in the second column of that part of that table which corresponds to the relevant entry in the first column of that part of that table or (b) corresponds to an offence contrary to a provision specified in part 2 of that table in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194029","194029"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45471","2014-03-31","Northern Ireland Office","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, for what reasons the use of the Royal Prerogative of Mercy granted in respect of members of the IRA was not announced in the London Gazette or the Belfast Gazette.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194051","194051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45472","2014-03-31","Northern Ireland Office","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, whether her Department is (a) undertaking or (b) plans to undertake a review of the check-off union subscription provision.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194045","194045"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45473","2014-03-31","Scotland Office","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, whether his Department is (a) undertaking or (b) plans to undertake a review of the check-off union subscription provision.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194046","194046"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45474","2014-03-31","Department for Transport","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department is (a) undertaking or (b) plans to undertake a review of the check-off union subscription provision.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194047","194047"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45475","2014-03-31","Wales Office","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, whether his Department is (a) undertaking or (b) plans to undertake a review of the check-off union subscription provision.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194049","194049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45476","2014-03-31","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether his Department is (a) undertaking or (b) plans to undertake a review of the check-off union subscription provision.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 194050","194050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45564","2014-04-01","Department of Health","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions he has had with the Health and Safety Executive on health and safety in NHS hospitals.","Biography information for Jesse Norman","Jesse Norman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 903440","903440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46159","2014-04-01","Department of Health","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if his Department will provide support for small rural GP surgeries additional to that provided through the new GP surgery funding formula.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 903442","903442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46160","2014-04-01","Department of Health","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress has been made by the taskforce reviewing the effects of the Working Time Directive on the NHS.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 903434","903434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/46161","2014-04-01","Department of Health","2014-03-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he has taken to improve patient choice in the NHS.","Biography information for David Tredinnick","David Tredinnick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 903438","903438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44940","2014-03-27","Attorney General","2014-03-25","To ask the Attorney General, if he will make it his policy to introduce the option of anonymity for victims of female genital mutilation in court trials.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193654","193654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44941","2014-03-27","Attorney General","2014-03-25","To ask the Attorney General, when the next inspection of the Services Prosecuting Authority is planned by HM Crown Prosecution Service Inspectorate.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193655","193655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44942","2014-03-27","Home Office","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many assets of criminal origin have been repatriated from the UK to jurisdictions overseas in each year since 2008-09.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193656","193656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44943","2014-03-27","Attorney General","2014-03-25","To ask the Attorney General, how many and what value of asset freezing orders have been enforced in the UK at the request of overseas jurisdictions in each year since 2008-09.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193657","193657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44944","2014-03-27","Attorney General","2014-03-25","To ask the Attorney General, what steps he is taking to ensure that victims of female genital mutilation whose cases go to trial have access to the full range of support and special measures that are available to victims of other sexual offences.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193653","193653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44945","2014-03-27","Attorney General","2014-03-25","To ask the Attorney General, for how many cases the Serious Fraud Office has sought additional funding from the Exchequer in the last two years; and on how many occasions such funding was granted (a) in part and (b) in full.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193705","193705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44946","2014-03-27","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the number of people in Kilmarnock and Loudoun constituency who are paid at least (a) the minimum wage and (b) the amount defined by the Living Wage Foundation as a living wage.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193706","193706"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44947","2014-03-31","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, which FTSE350 companies his Department has named and shamed for non-adherence to the Prompt Payment Code; and when each such action was taken.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193659","193659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44948","2014-03-31","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, which FTSE350 companies that he wrote to in November 2012 asking them to sign up to the Prompt Payment Code have failed to do so.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193658","193658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44949","2014-03-31","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent assessment he has made of the average amount owed to small firms in late payment.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193632","193632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44950","2014-03-27","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent steps his Department has taken to support the rail manufacturing industry.","Biography information for Jake Berry","Jake Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193532","193532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44951","2014-03-27","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many students were in higher education in Rossendale and Darwen constituency in 2013.","Biography information for Jake Berry","Jake Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193570","193570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44952","2014-03-27","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will limit the number of (a) alternative learning providers and (b) students studying at alternative learning providers over the next 10 years.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193607","193607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44953","2014-03-27","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent change there has been to the fair value of previously issued student loans; and what the current (a) face value and (b) fair value of existing student loans is.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193608","193608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44954","2014-03-27","Cabinet Office","2014-03-25","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what proportion of the working population of Rossendale and Darwen constituency is employed in the (a) public and (b) private sector.","Biography information for Jake Berry","Jake Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193530","193530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44955","2014-03-27","HM Treasury","2014-03-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he had with Atos and employers providing workplace-based childcare before the announcement of his policy on tax relief for childcare.","Biography information for Mr William Bain","Mr William Bain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193517","193517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44956","2014-03-27","HM Treasury","2014-03-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many cases of child benefit fraud his Department is investigating.","Biography information for Jake Berry","Jake Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193521","193521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44957","2014-03-27","HM Treasury","2014-03-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many HM Revenue and Customs staff were employed on detection of (a) tobacco and (b) alcohol smuggling in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jake Berry","Jake Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193522","193522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44958","2014-03-27","HM Treasury","2014-03-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what his Department's policy is on allowing officials to appear before all-party parliamentary groups.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193566","193566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44959","2014-03-31","HM Treasury","2014-03-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of the changes announced in the 2014 Budget Statement on the price of annuities; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193587","193587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44960","2014-03-31","HM Treasury","2014-03-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to paragraph 2.30 of Budget 2014, what the (a) total and (b) annual monetary value will be of the compensation package for higher electricity costs for energy intensive industries resulting from the Renewables Obligation and Feed-in Tariffs; what the eligibility criteria for this scheme will be; and what estimate he has made of the number of energy intensive industries that will meet these criteria.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193580","193580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44961","2014-03-31","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many energy-intensive industries have received compensation for the carbon price floor and EU Emissions Trading System to date; and what the total monetary value of this compensation was.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193581","193581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44962","2014-03-27","HM Treasury","2014-03-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make an assessment of the effects of the introduction of tax relief on childcare on existing employer-provided childcare schemes in each of the next four financial years.","Biography information for Mr William Bain","Mr William Bain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193535","193535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44963","2014-03-27","HM Treasury","2014-03-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will estimate the administration costs of the introduction of tax relief on childcare in each of the next four financial years.","Biography information for Mr William Bain","Mr William Bain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193536","193536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44964","2014-03-27","HM Treasury","2014-03-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will publish the guidance given to HM Revenue and Customs on how that body should exercise its new powers to directly remove money from an individual's bank account.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193549","193549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44965","2014-03-27","HM Treasury","2014-03-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps HM Revenue and Customs is required to take to prove that a debt is owed before officials directly extract money from a person's bank account.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193550","193550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44966","2014-03-31","HM Treasury","2014-03-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the number of families eligible for tax-free childcare in Brigg and Goole constituency.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193623","193623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44967","2014-03-27","HM Treasury","2014-03-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with Ministers in the Scottish Government on extending the scope of the existing Regional Air Connectivity Fund.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193664","193664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44968","2014-03-27","HM Treasury","2014-03-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the number of cathedrals that will benefit from the grant scheme for repairs announced in the 2014 Budget.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193665","193665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44969","2014-03-27","HM Treasury","2014-03-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with the Scottish Government on the allocation of funds from the Potholes Challenge Fund.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193666","193666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44970","2014-03-27","HM Treasury","2014-03-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the number of people who have utilised their full tax-free ISA allowance in each of the last three years in (a) the UK, (b) Scotland and (c) each parliamentary constituency.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193677","193677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44971","2014-03-27","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the number of energy intensive businesses in (a) the UK and (b) Scotland which will benefit from compensation for higher prices resulting from the renewables obligation and small scale feed-in tariffs.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193678","193678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44972","2014-03-27","HM Treasury","2014-03-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the likely costs to businesses of the introduction of a new one pound coin.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193682","193682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44974","2014-03-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 28 January 2014, Official Report, column 476W, on land: contamination, what proportion of the revenue support grant arises from a calculation of the cost to local authorities of fulfilling their duties under Part 2A of the Environmental Protection Act 1990.","Biography information for Joan Walley","Joan Walley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193553","193553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44975","2014-03-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many affordable homes have been (a) started and (b) completed in (a) Rossendale and (b) Darwen since May 2010.","Biography information for Jake Berry","Jake Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193548","193548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44976","2014-03-31","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to give local authorities powers to restrict the number of betting shops opening in their areas; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Clive Efford","Clive Efford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193727","193727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44977","2014-03-31","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many and what proportion of local authorities which registered for emergency financial assistance under the Bellwin Scheme as a result of recent flooding have received payment within 15 working days.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193630","193630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44978","2014-03-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he will publish the Government's response to the consultation on its commitment to implement zero carbon homes by 2016.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193636","193636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44979","2014-03-31","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what recent representation he has received on multiple occupancy properties.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193638","193638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44980","2014-03-31","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many multiple occupancy properties there were in the UK in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193639","193639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44981","2014-03-31","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will make an assessment of potential effect on a neighbourhood of houses being converted into multiple occupancy properties.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193640","193640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44982","2014-03-31","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of how many multiple occupancy properties do not have the correct licence.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193641","193641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44983","2014-03-31","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will make an assessment of the fire safety of houses converted into multiple occupancy properties.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193642","193642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44984","2014-04-02","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of the Ofcom voluntary code of practice on broadband speeds; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193662","193662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44985","2014-03-31","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions she has had with the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills and the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government on changes to planning regulations relating to betting shops and changes of use for business premises; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Clive Efford","Clive Efford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193728","193728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44986","2014-03-31","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, when she will hold the first meeting of the working party to discuss the future of football governance; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Clive Efford","Clive Efford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193729","193729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44987","2014-03-31","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, which Government departments will be represented on the working party to discuss the future of football governance; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Clive Efford","Clive Efford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193730","193730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44988","2014-03-27","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what targets have been set for the rollout of superfast broadband in Devon and Somerset; and whether Broadband Delivery UK has met those targets.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193602","193602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44989","2014-03-27","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what funding her Department makes available to allow non-elite disabled cyclists to acquire specialist sporting equipment.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193574","193574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44990","2014-03-31","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what guidance her Department has issued to local authorities on support for community-run libraries.","Biography information for Sarah Teather","Sarah Teather","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193592","193592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44991","2014-03-31","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what discussions he or officials of his Department have had with their US counterparts on the Annual Report of the US Defense Department Office of Test and Evaluation on the F-35 programme.","Biography information for Thomas Docherty","Thomas Docherty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193585","193585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44992","2014-03-27","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the timetable is for the introduction of the Type 26 Frigate.","Biography information for Jake Berry","Jake Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193523","193523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44993","2014-03-27","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the annual saving to the defence budget will be from the disbandment of the Second Battalion of the Royal Regiment of Fusiliers.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193518","193518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44994","2014-03-27","Home Office","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will place in the Library a copy of the report, The medical implications of vehicle-mounted water cannon with special reference to the Ziegler Wasserwerfer 9000 (WaWe 9) system, published by the Defence Science and Technology Laboratory in 2013.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193719","193719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44995","2014-03-27","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to ensure that the value for money assessment prepared for the closure of DSG Ashchurch is in accord with Joint Service Protocol 507; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193644","193644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44996","2014-03-31","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what pension cost saving has been made from the early termination of employment of armed forces personnel.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193625","193625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44997","2014-03-31","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what advice on pensions has been given to armed forces personnel who are made redundant.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193626","193626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44998","2014-03-27","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) allegations of, (b) investigations of, (c) prosecutions for and (d) convictions for (i) rape and (ii) sexual assault fell under the jurisdiction of the Service Police in Cyprus in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193650","193650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/44999","2014-03-27","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when the value for money report for the proposed closure of the DSG Ashchurch site will be produced; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193651","193651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45000","2014-03-27","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many personnel have been dismissed under AGAI 67 in each year since 2008; what the reasons were for each such dismissal; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193647","193647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45001","2014-03-27","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will place in the Library any legal advice his Department has received on the legality of the AGAI 67 internal sanctions regime; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193648","193648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45002","2014-03-27","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-03-25","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, What recent discussions he has had with ministerial colleagues about the Government's policy on devolution and decentralisation.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193672","193672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45003","2014-03-27","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-03-25","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, how many registered voters there are who are (a) Commonwealth and (b) Irish but not British citizens.","Biography information for Jake Berry","Jake Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193520","193520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45004","2014-03-27","Department for Education","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions he held with schools and local authorities for the purposes of drafting departmental advice on universal infant free school meals.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193601","193601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45005","2014-03-27","Department for Education","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, who is responsible for monitoring and approving the use of Government-funded credit cards by employees of Ofsted.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193569","193569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45006","2014-03-27","Department for Education","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to reduce absences from school due to bullying.","Biography information for Jake Berry","Jake Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193533","193533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45007","2014-03-27","Department for Education","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what records his Department keeps of use of Government-funded credit cards by employees of Ofsted.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193571","193571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45008","2014-03-27","Department for Education","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will make an estimate of the capital costs incurred by schools as a result of the implementation of universal infant free school meals; and whether the capital funding provided by his Department to schools to date covers such costs.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193576","193576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45009","2014-03-27","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many traineeships have been taken up in each parliamentary constituency since their introduction.","Biography information for Jake Berry","Jake Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193519","193519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45010","2014-03-27","Department for Education","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many people have entered (a) teacher training and (b) the teaching profession as qualified teachers in each of the last five years; and how many unqualified teachers have been employed in (i) England and (ii) North Yorkshire in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Baroness McIntosh of Pickering","Miss Anne McIntosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193524","193524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45011","2014-03-27","Department for Education","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether his Department issues guidance to local authorities on how best to make use of unutilized foster carers.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193526","193526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45012","2014-03-27","Department for Education","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to increase links between education and employment.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193671","193671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45013","2014-03-31","Department for Education","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the current level of teachers teaching ability whilst using tablet computers in primary schools.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193624","193624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45014","2014-03-31","Department for Education","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will issue to schools specific guidance on removing asbestos from premises.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193714","193714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45015","2014-03-27","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, when he expects the smart meter central delivery body to set out plans for assiting microbusinesses to use smart meters.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193679","193679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45016","2014-03-27","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps the Government plans to take to deliver the commitments on nuclear security contained in paragraph 27 of the Hague Nuclear Security Summit Communiqué held in the Hague on 24 and 25 March 2014.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193687","193687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45017","2014-03-27","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps the Government plans to take to deliver the commitments on nuclear security contained in paragraph 21 of the Hague Nuclear Security Summit Communiqué of the Nuclear Security Summit held in the Hague on 24 and 25 March 2014 to keep the national stockpile of separated plutonium to the minimum level.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193688","193688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45020","2014-03-31","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate he has made of the number of people who have switched energy suppliers in (a) Brigg and Goole constituency, (b) Yorkshire and Humber and (c) England in each of the last 60 months.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193622","193622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45021","2014-04-02","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps he plans to take to prevent leaks and improve monitoring at existing (a) in use and (b) extinct or abandoned onshore oil and gas sites.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193663","193663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45022","2014-03-27","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what (a) direct and (b) indirect bilateral funding arrangements his Department has with governmental or non-governmental projects and bodies in Argentina.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193646","193646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45023","2014-04-02","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many old oil and gas wells there are in the UK for which no firm or company is responsible; and how such wells are monitored for leaks.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193643","193643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45024","2014-03-31","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the contribution of the Minister of State of 3 March 2014, Official Report, column 725, on Government levies on energy bills, when he plans to present to the House the first annual report on consumer-funded policies, covering actual expenditure and forecast expenditure.","Biography information for Tom Greatrex","Tom Greatrex","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193691","193691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45025","2014-03-31","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the contribution of the Minister of State of 3 March 2014, Official Report, column 721, on Government levies on energy bills, what assessment he has made of the potential effects of a freeze of the carbon floor price on the number and capacity of projects that will be brought forward under the levy control framework.","Biography information for Tom Greatrex","Tom Greatrex","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193690","193690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45026","2014-03-27","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what his Department's policy is on allowing officials to appear before all-party parliamentary groups.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193555","193555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45027","2014-03-31","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, who has been appointed as a non-executive director of his Department since the publication of information on non-executive directors in his Department's Annual Report and Accounts 2012-13; what the date of each such appointment was; what annual fee is payable to each such person; what expenses and allowances each such person has claimed to date; and what other interests or employment each such person has.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193606","193606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45028","2014-03-27","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what his Department's policy is on allowing officials to appear before all-party parliamentary groups.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193556","193556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45029","2014-03-27","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the letter of 19 March 2014 from the Parliamentary Under-Secretary for Water, Forestry, Rural Affairs and Resource Management to the hon. Member for Torbay, what the evidential basis is for his statement that offering a water company funding for domestic users who happen to occupy business premises would risk such a payment being classified as state aid under European legislation.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193604","193604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45030","2014-03-27","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what evidence his Department has collected on the effect of badger culls conducted in Ireland on levels of bovine TB in that country.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193609","193609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45031","2014-03-27","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what resources are being allocated to prevent sheep rustling.","Biography information for Baroness McIntosh of Pickering","Miss Anne McIntosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193599","193599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45034","2014-03-27","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what facilities exist for the retention and care of non-native wildlife species confiscated in the UK; where those facilities are located; and how many times such non-native wildlife species confiscated have been returned to the people or location where they were first confiscated.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193703","193703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45035","2014-03-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations his Department made to the Spanish government on the Alcaidesa marina in La Linea; when such representations were made and by whom; and what further steps he intends to take on this issue.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193675","193675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45036","2014-03-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how much of the Alcaidesa marina in La Linea has been constructed in British-Gibraltar territorial waters.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193674","193674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45037","2014-03-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has been informed that the Alcaidesa marina in La Linea has been partly constructed in British-Gibraltar Territorial Waters.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193673","193673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45038","2014-03-31","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the Government plans to send representatives to the St Petersburg International Economic Forum; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193696","193696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45039","2014-03-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 28 February 2014, Official Report, column 525W, on Argentina, how much his Department has spent under each cost heading in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193652","193652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45040","2014-03-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received on the role and influence of South Sudan's neighbouring countries in the conflict in South Sudan.","Biography information for Stephen Mosley","Stephen Mosley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193645","193645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45041","2014-03-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will take diplomatic steps to respond to reports of violations of human rights and judicial processes in the simultaneous sentencing to death of 529 people in Egypt; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193616","193616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45042","2014-03-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he has taken to increase the number of UK embassies and consulates through co-operation with Commonwealth governments.","Biography information for Jake Berry","Jake Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193531","193531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45043","2014-03-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what role the UK's embassies and consulates play in preventing human trafficking in source countries.","Biography information for Jake Berry","Jake Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193547","193547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45044","2014-03-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will raise with his Egyptian counterpart the jailing of journalists for legitimate news reporting activities and the case of Mr Hossam Meneai; and if he will make representations calling for Mr Menaei's release.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193534","193534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45045","2014-03-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent reports he has received on the security situation in Bahrain.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193551","193551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45046","2014-03-31","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received on the plans of the Spanish government to grant Spanish citizenship to the descendants of Sephardic Jews who were expelled from Spain in the 15th century; whether he has made representations to the Spanish government on that matter; and if he will seek assurances about the capability and integrity of the proposed system for establishing eligibility for such grants of citizenship.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193598","193598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45047","2014-03-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what his Department's policy is on allowing officials to appear before all-party parliamentary groups.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193557","193557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45048","2014-03-27","Department of Health","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will commission national guidance on ensuring Parkinson's disease patients do not miss doses of their medication in hospital.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193605","193605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45049","2014-03-27","Department of Health","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his Department's policy is on allowing officials to appear before all-party parliamentary groups.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193559","193559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45050","2014-03-27","Department of Health","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what stomacare products were prescribed in each NHS hospital trust and primary care trust in England in each of the last five years by (a) product and (b) manufacturer.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193610","193610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45051","2014-03-27","Department of Health","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will estimate the resource implications of requiring all ambulance trusts to meet category A eight-minute response time in all rural locations.","Biography information for Andrew George","Andrew George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193611","193611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45052","2014-03-27","Department of Health","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what comparative assessment he has made of the performance of ambulance trusts serving predominantly (a) rural and (b) urban areas against the (i) eight-minute and (ii) 19-minute response time targets for category A patients.","Biography information for Andrew George","Andrew George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193612","193612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45053","2014-03-31","Cabinet Office","2014-03-25","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the mortality rate from cancer has been in (a) Brigg and Goole constituency, (b) Yorkshire and Humber and (c) England in the last 15 years.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193620","193620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45054","2014-03-27","Department of Health","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to review ambulance response targets for category A and category C call-outs.","Biography information for Andrew George","Andrew George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193613","193613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45055","2014-03-27","Department of Health","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many NHS staff in (a) Jarrow constituency, (b) South Tyneside, (c) Gateshead, (d) the North East and (e) the UK have been made redundant in each year since 2005.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193546","193546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45056","2014-03-27","Department of Health","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many individual funding requests for Fampridine have been made to NHS England since April 2013; and how many such requests have been approved.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193572","193572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45057","2014-03-27","Department of Health","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what calculations were used to assess the costs and benefits of using Fampridine to treat multiple sclerosis patients.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193573","193573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45058","2014-03-27","Department of Health","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will estimate the annual cost to the (a) NHS and (b) economy of people with multiple sclerosis who suffer from deteriorating spasticity.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193575","193575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45059","2014-03-27","Department of Health","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what powers clinical commissioning groups have to reduce missed GP appointments; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193603","193603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45060","2014-03-27","Department of Health","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many National Health Service staff in (a) Jarrow constituency, (b) South Tyneside, (c) Gateshead, (d) the North East and (e) the UK who have been made redundant since May 2010 have been re-employed by an NHS organisation on (i) a permanent basis and (ii) a fixed-term contract basis.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193528","193528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45061","2014-03-31","Department of Health","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the proportion of local authorities in England which have rescinded agreements made with NHS mental health trusts under section 75 of the National Health Services Act 2006 in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193631","193631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45062","2014-03-31","Department of Health","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 24 February 2014, Official Report, column 202W, on vaccination, which (a) Minister and (b) senior civil servant in his Department is directly responsible for vaccination and vaccination policy.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193637","193637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45063","2014-03-27","Department of Health","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether it is his policy that pregnant women resident in the UK will continue to have free access to NHS maternity services regardless of their immigration status.","Biography information for Mr John Leech","Mr John Leech","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193634","193634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45064","2014-03-27","Department of Health","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many abortion notification HSA4 forms have been referred to (a) to the General Medical Council and (b) the police following scrutiny by his Department since 2006.","Biography information for Jim Dobbin","Jim Dobbin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193618","193618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45065","2014-03-31","Department of Health","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of children in (a) Brigg and Goole constituency, (b) Yorkshire and Humber and (c) England were classed as overweight in each year since 1997.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193621","193621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45066","2014-03-27","Department of Health","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will review the (a) response time targets and (b) resources available for ambulance trusts which serve in largely or predominantly rural areas.","Biography information for Andrew George","Andrew George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193614","193614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45067","2014-03-27","Department of Health","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make a comparative assessment of response (a) outcomes and (b) times for category A calls for ambulance trusts in (i) rural and (ii) urban locations.","Biography information for Andrew George","Andrew George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193615","193615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45068","2014-03-31","Department of Health","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the proportion and number of people in England who have been medicated for psychiatric disorders in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193660","193660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45069","2014-03-27","Department of Health","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of proposed changes in the Immigration Bill on the role of GPs on the level of public trust in GPs; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr John Leech","Mr John Leech","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193635","193635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45070","2014-03-27","Department of Health","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress he has made in implementing (a) the National Cancer Survivorship Initiative recommendations and (b) the National Cancer Survivorship Initiative recommendation that services to treat complex problems arising from cancer treatment be commissioned on a national basis; and what assessment he has made of complex problems arising from bone marrow transplant in the context of such treatments.","Biography information for Jim Dobbin","Jim Dobbin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193649","193649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45071","2014-03-31","Department of Health","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that people are fully informed of the health risks of taking legal highs.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193689","193689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45072","2014-03-31","Department of Health","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of the timeframe within which it will be able to negotiate a cost-effective price for the meningitis B vaccine.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193692","193692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45073","2014-03-31","Department of Health","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the proportion of total funding for cancer research carried out in the UK that came from government in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12, (c) 2012-13 and (d) 2013-14.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193693","193693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45074","2014-03-27","Department of Health","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what sponsorship arrangements are in place between manufacturers of stoma care products and individual NHS trusts; and how many such arrangements were in place in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193680","193680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45075","2014-03-31","Department of Health","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many respiratory syncytial virus (RSV) vaccinations were administered in England in the last 12 months; what guidance his Department has issued on whether babies born prematurely or at risk of bronchiolitis should be given the RSV vaccination; and what assessment his Department has made of the potential benefits of administering the RSV vaccination to all babies born between November and February.","Biography information for Richard Harrington","Richard Harrington","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193698","193698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45076","2014-03-27","Department of Health","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the response outcomes were for each ambulance trust for category B calls in each of the 10 years for which records are available up to 2011.","Biography information for Andrew George","Andrew George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193685","193685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45077","2014-03-27","Department of Health","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer to the hon. Member for Congleton of 20 March 2014, Official Report, column 722W, on abortion, on how many occasions departmental medical practitioners have requested further details from a patient's medical records via the doctor approving termination in each of the last five years for which records are available.","Biography information for Jim Dobbin","Jim Dobbin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193683","193683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45078","2014-03-27","Department of Health","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whom he has appointed to undertake the NHS England Review into consultant-led obstetric maternity services at Stafford Hospital; and what timetable applies for (a) the final report and (b) decision by the Government.","Biography information for Joan Walley","Joan Walley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193707","193707"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45079","2014-03-27","Department of Health","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Written Statement of 26 February 2014, Official Report, columns 21-3WS, on Mid Staffordshire NHS Foundation Trust, what his assessment is of the clinical services changes which can occur ahead of the NHS England Report and Government decision.","Biography information for Joan Walley","Joan Walley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193708","193708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45080","2014-03-27","Department of Health","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the latest date is for the review to report acceptance of the Trust Special Administrator recommendations consistent with achieving University Hospital of North Staffordshire NHS Trust responsibilities for appropriate Stafford Hospital services by his deadline of Autumn 2014 as specified in the statement on Mid-Staffordshire NHS Foundation Trust Special Administration of 26 February 2014.","Biography information for Joan Walley","Joan Walley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193713","193713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45081","2014-03-27","Department of Health","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what representations he has received in respect of the situation following his acceptance in full of the Trust Special Administrator for Mid Staffordshire Hospital Trust's recommendation and additional decisions to instigate a review of consultant-led maternity services at Stafford.","Biography information for Joan Walley","Joan Walley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193711","193711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45082","2014-03-27","Department of Health","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the (a) financial viability and (b) medical safety of the Trust Special Administrator-provided services at Stafford Hospital pending the competition of the NHS England Review; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Joan Walley","Joan Walley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193710","193710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45083","2014-03-27","Department of Health","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what extra provision is being provided by (a) University Hospital of North Staffordshire and (b) other hospitals to enhance services at the Trust Special Administrator-run Mid Staffordshire Hospital Trust pending the outcome of the NHS England Review; and what the extra cost is of such provision.","Biography information for Joan Walley","Joan Walley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193709","193709"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45084","2014-03-31","Department of Health","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of trends in the incidence of quality failures in NHS hospital histopathology laboratories over the last five years.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193694","193694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45085","2014-03-27","Department of Health","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how long it will take for the University Hospital of North Staffordshire (UHNS) NHS Trust to complete all contractual commitments, including transfer of undertakings from Staffordshire Hospital to UHNS.","Biography information for Joan Walley","Joan Walley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193712","193712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45086","2014-03-27","Home Office","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the efficacy of the existing tactics in place for use of water cannon in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193723","193723"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45087","2014-03-31","Home Office","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the potential of water cannon to cause (a) temporary and (b) permanent injury.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193717","193717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45088","2014-03-27","Home Office","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many police officers in England are trained to use water cannon.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193722","193722"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45089","2014-03-31","Home Office","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what draft guidance on the instances where water cannon may be deployed has been (a) written and (b) consulted on.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193718","193718"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45090","2014-03-27","Home Office","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will review the appropriateness of water cannon tactics used in Northern Ireland ahead of their possible use in London.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193724","193724"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45091","2014-03-27","Home Office","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the cost of updating awareness training for public order-trained staff operating alongside water cannon.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193725","193725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45092","2014-03-27","Home Office","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will review the strategic policing requirement of water cannon based on planning assumptions around three spontaneous sets of disorder ahead of their deployment in London.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193726","193726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45093","2014-03-27","Home Office","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what information her Department holds on how many injuries have been associated with the use of water cannon in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193720","193720"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45094","2014-03-27","Home Office","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she plans to take to ensure that the temperature of water within a water cannon tank is retained at five degrees celsius.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193721","193721"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45095","2014-03-31","Home Office","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the maximum use period is of (a) a new water cannon and (b) a used water cannon of the type the Metropolitan Police Service wishes to purchase from Germany.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193716","193716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45096","2014-03-31","Home Office","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of (a) the cost of one water cannon, (b) annual storage costs of one water cannon and (c) annual maintenance costs of one water cannon.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193715","193715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45097","2014-03-27","Home Office","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department has taken in the last 12 months to reduce the burden of administration for the police.","Biography information for Jake Berry","Jake Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193681","193681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45098","2014-03-31","Home Office","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans the Government has to publish reports on the review of the balance of competences relating to EU migration; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193695","193695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45099","2014-03-31","Home Office","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have been arrested for breach of a forced marriage protection order in each year since such orders came into force.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193700","193700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45100","2014-03-27","Home Office","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans she has to reform anti-social behaviour orders; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Jake Berry","Jake Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193527","193527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45101","2014-03-27","Home Office","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will place in the Library a record of the regions and sub-regions within the UK subject to the highest number of refusals of people seeking a visa to study in institutions in the UK.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193529","193529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45102","2014-03-27","Home Office","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what her Department's policy is on allowing officials to appear before all-party parliamentary groups.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193560","193560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45103","2014-03-31","Home Office","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many unaccompanied migrant children have been forcibly removed to another country in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sarah Teather","Sarah Teather","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193591","193591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45104","2014-03-31","Home Office","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many asylum applicants receiving support under section 4 of the Immigration and Asylum Act 1999 have been receiving support for more than (a) two years, (b) four years and (c) six years; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sarah Teather","Sarah Teather","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193593","193593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45105","2014-03-31","Home Office","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she will announce the asylum support rates for 2014-15.","Biography information for Sarah Teather","Sarah Teather","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193594","193594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45106","2014-03-27","Department for International Development","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what her Department's policy is on allowing officials to appear before all-party parliamentary groups.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193561","193561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45107","2014-03-27","Department for International Development","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the World Health Organisation and United Nations Children's Fund report entitled Integrated Global Action Plan for the Prevention and Control of Pneumonia and Diarrhoea; and whether she intends to take the steps recommended in this report to support integrated healthcare solutions, incorporating water, sanitation and hygiene strategies.","Biography information for Jim Dobbin","Jim Dobbin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193676","193676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45108","2014-03-27","Department for International Development","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what support the Government offered for World Water Day 2014.","Biography information for Jim Dobbin","Jim Dobbin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193686","193686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45109","2014-03-31","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many forced marriage protection orders have been granted with a power of arrest attached in each year since such orders came into force.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193701","193701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45110","2014-03-31","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what calculations were used to calculate the mean fee income for full-time criminal barristers published by his Department on 2 January 2014; and for what reasons VAT was included in the estimate of barristers' earnings.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193702","193702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45111","2014-03-27","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what his Department's policy is on allowing officials to appear before all-party parliamentary groups.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193562","193562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45112","2014-03-31","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what his plans are for HMP The Verne.","Biography information for Sarah Teather","Sarah Teather","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193595","193595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45113","2014-03-31","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what restrictions, by category of prisoner, are placed on access to (a) a prisoner's own books and (b) books from the prison library in the first four weeks of a prison sentence.","Biography information for Lord Blunkett","Mr David Blunkett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193597","193597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45114","2014-03-31","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been convicted of an offence contrary to section (a) 1, where the victim was a child, and (b) 5 of the Sexual Offences Act 1956 in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193577","193577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45115","2014-03-31","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been convicted of an offence contrary to articles (a) 5 and 6, where the victim was a child, and (b) 12, 13 and 14 of the Sexual Offences (Northern Ireland) Order 2008 in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193578","193578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45116","2014-03-31","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been convicted of an offence contrary to sections (a) 1 and 2, where the victim was a child, and (b) 18, 19 and 20(1), (2)(a) and (3) of the Sexual Offences (Scotland) Act 2009 in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193579","193579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45117","2014-03-31","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been convicted of an offence contrary to sections (a) 1 and 2 where the victim was a child, and (b) 5, 6 and 7 of the Sexual Offences Act 2003 in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193582","193582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45118","2014-03-27","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, for what reason the rules governing the provision of books to prisoners have recently been changed.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193552","193552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45119","2014-03-27","Northern Ireland Office","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what her Department's policy is on allowing officials to appear before all-party parliamentary groups.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193563","193563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45120","2014-03-27","Northern Ireland Office","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what recent discussions she has had with members of the US Administration on recent developments in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193668","193668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45121","2014-03-27","Scotland Office","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what his Department's policy is on allowing officials to appear before all-party parliamentary groups.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193564","193564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45122","2014-03-27","Department for Transport","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what his Department's policy is on allowing officials to appear before all-party parliamentary groups.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193565","193565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45123","2014-03-31","Department for Transport","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans he has to review the National Rail Conditions of Carriage.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193586","193586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45124","2014-03-27","Department for Transport","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent estimate he has made of the number of schools that undertake cycling training; whether his Department provides information to schools on the wearing of cycle helmets by children; and if he will take steps to ensure that a Travel to School Policy becomes compulsory for all local education authorities in relation to schoolchildren and safety.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193554","193554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45125","2014-03-27","Department for Transport","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what compensation will be available to train operating companies as a result of the rail line closures in the South West of England in early 2014.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193600","193600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45126","2014-03-31","Department for Transport","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the (a) date, (b) amount and (c) reasons were for any fines or penalties his Department has paid to HM Treasury since May 2010.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193583","193583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45127","2014-03-27","Department for Transport","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he plans to take to relieve congestion on roads.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193669","193669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45128","2014-03-31","Department for Transport","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the potential economic benefits to (a) the North-West and (b) Warrington of further upgrading the West-East line as proposed in the HS2 Plus Report.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193697","193697"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45129","2014-03-31","Department for Transport","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect of a regional transport hub at Crewe on the proposal by Warrington Borough Council for an alternative route for the High Speed 2 line north of Crewe; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193627","193627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45130","2014-03-27","Department for Transport","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 24 March 2014, Official Report, column 4W, on railways: Chester, if he will hold discussions with the Secretary of State for Wales on the potential implications for (a) rail services in Chester and (b) Chester railway station of the recommendation in the report on the Commission on Devolution in Wales that the Wales and Borders rail franchise should be devolved to the National Assembly for Wales.","Biography information for Stephen Mosley","Stephen Mosley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193684","193684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45131","2014-03-27","Wales Office","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what assessment he has made of the growth prospects of small and medium-sized enterprises in Wales.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193670","193670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45132","2014-03-27","Wales Office","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what his Department's policy is on allowing officials to appear before all-party parliamentary groups.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193567","193567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45133","2014-03-27","Women and Equalities","2014-03-25","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what the Government Equalities Office's policy is on allowing officials to appear before all-party parliamentary groups.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193558","193558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45134","2014-03-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of average waiting times for Atos (a) personal independence payments and (b) work assessments in Beverley and Holderness constituency; and what steps he is taking to achieve a reduction in waiting times for such assessments.","Biography information for Graham Stuart","Mr Graham Stuart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193525","193525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45135","2014-03-31","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 18 March 2014, Official Report, column 547W, on the Work Programme, if he will place in the Library the draft findings of the Work Programme evaluation received by his Department in August 2013.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193596","193596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45136","2014-03-31","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, for what reasons he has not yet placed the business case for universal credit in the public domain.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193588","193588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45137","2014-03-31","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many personal independence payment applications have been processed in each month since April 2013.","Biography information for Tom Greatrex","Tom Greatrex","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193589","193589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45138","2014-03-31","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in receipt of jobseeker's allowance were sanctioned for failing to complete their job search evidence form on 25 December 2013.","Biography information for Tom Greatrex","Tom Greatrex","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193590","193590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45139","2014-03-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what his Department's policy is on allowing officials to appear before all-party parliamentary groups.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193568","193568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45140","2014-03-31","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the overall cost to his Department of data entry associated with universal credit.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193629","193629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45141","2014-03-31","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will amend the point at which housing benefit payments are halted or reduced when a claimant finds work to better take account of salaries that are paid in arrears.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193619","193619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45142","2014-03-31","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the work of his Department's youth hubs.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193584","193584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45143","2014-03-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the benefit cap.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193667","193667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45144","2014-03-31","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the cost to his Department was of data entry used under universal credit in each quarter since 2010.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193661","193661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45145","2014-03-31","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many staff his Department has employed in data entry roles relating to universal credit in (a) England, (b) the North West and (c) Lancashire in each quarter since 2010.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193699","193699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45146","2014-03-31","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what change there has been in his Department's data entry spending in the last year; and what the reasons are for any such change.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193628","193628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/45147","2014-03-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent discussions his Department has had (a) with Post Office Ltd and (b) other payment services providers on offering a wider range of payment outlets at which Post Office Card Account customers can access pensions and benefits.","Biography information for Peter Aldous","Peter Aldous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 193617","193617"
