"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939906","2018-07-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many official discussions have taken place between policy teams for the UK leaving in the EU in relevant agencies of his Department and (a) port authorities, (b) major retailers, and (c) haulage firms on the different arrangements that will need to be put in place for the inspection of plant and animal materials imported to the UK from EU countries; and on what dates those discussions took place.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163576","163576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939907","2018-07-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what representations his Department has received on the extent to which (a) olanzapine and (b) quetiapine have not been prescribed on account of limitations on the availability of those drugs over the last three years; and what information his Department holds on the number of people who were prescribed (a) olanzapine and (b) quetiapine but were not able to receive those drugs due to limited availability in (i) 2016, (ii) 2017 and (iii) 2018 to date.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163502","163502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939908","2018-07-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with which manufacturers of (a) olanzapine and (b) quetiapine his Department has had discussions since 2017.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163503","163503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939909","2018-07-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what support his Department is giving to the Woodland Trust to assist them in the recovery work on the Smithhills Estate.","Biography information for Chris Green","Chris Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163577","163577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939910","2018-07-17","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, if his Department will take steps to tackle fake news by extending current regulation and guidance on the prominence given to public service broadcasters in printed television guides to (a) such guides and similar information provided online and (b) the operation of voice assistants when they asked for news headlines.","Biography information for Darren Jones","Darren Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163609","163609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939911","2018-07-17","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the Order of Battle is of the Royal Regiment of Scotland.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163481","163481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939912","2018-07-17","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the manpower establishment by rank and number is of each battalion of the Royal Regiment of Scotland; and what the manpower shortfall is for each such battalion.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163482","163482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939913","2018-07-17","Scotland Office","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, with reference to the oral contribution of the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Wales of 11 July 2018, Official Report, column 949, on Industrial Strategy, when he last discussed onshore wind sites in Scotland being able to access future Contract for Difference auctions.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163587","163587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939914","2018-07-17","Scotland Office","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, with reference to the oral contribution of the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Wales of 11 July 2018, Official Report, column 949, on Industrial Strategy, what the timescale is for the announcement relating to onshore wind policy for Scotland.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163588","163588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939915","2018-07-17","Scotland Office","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, pursuant to the oral contribution of the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Wales of 11 July 2018, Official Report, column 949, on Industrial Strategy, whether the proposed announcement on onshore wind include making onshore wind sites in Scotland eligible for future Contract for Difference auctions; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163589","163589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939916","2018-07-17","Department for Transport","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much funding has been allocated from the public purse for advertising the LNER service on London buses.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163590","163590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939917","2018-07-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Environment and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the oral contribution of the Minister for Defence Procurement of 9 July 2018, on Leaving the EU: Defence and Military Aerospace Industry, Official Report, column 694, how many civil servants are part of the cross-departmental group; and from which departments those civil servants are drawn.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163529","163529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939918","2018-07-17","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the oral contribution of the Minister for Defence Procurement of 9 July 2018, on Leaving the EU: Defence and Military Aerospace Industry, Official Report, column 694, when his Department plans to publish the Future Combat Air Strategy.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163530","163530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939919","2018-07-17","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the oral contribution of the Minister for Defence Procurement of 9 July 2018, on Leaving the EU: Defence and Military Aerospace Industry, Official Report, column 694, which European countries are working with the UK on the Future Combat Air Strategy.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163531","163531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939920","2018-07-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many BAME women by age group were detained under the Mental Health Act 1983 in 2016-17.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163563","163563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939921","2018-07-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many (a) women and (b) men by age group were detained under sections 135 and 136 of the Mental Health Act 1983 in 2016-17.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163564","163564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939922","2018-07-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department holds information on the number of women and men who were primary carers at the time they were detained under the provisions of the Mental Health Act 1983 in 2016-17; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163565","163565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939923","2018-07-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the report, Nicaragua: Shoot to kill: Nicaragua's strategy to repress protest, published by Amnesty International in May 2018.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163552","163552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939924","2018-07-16","Treasury","2018-07-12","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 27 June 2018 to Question 158255, on Western Sahara: Imports, whether products entering the UK under the ISO code EH pay import duty.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163555","163555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939925","2018-07-16","Treasury","2018-07-12","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 6 July 2018 to Question 158255, on Import Duties: Western Sahara, for what reasons the Western Sahara Campaign UK is included in the list of consultees when it states that it was not consulted.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163556","163556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939926","2018-07-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he has made an assessment of the (a) potential effect of increased water rates on people with (i) Chrones and (ii) similar conditions who use more water than the average household and (b) requirement to put in place plans for those people in the event of such an increase; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163557","163557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939927","2018-07-16","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what discussions he has had with the Housing Minister on the findings of the Race Disparity Audit in relation to accommodation for Gypsies and Travellers and the Government review, Powers for dealing with unauthorised development and encampments.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163553","163553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939928","2018-07-16","Department for Education","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of funding per child in maintained nursery schools.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163603","163603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939929","2018-07-16","Department for Education","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether the level of free childcare funding per two-year-old in maintained nursery schools has risen in line with inflation.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163604","163604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939930","2018-07-16","Department for Education","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether he has made an assessment of the potential merits of reviewing eligibility for 30-hours free childcare annually; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163605","163605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939931","2018-07-16","Department for Education","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether his Department provides support for maintained nurseries to formulate their three-year budgets beyond 2020.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163606","163606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939932","2018-07-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate her Department has made of the number of students receiving child tax credits and who will be transferred to universal credit this year in (a) Scotland and (b) the UK; and what assessment she has made of changes in the level of funding for those students.","Biography information for Lesley Laird","Lesley Laird","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163623","163623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939933","2018-07-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the implications of the judgment of the European Court of Justice in cases C-104/16 P Council V Front Polisario and C-266/16 Western Sahara Campaign UK for his policies on the territory of, and products originating from, Western Sahara.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163610","163610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939934","2018-07-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the implications of the judgment of the European Court of Justice in cases C-104/16 P Council V Front Polisario and C-266/16 Western Sahara Campaign UK for the recent trade proposals to the European Council of Ministers.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163611","163611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939935","2018-07-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will help secure access to British Southern Cameroons territory for the office of the UN High Commissioner for Human Rights.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163505","163505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939936","2018-07-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he is planning for an increase in water rates; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163558","163558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939937","2018-07-17","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, when he plans to publish proposals to modernise the eCommerce directive.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163522","163522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939938","2018-07-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of a widespread adoption of the NICE Quality Standard on Spondyloarthritis.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163635","163635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939939","2018-07-17","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what progress his Department is making on the implementation of the Local Full Fibre Networks programme, announced in Spring Budget 2017.","Biography information for Drew Hendry","Drew Hendry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163585","163585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939940","2018-07-17","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions his Department has had with the Scottish Government on the Local Full Fibre Networks programme, announced in Spring Budget 2017.","Biography information for Drew Hendry","Drew Hendry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163586","163586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939941","2018-07-17","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when he plans to respond to Question 150069, on CCTV recordings, tabled by the hon. Member for Scunthorpe on 4 June 2018.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163551","163551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939942","2018-07-16","Home Office","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will make an assessment of the implications for his policies of the report Waiting in the Dark: How the asylum system dehumanises, disempowers and damages, published in May 2018 by Refugee Action.","Biography information for Faisal Rashid","Faisal Rashid","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163629","163629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939943","2018-07-16","Home Office","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference evidence in the report, Waiting in the Dark: How the asylum system dehumanises, disempowers and damages, published by Refugee Action in May 2019, what assessment has he made of the reasons for the high number of decisions overturned on appeal.","Biography information for Faisal Rashid","Faisal Rashid","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163630","163630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939944","2018-07-16","Treasury","2018-07-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the reasons for the reductions in the level of investment in the UK car industry in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Faisal Rashid","Faisal Rashid","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163631","163631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939945","2018-07-17","Home Office","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many children have been detained in Immigration Removal Centres in each year for which information is available.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163532","163532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939946","2018-07-17","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the number of victims of domestic abuse who have (a) slept rough and (b) experienced homelessness in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163484","163484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939947","2018-07-17","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many households were registered as statutorily overcrowded in (a) Camberwell and Peckham, (b) Southwark and (c) London in each of the last 5 years.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163485","163485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939948","2018-07-17","Department for Transport","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many trains per hour stopped at Nunhead train station in June in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163486","163486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939949","2018-07-17","Department for Transport","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the introduction of the new Govia Thameslink timetable in Camberwell and Peckham.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163487","163487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939950","2018-07-17","Department for Transport","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 4 July 2018 to Question 158209 on Govia Thameslink Railway, when his Department plans to conclude its review on whether Govia Thameslink Railway has met their contractual obligations.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163488","163488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939951","2018-07-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when the National Prison Healthcare Board was created; how many times that Board has met; and how many times (a) Ministers and (b) officials from his Department have attended meetings of that Board.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163540","163540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939952","2018-07-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many officials from his Department work exclusively on prison healthcare.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163541","163541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939953","2018-07-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many officials from his Department have made visits to prisons in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163542","163542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939954","2018-07-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many officials from his Department represent it on the National Prison Healthcare Board.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163543","163543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939955","2018-07-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, which Minister of his Department is responsible for prison healthcare, and how many times that Minister has visited prisons in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163544","163544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939956","2018-07-16","Department for Transport","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of progress on the Rail Delivery Group’s plan to introduce a national train driver academy.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163566","163566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939957","2018-07-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he plans to reduce the cost to the NHS of reimbursement prices for special medicinal products; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163554","163554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939958","2018-07-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what representations he has made to Ofgem regarding its Targeted Charging Review and the effect of that review on (a) the steel sector and (b) energy intensive industries in the UK.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163607","163607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939959","2018-07-16","Department for Transport","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the effect on train operating company (a) revenues and (b) premium payments to the Government of not implementing in full in December 2018 a new railway timetable or providing the planned level of service.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163567","163567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939960","2018-07-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to protect ancient woodland in England.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163624","163624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939961","2018-07-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what arrangements he has planned for agriculture chemicals registration in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Colin Clark","Colin Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163617","163617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939962","2018-07-16","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department is taking to increase tourism to (a) nature reserves and (b) sites of ancient woodland.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163625","163625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939963","2018-07-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his department is taking to support GP services in the East Midlands.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163626","163626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939964","2018-07-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will suspend all cage trapping of badgers in cull areas owing to the unusually dry and hot weather.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163504","163504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939965","2018-07-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, for what reasons the Government abstained in the vote on the UN Human Rights Council resolution to dispatch an independent commission to investigate whether Israel breached international humanitarian law with its use of force against Palestinian civilians.","Biography information for Faisal Rashid","Faisal Rashid","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163632","163632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939966","2018-07-23","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what rights tenants have to ensure that solar panels fitted to domestic properties are (a) safe and (b) comply with safety regulations.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163506","163506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939967","2018-07-16","Department for Transport","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he plans to review the provisions of rail franchise agreements as a result of the decision not to introduce in full a new railway timetable in December 2018; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163568","163568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939968","2018-07-23","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether his Department holds information on tenants in rented accommodation who have asked for solar panels to be removed because of safety concerns; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163507","163507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939969","2018-07-16","Department for Transport","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect of the decision not to introduce in full a new railway timetable in December 2018 on the services of rail freight operators.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163569","163569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939970","2018-07-16","Department for Transport","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect of the decision not to introduce in full a new railway timetable  in December 2018 on the services provided by open access operators.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163570","163570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939971","2018-07-16","Department for Transport","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he made of the potential level of use of Intercity Express Programme rolling stock on the east coast main line as a result of not introducing in full a new railway timetable  in December 2018 or providing the planned level of service.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163571","163571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939972","2018-07-16","Department for Transport","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the reasons for the increased number of short-form units in use across the Northern Rail franchise in the last month.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163572","163572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939973","2018-07-17","Women and Equalities","2018-07-12","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, when the Government plans to bring forward legislative proposals in response to the Supreme Court's recent ruling on heterosexual civil partnerships.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163584","163584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939974","2018-07-16","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what the projected public expenditure on the right to buy for housing association tenants is in each of the next five years.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163515","163515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939975","2018-07-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 11 July 2018 to Question 160717 on Alcoholic Drinks: Industry, if he will publish the (a) dates, (b) attendees and (c) topics of each of those meetings.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163527","163527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939976","2018-07-16","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what the projected amount of (a) investments and (b) returns is for the Help to Buy Equity Loan scheme in each of the next 10 years.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163516","163516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939977","2018-07-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 19 June 2018 to Question 153800 on Jobcentre Plus: data protection, if he will publish the Physical Security Survey relating to Peterlee Jobcentre.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163539","163539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939978","2018-07-16","Department for Transport","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans he has to delay the East Midlands rail franchise process as a result of the decision not to introduce the December 2018 timetable.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163573","163573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939979","2018-07-16","Department for Transport","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what specification and configuration of electric trains the new depot at Kettering will be built for; and where those trains will receive heavy maintenance.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163574","163574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939980","2018-07-17","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether there is an equivalent offence in planning terms to treating in electoral law.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163534","163534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939981","2018-07-16","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he has received assurances from Capita that firefighters employed by them after the privatisation of the Defence Fire and Rescue Service will remain on comparable pay structures to those used by regional fire authorities.","Biography information for Ruth Smeeth","Ruth Smeeth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163592","163592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939982","2018-07-16","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what resources were made available by his Department to the in-house team bidding to continue operating the Defence Fire and Rescue Service during the recent outsourcing process.","Biography information for Ruth Smeeth","Ruth Smeeth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163593","163593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939983","2018-07-16","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what contingency plans are in place to ensure continuity of Defence Fire and Rescue services in the event that Capita is no longer a viable entity.","Biography information for Ruth Smeeth","Ruth Smeeth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163594","163594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939984","2018-07-16","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether Serco is appealing the contract award for the outsourcing of the Defence Fire and Rescue Service to Capita; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ruth Smeeth","Ruth Smeeth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163595","163595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939985","2018-07-16","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps are being taken at each establishment covered by the Defence Fire and Rescue Service to account for any changes of provision by that service under the new contract; and what site-based risk assessments have been undertaken in connection with any such changes.","Biography information for Ruth Smeeth","Ruth Smeeth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163596","163596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939986","2018-07-16","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the contract awarded to Capita for the provision of Defence Fire and Rescue Services includes ongoing maintenance and testing of fire extinguishers.","Biography information for Ruth Smeeth","Ruth Smeeth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163597","163597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939987","2018-07-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his Department is taking steps to monitor reports of state-sponsored violence in the Chittagong Hill Tracts.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163608","163608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939988","2018-07-17","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the target time is for cases to be brought to resolution at magistrates' courts; and how many times that target has not been met in West Yorkshire in the last three years.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163533","163533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939989","2018-07-16","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been issued a postal requisition in (a) total and (b) each Crown Prosecution Service region; and of those people how many (i) failed to (A) attend court and (B) report to a police station and (ii) attended a magistrates court in each year since 2011.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163521","163521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939990","2018-07-16","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will set a target for the maximum time limit for people to wait for a personal independence payments appeal to be heard.","Biography information for Dr Paul Williams","Dr Paul Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163628","163628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939991","2018-07-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he has taken since his appointment to secure the release of Nazanin Zaghari-Ratcliffe from imprisonment in Iran; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163618","163618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939992","2018-07-17","Home Office","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the total number of ePassport border gates was at each set of UK passport controls, including airports and juxtaposed controls at Brussels and Calais in each of the last five years for which figures are available; how many hours each ePassport border gate was (a) operational and (b) not operational; which ePassport border gates were not operational; and for how long each such gate was not operational in each of those years.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163619","163619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939993","2018-07-17","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to chapter 1 paragraph 76(a) of the White Paper, The future relationship between the United Kingdom and the European Union, Cm9593, what the Government's definition is of talented people.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163578","163578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939994","2018-07-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what limit there is on the amount of money awarded to people of the Windrush generation in backdated benefits claims.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163500","163500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939995","2018-07-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many representations his Department has received on disallowed pension contributions for the Windrush generation in (a) 2017 and (b) 2018.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163501","163501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939996","2018-07-23","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether his Department has received reports of concerns regarding solar panels fitted to domestic properties which have caught fire or exploded; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163508","163508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939997","2018-07-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 27 February to Question 128285 on Green Deal Scheme, what progress the Government has made on improving and revitalising the Green Deal; what progress his Department has made on considering the results from the call for Evidence on the Green Deal Framework; and what the timetable is for consultations on potential reforms to the Green Deal.","Biography information for Ged Killen","Ged Killen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163633","163633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939998","2018-07-17","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, who is responsible for running HMP & YOI Doncaster.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163591","163591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939999","2018-07-18","Cabinet Office","2018-07-12","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when he plans to answer Question 160381; and for what reason an answer was not provided by the named day.","Biography information for Ged Killen","Ged Killen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163634","163634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940000","2018-07-16","Treasury","2018-07-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to chapter 1 paragraph 16(a) of the White Paper The future relationship between the United Kingdom and European Union, Cm9593, which individual or body will be responsible for determining who is a trusted trader.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163579","163579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940001","2018-07-16","Treasury","2018-07-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to chapter 1 paragraph 16(a) of the White Paper The future relationship between the United Kingdom and the European Union, Cm9593, what the Government's definition of a trusted trader is.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163580","163580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940002","2018-07-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to chapter 1 paragraph 84 of the White Paper, The future relationship between the United Kingdom and the European Union, Cm9593, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of continued use of the European Health Insurance Card.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163581","163581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940003","2018-07-16","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to paragraph 89 of the White Paper, The future relationship between the United Kingdom and the European Union, Cm9593, whether the EU ban on mobile phone roaming charges will continue to apply to UK citizens.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163582","163582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940004","2018-07-16","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to chapter 1 paragraph 108 of the White Paper, The future relationship between the United Kingdom and the European Union, Cm9593, whether the retention of a common rulebook on state aid will prevent the UK public sector adopting procurement rules that give preferential treatment to UK-manufactured vehicles.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163583","163583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940005","2018-07-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether the provisions of the White Paper, The future relationship between the United Kingdom and the European Union, Cm9593, will enable him to bring forward legislative proposals for a ban on the export of livestock.","Biography information for Sir Desmond Swayne","Sir Desmond Swayne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163479","163479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940006","2018-07-16","Cabinet Office","2018-07-12","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether the figure of 33 per cent of Government procurement spend going to SME's is a target or an aspiration.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163517","163517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940007","2018-07-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the compliance of boilers sold in the UK with minimum efficiency requirements.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163480","163480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940008","2018-07-17","Department for International Development","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what mechanisms the Government plans to use to analyse progress on implementing Sustainable Development Goal 5 for the Voluntary National Review in 2019.","Biography information for Mr Paul Sweeney","Mr Paul Sweeney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163612","163612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940009","2018-07-17","Department for International Development","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps the Government plans to take to ensure that it collects data from vulnerable and marginalised groups when evaluating progress on implementing Sustainable Development Goal 5 for the Voluntary National Review in 2019.","Biography information for Mr Paul Sweeney","Mr Paul Sweeney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163613","163613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940010","2018-07-17","Department for International Development","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what form of consultation the Government plans to conduct with civic society to measure progress on Sustainable Development Goal 5 for the Voluntary National Review in 2019.","Biography information for Mr Paul Sweeney","Mr Paul Sweeney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163614","163614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940011","2018-07-17","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, which sections of the White Paper, The Future Relationship between the United Kingdom and the European Union, published on 12 July 2018, his Department shared with the Welsh Government before 12 July 2018.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163536","163536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940012","2018-07-17","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, at what time and on what date his Department shared the finished White Paper, The Future Relationship with the United Kingdom and the European Union, published on 12 July 2018, with the Welsh Government.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163537","163537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940013","2018-07-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his department are taking to (a) reduce fuel poverty and (b) prevent excess winter deaths in the winter of 2018-19.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163560","163560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940014","2018-07-16","Wales Office","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how many communications staff based in Wales his Department employs.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163538","163538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940015","2018-07-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment he has made of the level of post-diagnostic support for people who are diagnosed with autism at age 25 or over.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163598","163598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940016","2018-07-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much funding his Department has allocated for the repair and maintenance of footpaths in South Yorkshire.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163561","163561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940017","2018-07-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the average autism diagnosis waiting time was for (a) children under the age of 18 and (b) people aged 18 or over by gender in each year since 2012.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163599","163599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940018","2018-07-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the average autism diagnosis waiting time was for (a) children under the age of 18 and (b) people aged 18 or over by ethnicity in each year since 2012.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163600","163600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940019","2018-07-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people in (a) the Dulwich and West Norwood constituency, (b) the London Borough of Southwark and (c) the London Borough of Lambeth have been diagnosed with autism by gender in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163601","163601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940020","2018-07-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations have been made to the Government of Bahrain on the denial of access to adequate medical treatment of imprisoned Bahraini political leader Hassan Mushaima.","Biography information for Karen Lee","Karen Lee","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163627","163627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940021","2018-07-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people by gender who have a diagnosis of autism have been in hospital for more than two years.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163602","163602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940022","2018-07-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 15 June 2018 to Question 152769 on Children: Day Care, what proportion of parents receiving universal credit currently receive the maximum amount for childcare costs in (a) Barnsley and (b) England.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163562","163562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940023","2018-07-17","Home Office","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the letter from the Minister of State for Immigration to the Chair of the Home Affairs Committee of 21 June 2018, reference DEP2018/0611, how many of the 204 Judicial Review challenges under paragraph 322(5) of the Immigration Act were settled out of court by his Department; and how many of the 223 appeals under paragraph 322(5) of the Immigration Act,has his Department settled out of court.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163535","163535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940024","2018-07-17","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what training he has undertaken on the (a) use of smartphones and (b) security risks smartphones pose; whether he has undertaken any such training since 3 July 2018; and whether he plans to attend any such training in the future.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163545","163545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940025","2018-07-17","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the appropriateness of (a) Ministers and (b) senior civil servants enabling voice recognition software on their smartphones; and what discussions he has had with the Cabinet Office on the risk smartphones pose to security.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163546","163546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940026","2018-07-16","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how may prosecutions relating to attacks by dogs on private property have been made in Lancashire since the introduction of the Anti-Social Behaviour, Crime and Policing Act 2014.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163519","163519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940027","2018-07-17","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment his Department has made of the level of threat to cyber security posed by the use of voice recognition software; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163547","163547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940028","2018-07-16","Home Office","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many attacks on people by dogs have been recorded by the police in Lancashire in the last 2 years.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163520","163520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940029","2018-07-17","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what processes on the enforcement of cyber security guidelines were undertaken when he acquired his current smartphone.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163548","163548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940030","2018-07-16","Department for Transport","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether (a) he, (b) Ministers and (b) officials of his Department were involved in the decision to choose 15 July 2018 as the implementation date for the interim Govia Thameslink Railway timetable.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163499","163499"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940031","2018-07-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations the Government has made to the Turkish Government on the cancellation of Istanbul Pride.","Biography information for Nick Herbert","Nick Herbert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163524","163524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940032","2018-07-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government has taken to support LGBT Rights in Turkey.","Biography information for Nick Herbert","Nick Herbert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163525","163525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940033","2018-07-17","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the total value of disposal receipts is to date from the disposal of sites identified in his Department's Better Defence Estate Strategy.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163523","163523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940034","2018-07-16","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, at what time on 12 July 2018 a copy of the White Paper entitled The Future Relationship between the United Kingdom and the European Union was available on the gov.uk website.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163518","163518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940682","2018-07-17","Department for Education","2018-07-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans are in place to prevent malnutrition during the school summer holidays in children eligible for free school meals.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163766","163766"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938449","2018-07-16","House of Commons Commission","2018-07-11","To ask the House of Commons Commission, what assessment it has made of the effect of the General Data Protection Regulation on the ability of hon. Members to carry out their work.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163097","163097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938450","2018-07-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Work and Pensions, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that safeguards are in place for eligible EU citizens’ to access welfare (a) during the implementation period and (b) after the conclusion of that implementation period of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162957","162957"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938451","2018-07-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his French and other European counterparts on the conflict in Nigeria between Fulani herdsmen and farming communities; and what diplomatic steps they are taking to reduce the conflict and protect communities.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163098","163098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938452","2018-07-16","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence pursuant to the oral contribution of the Parliamentary Under - Secretary of State and Minister for Defence People and Veterans of 9 July 2018, Official Report, column 706, whether it is his policy that the One Public Estate principles apply to public land that has its freehold vested within an association.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163148","163148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938453","2018-07-16","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the written statement of 28 June 2018, on Building Safety Update, HCWS811, of the 297 total private sector buildings assessed to be unlikely to meet current Building Regulations guidance, a) how many have informed residents and b) what measures his department has taken to ensure that all residents have been informed.","Biography information for Sarah Jones","Sarah Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163185","163185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938454","2018-07-17","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the level of under-reporting of sexual assault in prison.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163082","163082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938455","2018-07-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he is making to the Government of South Sudan on political reform and tackling corruption.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162975","162975"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938456","2018-07-16","Department for Transport","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of trends in the number of qualified HGV drivers in the road haulage industry for each year since 2010.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163149","163149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938457","2018-07-16","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, if he will respond to the letter of the hon. Member for Glasgow North of 26 April 2018, reference PG4747.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163138","163138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938458","2018-07-16","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made on the effectiveness of the training delivered by the Royal Marines to the England football team prior to the 2018 World Cup campaign.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163048","163048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938459","2018-07-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans his Department has to review the adequacy of the element of the Funeral Expenses Payment that is used to pay funeral directors, coffins and flowers to cover those costs.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163065","163065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938460","2018-07-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much has been spent from the public purse on palliative care services for children in (a) the London Borough of Southwark and (b) England in each of the last eight years.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162950","162950"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938461","2018-07-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make it his policy to require Clinical Commissioning Groups to provide annual funding to children’s (a) hospices and (b) palliative care services.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162951","162951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938462","2018-07-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will take steps to increase the allocation of funding for palliative care services for children.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162952","162952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938463","2018-07-16","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many victims of domestic abuse who presented at domestic violence refuges were unable to access domestic violence refuge services in (a) Southwark, (b) London and (c) England, in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162953","162953"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938464","2018-07-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what progress has been made on the provision of Focused Laser Ablation treatment for prostate cancer available on the NHS.","Biography information for Neil O'Brien","Neil O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163225","163225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938465","2018-07-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will publish the interim results of the further survey commissioned by his Department on Direct Pay clients.","Biography information for Paul Masterton","Paul Masterton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163182","163182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938466","2018-07-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether his Department issues guidance to hon. Members on the Child Maintenance Service to assist them with constituency casework.","Biography information for Paul Masterton","Paul Masterton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163183","163183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938467","2018-07-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Child maintenance arrears and compliance strategy 2012-17, published in January 2013, whether she has plans to implement an annual review of arrears under the Child Maintenance Service.","Biography information for Paul Masterton","Paul Masterton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163184","163184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938468","2018-07-16","Department for Transport","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions Highways England has had with Durham County Council on traffic management on Seaton Lane, Seaham, and its effect on road safety and congestion on the A19.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163066","163066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938469","2018-07-16","Department for Transport","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make funding available to improve road safety and relieve traffic congestion at Seaton Lane, Seaham.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163067","163067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938470","2018-07-16","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether he has made an assessment of the possible effect of levels of austerity on projected prison population numbers; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163103","163103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938471","2018-07-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information on the costs of goods he will require of manufacturers of special medicinal products under the Health Service Medical Supplies (Costs) Act 2017 and subsequent regulations; and if he will bring forward further regulatory proposals to control the costs of those products.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163104","163104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938472","2018-07-16","Department for Education","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the funding available for adult education courses within (a) Coventry and (b) the West Midlands.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162981","162981"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938473","2018-07-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what estimate he has made of the number of UK citizens living in (a) Germany and (b) France.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162982","162982"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938474","2018-07-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the (a) governance and (b) administration costs of Clinical Commissioning Groups in England; and what steps he is taking to ensure value for money for those costs.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162983","162983"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938475","2018-07-16","Department for Education","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what progress his Department is making on (a) improving and (b) strengthening the quality of (i) teachers and (ii) leaders in alternative provision; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163068","163068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938476","2018-07-16","Department for Education","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much funding his Department has allocated to businesses in Coventry to support the recruitment of apprentices in each of the last eight years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162984","162984"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938477","2018-07-16","Department for Education","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when his Department plans to publish the outcome of the alternative provision strand of the Teaching and Leadership Innovation Fund.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163069","163069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938478","2018-07-16","Department for Education","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many applications for funding were received for the alternative provision strand of his Department’s Teaching and Leadership Innovation Fund;  and how many of those applications have been approved.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163070","163070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938479","2018-07-16","Department for Education","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what progress his Department has made on building an evidence base for improving outcomes for children in alternative provision under his Department’s Alternative Provision Innovation Fund since September 2017 .","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163071","163071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938480","2018-07-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate he has made of the amount of funding allocated from the public purse to  businesses in Coventry to encourage (a) economic growth and (b) employment.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162985","162985"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938481","2018-07-16","Department for Education","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to tackle the level of school exclusions; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163072","163072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938482","2018-07-16","Department for Education","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to tackle the increase in off-rolling before examinations; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163073","163073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938483","2018-07-16","Department for Education","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to (a) improve the quality of independent alternative provision and (b) ensure that unsafe alternative providers (i) close and (ii) are not commissioned by schools to provide services.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163074","163074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938484","2018-07-16","Department for Education","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to improve the accessibility of routes to employment for pupils who have been excluded from school.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163075","163075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938485","2018-07-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the total monthly receipts to the public purse were from (a) the fee charged for applications to the Child Maintenance Service (CMS), (b) the collection fee for paying parents using the CMS Collect and Pay service, (c) the collection fee for receiving parents using the CMS Collect and Pay service and (d) enforcement fees levied on paying parents in each month since and including April 2016.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163063","163063"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938486","2018-07-16","Department for International Development","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether she has had any discussions with her EU counterparts on her proposal to introduce payments by results to funding of UN agencies.","Biography information for Mr Paul Sweeney","Mr Paul Sweeney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163187","163187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938487","2018-07-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate she has made of receipts to the public purse from Child Maintenance Service charges in each year from 2020-21 up to and including 2025/26.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163064","163064"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938488","2018-07-16","Department for International Development","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what discussions her Department has had with its European counterparts on the implementation of Sustainable Development Goal 5.","Biography information for Mr Paul Sweeney","Mr Paul Sweeney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163188","163188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938489","2018-07-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when new training on domestic abuse, piloted in May 2017, for Child Maintenance Service staff was rolled out nationally.","Biography information for Angela Crawley","Angela Crawley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163146","163146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938490","2018-07-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether Child Maintenance Options staff have received the new training on domestic abuse, piloted in May 2017 for Child Maintenance Service staff.","Biography information for Angela Crawley","Angela Crawley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163147","163147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938491","2018-07-16","Department for International Development","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how she plans to measure progress on Sustainable Development Goal 5 for the Voluntary National Review in 2019.","Biography information for Mr Paul Sweeney","Mr Paul Sweeney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163189","163189"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938492","2018-07-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when he plans to respond to letters to his predecessor from the hon. Member for North Durham on whistle blowing dated 5 May, 24 May and 25 June 2018.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163020","163020"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938493","2018-07-16","Home Office","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many and what proportion of weapons seized at the border were (a) prohibited firearms (b) 50 calibre firearms; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162979","162979"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938494","2018-07-16","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, on how many occasions Royal Fleet Auxiliary ships have been utilised by the UK and its allies in support of counter-narcotics operations since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163021","163021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938495","2018-07-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what alternative provision her Department plans to put in place for hon. Members' staff to use in place of the Basildon Service Centre for universal credit full service enquiries.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162976","162976"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938496","2018-07-16","Department for Education","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when he telephoned Dame Martina Milburn to encourage her to apply to be Chair the Social Mobility Commission; how many other people he so encouraged; and what the names are of those people.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163112","163112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938497","2018-07-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much money was spent on translation services in the NHS by language in the last financial year.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham P Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163076","163076"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938498","2018-07-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department takes to audit the (a) quality, (b) necessity and (c) value for money of translation services in the NHS.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham P Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163077","163077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938499","2018-07-16","Department for Education","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, on what dates the original application process opened and closed for the Chair of the Social Mobility Commission; how many people applied for that position before the closure of the original application process; whether the application process was then extended; how many people applied for that position after any such extension; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163113","163113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938500","2018-07-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people making a claim for universal credit have applied for an advance payment in the most recent 12 months for which data are available; and how many of those people have been (a) successful and (b) unsuccessful in such an application.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162992","162992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938501","2018-07-16","Department for Education","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many applicants were (a) long-listed, (b) shortlisted and (c) interviewed for the position of Chair of the Social Mobility Commission; how many people and who were on the panels to decide on the (i) long-list, (ii) shortlist and (iii) list of interviewees for that position; how many stages of interview took place for that position; and who interviewed the applicants in those interviews.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163114","163114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938502","2018-07-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the publication entitled A Healthier Future: Diet & Healthy Weight Delivery Plan, published by the Scottish Government on 2 July 2018, whether he plans to seek convergence of regulations on price promotion between Scotland and England.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163145","163145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938503","2018-07-16","Treasury","2018-07-11","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what resources HMRC has allocated to the inspection of the non-payment of travel time for care workers for the purposes of calculating the (a) national living wage and (b) national minimum wage in each of the last five years for which data are available.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162993","162993"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938504","2018-07-16","Department for International Trade","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, with reference to the Government press release, PM hails biggest Naval defence contract for a decade, published on 28 June 2018, if he will provide further detail on the calculations for the value of the Global Combat Ship Australia contract valued at £20 billion.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163022","163022"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938505","2018-07-16","Home Office","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate he has made of the number of people from the Windrush generation who live in (a) Lewisham, Deptford constituency and (b) the London borough of Lewisham.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163160","163160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938506","2018-07-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many local authorities are commissioning 15-minute social care visits.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162994","162994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938507","2018-07-16","Home Office","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many hours police officers spent on patrol in (a) the London Borough of Lewisham and (b) the Metropolitan Police Service area in each of the last seven years.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163161","163161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938508","2018-07-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure that local authorities cease commissioning of 15-minute social care visits.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162995","162995"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938509","2018-07-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the number of people whose social care package consists of 15-minute visits.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162996","162996"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938510","2018-07-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people have had universal credit payments reduced as a result of receiving carers allowance.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163118","163118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938511","2018-07-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claimants of universal credit have had their payments reduced as a result of receiving disability living allowance.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163119","163119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938512","2018-07-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claimants of universal credit have had payments reduced as a result of receiving personal independence payment.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163120","163120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938513","2018-07-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claimants of universal credit have had payments reduced as a result of receiving attendance allowance.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163121","163121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938514","2018-07-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the oral contribution of the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State of 21 November 2017, Official Report, column 352, when he plans to hold the ministerial meeting on the future of medical regulations.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163036","163036"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938515","2018-07-16","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many homes have been purchased using Help To Buy in the borough of Bolton; and how many of those homes were sold with a lease.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Sir David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162989","162989"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938516","2018-07-16","Department for Transport","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, further to the new arrangements introduced by the Government on volumetric concrete mixers, outlined in the Government’s response to its consultation on goods vehicle operator licensing exemptions and related regulatory changes, and with reference to the letter from Parliamentary Under Secretary of State for Roads, Local Transport and Devolution on the regulation of mobile concrete batching plant – decision on operating weight arrangements, issued in April 2018, what financial impact assessment his Department carried out before those decisions were made.","Biography information for Gavin Newlands","Gavin Newlands","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163134","163134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938517","2018-07-16","Department for Transport","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, further to the new arrangements introduced by the Government on volumetric concrete mixers, outlined in the Government’s response to its consultation on goods vehicle operator licensing exemptions and related regulatory changes, and with reference to the letter from the Parliamentary Under Secretary of State for Roads, Local Transport and Devolution on the regulation of mobile concrete batching plant – decision on operating weight arrangements, issued in April 2018, what environmental impact assessment was carried out before those decisions were made.","Biography information for Gavin Newlands","Gavin Newlands","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163135","163135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938518","2018-07-16","Scotland Office","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, whether he plans to visit a food bank in July 2018.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163186","163186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938519","2018-07-16","Home Office","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many of the 63 Windrush generation members that were wrongly removed from the UK first came to the attention of her Department as a result of the outsourcing company Capita’s trawl of past applications.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163105","163105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938520","2018-07-16","Department for Transport","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment the Government has made of the effect of congestion on London’s international competitiveness.","Biography information for Paul Scully","Paul Scully","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163125","163125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938521","2018-07-16","Home Office","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the oral contribution of the Minister for Immigration, of 4 June 2018, Official Report, column 22 on students wrongly accused of cheating in the Test of English for International Communication, what proportion of students who remain in the UK will be covered by the review.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163106","163106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938522","2018-07-16","Treasury","2018-07-11","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will establish a hardship fund to help prevent home repossessions of people unable to switch to mortgages with lower rates.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163107","163107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938523","2018-07-17","Department for Transport","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, further to the new arrangements introduced by the Government on volumetric concrete mixers, outlined in the Government’s response to its consultation on goods vehicle operator licensing exemptions and related regulatory changes, and with reference to the letter from the Parliamentary Under Secretary of State for Roads, Local Transport and Devolution on the regulation of mobile concrete batching plant – decision on operating weight arrangements, issued in April 2018, what financial impact assessment was carried out before those decisions were made.","Biography information for Gavin Newlands","Gavin Newlands","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163136","163136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938524","2018-07-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations the Government has made to the Mexican Government on freedom of religion in that country.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163013","163013"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938525","2018-07-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to help tackle the persecution of Christians in India.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163014","163014"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938526","2018-07-16","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what discussions he has had with his European counterparts on the maintenance of access to courts in EU countries for UK victims of consumer fraud resident in those countries after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163015","163015"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938527","2018-07-16","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what recent discussions he has had with his EU counterparts on future market access for UK members of the legal profession to (a) provide services and (b) attend courts in EU countries after the UK leaves the EU; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163016","163016"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938528","2018-07-16","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary for Justice, what the average waiting time was from plea and trial preparation hearing to the first day of trial for sexual offences against children for each Crown Court in England and Wales in the last two years.","Biography information for Ann Coffey","Ann Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162990","162990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938529","2018-07-16","Department for Education","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when the original application process (a) opened and (b) closed for the position of Chair of the Social Mobility Commission; how many people applied for that position before the closure of the original application process; and whether that application process was extended.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163115","163115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938530","2018-07-16","Home Office","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps he is taking to improve the performance of Border Force at UK Airports in clearing (a) EEA and (b) non-EEA passengers through immigration controls.","Biography information for Gavin Robinson","Gavin Robinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163117","163117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938531","2018-07-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the Government plans to change the constitutional arrangements between the UK and the British Overseas Territories.","Biography information for Dame Margaret Hodge","Dame Margaret Hodge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162949","162949"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938532","2018-07-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment her Department has made of the effect of the introduction of universal credit on the ability of victims of domestic violence to claim the benefits.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163043","163043"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938533","2018-07-16","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary for Justice, what the average waiting time was from plea and trial preparation hearing to the first day of trial for sexual offences against children for each Crown Court in Manchester in the last two years.","Biography information for Ann Coffey","Ann Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162991","162991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938534","2018-07-16","Home Office","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when he plans to respond to Question 146839, on criminal proceedings, tabled by the hon. Member for Scunthorpe 22 May 2018.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163094","163094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938535","2018-07-16","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent assessment he has made of the quality of service provided by contracts outsourced by his Department.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163044","163044"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938536","2018-07-16","Scotland Office","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what discussions he has had with representatives of the Royal Bank of Scotland (RBS) on the potential effect on local communities of the proposed closure of RBS branches.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163045","163045"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938537","2018-07-16","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will make an assessment on the effect of reductions in the level of  funding for Criminal Legal Aid on the (a) recruitment and (b) retention of Criminal Law Practitioners.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163046","163046"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938538","2018-07-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the oral contributions of the Prime Minister of 9 July 2018, on leaving the EU, Official Report, column 714, what progress has been made in stepping up preparations for a possible no deal with the EU on resolving the issue of the disputed jurisdiction of Lough Foyle and Carlingford Lough.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163018","163018"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938539","2018-07-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department plans to take to support people diagnosed with Erythropoietic Protoporphyria as a result of the decision by NICE not to license Scenesse.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163053","163053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938540","2018-07-16","Northern Ireland Office","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, pursuant to the Answer of 10 July 2018 to Question 161114, what representations she has received other than in written form from political parties in Northern Ireland on the subject of cutting MLA pay; and if she will publish the substance of such representations.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163019","163019"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938541","2018-07-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps is he taking to expand the size of UK’s Blue Belt.","Biography information for Giles Watling","Giles Watling","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163224","163224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938542","2018-07-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what duties are placed on local authorities to protect Ramsar sites from damage as a result of development.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163204","163204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938543","2018-07-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the timetable is for the appointment of a new contractor to complete the building of the new Royal Liverpool Hospital; and will he make a statement.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Dame Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163001","163001"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938544","2018-07-16","Department for Transport","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to his Department's consultation on the use of section 19 and section 22 permits for road passenger transport in Great Britain, published on 8 February 2018, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that new guidance for community transport operators does not lead to the closure of transport schemes for older people.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162997","162997"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938545","2018-07-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the timeframe is for all assessments for (a) personal independence payment and (b) employment support allowance in Birkenhead to be recorded using audio equipment.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162998","162998"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938546","2018-07-16","Cabinet Office","2018-07-11","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what recent discussions he has had with representatives of civil service staff on the civil service pay guidance 2018-19, published on  25 June 2018.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162999","162999"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938547","2018-07-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 4 July 2018 to Question 158194 on Hemel Hempstead Hospital, for what reason he does not have any plans to visit the Hemel Hempstead Hospital Site.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163042","163042"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938548","2018-07-16","Cabinet Office","2018-07-11","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether he plans further cyber security training for the Secretary of State for Defence; and whether he has had discussions with the Secretary of State for Defence on cyber security.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163090","163090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938549","2018-07-16","Home Office","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when the application for leave to remain in the UK submitted on 19 October 2017 under Immigration Case Ref 922984523 will be determined.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Sir Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162970","162970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938550","2018-07-16","Department for Transport","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent steps his Department has taken to support the growth of the rail supply chain in the North East.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163099","163099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938551","2018-07-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the potential benefits of a rail sector deal to the North East.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163100","163100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938552","2018-07-16","Department for Transport","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the economic benefit for the (a) North East and (b) UK of UK-based manufacturing of new rolling stock in the last five years.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163101","163101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938553","2018-07-16","Department for Transport","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what contracts for manufacturing rolling stock in the UK there have been in each of the last five years; and what assessment he has made of the effect of such contracts on the North East.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163102","163102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938554","2018-07-16","Department for Transport","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether it is the Government's policy that Cross Country train services from the north of England should continue to connect with Brockenhurst and Bournemouth without the need to change trains; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Sir Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162971","162971"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938555","2018-07-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what notifications his Department has received of outbreaks of the stain 9D of Bovine TB of the strain 9D and which locations those notifications came from.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162945","162945"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938556","2018-07-16","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will place in the Library copies of the (a) business case and (b) impact assessment conducted on the affordable housing strategic partnerships agreed by Homes England  announced on 3 July 2018.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162986","162986"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938557","2018-07-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent steps he has taken to secure investment in the Aerospace sector.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163029","163029"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938558","2018-07-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Written Statement of 10 July 2018 on Update on the Independent Medicines and Medical Devices Safety Review, HCWS841, what the (a) names and (b) objectives are of the clinicians on the clinical advisory group for surgical mesh.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163087","163087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938559","2018-07-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care,  pursuant to the Written Statement of 10 July 2018 on Update on the Independent Medicines and Medical Devices Safety Review, HCWS841, what estimate he has made of the number of potential exceptions there will be to the pause in the use of mesh for stress urinary incontinence; and how exceptions to the suspension will be determined.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163088","163088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938560","2018-07-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Written Statement of 10 July 2018 on Update on the Independent Medicines and Medical Devices Safety Review, HCWS841, if he will publish in detail the Government’s plan for a high vigilance programme of restricted practice for the use of surgical mesh to treat stress urinary incontinence.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163089","163089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938561","2018-07-16","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the number of tower blocks with flammable cladding which are covered by insurance for some or all of the costs of re-cladding.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162987","162987"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938562","2018-07-16","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to his oral contribution of 9 July 2018, Official Report, column 690, when he plans for the substantive findings of the Modernising Defence Programme to be published.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163049","163049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938563","2018-07-16","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to his oral contribution of 9 July 2018, Official Report, column 690, whether the £800 million referred to came from the nuclear contingency; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163050","163050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938564","2018-07-16","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to his oral contribution of 9 July 2018, Official Report, column 690, what that £800 million has been spent on.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163051","163051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938565","2018-07-16","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to his oral contribution of 9 July 2018, Official Report, column 690, for what reasons the Modernising Defence Programme's analysis of threats to the UK is not being informed by a new National Security Risk Assessment.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163052","163052"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938566","2018-07-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will hold discussions with (a) the Motor Neurone Disease Association and (b) people who have motor neurone disease on extending the special rules for terminal illness to include motor neurone disease.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163205","163205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938567","2018-07-16","Cabinet Office","2018-07-11","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what cyber security training has been undertaken by the Secretary of State for Defence.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163091","163091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938568","2018-07-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effect of Official Development Assistance spending on the achievement of the Sustainable Development Goals.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163150","163150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938569","2018-07-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to improve the transparency of Official Development Assistance spent by his Department.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163151","163151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938570","2018-07-16","Department for Education","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department has taken to promote University Technical Colleges.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163057","163057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938571","2018-07-16","Department for Education","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of trends in the number of pupils taking up STEM and ICT higher education courses in the last five years.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163058","163058"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938572","2018-07-16","Department for Education","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department has taken to put technical courses on parity with academic courses.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163059","163059"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938573","2018-07-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department has taken to promote parity of treatment of mental and physical health conditions.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163060","163060"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938574","2018-07-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department has taken to promote mental health first aid.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163061","163061"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938575","2018-07-16","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department has taken to promote mental health treatment in prisons.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163062","163062"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938576","2018-07-16","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy  on preventing building fires started as a result of faulty electrical appliances.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162988","162988"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938577","2018-07-16","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government what steps he has taken to communicate to new home buyers their right, introduced on 1 April 2017, to request the building inspection records for the property.","Biography information for Mrs Maria Miller","Mrs Maria Miller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163034","163034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938578","2018-07-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of industrial injuries disablement benefit claims decisions are changed at the mandatory reconsideration stage.","Biography information for Peter Aldous","Peter Aldous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163095","163095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938579","2018-07-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of industrial injuries disablement benefit claims decisions are changed on appeal.","Biography information for Peter Aldous","Peter Aldous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163096","163096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938580","2018-07-16","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment his Department has made of the take-up of the right of new home buyers to request the building inspection records for the property, which was introduced on 1 April 2017.","Biography information for Mrs Maria Miller","Mrs Maria Miller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163035","163035"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938581","2018-07-16","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to his speech of 10 July 2018 to the Centre for Social Justice, which prisons will receive the additional investment of £16,000,000; and how much of that money will be spent in each prison.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163003","163003"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938582","2018-07-16","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to his speech of 10 July 2018 to the Centre for Social Justice, what steps his Department is taken to ascertain whether the £16,000,000 investment in 11 prisons represents value for money to the public purse; and what steps are being taken to make contracts transparent on the work undertaken.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163004","163004"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938583","2018-07-16","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to his speech of 10 July 2018 to the Centre for Social Justice, what standards his Department plans for the £16,000,000 investment in 11 prisons to improve by prison receiving investment.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163005","163005"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938584","2018-07-16","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to his speech delivered on 10 July 2018 to the Centre for Social Justice, what the timetable is for the additional 10,000 prison places to be completed; and what assessment he has made of the potential effect of those additional places on prison officer to offender ratios.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163006","163006"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938585","2018-07-16","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to his speech of 10 July 2018 to the Centre for Social Justice,  if he will break down the £6,000,000 investment into counter-narcotics by (a) training expenditure, (b) detection equipment and (c) security improvements.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163007","163007"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938586","2018-07-16","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to his speech of 10 July 2018 to the Centre for Social Justice, in which parts of the prison estate the digital categorisation tool has been trialed; and what impact assessment findings have been made from that trial.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163008","163008"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938587","2018-07-16","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to his speech of 10 July 2018 to the Centre for Social Justice, which 10 prisons the Drug Taskforce is being deployed for; and what (a) law enforcement and (b) healthcare agencies are planned to be involved in that work.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163009","163009"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938588","2018-07-16","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to his speech of 10 July 2018 to the Centre for Social Justice, if his Department will publish its findings on the ten prisons in which the Drug Taskforce will be implemented.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163010","163010"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938589","2018-07-16","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to his speech of 10 July 2018 to the Centre for Social Justice, how much his Department is investing into training for prison staff on preserving evidence.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163011","163011"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938590","2018-07-16","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to his speech of 10 July 2018 to the Centre for Social Justice, who the members of the Drugs Taskforce will be.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163012","163012"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938591","2018-07-16","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the outcome is of recent discussions on bringing forward legislative proposals on a no body, no parole law.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162944","162944"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938592","2018-07-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many universal credit claimants are re-paying benefit overpayments; what the (a) mean and (b) median value is of those overpayments; and what the average period is for those benefit payments to be recovered in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163208","163208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938593","2018-07-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when the Government plans to publish its response to the recent consultation on employment status, which closed on 1 June 2018.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163000","163000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938594","2018-07-16","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) Jewish and (b) Muslim deaths have been processed in each coroner area in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Bob Blackman","Bob Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163078","163078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938596","2018-07-16","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many non-invasive autopsies have been (a) requested and (b) provided in each coroner area in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Bob Blackman","Bob Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163079","163079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938597","2018-07-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many universal credit claimants are re-paying benefit overpayments at 40 per cent from their standard allowance in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163209","163209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938598","2018-07-16","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, on how many occasions the three-day target for the release of bodies after initial report has not been met in each coroner area in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Bob Blackman","Bob Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163080","163080"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938599","2018-07-16","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and which coroner areas offer an out-of-hours service for cases other than homicide, mass fatalities and organ or tissue donation.","Biography information for Bob Blackman","Bob Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163081","163081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938600","2018-07-16","Department for Transport","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the Honorary Medical Advisory Panel is considering the use of Mean Absolute Relative Difference (MARD) as an accuracy measure for blood glucose monitoring devices as part of the review of the Driver and Vehicle Licensing Agency guidelines on driving and diabetes.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163210","163210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938601","2018-07-16","Home Office","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what support the Government provides to women wanting to exit prostitution.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163152","163152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938602","2018-07-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department has made an assessment of the effect on people living with diabetes of the changes to the Driver and Vehicle Licensing Agency (DVLA) guidelines on driving and diabetes given that NICE recommends that healthcare professionals take the DVLA’s guidance into account when offering glucose monitoring technology.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163211","163211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938603","2018-07-16","Home Office","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps he is taking to tackle organised sexual exploitation.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163153","163153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938604","2018-07-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the effect of pay between assignment (PBA) contracts on equal pay; what the average length of time workers have been on PBA contracts in the most recent period for which figures are available; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Dame Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163002","163002"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938605","2018-07-16","Home Office","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many confirmed victims of human trafficking have been subsequently re-trafficked after they have left the National Referral Mechanism.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163154","163154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938606","2018-07-16","Department for Education","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment his Department has made of whether home-schooled children receive the same level of social and academic education as children attending school.","Biography information for Wera Hobhouse","Wera Hobhouse","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163179","163179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938607","2018-07-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the potential of (a) outcome-based payment models and (b) risk sharing partnerships with industry to improve access to diabetes technology to support (i) monitoring, (ii) self-management and (iii) prevention.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163212","163212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938608","2018-07-16","Home Office","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the timetable is for his next steps in bringing forward a draft Domestic Abuse Bill.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163155","163155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938609","2018-07-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to increase the uptake of insulin pumps for people throughout England with type 1 diabetes.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163213","163213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938610","2018-07-16","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, where each headquarters is of regiments from (a) Scotland, (b) Wales and (c) Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163030","163030"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938611","2018-07-16","Home Office","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on drug-related fatalities of drug safety testing at (a) festivals, (b) nightclubs and (c) other large gatherings of young people.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163156","163156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938612","2018-07-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, for what reason the uptake of structured education programmes among people with type (a) 1 and (b) 2 diabetes in the CCG area of (i) Tameside and Glossop and (ii) North Derbyshire is low; whether he is taking steps to improve that uptake; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163214","163214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938613","2018-07-16","Home Office","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 26 June 2018 to Question 154594, whether the next meeting of the Modern Slavery Strategy and Implementation Group has been arranged; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163157","163157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938614","2018-07-16","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, where each (a) resettlement and (b) rehabilitation centre is for people leaving the armed forces.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163031","163031"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938615","2018-07-16","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many and what proportion of recruits to the armed forces came from (a) Scotland, (b) Wales, (c) Northern Ireland and (d) England in each of the last 5 years.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163032","163032"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938616","2018-07-16","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how much money was spent on advertising the activity of touring in England to the UK market in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163017","163017"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938617","2018-07-16","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the value of efficiencies created for the Dreadnought class ballistic missile submarine as a result of cooperation with the United States.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163023","163023"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938618","2018-07-16","Department for Education","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many students started a nursing degree apprenticeship in 2017-18.","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163190","163190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938619","2018-07-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claims have been rejected under each exception to the two child limit for (a) child tax credits and (b) universal credit.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163137","163137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938620","2018-07-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what his Department's recruitment target is for the nursing degree apprenticeship entry route, and what recent steps his Department has taken to meet that target.","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163191","163191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938621","2018-07-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what additional finding his Department plans to provide to employers to cover the educational costs of nursing degree apprenticeships.","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163192","163192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938622","2018-07-16","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many convictions for criminal offences were committed in North Wales for each (a) category and (b) offence in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163033","163033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938623","2018-07-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many families receive a child disability element in their child tax credit award; and what proportion of those families have a child who  qualifies for a lower rather than a higher child disability addition under universal credit.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163215","163215"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938624","2018-07-16","Department for Transport","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions he has had with the Scottish Government Cabinet Secretary for Transport on cross border transport infrastructure.","Biography information for Andrew Bowie","Andrew Bowie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163174","163174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938625","2018-07-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what progress has been made on the oil and gas sector deal.","Biography information for Andrew Bowie","Andrew Bowie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163175","163175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938626","2018-07-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many families receive a disabled child premium via income support; and of those families receiving that support how many have a child who will qualify for a lower rather than a higher child disability addition under universal credit.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163216","163216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938627","2018-07-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many families receive a disabled child premium via a job seekers allowance award; and of those families receiving that award how many have a child who will qualify for a lower rather than a higher child disability addition under universal credit.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163217","163217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938628","2018-07-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what progress his Department has made on the rural proofing of its policies.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162946","162946"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938629","2018-07-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate she has made of the number of families with a disabled child claiming means tested benefits or tax credit who will have a lower entitlement under universal credit, disregarding any transitional protection payments; and what estimate she has made of the average change in entitlement by families so affected.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163218","163218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938630","2018-07-16","Women and Equalities","2018-07-11","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what steps she is taking to tackle LGBT bullying in the workplace.","Biography information for Andrew Bowie","Andrew Bowie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163176","163176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938631","2018-07-16","Treasury","2018-07-11","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he plans to hold discussions with the Scottish Government on economic growth in (a) Scotland and (b) the UK.","Biography information for Andrew Bowie","Andrew Bowie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163177","163177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938632","2018-07-16","Home Office","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps he is taking to tackle far-right extremism in the UK.","Biography information for Andrew Bowie","Andrew Bowie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163178","163178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938633","2018-07-16","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much was spent by his Department on military personnel from each of the Royal Navy's (a) services and (b) branches in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163024","163024"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938634","2018-07-16","Treasury","2018-07-11","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many parents with disabled children in residential settings are in receipt of tax credits based on the rule under tax credit regulations that payment for a child in residential accommodation can continue so long as they are in care solely because of their disability.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163219","163219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938635","2018-07-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what his Department's policy is on prescriptions for dalteparin within primary care.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162958","162958"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938636","2018-07-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the number of referrals to hospital each year for the purpose of obtaining dalteparin on repeat prescription.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162959","162959"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938637","2018-07-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many prescriptions for dalteparin have been issued in (a) primary and (b) secondary care in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162960","162960"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938638","2018-07-16","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 3 July 2018 to Question 157090, on Ministry of Justice: buildings, how many days each Minister of his Department has spent in Petty France between 11 April and 11 May 2018.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163055","163055"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938639","2018-07-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what financial support is available to meet the need of disabled children with looked- after status.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163220","163220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938640","2018-07-16","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what  the current strength is of Army Headquarters (a) Home Command and (b) Field Army.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163025","163025"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938641","2018-07-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether a carer who provides full-time care for a disabled person and is awaiting a decision on their claim for a qualifying disability benefit will be automatically placed in the no-conditionality group of universal credit.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163221","163221"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938642","2018-07-16","Department for Education","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of teachers in the London Borough of Lewisham have still been in teaching after (a) three, (b) four and (c) five years in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163162","163162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938643","2018-07-16","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what is the current strength of the British Army's (a) 1st Division, (b) 3rd Division and (c) Force Troops Command.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163026","163026"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938644","2018-07-16","Department for Education","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether his Department plans to fund Staying Put beyond 2019-20.","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163193","163193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938645","2018-07-16","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what was spent by his Department on military personnel from each of the Army's Regiments and Corps in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163027","163027"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938646","2018-07-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many families with a child in residential care are likely to lose universal credit payments for their child as a result of (a) section 22 of the Children Act 1989 and (b) section 17(6) of the Children (Scotland) Act 1995.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163222","163222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938647","2018-07-16","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the answer of 25 June to Question 155782 on Courts: Sunderland, what progress has been made by the HMCTS Property Board's deliberations on the future of the Sunderland court estate.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163092","163092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938648","2018-07-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many families with a child in residential school or residential college are likely to lose universal credit payments for their child as a result of (a) section 22 of the Children Act 1989 and section 17(6) of the Children (Scotland) Act 1995.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163223","163223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938649","2018-07-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of approving the home as a place for pregnant women to take misoprostol.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163093","163093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938650","2018-07-16","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, when he plans to respond to the correspondence from the hon. Member for Colne Valley, sent on 23 May 2018, in reference to the National Planning Policy Framework.","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163194","163194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938651","2018-07-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 21 June 2018 to Question 153431 on Schools: Air Pollution, when his Department last met officials of the (a) Department for Education and (b) Department for Transport to discuss air quality around schools; and if he will place the minutes of those meetings in the Library.","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163195","163195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938652","2018-07-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 24 January 2018 to Question 123107 on Public Footpaths, what funding he plans to allocate to national trails for 2018-19; and how much funding his Department has allocated for 2018-19 to maintain the Pennine Way.","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163196","163196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938653","2018-07-16","Department for Education","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much funding per pupil has been allocated to schools in (a) Kirklees and (b) Yorkshire in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163197","163197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938654","2018-07-16","Department for Transport","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to his oral contribution of 4 June 2018, Official Report, column 69, what discussions his Department has had with representatives of Trans-Pennine Express on accessibility for disabled passengers on trains since that date.","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163198","163198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938655","2018-07-16","Department for Transport","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment he has made of the cost benefit ratio of (a) HS2 and (b) the Missing Link solution in Gloucestershire; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162980","162980"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938656","2018-07-16","Department for Transport","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to his oral contribution of 5 July 2018, Official Report, column 491, when the improvement works to the Manchester to Leeds railway line will commence.","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163199","163199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938657","2018-07-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when he plans to respond to the correspondence from the hon. Member for Colne Valley that was sent on the 23 May and again on 12 June 2018 on ambulance response times.","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163200","163200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938658","2018-07-16","Treasury","2018-07-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what figures his Department collects on high street bank closures.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163126","163126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938659","2018-07-16","Treasury","2018-07-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of trends in the number of job losses as a result of high street bank closures in the last five years.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163127","163127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938660","2018-07-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department is taking to support manufacturing jobs in (a) Ellesmere Port and Neston constituency, (b) the North West and (c) the UK.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163128","163128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938661","2018-07-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent estimate he has made of the number of workers in the (a) hospitality and (b) retail sectors who are paid less than the (i) national living wage and (ii) national minimum wage as a result of being required to work beyond the end of their shift.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163129","163129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938662","2018-07-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent assessment he has made of the prevalence of short-notice shift cancellation in the (a) retail and (b) hospitality sectors whereby employees arrive at work and are told they are not needed or are sent home before the end of their shift.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163130","163130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938663","2018-07-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what progress his Department has been made on producing guidance for people who have undertaken unpaid work trials.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163131","163131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938664","2018-07-16","Women and Equalities","2018-07-11","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, with reference to the Government’s response to the Taylor Review, published on 7 February 2018, when his Department plans to update the pregnancy and maternity discrimination pages on gov.uk.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163132","163132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938665","2018-07-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the Government’s response to the Taylor Review, published on 7 February 2018, when he plans to update public guidance for employers and workers on the rules for paying interns.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163133","163133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938666","2018-07-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Iranian counterpart on the case of Nazanin Zahari-Ratcliffe since his appointment as Foreign Secretary, and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163171","163171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938667","2018-07-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether (a) he and (b) Ministers in his Department have plans to visit Iran.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163172","163172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938668","2018-07-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has plans to seek diplomatic protection for Nazanin Zahari-Ratcliffe.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163173","163173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938669","2018-07-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make an estimate of the potential savings to the NHS budget of limiting access to gluten-free food via prescription.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163037","163037"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938670","2018-07-16","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of potential merits of bringing forward legislative changes to the Equality Act in order to ensure that claimants of housing benefit and universal credit are able to access accommodation in the private rented sector similar to such provisions in the Republic of Ireland.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162961","162961"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938671","2018-07-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to paragraph 6.14 of Autumn Budget 2017, what progress has been made on making it easier for claimants to have the housing element of their award paid directly to their landlord.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162962","162962"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938672","2018-07-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if his Department will take steps to notify private landlords, with a tenant’s permission, of the outcome of universal credit award decisions.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162963","162963"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938673","2018-07-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of enabling arrears in the private rented sector to be deducted from benefits after a tenant moves from one property to another.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162964","162964"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938674","2018-07-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what his policy is on the pre-authorisation of parental orders to enable legal parenthood to be conferred on surrogate parents at the point a child is born.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162965","162965"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938675","2018-07-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the (a) equity and (b) efficacy of existing time limits in relation to parental orders for surrogate parenthood.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162966","162966"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938676","2018-07-16","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what data his Department collects on parental orders and surrogate births; and what assessment he has made of the potential merits of ensuring greater transparency of that data.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162967","162967"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938677","2018-07-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information his Department holds on (a) the practices in place to allow medical professionals to identify fetal alcohol spectrum disorders in (i) newborn and (ii) young children and (b) how those cases are recorded.","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163201","163201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938678","2018-07-16","Scotland Office","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what overseas visits he has (a) been on since the beginning of 2018 and (b) planned for the rest of 2018 to promote the interests of (i) Scotland and (ii) Scottish trade.","Biography information for Lesley Laird","Lesley Laird","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163206","163206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938679","2018-07-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will introduce itemised bills for overseas visitors using NHS services; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163056","163056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938680","2018-07-16","Department for Transport","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate his Department has made of the cost of implementing the new community transport guidelines for charities and other community transport providers; and if his Department will alleviate those costs.","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163202","163202"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938681","2018-07-16","Scotland Office","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of automation on jobs in Scotland.","Biography information for Lesley Laird","Lesley Laird","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163207","163207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938682","2018-07-16","Department for Transport","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what consultations with charities and other providers of community transport his Department had prior to introducing new guidance on that matter.","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163203","163203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938683","2018-07-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions his Department has had with people diagnosed with Erythropoietic Protoporphyria on the decision by NICE not to license Scenesse for availability on the NHS.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163054","163054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938684","2018-07-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 26 June 2018 to Question 154743 on Surgical Mesh Implants, what recent discussions his Department has had with Dr Andrew Baranowski of the British Pain Society.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163139","163139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938685","2018-07-16","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the estimated date of disposal has changed for any of the disposal sites identified in his Department's Better Defence Estate Strategy of November 2016.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163028","163028"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938686","2018-07-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people under the age of 18 have presented at A&E in need of treatment for self-harm in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163163","163163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938687","2018-07-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people under the age of 18 have been treated in mental health units for self-harm in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163164","163164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938688","2018-07-16","Department for Education","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many maintained nursery schools there are in (a) London and (b) England.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163165","163165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938689","2018-07-16","Department for Education","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many maintained nursery schools there were in (a) London and (b) England in (i) 2000, (ii) 2010 and (iii) 2017.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163166","163166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938690","2018-07-16","Home Office","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate he has made of the number of people who have applied for the right to reside in the UK as carers under Ruiz-Zambrano case law since 2011; and of those people how many were successful.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163108","163108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938691","2018-07-16","Department for Education","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many private nursery schools there were in (a) London and (b) England as of 1 July 2018.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163167","163167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938692","2018-07-16","Department for Education","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many private nursery schools there were in (a) London and (b) England in (i) 2000, (ii) 2010 and (iii) 2017.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163168","163168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938693","2018-07-16","Home Office","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will provide a breakdown by nationality of people who have (a) applied for and (b) been successful in their applications for the right to reside in the UK as carers under Ruiz-Zambrano case law since 2011.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163109","163109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938694","2018-07-16","Home Office","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate he has made of the number of people resident in the UK who derive their right to reside from their status as primary carers under Ruiz-Zambrano case law.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163110","163110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938695","2018-07-16","Department for Education","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of maintained nursery schools were rated (a) good and (b) outstanding at their last Ofsted inspection.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163169","163169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938696","2018-07-16","Home Office","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans he has to bring forward proposals on the status of Zambrano carers after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163111","163111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938697","2018-07-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate his Department has made of the (a) value and (b) volume of (i) plant material, (ii) meat or animal material and (iii) other food products imported at each point of entry into the UK; and what records of those imports are make at each point of entry.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163122","163122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938698","2018-07-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions he has had with HMRC on the capacity of its customs computer system for plant and animal imports to process potential increased volumes of applications after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163123","163123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938699","2018-07-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to help ensure the supply of (a) olanzapine and (b) quetiapine meets demand for those drugs.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162968","162968"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938700","2018-07-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what representations his Department has made to manufacturers of (a) olanzapine and (b) quetiapine on the supply of those drugs since 2017.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162969","162969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938701","2018-07-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the terms of reference of the Independent Review of the Financial Reporting Council 2018, if he will publish summary meeting notes for all meetings of that review.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163124","163124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938702","2018-07-16","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will place in the Library a copy of the written evidence submitted by his Department to the High Court in respect of the judicial review being brought by Christchurch Borough Council scheduled for a hearing on 30 July 2018.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Sir Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162972","162972"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938703","2018-07-16","Department for Education","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many private nursery schools were rated (a) Good and (b) Outstanding at their last Ofsted inspection.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163170","163170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938704","2018-07-16","Department for Education","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of (a) maintained nursery schools, (b) local authority maintained primary schools, (c) maintained secondary schools, (d) primary academies and (e) secondary academy schools were in budget deficit in (i) the last and (ii) each of the preceding three financial years.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163116","163116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938705","2018-07-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, which marine life and seabed habitats have been identified for protection in the proposed marine conservation zone at Selsey Bill and the Hounds.","Biography information for Gillian Keegan","Gillian Keegan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163226","163226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938706","2018-07-16","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what consultations he is undertaking with (a) Christchurch Borough Council and (b) East Dorset District Council on the content of potential draft secondary legislation on future harmonisation of council taxes in Dorset.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Sir Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162973","162973"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938707","2018-07-16","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 23 April 2018 to Question 135849 on National Citizen Service Trust, whether around £9,781,587 has been written off by the Government for places that were not filled in 2016 for the National Citizen Service.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163141","163141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938708","2018-07-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will take account of the Royal Society's update of its report of June 2012 on shale gas extraction before continuing his plans to extract such gas.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163047","163047"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938709","2018-07-16","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 23 April 2018 to Question 135849, whether a delivery partner of the National Citizen Service programme is permitted to profit from their service delivery contracts.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163142","163142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938710","2018-07-16","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what the timetable is for the Government's publication of draft secondary legislation on local government reorganisation in Dorset; and what account the Government is taking of the consequences for that timetable of the timing of the hearing on 30 July 2018 of the judicial review application being brought by Christchurch Borough Council on local government reorganisation in Dorset.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Sir Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162974","162974"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938711","2018-07-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of recent attacks upon Christians in the Indian state of Tamil Nadu.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162977","162977"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938712","2018-07-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will deposit in the National Archives the Registers of Births, Deaths and Marriages for the Chagos Archipelago between 1884 and 1971.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163140","163140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938713","2018-07-16","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether the National Citizen Service Trust has plans to collaborate with the Parliament Education Service in the summer of 2018 to increase citizenship and democratic engagement.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163143","163143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938714","2018-07-16","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice,  how many people have an outstanding statutory charge placed by the Legal Aid Agency against their property.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162954","162954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938715","2018-07-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many prescriptions of (a) individual benzodiazepine drugs and (b) individual antidepressants were dispensed in the community in 2017.","Biography information for Darren Jones","Darren Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163180","163180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938716","2018-07-16","Department for Education","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will publish the number of permanent exclusions from school as a proportion of the overall school population in each local authority area in each of the last five years where figures are available.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162978","162978"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938717","2018-07-16","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what progress his Department has made on the rural proofing of its policies.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162947","162947"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938718","2018-07-16","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the (a) mean and (b) median amount owed is on outstanding statutory charges placed by the Legal Aid Agency.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162955","162955"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938719","2018-07-16","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that viewers can easily find public service content outside of the main electronic  programming guide.","Biography information for Darren Jones","Darren Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163181","163181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938720","2018-07-16","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what guidance his Department provides to local authorities on the consideration that local planning authorities should give to the position of general aviation aerodromes in a network when determining planning applications to remove such aerodromes from use.","Biography information for Sir Paul Beresford","Sir Paul Beresford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162941","162941"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938721","2018-07-16","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the (a) mean and (b) median amount of interest owed is for statutory charges placed by the Legal Aid Agency.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162956","162956"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938722","2018-07-16","Treasury","2018-07-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of the change in the value of the pound on private pension funds since the EU referendum.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163158","163158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938723","2018-07-16","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what his policy is on the mixed-use development of aerodromes.","Biography information for Sir Paul Beresford","Sir Paul Beresford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162942","162942"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938724","2018-07-16","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether planning for General Aviation is included in the new National Planning Policy Framework.","Biography information for Sir Paul Beresford","Sir Paul Beresford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162943","162943"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938725","2018-07-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he plans to pay the pension arrears owing to the former members of HM's overseas civil service who remained at their posts after Southern Rhodesia became independent.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162948","162948"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938726","2018-07-16","Home Office","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if his Department plans to require EU citizens arriving in the UK for the first time during the implementation period and intending to apply for pre-settled status to also register their stay.","Biography information for Steve Double","Steve Double","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163144","163144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938727","2018-07-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people were in receipt of the state pension in (a) 2010 and (b) 2018 in Linlithgow and East Falkirk constituency.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163159","163159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938728","2018-07-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many children under the age of 18 were treated in A&E for a mental health crisis in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163083","163083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938729","2018-07-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent steps he has taken to ensure the adequate provision of EpiPen 0.3mg Adrenaline Auto-Injectors in the UK; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jo Swinson","Jo Swinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163039","163039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938730","2018-07-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he has had recent discussions with his Scottish counterpart on the adequate provision of EpiPen 0.3mg Adrenaline Auto-Injectors in the UK.","Biography information for Jo Swinson","Jo Swinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163040","163040"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938731","2018-07-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent discussions he has had with representatives of Pfizer on the supply of an adequate number of EpiPen 0.3mg Adrenaline Auto-Injectors to the UK.","Biography information for Jo Swinson","Jo Swinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163041","163041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938732","2018-07-16","Department for Education","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to ensure that schools raise awareness of mental health problems experienced by children and young people.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163038","163038"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938733","2018-07-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of trends in the number of children being treated in A&E for a mental health crisis since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163084","163084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938734","2018-07-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he plans to take to increase support for children experiencing mental ill health to prevent them from presenting with a mental health crisis at A&E.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163085","163085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938735","2018-07-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information his Department holds on the timetable for publication of the systematic review of the evidence relating to the mental health of children and young people carried out by the National Collaborating Centre for Mental Health and University College London used to inform the Government's Green Paper of December 2017, Transforming Children and Young People's Mental Health Provision, Cm 9523.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163086","163086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/937715","2018-07-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what progress he has made on ensuring the protection of UK food products through a protected designation of origin scheme after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Richard Graham","Richard Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 906415","906415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/937721","2018-07-12","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of trends in the number of high street store closures throughout the UK in 2018; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162480","162480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/937722","2018-07-12","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment his Department has made of the cumulative effect on local economies of the closures of high street stores in (a) the North East and (b) the UK in 2018.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162481","162481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/937723","2018-07-12","Treasury","2018-07-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment he has made of trends in the level of bank branch closures in the North East; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162482","162482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/937724","2018-07-16","Home Office","2018-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate he has made of the number of families where family members are held in separate immigration detention centres.","Biography information for Kate Hollern","Kate Hollern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162581","162581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/937725","2018-07-16","Home Office","2018-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he has plans to increase the (a) staff and (b) resources of his Department to ensure that decisions on applications for visas are made within target times.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162572","162572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/937726","2018-07-12","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that the service sector has tariff-free access to the Single Market after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Kate Hollern","Kate Hollern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162582","162582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/937727","2018-07-12","Department for Transport","2018-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the importance of rail research and development to the UK rail industry.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162579","162579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/937728","2018-07-12","Treasury","2018-07-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps the Government is taking to help keep fuel prices for motorists low.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162580","162580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/937729","2018-07-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how often staff in her Department that monitor the online journals for universal credit are notified when someone posts on their online journal.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162573","162573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/937730","2018-07-16","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that internet service providers remove incorrect information relating to business locations when informed of errors by affected people.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162574","162574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/937731","2018-07-16","Department for Education","2018-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when nationality and country of birth data collected by schools for immigration purposes in the 2016-18 school census will be deleted as required by the Education Act 1996.","Biography information for Darren Jones","Darren Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162611","162611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/937732","2018-07-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether the NHS provides guidance to new Mothers on potential links between breast feeding and diabetes.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162559","162559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/937733","2018-07-16","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will take steps to provide additional protection to tenants facing eviction as a result of the end of an assured shorthold tenancy.","Biography information for Kate Hollern","Kate Hollern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162583","162583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/937734","2018-07-12","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department is taking to engage with staff unions to reduce staff turnover in HMCTS; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162560","162560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/937735","2018-07-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he takes to ensure that drugs are sold to the NHS at a price which represents value for money to the public purse.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162561","162561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/937736","2018-07-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he has recently had discussions with the Royal College of Nursing on the link between BRCA genes and breast cancer; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162562","162562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/937737","2018-07-12","Treasury","2018-07-10","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether his Department takes steps to provide tax relief to young first-time drivers for their first year of car insurance.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162563","162563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/937738","2018-07-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make it his policy to provide targeted support for people over the age of 55 who have problems with alcohol.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162564","162564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/937739","2018-07-16","Department for Transport","2018-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what progress is being made on plans for electrification of the trans-pennine railway line.","Biography information for Kate Hollern","Kate Hollern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162584","162584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/937740","2018-07-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department has had discussions with (a) the Royal College of Nursing and (b) patients with blood group O on potential supply problems of blood group O.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162565","162565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/937741","2018-07-16","Department for Education","2018-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference the Industrial Training (Construction Board) Order 1964 (Amendment) Order 1992, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of extending the scope of the Construction Industry Training Board to include glaziers.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162592","162592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/937742","2018-07-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans are in place to ensure that veterinary surgeons working in meat hygiene from (a) other EU member states and (b) non-EU states to access their pensions if they are no longer domiciled in the UK after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162459","162459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/937743","2018-07-16","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent assessment he has made of adequacy of funding for supported contact centres by Cafcass.","Biography information for Darren Jones","Darren Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162612","162612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/937744","2018-07-16","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the effect of the General Data Protection Regulation on organisations operating on a not-for-profit basis; and what steps he is taking to minimise administrative costs placed on those organisations as a result of the General Data Protection Regulation.","Biography information for Darren Jones","Darren Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162613","162613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/937745","2018-07-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to ensure that all disability and medical assessment centres are accessible to all constituents.","Biography information for Darren Jones","Darren Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162614","162614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/937746","2018-07-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps her Department is taking to ensure the maintenance of access to services in the event that a contracted assessment centre is rendered temporarily inaccessible.","Biography information for Darren Jones","Darren Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162615","162615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/937747","2018-07-12","Treasury","2018-07-10","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 9 July 2018 to Question 160685 on Midland Metropolitan Hospital: Repairs and Maintenance, how many times (a) he (b) Ministers in his Department and (c) official in his Department have had meetings with counterparts in the Department for Health and Social Care on Midland Metropolitan Hospital since January 2018; and what the dates were of those meetings.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162471","162471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/937748","2018-07-12","Home Office","2018-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of  2 July 2018 to Question 157630 on UK Border Force: Heathrow Airport, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that UK Border Force has the capacity deal with the forecast increase in the number of passengers in the summer.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162472","162472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/937749","2018-07-16","Cabinet Office","2018-07-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 6 July to Question 160071 on Payment Performance Data, and with reference to the Second Joint report from the Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy and Work and Pensions Committees of Session 2017–19 on Carillion, HC 769, when he plans to publish Payment Performance Data consolidated across all Government Departments, Executive Agencies and Non Departmental Public Bodies.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162474","162474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/937750","2018-07-16","Home Office","2018-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, in what form his Department records incidents of (a) metal and (b) stone theft from heritage buildings; and how many of those incidents to place in each month of this year.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham P Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162529","162529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/937751","2018-07-16","Home Office","2018-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 19 June 2018 to Question 153803 on Metals: Theft, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to ban squatting in commercial properties to prevent the theft of (a) metal and (b) other commodities from those properties.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham P Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162530","162530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/937752","2018-07-16","Home Office","2018-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many and what proportion of metal theft crimes were committed alongside incidences of illegal occupation of commercial premises.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham P Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162531","162531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/937753","2018-07-16","Home Office","2018-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to her Answer of 2 July to Question 157630 on UK Border Force: Heathrow, how many times UK Border Force did not meet its target for processing non-EEA nationals at Heathrow in the first six months of this year and what the comparable figure was for 2017.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162473","162473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/937754","2018-07-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what comparative assessment his Department has made of the  welfare of (a) caged and (b) non-caged game birds; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162527","162527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/937755","2018-07-12","Cabinet Office","2018-07-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the five most common cancer diagnoses were among (a) men and (b) women in (i) 2007 and (ii) 2017.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162495","162495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/937756","2018-07-16","Scotland Office","2018-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what discussions he has had with Cabinet colleagues on the support available to Scotland’s agriculture, food and farming sectors to ensure that all business transactions and procedures remain consistent after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Lesley Laird","Lesley Laird","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162625","162625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/937757","2018-07-16","Scotland Office","2018-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what discussions he has had with Cabinet colleagues on the support available to Scotland’s manufacturing and construction sectors to ensure that all business transactions and procedures remain consistent after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Lesley Laird","Lesley Laird","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162626","162626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/937758","2018-07-16","Scotland Office","2018-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what discussions he has had with Cabinet colleagues on the support available to Scotland’s banking and financial sectors to ensure that all business transactions and procedures remain consistent after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Lesley Laird","Lesley Laird","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162627","162627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/937759","2018-07-16","Scotland Office","2018-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what discussions he has had with Cabinet colleagues on the support available to Scotland’s life sciences sector to ensure that all business transactions and procedures remain consistent after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Lesley Laird","Lesley Laird","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162628","162628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/937760","2018-07-16","Scotland Office","2018-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, whether he has discussions with food bank service providers in Scotland in the last twelve months; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lesley Laird","Lesley Laird","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162629","162629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/937761","2018-07-12","Scotland Office","2018-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, whether he has had discussions with the Secretary of State for International Trade on extending existing fur import bans to cover all species exploited by the fur trade; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lesley Laird","Lesley Laird","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162630","162630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/937762","2018-07-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent progress his Department has made being made on establishing a site for a UK space launch facility.","Biography information for Jamie Stone","Jamie Stone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162607","162607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/937763","2018-07-16","Home Office","2018-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what additional funding his Department has allocated to local police forces for the policing of fracking sites.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162620","162620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/937764","2018-07-12","Prime Minister","2018-07-10","To ask the Prime Minister, when she plans to publish the declaration of interest of the new Attorney General.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162502","162502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/937765","2018-07-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much funding his Department plans to allocate to brain tumour research in each of the next five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162478","162478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/937766","2018-07-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much funding his Department has allocated to brain tumour research in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162479","162479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/937767","2018-07-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans he has to continue funding National Trails beyond the current financial year.","Biography information for Sir Hugo Swire","Sir Hugo Swire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162491","162491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/937768","2018-07-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of including National Trails in the ongoing review of National Parks and Areas of Outstanding Natural Beauty.","Biography information for Sir Hugo Swire","Sir Hugo Swire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162492","162492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/937769","2018-07-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to promote use of National Trails.","Biography information for Sir Hugo Swire","Sir Hugo Swire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162493","162493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/937770","2018-07-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate he has made of the number of people who use National Trails every year.","Biography information for Sir Hugo Swire","Sir Hugo Swire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162494","162494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/937771","2018-07-16","Department for Education","2018-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the timetable is for the next School Teachers’ Review Body report to be published.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162549","162549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/937772","2018-07-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he has plans to authorise a national clinical audit of ovarian cancer; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162542","162542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/937773","2018-07-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many Chairs of NHS Trusts in the North West have previously been Chairs of other NHS trusts; and if he will list those Chairs.","Biography information for Christian Matheson","Christian Matheson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162588","162588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/937774","2018-07-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to increase ovarian cancer survival rates.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162543","162543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/937775","2018-07-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to increase the level of early diagnosis of ovarian cancer.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162544","162544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/937776","2018-07-16","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the independent report written by the hon. Member for Ludlow entitled Growing the contribution of defence to UK prosperity, published by his Department on 9 July 2018, if he will issue a formal response to each recommendation made in that report.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162496","162496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/937777","2018-07-16","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 9 July 2018 to Question 160710 on Patrol Craft, whether his Department exempted the orders for Batch 2 River-class offshore patrol vessels from international competition under Article 346 of the Treaty on the Functioning of the European Union.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162497","162497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/937778","2018-07-12","Cabinet Office","2018-07-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether his Department has estimated the potential cost of introducing voter ID requirements in every polling station throughout England for the next scheduled general election.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162590","162590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/937779","2018-07-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 27 June 2018 to Question 155725 on Energy: Environment Protection, whether he plans to publish a Clean Energy Sector Deal in (a) 3 months, (b) 6 months, (c) 9 months, (d) 12 months.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162508","162508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/937780","2018-07-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he has plans for his Department to become accredited by the National Living Wage Foundation.","Biography information for Wera Hobhouse","Wera Hobhouse","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162604","162604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/937781","2018-07-16","Cabinet Office","2018-07-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, which (a) Executive Agencies, (b) non-ministerial government departments and (c) non-departmental public bodies are accredited by the National Living Wage Foundation in relation to  paying the real living wage.","Biography information for Wera Hobhouse","Wera Hobhouse","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162605","162605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/937782","2018-07-16","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when he plans to publish an Answer to Question 152827 tabled by the hon. Member for Dwyfor Meirionnydd on 12 June 2018.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162597","162597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/937783","2018-07-16","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether he has plans for his Department to be accredited by the National Living Wage Foundation in relation to paying the real living wage; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Wera Hobhouse","Wera Hobhouse","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162606","162606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/937784","2018-07-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to tackle abuse of NHS staff by (a) patients and (b) relatives of patients.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162575","162575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/937785","2018-07-16","Home Office","2018-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate he has made of the cost that will be incurred by South Yorkshire Police Force of the official visit of the President of the United States.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162475","162475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/937786","2018-07-16","Home Office","2018-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps his Department is taking to support people from economically disadvantaged backgrounds with the cost of applications for child citizenship.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162603","162603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/937787","2018-07-16","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent steps he is taking to reduce waiting times for personal independence payment tribunals.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162484","162484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/937788","2018-07-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate he has made of the proportion of the cost of recycling borne by (a) manufacturers and producers and (b) consumers.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162483","162483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/937789","2018-07-12","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the causes of the damage to a Royal Air Force C-130J in operations against Daesh in Syria in August 2017; and whether any British service personnel were harmed in that operation.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162457","162457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/937790","2018-07-16","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment his Department has made of the effects of waiting times for PIP tribunals on vulnerable people.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162485","162485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/937791","2018-07-16","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many and what proportion of houses rented by his Department have been unoccupied in each of the last five years; and how much rent his Department has paid for those houses in each of those years.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162509","162509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/937792","2018-07-12","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 16 March 2018 to Question 132273 on Ministry of Defence: Empty Property, whether any of those unoccupied houses are being used by his Department for training or exercises.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162510","162510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/937793","2018-07-12","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 16 March 2018 to Question 132273 on Ministry of Defence: Empty Property, what plans he has to return those house back to Annington Homes; and what estimate he has made of the dilapidation costs.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162511","162511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/937794","2018-07-16","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 16 March 2018 to Question 132273 on Ministry of Defence: Empty Property, if he will list the (a) parliamentary constituencies and (b) local authority areas those void properties are in.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162512","162512"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/937795","2018-07-12","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 16 March 2018 to Question 132273, on Ministry of Defence: Empty Property, what the average number of bedrooms is in those void properties.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162513","162513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/937796","2018-07-12","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 16 March 2018 to Question 132273 on Ministry of Defence: Empty Property, how many of those empty properties are (a) Officers’ Families’ Quarters and (b) Servicemen’s Families’ Quarters.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162514","162514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/937797","2018-07-12","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 16 March 2018 to Question 132273, on Ministry of Defence: Empty Property, what grade those empty properties are under (a) the 4 Tier Grading System and (b) the Combined Accommodation Assessment System.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162515","162515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/937798","2018-07-16","Department for Transport","2018-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, on what date he plans to publish his Department's annual report and accounts for 2017-18.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162532","162532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/937799","2018-07-16","Department for Transport","2018-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 16 March 2018 to Question 132026 on Railways: Franchises, if he will place an updated copy of the contracted franchise payment profiles for all train operating companies in the Library before the summer recess.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162533","162533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/937800","2018-07-12","Cabinet Office","2018-07-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 18 June 2018 to Question 150180 on Elections: Freedom of Information, what steps the Government plans to take to (a) maintain the secrecy of voting and (b) ensure that voters can not be identified as a result of bringing Returning Officers under the Freedom of Information Act.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162591","162591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/937801","2018-07-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many women and girls have been admitted to hospital with toxic shock syndrome in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Rosie Duffield","Rosie Duffield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162609","162609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/937802","2018-07-12","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many family legal help starts by type of family law there were in each quarter since the first quarter of 2012.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162517","162517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/937803","2018-07-12","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) civil legal help and (b) civil representation provider offices there were in each legal aid area in each quarter since the first quarter of 2012.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162518","162518"
