"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76744","2014-07-14","Department for Education","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when data on children's travel behaviour stopped being collected as part of the School Census.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204703","204703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76745","2014-07-14","Department for Education","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, in how many schools in England is lead paint present.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204968","204968"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76746","2014-07-14","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what recent assessment his Department has made of the effect of climate change on global sea levels.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204914","204914"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76747","2014-07-14","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many journeys Ministers of his Department have made using the Government Car Service; and how many such journeys were for the transportation of a red box.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204936","204936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76748","2014-07-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many people were employed by the Environment Agency in a full-time capacity in each month since June 2010.","Biography information for Tom Greatrex","Tom Greatrex","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204990","204990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76749","2014-07-14","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many people have been employed full-time by the Office of Unconventional Gas and Oil in each month since June 2010.","Biography information for Tom Greatrex","Tom Greatrex","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204857","204857"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76750","2014-07-14","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment he has made of the quantity of shale gas in the Bowland reserve that is located (a) above and (b) below a depth of one kilometre from the surface.","Biography information for Tom Greatrex","Tom Greatrex","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204858","204858"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76751","2014-07-14","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what forecast he has made of the price of uranium between 2023 and 2058.","Biography information for Tom Greatrex","Tom Greatrex","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204859","204859"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76752","2014-07-14","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate he has made of the amount of electricity that passed through interconnections from (a) England to Scotland and (b) Scotland to England in each month since January 2010.","Biography information for Tom Greatrex","Tom Greatrex","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204953","204953"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76753","2014-07-14","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of measures to compensate householders who suffer faulty work under the Affordable Warmth Obligation.","Biography information for Mr John Denham","Mr John Denham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204877","204877"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76754","2014-07-14","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if he will estimate how much money his Department has spent in Morecambe and Lunesdale constituency since May 2010.","Biography information for David Morris","David Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204775","204775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76755","2014-07-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the cost to a local authority of processing an environmental impact assessment for unconventional oil and gas extraction.","Biography information for Tom Greatrex","Tom Greatrex","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204827","204827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76756","2014-07-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the future prospects for farmlands and the pressures posed by a growing population and increased use of energy crops.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204831","204831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76757","2014-07-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will estimate how much money his Department has spent in Morecambe and Lunesdale constituency since May 2010.","Biography information for David Morris","David Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204776","204776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76758","2014-07-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what his policy is on the inclusion of Upper Lune Valley in the (a) Cumbrian National Park and (b) Trough of Bowland area of outstanding natural beauty.","Biography information for David Morris","David Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204798","204798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76759","2014-07-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to encourage investment in agricultural technologies to increase the efficiency of food production.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204794","204794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76760","2014-07-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, which organisations, groups and industry bodies his Department has met since 2010 to discuss lost commercial fishing gear and its effect on UK waters and marine animals.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204909","204909"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76761","2014-07-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what proportion of commercial landings of fish and shellfish from UK-registered fishing vessels were taken from a depth below 800 metres in (a) 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012 and (d) 2013.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204911","204911"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76762","2014-07-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what tonnage of fish and shellfish quota was allocated to the UK under the Deep Sea Access Regime in (a) 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012 and (d) 2013.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204912","204912"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76763","2014-07-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether his Department is working with the fishing industry to ensure lost commercial fishing gear is reported to relevant authorities in line with requirements under (a) the Common Fisheries Policy and (b) other international agreements.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204913","204913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76764","2014-07-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much funding was awarded under the Farming and Forestry Improvement Scheme to (a) Westmorland and Lonsdale, (b) Cumbria and (c) North West England; and what the (i) type and (ii) purpose was of the funding provided in each such area.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204835","204835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76765","2014-07-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the financial effect on hill farmers of recent changes to the CAP which takes into account the abolition of the Uplands Entry Level Stewardship and the increase in the moorlands rate and the severely disadvantaged area rate.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204823","204823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76766","2014-07-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many journeys Ministers of his Department have made using the Government Car Service; and how many such journeys were for the transportation of a red box.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204937","204937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76767","2014-07-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many UK-registered fishing vessels practise bottom trawling below a depth of 600 metres; and for what proportion of time spent at sea those bottom trawlers trawl below (a) 600 metres and (b) 800 metres.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204910","204910"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76768","2014-07-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 8 July 2014, Official Report, column 175W, on Food Supply Networks Review, how many times he has met Professor Chris Elliott since March 2014.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204975","204975"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76769","2014-07-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what proportion of the total commercial landings of fish and shellfish from UK registered fishing vessels was taken from a depth below 600 metres in (a) 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012 and (d) 2013.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204919","204919"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76770","2014-07-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to quantify and mitigate the effects of abandoned, lost and discarded fishing gear in UK and international waters.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204920","204920"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76771","2014-07-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the efficacy of EU restrictive measures against Côte d'Ivoire.","Biography information for Stephen Phillips","Stephen Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204917","204917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76772","2014-07-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many journeys Ministers of his Department have made using the Government Car Service; and how many such journeys were for the transportation of a red box.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204938","204938"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76773","2014-07-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent reports he has received on the Palestinian Authority's policy of payment of salaries to the families of convicted terrorists; what information his Department holds on the basis and scale of such payments; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Peter Bone","Mr Peter Bone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204894","204894"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76774","2014-07-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what support his Department is providing to the government of Niger to assist it to tackle terrorism and organised crime.","Biography information for Stephen Phillips","Stephen Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204915","204915"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76775","2014-07-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of progress made by Albania towards EU accession candidate status.","Biography information for Stephen Phillips","Stephen Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204916","204916"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76776","2014-07-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what policy statements were announced by the Government at the Our Ocean conference held on 16 and 17 June 2014; and what steps the Government plans to take to implement those proposals.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204954","204954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76777","2014-07-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many staff of his Department have been seconded to (a) other Ministries of Foreign Affairs and (b) international organisations in each year since 2010; and to which (i) other Ministries of Foreign Affairs and (ii) international organisations such staff have been seconded.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204741","204741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76778","2014-07-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how much his Department has spent from the Conflict Pool in each country in each year since its launch.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204829","204829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76779","2014-07-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 3 July 2014, Official Report, column 735W, on the South Pacific, what his Department is projected to spend on the Senior Pacific Police Leadership Programme in (a) 2014-15 and (b) 2015-16; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204830","204830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76780","2014-07-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will discuss with his Chinese counterpart the case of Zhang Shaojie, a Christian leader in Henan Province, who has been jailed for 12 years.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204848","204848"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76781","2014-07-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the eligibility criteria are for projects requiring Conflict Pool funding.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204734","204734"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76782","2014-07-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how much has been spent on the GREAT campaign in each country in each year since the campaign's launch.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204736","204736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76783","2014-07-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many secondees from which other Ministries of Foreign Affairs  his Department has received in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204742","204742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76784","2014-07-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the cost was of his Department's Black and Minority Ethnic campaign.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204743","204743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76785","2014-07-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to the Colombian government on the harassment of the Patriotic March leader David Florez in Colombia on 7 July 2014.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204785","204785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76786","2014-07-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer to the hon. Member for Chichester, Official Report, column 172W, on 8 July 2014, on Diego Garcia, for what reason records of flight occurrence logs were water damaged; in what format the records are kept; and whether that format has been changed since the damage.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204744","204744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76787","2014-07-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what information his Department holds on (a) the number of UK citizens employed by EU institutions and (b) the proportion of the annual staff budget of the European Parliament spent on staff salaries for UK citizens.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204783","204783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76788","2014-07-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many diplomatic cars have been sold by his Department in each year since 2010; how much each car was sold for; and how much was raised in total from such sales.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204737","204737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76789","2014-07-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how much each (a) HM Embassy and (b) UK High Commission spend on hosting a party to mark the official birthday of HM Queen Elizabeth II in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204740","204740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76790","2014-07-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many individuals in his Department have participated in (a) Disability awareness and (b) Lesbian, Gay, Bisexual and Transgender training in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204738","204738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76791","2014-07-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what professional courses civil servants in his Department have attended since 2010; and how many officials attended each such course.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204739","204739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76792","2014-07-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many complaints of sexual harassment in his Department have been (a) formally reported and (b) upheld in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204735","204735"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76793","2014-07-14","Department of Health","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of GPs needed to eliminate any shortfall in primary health care.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204732","204732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76794","2014-07-14","Cabinet Office","2014-07-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many babies have been born at Warrington Hospital in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204786","204786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76795","2014-07-14","Department of Health","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to support the carers of people who have dementia.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204715","204715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76796","2014-07-14","Department of Health","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he intends to take to ensure that women are made aware of the abortifacient nature of the drug ulipristal acetate; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204752","204752"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76797","2014-07-14","Department of Health","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to monitor the standard of care received by cancer patients and to reduce regional variations in the standard of such care.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204712","204712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76798","2014-07-14","Department of Health","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to improve out-of-hours primary care provision and to minimise dependence on accident and emergency facilities to provide primary care.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204729","204729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76799","2014-07-14","Department of Health","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions his Department had in advance of the decision to end the independent production of the annual report to Parliament on research and development work relating to assistive technology and to reduce the scope of that report.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204749","204749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76800","2014-07-14","Department of Health","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent representations he has received from doctors on the reforms in GP contracts needed to increase the number of GPs.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204730","204730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76801","2014-07-14","Department of Health","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to increase GP numbers.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204731","204731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76802","2014-07-14","Department of Health","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he will lay before Parliament the 2013-14 report on research and development work relating to assistive technology.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204719","204719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76803","2014-07-14","Department of Health","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will include forming and developing relationship in the eligibility criteria of the Care Act 2014 Part 1 regulations.","Biography information for Oliver Colvile","Oliver Colvile","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204705","204705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76804","2014-07-16","Department of Health","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with NHS England on Specialised Services Circular 1407 and its potential effect on the use of robotic assisted surgery; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stewart Jackson","Mr Stewart Jackson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204682","204682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76805","2014-07-15","Department of Health","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will ask NHS England to establish a Clinical Reference Group for Robotic Assisted Surgery to consider the use of technology across the full range of specialties where the Da Vinci system can be used; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stewart Jackson","Mr Stewart Jackson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204683","204683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76806","2014-07-15","Department of Health","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will ask NHS England to amend Specialised Services Circular 1407 to allow NHS trusts to continue to train surgeons on the use of robotic assisted surgery in the absence of a national commissioning policy.","Biography information for Mr Stewart Jackson","Mr Stewart Jackson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204688","204688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76807","2014-07-15","Department of Health","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the net cost of supported living in (a) Ribble Valley constituency, (b) Lancashire and (c) the UK.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204689","204689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76808","2014-07-15","Department of Health","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the net cost of intentional communities in (a) Ribble Valley constituency, (b) Lancashire and (c) the UK.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204690","204690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76809","2014-07-15","Department of Health","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many intentional communities have closed in (a) Ribble Valley constituency, (b) Lancashire and (c) the UK since 2005; and how many remain open in each area.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204691","204691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76810","2014-07-15","Department of Health","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people were in supported living or intentional communities in (a) Ribble Valley constituency, (b) Lancashire and (c) the UK in 2005.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204692","204692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76811","2014-07-14","Department of Health","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the proportion of funding from the NHS's budget which goes to private sector companies and which is spent on (a) healthcare and (b) shareholder dividend.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204856","204856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76812","2014-07-16","Department of Health","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people in England on end-of-life registers were in work for each of the last five years.","Biography information for Liz Kendall","Liz Kendall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204905","204905"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76813","2014-07-14","Department of Health","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect on overall satisfaction levels of waiting times for GP appointments; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Richard Graham","Richard Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204832","204832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76814","2014-07-14","Department of Health","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will estimate how much money his Department has spent in Morecambe and Lunesdale constituency since May 2010.","Biography information for David Morris","David Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204777","204777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76815","2014-07-14","Department of Health","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the targets are on waiting times for appointments within the latest GP contract.","Biography information for Richard Graham","Richard Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204796","204796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76816","2014-07-14","Department of Health","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the proportion of GPs work taken up by administration; and what changes there have been in that proportion in the last five years.","Biography information for Richard Graham","Richard Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204797","204797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76817","2014-07-14","Department of Health","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to improve pancreatic cancer survival rates.","Biography information for Mike Gapes","Mike Gapes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204847","204847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76818","2014-07-14","Department of Health","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to increase research funding for pancreatic cancer treatments.","Biography information for Mike Gapes","Mike Gapes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204844","204844"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76819","2014-07-14","Department of Health","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people aged under 18 have presented at accident and emergency departments in need of treatment for self-harm at hospitals in the Greater Birmingham area in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204952","204952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76820","2014-07-14","Department of Health","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure earlier diagnosis of pancreatic cancer.","Biography information for Mike Gapes","Mike Gapes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204845","204845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76821","2014-07-14","Department of Health","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that GPs make earlier referrals in cases of possible pancreatic cancer.","Biography information for Mike Gapes","Mike Gapes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204846","204846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76822","2014-07-14","Department of Health","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many non-specialist trust acute hospitals were in financial deficit at the end of the 2013-14 financial year.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204958","204958"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76823","2014-07-14","Department of Health","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) radiographers and (b) radiologists were in practice in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Baroness McIntosh of Pickering","Miss Anne McIntosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204908","204908"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76824","2014-07-14","Department of Health","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the performance of the Innovation, Health and Wealth programme; and what the costs of the programme to date have been in respect of (a) the NHS and (b) external consultancies.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204839","204839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76825","2014-07-14","Department of Health","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to his Department's publication, The NHS as an Innovative Organisation: A Framework and Guidance on the Management of Intellectual Property in the NHS, published in 2002, which of the conclusions of that report have been adopted; and what assessment he has made of the effect on the NHS of their adoption.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204840","204840"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76826","2014-07-14","Department of Health","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 18 June 2014, Official Report, column 617W, on the NHS, if he will ensure that his Department's proposals arising from the Innovation, Health and Wealth review of NHS intellectual property that was completed in Autumn 2012 will be published before the summer recess.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204841","204841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76827","2014-07-14","Department of Health","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which neuro-oncology centres in the UK have the highest survival rates for patients with brain tumours.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204863","204863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76828","2014-07-14","Department of Health","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the mean and median waiting time for treatment in Warrington Hospital's accident and emergency department was in 2007-08 and in each year since.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204864","204864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76829","2014-07-14","Department of Health","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the implications for the NHS of the decision by the General Dental Council to raise their compulsory statutory annual retention fee from £576 per annum to £945 per annum.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204838","204838"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76830","2014-07-14","Department of Health","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many full-time equivalent GPs were working in Warrington in each year since 2007-08.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204865","204865"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76831","2014-07-14","Department of Health","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many journeys Ministers of his Department have made using the Government Car Service; and how many such journeys were for the transportation of a red box.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204939","204939"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76832","2014-07-14","Cabinet Office","2014-07-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many early deaths from cancer have occurred among (a) men and (b) women in each local authority area in each year since 2001; and what proportion of those diagnosed with cancer such deaths represented.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204962","204962"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76833","2014-07-14","Department of Health","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of whether childhood exposure to lead can lead to the early onset of dementia.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204967","204967"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76834","2014-07-14","Home Office","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average time taken for the Director General, UK Visas and Immigration to reply to hon. Members in (a) all and (b) urgent visit visa cases was in the last 12 months; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mike Gapes","Mike Gapes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204979","204979"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76835","2014-07-14","Home Office","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what guidance she has issued to UK Visas and Immigration Directorate on responding to hon. Members' representations on visit visa cases.","Biography information for Mike Gapes","Mike Gapes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204977","204977"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76836","2014-07-14","Home Office","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when the hon. Member for Ilford South will receive a reply from the Director General, UK Visas and Immigration to the urgent representations he made on behalf of his constituents Mr and Mrs Mehta on 16 June 2014; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mike Gapes","Mike Gapes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204976","204976"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76837","2014-07-14","Home Office","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many journeys Ministers of her Department have made using the Government Car Service; and how many such journeys were for the transportation of a red box.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204940","204940"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76838","2014-07-14","Home Office","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps the Government is taking to tackle gender-based violence in gangs (a) generally and (b) in respect of sexual violence against girls and young women; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Hywel Francis","Dr Hywel Francis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204922","204922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76839","2014-07-14","Home Office","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many UK Border Agency staff are based at (a) its Belfast public enquiry office, (b) Belfast City Airport, (c) Belfast International Airport, (d) City of Derry Airport and (e) ports and harbours in Northern Ireland; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204924","204924"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76840","2014-07-14","Home Office","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, for what reasons hon. Members' recent representations to the Director General, UK Visas and Immigration were not referred to the post for a review; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mike Gapes","Mike Gapes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204978","204978"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76841","2014-07-14","Home Office","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many UK Border Agency staff employed in Northern Ireland (a) are recruited locally and (b) reside in Northern Ireland; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204925","204925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76842","2014-07-14","Home Office","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the Butler-Sloss Inquiry into child abuse will have scope to include public bodies and non-state institutions based in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204875","204875"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76843","2014-07-14","Home Office","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will include Kincora Boys Home in East Belfast in the scope of the Butler-Sloss child abuse inquiry.","Biography information for Naomi Long","Naomi Long","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204811","204811"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76844","2014-07-14","Home Office","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many passport renewals for people in (a) Warrington Borough and (b) Warrington North constituency were completed within three weeks of receipt in each year since 2009 and in 2014 to date.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204790","204790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76845","2014-07-14","Home Office","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will estimate how much money her Department has spent in Morecambe and Lunesdale constituency since May 2010.","Biography information for David Morris","David Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204778","204778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76846","2014-07-14","Home Office","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions she had with the Scottish Government on the Butler-Sloss inquiry into child abuse.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204699","204699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76847","2014-07-14","Home Office","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will take steps to ensure that staff of her Department alleviate distress suffered by families who are subject to questioning at border control because the children have different surnames to their parents.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204701","204701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76848","2014-07-14","Home Office","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make it her policy that appropriate information about parents is included on children's passports and collected to reduce difficulties at border control for children whose surnames differ from their parents' surnames.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204704","204704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76849","2014-07-14","Home Office","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if her Department will amend the official observations section of children's passports to allow a note when a holder's parent has a different surname to that of the child.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204702","204702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76850","2014-07-14","Home Office","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to reduce the number of cannabis factories across the UK.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204714","204714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76851","2014-07-14","Home Office","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will review the availability of language test centres in Ukraine in response to the current security situation in parts of that country.","Biography information for Mark Lazarowicz","Mark Lazarowicz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204792","204792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76852","2014-07-14","Home Office","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much HM Passport Office has spent on couriers to deliver passports in each month since January 2013.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204745","204745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76853","2014-07-14","House of Commons Commission","2014-07-09","To ask the hon. Member for Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross representing the House of Commons Commission, whether members of the House of Commons Management Board require authorisation from the Chief Executive, House of Commons Commission or any other authority before undertaking external speaking engagements related to their professional role.","Biography information for Thomas Docherty","Thomas Docherty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204886","204886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76854","2014-07-14","House of Commons Commission","2014-07-09","To ask the hon. Member for Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross representing the House of Commons Commission, what assessment the Commission has made of the effectiveness to date of the introduction of Office 365; and on what evidence and measures the Commission based that assessment.","Biography information for Thomas Docherty","Thomas Docherty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204885","204885"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76855","2014-07-14","House of Commons Commission","2014-07-09","To ask the hon. Member for Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross representing the House of Commons Commission, who within the House is accountable for data security.","Biography information for Thomas Docherty","Thomas Docherty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204883","204883"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76856","2014-07-14","House of Commons Commission","2014-07-09","To ask the hon. Member for Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross representing the House of Commons Commission, how many contractors supporting PICT and other information technology projects in the House have had their contracts (a) terminated and (b) not renewed due to poor performance.","Biography information for Thomas Docherty","Thomas Docherty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204884","204884"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76857","2014-07-14","Department for International Development","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if her Department will review its decision in 2012 to end its involvement in the Bost Agri project; and if she will make an assessment of any lessons to be learned from that decision and its consequences.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204834","204834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76858","2014-07-14","Department for International Development","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 11 June 2014, Official Report, column 181W, on Afghanistan, on what date in November 2013 her Department completed its move at Bost airfield; and under whose control that airfield now is.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204879","204879"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76859","2014-07-14","Department for International Development","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what her policy is on advising other countries on the use of private finance initiative-type financing models to low-income countries either directly or through the International Finance Corporation.","Biography information for Fiona O'Donnell","Fiona O'Donnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204825","204825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76860","2014-07-14","Department for International Development","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what conditions her Department has imposed on the release of development aid for Iraq; and what arrangements she has made for oversight of the distribution of such aid.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204880","204880"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76861","2014-07-14","Department for International Development","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what funding her Department provided to each country in receipt of UK development aid (a) directly and (b) indirectly per head of population in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mr Peter Bone","Mr Peter Bone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204898","204898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76862","2014-07-14","Department for International Development","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what programmes her Department funds and operates in Papua New Guinea.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204950","204950"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76863","2014-07-14","Department for International Development","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to Questions 167-8 of the oral Evidence given by the Minister of State at her Department to the International Development Committee on 8 May 2014, how much funding her Department gave to the Palestinian Authority in each of the last 10 years which was used (a) directly and (b) indirectly to pay salaries to the families of convicted terrorists.","Biography information for Mr Peter Bone","Mr Peter Bone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204896","204896"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76864","2014-07-14","Department for International Development","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much funding her Department provided (a) directly and (b) indirectly to the Palestinian Authority in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mr Peter Bone","Mr Peter Bone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204897","204897"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76865","2014-07-14","Department for International Development","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to Questions 167-8 of the oral Evidence given by the Minister of State at her Department to the International Development Committee on 8 May 2014, if she will review her policy of paying money to the Palestinian Authority which may be used to pay salaries to the families of convicted terrorists.","Biography information for Mr Peter Bone","Mr Peter Bone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204895","204895"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76866","2014-07-14","Department for International Development","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent steps her Department has made in providing humanitarian aid to the Kurdistan Regional Government in response to the influx of refugees to that area.","Biography information for John Spellar","Mr John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204720","204720"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76867","2014-07-14","Department for International Development","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent assessment she has made of which Commonwealth countries are most at risk from rising sea levels.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204923","204923"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76868","2014-07-14","Department for International Development","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much funding the Government is providing to the World Bank to prevent deforestation; over what period such funding will be provided; and how many hectares of rainforest are being protected from such deforestation.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204921","204921"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76869","2014-07-14","Department for International Development","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many journeys Ministers of her Department have made using the Government Car Service; and how many such journeys were for the transportation of a red box.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204941","204941"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76870","2014-07-14","Department for International Development","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent assessment she has made of which countries are most at risk from deforestation.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204959","204959"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76871","2014-07-14","Department for International Development","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what rainforest projects her Department is supporting.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204961","204961"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76872","2014-07-14","Department for International Development","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many of her Department's projects involve indigenous communities in (a) all and (b) Commonwealth rainforests.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204970","204970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76873","2014-07-14","Department for International Development","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 1 July 2014, Official Report, column 592W, on developing countries, which organisations based (a) in the UK and (b) overseas, with which her Department has contracts, restrict employment in certain posts because they require a particular understanding of the faith-based values and beliefs of that organisation; and what proportion of such posts are so restricted in each such organisation.","Biography information for Mr John Denham","Mr John Denham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204971","204971"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76874","2014-07-14","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the potential effect of the privatisation of Ministry of Justice shared services on jobs in Bootle constituency.","Biography information for Mr Joe Benton","Mr Joe Benton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204927","204927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76875","2014-07-14","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to protect personal data held by Ministry of Justice Shared Services when that data is off-shored to countries with less robust data protection than the UK.","Biography information for Mr Joe Benton","Mr Joe Benton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204929","204929"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76876","2014-07-14","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what discussions took place between officials in his Department, the Home Office and STERIA before the decision to privatise Ministry of Justice shared services was taken.","Biography information for Mr Joe Benton","Mr Joe Benton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204926","204926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76877","2014-07-14","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when his Department's review of veterans in the criminal justice system will be published.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204963","204963"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76878","2014-07-14","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, for what reason his Department did not consult the Public and Commercial Services Union on an in-house bid for the Ministry of Justice shared services contract.","Biography information for Mr Joe Benton","Mr Joe Benton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204928","204928"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76879","2014-07-14","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, in how many cases involving adults and children jointly charged, the child co-defendants were tried together with the adults in (a) an adult magistrates' court and (b) a Crown Court.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204969","204969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76880","2014-07-15","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, for what reason the new electronic tagging system was not subject to a pilot before the decision to implement it was taken.","Biography information for Mr Elfyn Llwyd","Mr Elfyn Llwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204991","204991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76881","2014-07-14","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many journeys Ministers of his Department have made using the Government Car Service; and how many such journeys were for the transportation of a red box.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204942","204942"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76882","2014-07-15","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the purpose is of the new electronic tagging system; and what evidence his Department analysed or collected on the potential effect of that system on crime and reconviction rates.","Biography information for Mr Elfyn Llwyd","Mr Elfyn Llwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204992","204992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76883","2014-07-14","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department has taken to implement Schedule 1, paragraph 35 of the Criminal Justice and Immigration Act 2008 on reviewing youth rehablitation orders in each court since May 2010.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204985","204985"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76884","2014-07-14","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many extra places will be created in public sector prisons; from what date; and for how long.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204721","204721"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76885","2014-07-14","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of prisoners who were given a life sentence (a) applied for and (b) were refused Category D prison status in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204727","204727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76886","2014-07-14","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of prisoners who were given a life sentence (a) applied for and (b) were refused a resettlement licence in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204726","204726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76887","2014-07-14","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners liable to be deported were released from prison on resettlement licence in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204718","204718"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76888","2014-07-14","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many complaints were received by his Department of judges having undeclared (a) financial, (b) family or (c) political interests in particular trials in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204716","204716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76889","2014-07-14","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what budget has been set aside for funding HM Prison Service Reserve.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204746","204746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76890","2014-07-14","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many off-payroll engagements for more than £220 a day and for a period of longer than six months were established in each of the last four years; and what the total cost of such payments has been.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204748","204748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76891","2014-07-14","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of prisoners who were liable for deportation (a) applied for and (b) were refused a resettlement licence in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204756","204756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76892","2014-07-14","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of prisoners who were given an indeterminate sentence for public protection (a) applied for and (b) were refused Category D prison status in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204753","204753"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76893","2014-07-14","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of prisoners who were given an indeterminate sentence for public protection (a) applied for and (b) were refused a resettlement licence in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204754","204754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76894","2014-07-14","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of prisoners who were liable for deportation (a) applied for and (b) were refused Category D prison status in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204755","204755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76895","2014-07-15","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether the procurement process for the electronic tagging contract complied with Cabinet Office procedures on openness and transparency.","Biography information for Mr Elfyn Llwyd","Mr Elfyn Llwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204816","204816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76896","2014-07-15","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the value of the new electronic tagging contract is for each of the next nine financial years.","Biography information for Mr Elfyn Llwyd","Mr Elfyn Llwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204815","204815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76897","2014-07-15","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which companies have been awarded contracts for electronic tagging in respect of the next nine years; how much each such company will be paid; what services each such company will provide; and for how long each such company will provide services.","Biography information for Mr Elfyn Llwyd","Mr Elfyn Llwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204814","204814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76898","2014-07-14","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the status is of each prison building and site for prisons closed since May 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204708","204708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76899","2014-07-14","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the number of former prison staff who will be members of Her Majesty's Prison Service Reserve.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204693","204693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76900","2014-07-14","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, to how many former prison staff his Department has written on the formation of Her Majesty's Prison Service Reserve.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204694","204694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76901","2014-07-14","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether spaces in segregation units and in hospital or medical wings count towards a prison's certified normal accommodation.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204695","204695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76902","2014-07-14","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether former prison staff recruited to Her Majesty's Prison Service Reserve will be liable to return all or part of any severance or redundancy packages they received.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204696","204696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76903","2014-07-14","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many children in the child protection system entered the youth justice system in England and Wales in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204951","204951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76904","2014-07-14","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will extend the role of registered intermediaries to include participation in all court proceedings involving children.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204949","204949"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76905","2014-07-14","Department of Health","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make an assessment of the potential use of mindfulness in prisons to (a) reduce violence in prisons, (b) improve the mental health of prisoners and (c) reduce reoffending.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204828","204828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76906","2014-07-14","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will estimate how much money his Department has spent in Morecambe and Lunesdale constituency since May 2010.","Biography information for David Morris","David Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204779","204779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76907","2014-07-14","Leader of the House","2014-07-09","To ask the Leader of the House, how many mobile telephones, BlackBerrys and laptops were lost by his Office in (a) 2013 and (b) 2014 to date.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204800","204800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76910","2014-07-14","Northern Ireland Office","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many journeys Ministers of her Department have made using the Government Car Service; and how many such journeys were for the transportation of a red box.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204943","204943"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76911","2014-07-14","Northern Ireland Office","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, pursuant to the Answer of 8 July 2014, Official Report, columns 269-74W, on electoral register, what the registration rates were in each ward listed.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204747","204747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76912","2014-07-14","Northern Ireland Office","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many mobile telephones, BlackBerrys and laptops were lost by her Department in (a) 2013 and (b) 2014 to date.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204801","204801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76913","2014-07-14","Cabinet Office","2014-07-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many mobile telephones, BlackBerrys and laptops were lost by No. 10 Downing Street in (a) 2013 and (b) 2014 to date.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204802","204802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76914","2014-07-14","Public Accounts Commission","2014-07-09","To ask the Chairman of the Public Accounts Commission, how many mobile telephones, BlackBerrys and laptops were lost by the National Audit Office in (a) 2013 and (b) 2014 to date.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204807","204807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76915","2014-07-14","Scotland Office","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how many mobile telephones, BlackBerrys and laptops were lost by his Department in (a) 2013 and (b) 2014 to date.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204803","204803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76916","2014-07-14","Scotland Office","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how many journeys Ministers of his Department have made using the Government Car Service; and how many such journeys were for the transportation of a red box.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204944","204944"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76917","2014-07-14","Speaker's Committee for the Independent Parliamentary Standards Authority","2014-07-09","To ask the hon. Member for Broxbourne, representing the Speaker's Committee for the Independent Parliamentary Standards Authority, how many mobile telephones, BlackBerrys and laptops were lost by the Independent Parliamentary Standards Authority in (a) 2013 and (b) 2014 to date.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204809","204809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76918","2014-07-14","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2014-07-09","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, how many mobile telephones, BlackBerrys and laptops were lost by the Electoral Commission in (a) 2013 and (b) 2014 to date.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204808","204808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76919","2014-07-14","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2014-07-09","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, which wards, by town, county and parliamentary constituency had a postal vote turnout greater than 80 per cent at the last local elections for which figures are available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204710","204710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76920","2014-07-14","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2014-07-09","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what the 100 local authority wards with the lowest turnout for voting at polling stations are; and what the proportion of the total turnout for postal voting in these wards is.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204717","204717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76921","2014-07-14","Department for Transport","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he last met the traffic commissioners to discuss safety standard adherence by bus or coach companies.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204709","204709"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76922","2014-07-14","Department for Transport","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, on how many occasions traffic commissioners have sanctioned (a) bus operators and (b) coach operators for failing to meet safety standards since 2000.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204707","204707"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76923","2014-07-14","Department for Transport","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, on how many occasions traffic commissioners have (a) revoked a bus or coach operator's licence and (b) curtailed the number of vehicles which an operator is allowed to run under its licence for failing to meet safety standards since 2000.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204706","204706"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76925","2014-07-14","Department for Transport","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many and what proportion of driving licences were withdrawn from people ordinarily resident in Scotland on the basis of alcohol abuse (a) following road accidents and (b) at the request of medical practitioners in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204722","204722"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76926","2014-07-14","Department for Transport","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many mobile telephones, BlackBerrys and laptops were lost by his Department in (a) 2013 and (b) 2014 to date.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204804","204804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76927","2014-07-14","Department for Transport","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many vessels with valid licences to operate from the UK in the short sea freight sector are registered under (a) the UK flag or (b) Red Ensign Group registries; and what proportion of those are qualifying vessels under the Tonnage Tax scheme.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204833","204833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76928","2014-07-14","Department for Transport","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect on services to Carnforth Station when High Speed 2 is completed.","Biography information for David Morris","David Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204817","204817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76929","2014-07-14","Department for Transport","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will discuss with the Secretary of State for the Home Department the posibility of redeploying staff at the Driver Vehicle Licensing Agency offices in Northern Ireland who are currently facing redundancy to carry out urgent work on processing passport applications across the UK.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204852","204852"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76930","2014-07-14","Department for Transport","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which governmental body will make funds available for a feasibility study on developing a highway road tunnel under Morcambe Bay from Heysham M6 Link Road to Barrow-in-Furness.","Biography information for David Morris","David Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204818","204818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76931","2014-07-14","Department for Transport","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will estimate how much money his Department has spent in Morecambe and Lunesdale constituency since May 2010.","Biography information for David Morris","David Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204780","204780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76932","2014-07-14","Department for Transport","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which governmental body will make funds available to fund a feasibility study into the reinstatement of platforms at Carnforth Station on the West Coast Main Line.","Biography information for David Morris","David Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204810","204810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76933","2014-07-14","Department for Transport","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many new training roles for UK seafarers were created under the approved core training commitments submitted by company groups that qualified for the Tonnage Tax scheme between October 2012 and September 2013; how many such roles he expects to be created between October 2013 and September 2014; and what the cumulative training commitment is of companies qualifying for that scheme in 2013-14.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204843","204843"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76934","2014-07-14","Department for Transport","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the number of part-worn tyres sold in the UK in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204878","204878"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76935","2014-07-14","Department for Transport","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many vessels with valid licences to operate from the UK in the short sea passenger ferry sector are registered under (a) the UK flag or (b) Red Ensign Group registries; and what proportion of those vessels are qualifying vessels under the Tonnage Tax scheme.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204842","204842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76936","2014-07-14","Department for Transport","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much Northern Rail has pledged to invest in station upgrades under the franchise extension announced on 27 March 2014.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204862","204862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76937","2014-07-14","Department for Transport","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the relevant local authority is to fund or reinstate Carnforth Station rail platforms on the West Coast mainline following their removal in error in the 1970s.","Biography information for David Morris","David Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204868","204868"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76938","2014-07-14","Department for Transport","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what his policy is on upgrading Carnforth Railway Station for additional future services.","Biography information for David Morris","David Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204869","204869"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76939","2014-07-14","Department for Transport","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much his Department has allocated for road repairs in (a) Westmorland and Lonsdale constituency, (b) South Lakeland, (c) Cumbria and (d) the North West (i) since 2010 and (ii) between 2005 and 2010.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204867","204867"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76940","2014-07-14","Department for Transport","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many journeys Ministers of his Department have made using the Government Car Service; and how many such journeys were for the transportation of a red box.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204945","204945"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76943","2014-07-14","Wales Office","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how many journeys Ministers of his Department have made using the Government Car Service; and how many such journeys were for the transportation of a red box.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204947","204947"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76944","2014-07-14","Wales Office","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how many mobile telephones, BlackBerrys and laptops were lost by his Department in (a) 2013 and (b) 2014 to date.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204805","204805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76945","2014-07-14","Wales Office","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what assessment he has made on the potential effect of universal credit on the education maintenance allowance in Wales.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204812","204812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76946","2014-07-14","Women and Equalities","2014-07-09","To ask the Ministers for Women and Equalities, how many mobile telephones, BlackBerrys and laptops were lost by the Government Equalities Office in (a) 2013 and (b) 2014 to date.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204799","204799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76947","2014-07-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in receipt of housing benefit have moved to smaller properties since the introduction of the under-occupancy penalty in (a) 2014 to date and (b) 2013.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204813","204813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76948","2014-07-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many mobile telephones, BlackBerrys and laptops were lost by his Department in (a) 2013 and (b) 2014 to date.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204806","204806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76949","2014-07-14","Cabinet Office","2014-07-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what changes there have been in the unemployment rate in (a) Westmorland and Lonsdale, (b) South Lakeland, (c) Cumbria and (d) the North West (i) since 2010 and (ii) between 2005 and 2010.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204788","204788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76950","2014-07-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will classify motor neurone disease as a terminal illness which qualifies for a fast-track assessment for welfare claims.","Biography information for Fiona O'Donnell","Fiona O'Donnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204826","204826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76951","2014-07-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will estimate how much money his Department has spent in Morecambe and Lunesdale constituency since May 2010.","Biography information for David Morris","David Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204782","204782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76952","2014-07-14","Cabinet Office","2014-07-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what change in employment levels there has been in (a) Westmorland and Lonsdale constituency, (b) South Lakeland, (c) Cumbria and (d) the North West (i) since 2010 and (ii) between 2005 and 2010.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204866","204866"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76953","2014-07-14","Cabinet Office","2014-07-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many unemployed young people have been out of work for more than (a) four, (b) six, (c) 12 and (d) 24 months.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204860","204860"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76954","2014-07-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much his Department has spent on (a) accommodation, (b) taxis or private cars and (c) alcoholic beverages in the last year.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204861","204861"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76955","2014-07-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many journeys Ministers of his Department have made using the Government Car Service; and how many such journeys were for the transportation of a red box.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204948","204948"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76956","2014-07-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, which claimants will be exempt from participating in the supervised jobsearch pilot scheme.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204988","204988"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76957","2014-07-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 7 July 2014, Official Report, column 110W, on personal independence payment, what the average clearance times were for claims from terminally ill people at (a) 31 January 2014 and (b) 30 June 2014.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204989","204989"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76958","2014-07-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what forecast his Department made of total IT spending in (a) the full business case for universal credit currently being considered by HM Treasury and (b) the business case previously approved for universal credit.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204986","204986"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76959","2014-07-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average time between claim and a decision on disability living allowance for parents, guardians or representatives of disabled children under 16 years of age was in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204918","204918"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76960","2014-07-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what training employees of his Department receive about how to engage with people who (a) have mental health problems and (b) exhibit suicidal behaviour.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204966","204966"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76961","2014-07-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much his Department has spent on (a) mobile telephones, (b) tablet computers and (c) office furniture in the last year.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204974","204974"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76962","2014-07-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people have disclosed an intention to commit suicide while (a) on the telephone to employees of his Department and (b) in person in his Department's premises or offices in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204964","204964"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76963","2014-07-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people are currently waiting for an assessment for personal independence payment in the Halton local authority area; and what the average waiting time for an assessment is in that area.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204960","204960"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77166","2014-07-15","Department of Health","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he next plans to meet representatives of NHS foundation trusts plans to discuss measures to address deficits.","Biography information for Sir Henry Bellingham","Mr Henry Bellingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 904856","904856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77824","2014-07-15","Department of Health","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department has taken to act on the recommendations made by the Health and Care Professions Council to extend statutory regulation to new groups of healthcare professionals.","Biography information for Stephen Gilbert","Stephen Gilbert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 904866","904866"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77825","2014-07-15","Department of Health","2014-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with Ministers of the Welsh Government on the operation of the new Welsh law on presumed consent for organ donation for English residents who are patients in Wales and Welsh residents who are patients in England.","Biography information for Glyn Davies","Glyn Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 904865","904865"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76234","2014-07-10","Attorney General","2014-07-08","To ask the Attorney General, how many mobile telephones, BlackBerrys and laptops were lost by the Law Officers' Departments in (a) 2013 and (b) 2014 to date.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204463","204463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76235","2014-07-10","Attorney General","2014-07-08","To ask the Attorney General, what costs his Department has incurred in prosecuting the case of (a) Christopher Huhne and (b) Vasiliki Pryce.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204655","204655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76236","2014-07-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many mobile telephones, BlackBerrys and laptops were lost by his Department in (a) 2013 and (b) 2014 to date.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204462","204462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76237","2014-07-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, which organisations collect subscriptions through the employers' payroll service in their Department and its agencies.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204494","204494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76238","2014-07-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will take steps to prevent sister companies offering similar products to consumers at substantially different prices.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204404","204404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76239","2014-07-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many higher apprenticeships were delivered via the (a) Higher Education Funding Council for England and (b) Skills Funding Agency in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Bailey","Mr Adrian Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204399","204399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76240","2014-07-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many investigations of illegal money lenders have been carried out by illegal lending units in England, Scotland and Wales in each of the last five years; and how many such investigations have resulted in criminal convictions.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204420","204420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76241","2014-07-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, on what dates (a) he, (b) Ministers in his Department and (c) officials in his Department had meetings with Adrian Beecroft between May 2012 and June 2014.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204448","204448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76242","2014-07-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent discussions he has had with the Scottish Government on the practice of blacklisting in public sector procurement contracts.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204523","204523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76243","2014-07-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many businesses in England were registered as agricultural businesses in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204540","204540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76244","2014-07-10","Cabinet Office","2014-07-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how (a) the UK Government and (b) Northern Ireland is represented on the EU Consultative Multi-stakeholder Group on Social Business.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204614","204614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76245","2014-07-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent discussions he has had with Ofcom on any regulatory changes in regard to the Universal Postal Service; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stewart Jackson","Mr Stewart Jackson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204602","204602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76246","2014-07-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department is taking to encourage the manufacturing industry in Scotland.","Biography information for Iain McKenzie","Iain McKenzie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204600","204600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76247","2014-07-14","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-07-08","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, whether the £1.13 billion earmarked for the Glasgow area from the Growth Deal is dependent on the existence of shovel ready projects.","Biography information for Iain McKenzie","Iain McKenzie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204598","204598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76248","2014-07-10","Cabinet Office","2014-07-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, which Government departments administer their own departmental civil service payrolls; and which Government departments' payrolls are administered by which other outside firms.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204611","204611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76249","2014-07-10","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-07-08","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, how many Lord Lieutenants in England and Wales are (a) from an ethnic minority community, (b) women and (c) from the lesbian, gay, bisexual, and transgender community; and what steps are being taken to increase the proportion of Lord Lieutenants who are representatives of such communities.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204621","204621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76250","2014-07-10","Cabinet Office","2014-07-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the number of people in Kilmarnock and Loudoun constituency who are paid at a rate below the living wage as defined by the Living Wage Foundation.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204636","204636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76251","2014-07-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many (a) minor, (b) serious and (c) fatal accidents at work have been reported in each region and constituent part of the UK in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204539","204539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76252","2014-07-14","Cabinet Office","2014-07-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much was spent from the public purse on (a) wine and (b) food served at the Best of British Creative Industries reception on 30 June 2014; what the other costs to the public purse were of hosting the event; how many catering staff were required to facilitate the event; and which Ministers attended the event.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204444","204444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76253","2014-07-10","Cabinet Office","2014-07-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many mobile telephones, BlackBerrys and laptops were lost by his Department in (a) 2013 and (b) 2014 to date.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204464","204464"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76254","2014-07-14","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-07-08","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, pursuant to the Statement of 7 July 2014, Official Report, columns 46-7, on local growth deals, when Glasgow will receive the first tranche of the £1.13 billion allocated to it.","Biography information for Iain McKenzie","Iain McKenzie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204671","204671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76255","2014-07-14","HM Treasury","2014-07-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many and what proportion of employees hired under the Employment Allowance Scheme are paid below the living wage as set by the Living Wage Foundation.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204666","204666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76256","2014-07-10","HM Treasury","2014-07-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many mobile telephones, BlackBerrys and laptops were lost by his Department in (a) 2013 and (b) 2014 to date.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204478","204478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76257","2014-07-14","HM Treasury","2014-07-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the reasons are for HM Revenue and Customs change of policy with regards to the imposition of tonnage tax on Isle of Wight ferries; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Turner","Mr Andrew Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204499","204499"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76258","2014-07-10","Department for Transport","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect of the European Fuel Quality Directive Article 7a (a) on petrol prices and (b) generally.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204433","204433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76259","2014-07-15","HM Treasury","2014-07-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people in (a) the UK and (b) East Yorkshire constituency no longer pay income tax as a result of changes in the personal income tax threshold introduced since 2010.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204487","204487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76260","2014-07-14","HM Treasury","2014-07-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when his Department received the business case for the meningococcal B vaccine; and when he expects to make a decision whether or not to approve the business case.","Biography information for Sir Tony Cunningham","Sir Tony Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204485","204485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76261","2014-07-10","HM Treasury","2014-07-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment has been made of the effect on the Scottish economy of house prices in Scotland.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204501","204501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76262","2014-07-14","HM Treasury","2014-07-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect on the economy of the Isle of Wight of the decision not to allow tonnage tax to apply to the Isle of Wight's ferry services.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Turner","Mr Andrew Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204482","204482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76263","2014-07-14","HM Treasury","2014-07-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect on (a) cadet training and (b) marine employment of the decision not to allow tonnage tax to apply to the Isle of Wight's ferry services.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Turner","Mr Andrew Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204483","204483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76264","2014-07-10","HM Treasury","2014-07-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what reduction in consumer credit licences for short-term loans he expects when the authorisation process under the new Financial Conduct Authority regime has been completed in 2016.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204419","204419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76265","2014-07-10","HM Treasury","2014-07-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make an assessment of whether changes made to child benefit legislation since May 2010 have resulted in unfair tax burdens falling on people who are living with a partner who has his or her own children in the household.","Biography information for Natascha Engel","Natascha Engel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204403","204403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76266","2014-07-14","HM Treasury","2014-07-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the current regulatory regime for dark pool trading in the UK.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204535","204535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76267","2014-07-14","HM Treasury","2014-07-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he has taken to monitor the functioning and usage of dark pool trading in the UK.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204536","204536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76268","2014-07-14","HM Treasury","2014-07-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the reasons for the differences in the level of change in house prices in Scotland compared to the rest of the UK in the second quarter of 2014.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204544","204544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76269","2014-07-10","Department of Health","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if his Department will conduct a separate consultation into the intellectual property implications of standardised tobacco packaging and its potential effect on the Exchequer.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204639","204639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76270","2014-07-10","HM Treasury","2014-07-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the issue of a proposed boundary change at Priory Court, Dover, in respect of the number of available business square metres required by HM Revenue and Customs (HMRC) at the facility under 10.14(a) of the Private Finance Initiative contract between HMRC and Mapeley STEPS Contractor Limited was discussed during the six month consultation before the previous revised, non-binding Estates Strategies issued by HMRC.","Biography information for Charlie Elphicke","Charlie Elphicke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204580","204580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76271","2014-07-10","HM Treasury","2014-07-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the next revised, non-binding Estates Strategies issued by HM Revenue and Customs (HMRC) will take account of a proposed boundary change at Priory Court, Dover, in respect of the number of available business square metres required by HMRC at the facility under 10.14(a) of the Private Finance Initiative contract between HMRC and Mapeley STEPS Contractor Limited.","Biography information for Charlie Elphicke","Charlie Elphicke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204575","204575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76272","2014-07-10","Church Commissioners","2014-07-08","To ask the right hon. Member for Banbury, representing the Church Commissioners, how many mobile telephones, BlackBerrys and laptops were lost by the Church Commissioners in (a) 2013 and (b) 2014 to date.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204465","204465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76273","2014-07-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many mobile telephones, BlackBerrys and laptops were lost by his Department in (a) 2013 and (b) 2014 to date.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204466","204466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76274","2014-07-10","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many new build libraries have opened in (a) England, (b) the West Midlands and (c) Birmingham in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204461","204461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76275","2014-07-10","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many public libraries there were in each region and constituent part of the UK in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204510","204510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76276","2014-07-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much was paid in (a) housing benefit and (b) council tax benefit to people in prison in the last period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204437","204437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76277","2014-07-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many second homes there were in each parish in Westmorland and Lonsdale on the most recent date for which data is available.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204423","204423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76278","2014-07-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to assist local authorities in acquiring necessary skills, partnerships and capacity to utilise the increased borrowing allowed against the Housing Revenue Account.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204424","204424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76279","2014-07-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to promote off-site methods of house building construction.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204425","204425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76280","2014-07-10","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many public libraries have closed in (a) Birmingham and (b) the West Midlands in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204447","204447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76281","2014-07-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will make an assessment of the effect of the removal of recycling credits by Lancashire County Council on weekly waste collections in that county.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204408","204408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76282","2014-07-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the financial effect on Ribble Valley Borough Council of the withdrawal of recycling credits by Lancashire County Council.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204409","204409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76283","2014-07-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will provide support to district councils in Lancashire from which recycling credits have been withdrawn by Lancashire County Council.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204410","204410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76284","2014-07-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what support his Department provides to local authorities who wish to retain weekly general waste collections.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204411","204411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76285","2014-07-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what guidance his Department provides to local authorities on the provision of recycling credits by county councils to district councils.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204412","204412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76286","2014-07-14","Cabinet Office","2014-07-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment his Department has made of the quality and consistency of youth services outsourced by local authorities.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204632","204632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76287","2014-07-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the duration of his Department's lease at 2 Marsham Street is; and what break clause arrangements there are.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204622","204622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76288","2014-07-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to promote the use of community land trusts as a way of delivering affordable housing.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204629","204629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76289","2014-07-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will make an assessment of the effectiveness of the Leeds City Council Community Levy.","Biography information for Stuart Andrew","Stuart Andrew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204538","204538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76290","2014-07-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what (a) financial, (b) staffing and (c) capacity-building support and assistance his Department has given to Sussex Safer Roads Partnership in respect of (i) activities relating to Operation Crackdown and (ii) all other activities in each year since its inception.","Biography information for Mike Weir","Mr Mike Weir","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204565","204565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76291","2014-07-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what metrics his Department applies to assess the performance of Sussex Safer Roads Partnership's contribution to Operation Crackdown.","Biography information for Mike Weir","Mr Mike Weir","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204566","204566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76292","2014-07-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will publish his assessment of the effectiveness of the protocols governing Sussex Safer Roads Partnership's contribution to Operation Crackdown.","Biography information for Mike Weir","Mr Mike Weir","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204567","204567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76293","2014-07-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the average level of local authority debt is per capita.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204610","204610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76294","2014-07-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, in which instances the Planning Inspectorate has (a) removed and (b) amended to weaken (i) the code for sustainable homes and (ii) BREEAM standards from a development plan document prepared by a local planning authority since 13 March 2014; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204645","204645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76295","2014-07-10","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to the report of the independent review of the BBC's coverage of rural arrairs commissioned by the BBC Trust and published in June 2014, if he will discuss with the BBC Trust the finding of that report that BBC coverage does not fully reflect the economic and social concerns of people who  live in the countryside.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204561","204561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76296","2014-07-10","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the benefits to (a) tourism and (b) the economy following the 2014 Commonwealth Games in Glasgow.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204511","204511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76297","2014-07-10","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he is taking to ensure that the 2014 Glasgow Commonwealth Games will provide lasting benefits to the area.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204615","204615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76298","2014-07-10","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many mobile telephones, BlackBerrys and laptops were lost by his Department in (a) 2013 and (b) 2014 to date.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204467","204467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76299","2014-07-14","Ministry of Defence","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many service complaints went to a full board hearing in the last five years.","Biography information for Yvonne Fovargue","Yvonne Fovargue","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204445","204445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76300","2014-07-14","Ministry of Defence","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many service complaints were filed in the last five years; and how many such complaints related to allegations of bullying.","Biography information for Yvonne Fovargue","Yvonne Fovargue","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204443","204443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76301","2014-07-10","Ministry of Defence","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department has plans to offer military support to countries in Africa facing Islamic extremism; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204391","204391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76302","2014-07-10","Ministry of Defence","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what his priorities are for the forthcoming NATO summit in Newport, Wales.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204612","204612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76303","2014-07-14","Ministry of Defence","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans he has for the future establishment, equipment and role of the Royal Armoured Corps; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204541","204541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76304","2014-07-14","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-07-08","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what level of representation Liverpool will have on the Northern Futures Board.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204498","204498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76305","2014-07-14","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-07-08","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, when he expects to reply to the question tabled on 11 June 2014 by the hon. Member for Carmarthen West and South Pembrokeshire.","Biography information for Simon Hart","Simon Hart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204481","204481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76306","2014-07-10","Cabinet Office","2014-07-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many mobile telephones, BlackBerrys and laptops were lost by his Office in (a) 2013 and (b) 2014 to date.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204468","204468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76307","2014-07-14","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-07-08","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what notification his Department has received from the Scottish Government on the devolution from them of further decision-making powers to local authorities in the Clyde Valley area to allow them to attract further investment as part of the City Deal for Glasgow.","Biography information for Ann McKechin","Ann McKechin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204675","204675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76308","2014-07-14","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-07-08","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what agreement has been reached with the Scottish Government on (a) support and (b) funding for the infrastructure plan to build a rail link between Glasgow and the airport as part of the City Deal for Glasgow.","Biography information for Ann McKechin","Ann McKechin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204679","204679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76309","2014-07-14","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-07-08","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what agreement has been reached with the Scottish Government on the devolution of funding for skills and training to the relevant local authorities as part of the City Deal for Glasgow.","Biography information for Ann McKechin","Ann McKechin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204676","204676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76310","2014-07-14","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-07-08","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what agreement has been reached with the Scottish Government on the devolution of powers to allow the relevant local authorities to better regulate or procure bus services as part of the City Deal for Glasgow.","Biography information for Ann McKechin","Ann McKechin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204677","204677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76311","2014-07-14","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-07-08","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what meetings Ministers or officials of his Department have had with Ministers of the Scottish Government to discuss the City Deal for Glasgow in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Ann McKechin","Ann McKechin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204678","204678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76312","2014-07-14","Department for Education","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to his Department's press release, Deal to provide life-saving defibrillators to schools, published in April 2014, what progress has been made on securing a supplier who will offer defibrillators to all schools at a reduced price in time for autumn term.","Biography information for Tracey Crouch","Tracey Crouch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204673","204673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76313","2014-07-10","Department for Education","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to prevent bullying in infant and junior schools.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204382","204382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76314","2014-07-10","Department for Education","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many mobile telephones, BlackBerrys and laptops were lost by his Department in (a) 2013 and (b) 2014 to date.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204469","204469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76315","2014-07-10","Department for Education","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that parents are made aware of the use of halal meat in school dinners where non-halal meat is not an option.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204383","204383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76316","2014-07-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many young people who had been in receipt of free school meals applied to the universities of Oxford and Cambridge in 2010-11.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204496","204496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76317","2014-07-10","Department for Education","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to increase the uptake of foreign languages in schools.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204492","204492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76318","2014-07-10","Department for Education","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of qualified teachers who completed their studies in the last three years have a permanent teaching position.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204490","204490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76319","2014-07-10","Department for Education","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what his policy is on a national pay grading structure for teaching assistants.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204429","204429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76320","2014-07-10","Department for Education","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will take steps to ensure that pupils prevented from attending school as a result of strike action are given an opportunity to catch up on school work missed owing to the absence of teaching staff.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204398","204398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76321","2014-07-10","Department for Education","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what value of land has been sold by academy trusts since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204507","204507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76322","2014-07-10","Department for Education","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what guidance his Department provides for early years professionals on support for children with cerebral palsy; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204515","204515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76323","2014-07-10","Department for Education","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the number of teaching assistants that administer medicine to children in local authority schools in England.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204509","204509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76324","2014-07-10","Department for Education","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the first tier tribunal decision notice of 2 July 2014, reference EA/2013/0270*, if he will take steps so that personal information in all future free school applications can be redacted easily and quickly and at reasonable cost; if he will make it his policy to release all future free school applications with any personal information that could identify individuals redacted; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204581","204581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76325","2014-07-10","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what consideration he has given to supporting the micro combined heat and power fuel cell industry; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204582","204582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76326","2014-07-10","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps he is taking to fill the position of chair of the Energy Efficiency Deployment Office.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204608","204608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76327","2014-07-10","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what security evaluation he has made of the proposed designs of the reactors and spent nuclear fuel for small modular reactor nuclear power plants.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204418","204418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76328","2014-07-10","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what further reviews of the non-domestic scheme of the Renewable Heat Incentive tariff rates are planned before April 2016.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204428","204428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76329","2014-07-10","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many off gas-grid properties have had renewable heating measures installed under the Renewables Heat Incentive.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204416","204416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76330","2014-07-10","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the annual budget is of his Department's new Nuclear Innovation and Research Office (NIRO); how many staff work full-time at NIRO; how many of those are secondees and from which organisations they are seconded; whether secondees are paid from public funds; what consideration was given to appointing a social scientist to the board of NIRO; what publications have been issued to date by NIRO; whether all research undertaken by or for NIRO is published in full; and what the web address is of the site where minutes of the NIRO board are posted.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204421","204421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76331","2014-07-10","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what criteria were used to appoint members to the Nuclear Innovation and Research Advisory Board; what annual budget is allocated to support the Board; what studies have been commissioned by or from the Board; and what the web address is of the site where the Board's meeting agendas are posted.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204422","204422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76332","2014-07-14","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if he will take steps to encourage the upgrading of (a) oil and (b) liquefied petroleum gas boilers in off-gas grid areas.","Biography information for Simon Hart","Simon Hart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204405","204405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76333","2014-07-14","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps he plans to take to ensure the delivery in rural areas of the 15 per cent proportion of the carbon saving community obligation; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Hart","Simon Hart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204406","204406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76334","2014-07-10","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, which organisations collect subscriptions through the employers' payroll service in their Department and its agencies.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204493","204493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76335","2014-07-10","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many non-domestic customers have taken out a Green Deal loan.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204381","204381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76336","2014-07-10","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many mobile telephones, BlackBerrys and laptops were lost by his Department in (a) 2013 and (b) 2014 to date.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204470","204470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76337","2014-07-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many mobile telephones, BlackBerrys and laptops were lost by his Department in (a) 2013 and (b) 2014 to date.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204471","204471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76338","2014-07-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 26 June 2014, Official Report, column 330W, on beavers: Devon, for what reasons he plans to recapture and rehome the wild beavers in Devon; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204414","204414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76339","2014-07-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 26 June 2014, Official Report, column 330W, on beavers: Devon, what other options have been discussed by his Department, Natural England and the Animal Health and Veterinary Laboratories Agency apart from recapturing and rehoming the population of wild beavers in Devon.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204413","204413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76340","2014-07-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many English rivers he assesses are of good ecological status.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204542","204542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76341","2014-07-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what proportion of the total land mass of the UK was classified as a marine protected area or a marine conservation area in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204634","204634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76342","2014-07-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the contribution of the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs of 7 July 2014, Official Report, columns 127-31, on Common Agricultural Policy, where the 10 centres for digital assistance for farmers will be located.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204672","204672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76343","2014-07-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent steps he has taken to encourage the repeal of blasphemy laws in Pakistan.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204618","204618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76344","2014-07-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions his Department has had with the European Commission's Radicalisation Awareness Network and its Working Group on Voices of Victims of Terrorism in the last three years.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204620","204620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76345","2014-07-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to emphasise adherence to fundamental freedoms of religion and association as part of the UK's foreign policy.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204616","204616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76346","2014-07-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when he last met his Israeli counterpart to discuss the political situation in Israel and Palestine; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Iain McKenzie","Iain McKenzie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204601","204601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76347","2014-07-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made relations with the government of Zimbabwe; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204528","204528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76348","2014-07-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what work has been done by experts from the Preventing Sexual Violence Initiative on the reported use of sexual violence by the military in Burma.","Biography information for Fiona O'Donnell","Fiona O'Donnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204537","204537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76349","2014-07-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to his Colombian counterpart drawing his attention to public support for human rights activists in Colombia.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204546","204546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76350","2014-07-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to his Colombian counterpart about ensuring that British businesses and investors do not buy illegally obtained Colombian land before it is restored to its rightful owners.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204547","204547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76351","2014-07-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received on the prevalence of Colombian paramilitary involvement with the police and the armed forces of that country.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204552","204552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76352","2014-07-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to his Colombian counterpart about guarantees for the safety of Colombian land restitution claimants.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204550","204550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76353","2014-07-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his US counterpart on tackling the threat from Islamic extremism in northern Africa.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204392","204392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76354","2014-07-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions (a) he and (b) other Ministers in his Department have had with leading members of the Nigerian opposition party, the All Progressive Congress; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204401","204401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76355","2014-07-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will commission an inquiry into the international support network for Boko Haram in Nigeria and Cameroon; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204402","204402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76356","2014-07-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what consular assistance his Department offers to British nationals travelling in Bhutan.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204378","204378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76357","2014-07-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what support his Department plans to offer to Nigeria in tackling the threat of Boko Haram.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204388","204388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76358","2014-07-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of links between Boko Haram and other Islamic extremist groups in Africa.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204389","204389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76359","2014-07-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will discuss with his counterpart in Cameroon the need for constructive dialogue between that country and Nigeria in tackling Boko Haram; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204390","204390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76360","2014-07-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many mobile telephones, BlackBerrys and laptops were lost by his Department in (a) 2013 and (b) 2014 to date.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204472","204472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76361","2014-07-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department has taken to strengthen trading relations between the UK and (a) Albania and (b) Montenegro.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204379","204379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76362","2014-07-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what condolences the UK has offered to Israel following the discovery of the bodies of the three murdered teenagers, Naftali Freikel, Gilad Sha'ar and Eyal Yifrah.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204384","204384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76363","2014-07-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the rise of Islamic terrorism in Northern Iraq.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204386","204386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76364","2014-07-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the rise in Islamic terrorism in Nigeria.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204387","204387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76365","2014-07-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department has taken to strengthen trading relations between the UK and Bosnia and Herzegovina.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204397","204397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76366","2014-07-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what security guidance his Department provides to British nationals wishing to travel to Ukraine.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204396","204396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76367","2014-07-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps HM Embassy in Bangkok is taking to retrieve the passport of Andy Hall.","Biography information for Mr David Ward","Mr David Ward","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204441","204441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76368","2014-07-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Thai counterpart on allegations of the mistreatment of elephants in trekking camps in Thailand.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204394","204394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76369","2014-07-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many British nationals have required emergency consular assistance in Somalia in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204395","204395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76370","2014-07-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether experts from the Preventing Sexual Violence Initiative have been sent to Burma to investigate the attempted rape of an ethnic Chin woman by a soldier from the Burmese Army.","Biography information for Fiona O'Donnell","Fiona O'Donnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204480","204480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76371","2014-07-14","Department of Health","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with the Chancellor of the Exchequer on the approval of his Department's business case for the meningococcal B vaccine.","Biography information for Sir Tony Cunningham","Sir Tony Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204486","204486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76372","2014-07-14","Department of Health","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much his Department has allocated to the School Fruit and Vegetable scheme for the 2015-16 school year.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204446","204446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76373","2014-07-10","Department of Health","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent steps his Department has taken to raise awareness of charities set up to help people suffering from depression.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204491","204491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76374","2014-07-10","Department of Health","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 26 June 2014, Official Report, column 281W, on medical treatments, what the most plausible cost per quality adjusted life-year was for each technology appraisal conducted by the National Institute for Care Excellence since June 2010; what the estimated patient population was for each appraised indication; on which appraisals the end-of-life criteria were applied in each final appraisal determination; and on what dates each appraisal was (a) initiated and (b) concluded.","Biography information for Mr Stephen O'Brien","Mr Stephen O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204436","204436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76375","2014-07-10","Department of Health","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his Department has spent on anti-smoking awareness campaigns in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204385","204385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76376","2014-07-10","Department of Health","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients received hospital transport in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204432","204432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76377","2014-07-10","Department of Health","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average cost is of providing a patient with hospital transport.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204434","204434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76378","2014-07-10","Department of Health","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many mobile telephones, BlackBerrys and laptops were lost by his Department in (a) 2013 and (b) 2014 to date.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204473","204473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76379","2014-07-14","Department of Health","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 26 June 2014, Official Report, column 280W, on medical records: databases, for what reason the Health and Social Care Information Centre did not seek or obtain section 251 of the NHS Redress Act 2006 support for the trial survey.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204407","204407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76380","2014-07-10","Department of Health","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much money has been spent on hospital transport in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204431","204431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76381","2014-07-10","Department of Health","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will instigate a public inquiry into the issuing of prescriptions for Primodos to pregnant women through the NHS before 1978.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204489","204489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76382","2014-07-10","Department of Health","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what representations he has received on allegations that the Government was warned about the dangers of the pregnancy testing drug Primodos in 1967 but did not ban it until 1978; and what steps he has taken as a result of those representations.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204438","204438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76383","2014-07-10","Department of Health","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of recent research findings published in the Journal of the American Medical Association which indicate that adding tomosynthesis to digital mammography improves the accuracy of breast screening; and whether this new technique will be made available on the NHS.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204560","204560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76384","2014-07-10","Department of Health","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of progress by the NHS in making available to patients new types of bone-anchored hearing aid.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204558","204558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76385","2014-07-10","Department of Health","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps the NHS has taken to address recent increases in the incidence of whooping cough in the UK.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204559","204559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76386","2014-07-14","Department of Health","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make it his policy that all children's heart surgery units should be subject to the same level of scrutiny.","Biography information for Stuart Andrew","Stuart Andrew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204553","204553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76387","2014-07-10","Department of Health","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of recent research findings published by Newcastle University which indicate that use of ibuprofen may retard premature ageing and the development of diabetes and dementia.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204554","204554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76388","2014-07-10","Department of Health","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will encourage the organisers of the British Transplant Games to hold the games each year in Organ Transplant Week.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204555","204555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76389","2014-07-14","Department of Health","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much his Department spent on non-pharmaceutical dementia treatments in each year since 2004.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204548","204548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76390","2014-07-10","Department of Health","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his Department's strategy is to ensure that GPs can detect cancer and refer cancer patients for treatment quicker.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204557","204557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76391","2014-07-14","Department of Health","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many young people have attended the accident and emergency department at Stafford Hospital in each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204595","204595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76392","2014-07-14","Department of Health","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many young people have been seen in the accident and emergency department at Stafford Hospital in each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204593","204593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76393","2014-07-10","Department of Health","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to improve the medical care for patients suffering from heart disease.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204512","204512"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76394","2014-07-14","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the EU General Data Protection Regulation on medical research; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stewart Jackson","Mr Stewart Jackson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204543","204543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76395","2014-07-10","Department of Health","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what advice and training his Department provides to health visitors for supporting parents with children diagnosed with cerebral palsy; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204524","204524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76396","2014-07-10","Department of Health","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many young people have been admitted as day cases at Stafford Hospital in each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204574","204574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76397","2014-07-10","Department of Health","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people attended the accident and emergency department at Stafford Hospital in each of the years (a) 2009-10, (b) 2010-11, (c) 2011-12, (d) 2012-13 and (e) 2013-14.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204577","204577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76398","2014-07-10","Department of Health","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many young people attending the paediatrics assessment unit were not transferred from the accident and emergency department at Stafford Hospital in each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204578","204578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76399","2014-07-10","Cabinet Office","2014-07-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many babies were born at Stafford Hospital in each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204579","204579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76400","2014-07-14","Department of Health","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 7 July 2014, Official Report, column 43W, on ovarian hyperstimulation syndrome, what information the Human Fertilisation and Embryology Authority (HFEA) collects about the (a) identity of drugs used in treatment and (b) dosage used and the associated regimen for ovarian stimulation at each clinic; and what comparative assessment he has made of the collection of such data by the HFEA and by other countries that report data to the European Society of Human Reproduction and Embryology.","Biography information for Jim Dobbin","Jim Dobbin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204590","204590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76401","2014-07-10","Department of Health","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many children and young people have been seen as outpatients at Stafford Hospital in each of the years (a) 2009-10, (b) 2010-11, (c) 2011-12, (d) 2012-13 and (e) 2013-14.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204576","204576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76402","2014-07-14","Department of Health","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many total bed nights children and young people stayed overnight at Stafford Hospital in each of the years (a) 2009-10, (b) 2010-11, (c) 2011-12, (d) 2012-13 and (e) 2013-14.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204596","204596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76403","2014-07-14","Department of Health","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many children and young people were treated as inpatients at Stafford Hospital in each of the years (a) 2009-10, (b) 2010-11, (c) 2011-12, (d) 2012-13 and (e) 2013-14.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204597","204597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76404","2014-07-10","Department of Health","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much his Department has spent on providing translation and interpretation services in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204637","204637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76405","2014-07-10","Department of Health","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make it his policy that a final policy announcement on the standardised packaging of tobacco will be made on the floor of the House.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204638","204638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76406","2014-07-14","Department of Health","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Answer of 1 April 2014, Official Report, column 711, on brain tumours (children), what proportion of the £450 million which the Government has committed to enable earlier diagnosis of cancer has been allocated to reduce the delay of diagnosis of brain tumours in children.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204635","204635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76407","2014-07-14","Department of Health","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the cost to the NHS of (a) foetal alcohol syndrome and (b) foetal alcohol syndrome disorders.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204669","204669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76408","2014-07-14","Department of Health","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of children who were not registered with a GP in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204670","204670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76409","2014-07-14","Department of Health","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 16 June 2014, Official Report, column 494W, on mental health services: young people, when NHS England's review of Tier 4 Children and Adolescent Mental Health Services provision will be published.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204667","204667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76410","2014-07-14","Department of Health","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of voluntary labelling to warn against drinking in pregnancy.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204668","204668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76411","2014-07-14","Department of Health","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that drug retailers accurately describe the operations of their products; if he will require retailers of the drug Ulipristal acetate to detail accurately its abortifacient effects; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jim Dobbin","Jim Dobbin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204592","204592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76412","2014-07-10","Home Office","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people on the Sex Offenders Register failed to complete their annual notification in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204659","204659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76413","2014-07-10","Home Office","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to monitor UK citizens suspected to be travelling, or are found to have travelled, to the Middle East to fight for ISIS and similar radical groups to ensure that upon their return they will not pose an internal threat through their own actions or the radicalisation of others.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204619","204619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76414","2014-07-10","Home Office","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the effect on people in Northern Ireland of delays in handling passport applications.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204609","204609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76415","2014-07-10","Home Office","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many places are currently available for immigration detainees; how many such places are currently occupied; what assessment she has made of the effect of fraud in English language tests on the number of immigration detainee places needed; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204643","204643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76416","2014-07-10","Home Office","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people were arrested following the recently uncovered English language test fraud; and how many of these people have been (a) held as an immigration detainee and (b) released.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204657","204657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76417","2014-07-10","Home Office","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what measures are in place to offer safe passage to the UK for those seeking refuge from institutionalised religious persecution across the world.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204617","204617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76418","2014-07-10","Home Office","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many Metropolitan Police officers were deployed on the streets in each year since 2010; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204525","204525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76419","2014-07-10","Home Office","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the number of people in (a) Kilmarnock and Loudoun, (b) Scotland and (c) the UK  who have used the premium one day service for passport application in each month since January 2014.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204518","204518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76420","2014-07-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of people in (a) the UK, (b) Scotland and (c) Kilmarnock and Loudoun constituency who are enrolled in  NEST and make additional payments by monthly direct debit.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204519","204519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76421","2014-07-10","Home Office","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what metrics her Department applies to assess the performance of Sussex Safer Roads Partnership's contribution to Operation Crackdown.","Biography information for Mike Weir","Mr Mike Weir","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204563","204563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76422","2014-07-10","Home Office","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will publish her assessment of the effectiveness of the protocols governing Sussex Safer Roads Partnership's contribution to Operation Crackdown.","Biography information for Mike Weir","Mr Mike Weir","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204564","204564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76423","2014-07-10","Home Office","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what (a) financial, (b) staffing and (c) capacity-building support and assistance her Department has given to Sussex Safer Roads Partnership in respect of (i) activities relating to Operation Crackdown and (ii) all other activities in each year since its inception.","Biography information for Mike Weir","Mr Mike Weir","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204562","204562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76424","2014-07-10","Home Office","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans she has to bring forward legislative proposals to ban the testing of household products on animals.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204393","204393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76425","2014-07-10","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps the Government is taking to address the problem of revenge pornography; and if he will meet representatives of the National Union of Students to discuss that matter.","Biography information for Andy Sawford","Andy Sawford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204400","204400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76426","2014-07-10","Home Office","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many women were detained whilst seeking asylum for (a) less than three days, (b) between four and seven days, (c) between eight and 14 days, (d) between 15 and 28 days, (e) between 29 days and three months, (f) between three months and one year and (g) over one year in the latest year for which figures are available.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204426","204426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76427","2014-07-10","Home Office","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many women who have sought asylum in the UK in each year since 2010 have (a) been granted asylum, (b) been detained pending application and (c) been refused asylum and removed.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204430","204430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76428","2014-07-10","Home Office","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of women who have been detained pending their asylum claims were subsequently granted asylum in each of the last three years for which figures are available.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204427","204427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76429","2014-07-10","Home Office","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many mobile telephones, BlackBerrys and laptops were lost by her Department in (a) 2013 and (b) 2014 to date.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204474","204474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76430","2014-07-10","Home Office","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much was spent on immigration security at UK airports in 2013.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204497","204497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76431","2014-07-14","Home Office","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many passport applications were defined as work in progress on 7 July 2014.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204442","204442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76432","2014-07-10","House of Commons Commission","2014-07-08","To ask the hon. Member for Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross representing the House of Commons Commission, how many mobile telephones, BlackBerrys and laptops were lost by the House of Commons Commission in (a) 2013 and (b) 2014 to date.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204475","204475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76433","2014-07-10","House of Commons Commission","2014-07-08","To ask the hon. Member for Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross representing the House of Commons Commission, if he will take steps to make the latest edition of Erskine May's Parliamentary Practice available free of charge online.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204435","204435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76434","2014-07-10","House of Commons Commission","2014-07-08","To ask the hon. Member for Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross representing the House of Commons Commission, if the House of Commons Commission will make available to the Welsh Affairs Committee funds to allow the hiring of Welsh translators to allow submissions to be provided without English translation.","Biography information for Susan Elan Jones","Susan Elan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204522","204522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76435","2014-07-14","Department for International Development","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if officials in her Department will meet displaced people from the Gambella region of Ethiopia to discuss forcible removal and abuse in the Ethiopian government's villagisation programme.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204545","204545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76436","2014-07-14","Department for International Development","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, when she last discussed the villagisation programme with the government of Ethiopia.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204549","204549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76437","2014-07-10","Department for International Development","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that the UK plays a leading role in tackling violence against women and girls in the most disadvantaged parts of the globe; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204529","204529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76438","2014-07-14","Department for International Development","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much funding has been committed to tackling malaria in each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204594","204594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76439","2014-07-10","Department for International Development","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that the processes governing the allocation of UK development assistance gives cognisance to the escalation of persecution against Christians.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204613","204613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76440","2014-07-10","Department for International Development","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 18 June 2014, Official Report, column 644W, on infrastructure projects: Jordan Valley, what positive benefits for Palestinians living in Area C have resulted so far from her Department's engagement with Israel.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204640","204640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76441","2014-07-10","Department for International Development","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many mobile telephones, BlackBerrys and laptops were lost by her Department in (a) 2013 and (b) 2014 to date.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204476","204476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76442","2014-07-14","Department for International Development","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what financial support for the Backpack Health Worker Team programme in Burma her Department will provide in the next two years.","Biography information for Fiona O'Donnell","Fiona O'Donnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204484","204484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76443","2014-07-14","Department for International Development","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether her Department is providing additional funding to The Border Consortium to help reverse recent ration cuts for refugees from Burma in camps in Thailand which they supply.","Biography information for Mr David Ward","Mr David Ward","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204439","204439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76444","2014-07-14","Department for International Development","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, which companies and organisations are subcontracted or given grants by the World Bank to carry out projects in Burma funded by British aid.","Biography information for Mr David Ward","Mr David Ward","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204440","204440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76445","2014-07-10","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of all sentences handed down at (a) Keighly Magistrates' Court and (b) Bradford Crown Court in each year since 2008 were custodial sentences.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204458","204458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76446","2014-07-10","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what his policy is on the wearing of the (a) niqab and (b) burka during interaction with (i) probation and (ii) prison officers.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204453","204453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76447","2014-07-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will publish the names of people who have taken multiple cases against different employers to an employment tribunal.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204454","204454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76448","2014-07-10","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been convicted of the offence of squatting in a residential building under section 144 of the Legal Aid, Sentencing and Punishment of Offenders Act 2012 on more than one occasion since its entry into force.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204455","204455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76449","2014-07-10","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners convicted of terrorist-related offences are held in open prisons.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204456","204456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76450","2014-07-10","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the highest number of absconds from prison by an individual offender has been in the last 20 years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204457","204457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76451","2014-07-10","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the Answer of 13 May 2014, Official Report, columns 506-8W, on sentencing: West Yorkshire, what proportion of offenders in each offence category the figures in the table represent for each of the years 2011, 2012 and 2013.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204500","204500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76452","2014-07-10","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many offenders have absconded from prison on more than one occasion in each of the last 20 years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204502","204502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76453","2014-07-10","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many mobile telephones, BlackBerrys and laptops were lost by his Department in (a) 2013 and (b) 2014 to date.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204477","204477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76454","2014-07-10","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners convicted of terrorist-related offences have been released from prison each of the last five years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204460","204460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76455","2014-07-10","Department of Health","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many offenders of each offence type have escaped from mental health units in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204459","204459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76456","2014-07-10","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average prison sentence was for offenders of each ethnicity convicted of each type of racially aggravated offence in the last five years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204641","204641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76457","2014-07-10","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the ethnicity of each (a) offender and (b) victim of each racially aggravated offence which resulted in a prison sentence was in the last five years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204642","204642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76458","2014-07-10","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of (a) offenders and (b) victims of religiously aggravated offences in each of the last five years were of each religious belief.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204656","204656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76459","2014-07-10","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many new matter starts were awarded in mental health in Blackpool North and Cleveleys constituency for (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12, (c) 2012-13, (d) 2013-14 and (e) 2014-15.","Biography information for Paul Maynard","Paul Maynard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204647","204647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76460","2014-07-10","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many new matter starts were awarded in mental health in the North West for (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12, (c) 2012-13, (d) 2013-14 and (e) 2014-15.","Biography information for Paul Maynard","Paul Maynard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204648","204648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76461","2014-07-10","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many new matter starts were awarded in mental health in Lancashire for (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12, (c) 2012-13, (d) 2013-14 and (e) 2014-15.","Biography information for Paul Maynard","Paul Maynard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204649","204649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76462","2014-07-10","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners convicted of terrorist-related offences have re-offended since being released in each of the last 10 years; and what the offence type was of each such re-conviction.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204644","204644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76463","2014-07-10","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many foreign national prisoners have been returned to each country where the UK has invested in prisons in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204658","204658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76464","2014-07-10","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of new matter starts are held back from being awarded at the outset of the contract; and on what grounds they are so held back.","Biography information for Paul Maynard","Paul Maynard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204650","204650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76465","2014-07-10","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many of those released from prison for offences committed during the riots in London in 2011 have been returned to prison following a further offence.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204646","204646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76466","2014-07-14","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether there have been significant delays in care proceedings involving children in family courts in England and Wales since the implementation of the legal aid reforms in 2013; and if he will publish statistics of the length of such proceedings.","Biography information for Mr Elfyn Llwyd","Mr Elfyn Llwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204623","204623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76467","2014-07-14","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the effect on the length of care proceedings involving children in England and Wales of the reforms to legal aid since April 2013.","Biography information for Mr Elfyn Llwyd","Mr Elfyn Llwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204624","204624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76468","2014-07-14","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many applicants did not receive legal aid to pursue residency and contact cases that they would have received before the reforms to legal aid since April 2013.","Biography information for Mr Elfyn Llwyd","Mr Elfyn Llwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204625","204625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76469","2014-07-14","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many applications for legal aid for family matters have been refused since April 2013; and how many of these were subsequently granted under the Exceptional Funding Scheme.","Biography information for Mr Elfyn Llwyd","Mr Elfyn Llwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204626","204626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76470","2014-07-14","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many litigants in person have appeared before courts in England and Wales in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Elfyn Llwyd","Mr Elfyn Llwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204627","204627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76471","2014-07-14","Home Office","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of the remedies available to people who are the subjects of erroneous or malicious reports to Sussex Police in respect of the Operation Crackdown online mechanism.","Biography information for Mike Weir","Mr Mike Weir","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204603","204603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76472","2014-07-10","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what (a) financial, (b) staffing and (c) capacity-building support and assistance his Department has given to the Sussex Safer Roads Partnership in respect of (i) activities relating to Operation Crackdown and (ii) all other activities in each year since its inception.","Biography information for Mike Weir","Mr Mike Weir","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204571","204571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76473","2014-07-14","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what advice he has taken from the Information Commissioner's Office about data protection and freedom of information issues arising from Sussex Police's promotion of the Operation Crackdown.","Biography information for Mike Weir","Mr Mike Weir","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204604","204604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76474","2014-07-10","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will publish his assessment of the effectiveness of the protocols governing Sussex Safer Roads Partnership's contribution to Operation Crackdown.","Biography information for Mike Weir","Mr Mike Weir","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204573","204573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76475","2014-07-10","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what metrics his Department applies to assess the performance of Sussex Safer Roads Partnership's contribution to Operation Crackdown.","Biography information for Mike Weir","Mr Mike Weir","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204572","204572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76476","2014-07-10","Home Office","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will make it his policy that persons who receive letters from Sussex Police related to Operation Crackdown will be entitled to simultaneous disclosure of (a) all evidence held in relation to the incident that triggered the report and (b) any related incidents on which the the service seeks to rely.","Biography information for Mike Weir","Mr Mike Weir","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204569","204569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76477","2014-07-10","Home Office","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of the compliance with the precepts of natural justice of the procedures adopted by Sussex Police in its promotion of Operation Crackdown.","Biography information for Mike Weir","Mr Mike Weir","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204570","204570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76478","2014-07-14","Home Office","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, for what reason people who have received letters from Sussex Police about alleged incidents within the remit of Operation Crackdown are advised that subject access requests under section 7 of the Data Protection Act are redundant.","Biography information for Mike Weir","Mr Mike Weir","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204605","204605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76479","2014-07-14","Home Office","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have been employed in web development and related roles in each year since the establishment of Operation Crackdown by Sussex Police; and what key performance indicators apply to them.","Biography information for Mike Weir","Mr Mike Weir","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204607","204607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76480","2014-07-14","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many victims bereaved by homicide received support from Victim Support under the National Homicide Service in each region of England and in Wales in each year since 2011.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204588","204588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76481","2014-07-14","Home Office","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the number of online reports made to Sussex Police in respect of the Operation Crackdown online mechanism which are (a) malicious and (b) erroneous.","Biography information for Mike Weir","Mr Mike Weir","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204606","204606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76482","2014-07-14","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, in how many court proceedings in England and Wales in each year since May 2010 video recording was taken to be (a) an available and (b) a not available special measure for eligible witnesses as defined in section 18 of the Youth Justice and Criminal Evidence Act 1999.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204589","204589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76483","2014-07-10","Home Office","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have been the subject of (a) reports and (b) letters resulting from Sussex Police's operation of Operation Crackdown in respect of (i) motoring and (ii) non-motoring incidents in each year since its inception.","Biography information for Mike Weir","Mr Mike Weir","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204568","204568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76484","2014-07-14","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been (a) arrested, (b) cautioned, (c) proceeded against and (d) convicted of an offence under the provisions of the Conservation of Habitats and Species Regulations 2010 in each year since their enactment.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204551","204551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76485","2014-07-10","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will place in the Library a copy of the course materials used to train magistrates in relation to domestic violence.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204508","204508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76486","2014-07-10","Department of Health","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many offenders who absconded from mental health units in each of the last 10 years remain at large.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204504","204504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76487","2014-07-10","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been (a) arrested for and (b) convicted of the offence of squatting in a residential building under section 144 of the Legal Aid, Sentencing and Punishment of Offenders Act 2012 since its entry into force.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204505","204505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76488","2014-07-10","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, in how many and what proportion of all offences resulting in a court-issued fine the maximum fine was handed down in the last five years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204503","204503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76489","2014-07-10","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which organisations collect subscriptions through the employer's payroll service in his Department and its agencies.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204513","204513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76490","2014-07-10","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners were released on temporary licence from each category of prison in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204514","204514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76491","2014-07-10","Department of Health","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what medical assessment is made of the mental health of ex-armed forces personal who are imprisoned in order to assess the presence of post traumatic stress disorder.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204516","204516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76492","2014-07-10","Department of Health","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment has been made of the number of prisoners who have previously served in the armed forces; and how many such people have been diagnosed with post traumatic stress disorder.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204517","204517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76493","2014-07-10","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the process is for awarding (a) new matter starts in mental health and (b) extra new matter starts in mental health when firms exhaust their original quota.","Biography information for Paul Maynard","Paul Maynard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204651","204651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76494","2014-07-14","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 26 June 2014, Official Report, column 305W, on homicide: victim support schemes, what evaluation mechanisms are included in the Grant for Coordination and Delivery of Support to those Bereaved by Homicide.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204663","204663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76495","2014-07-10","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many offenders convicted of failing to comply with the notification requirements of the Sex Offenders Register in each of the last five years were given each type of available sentence for the offence.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204660","204660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76496","2014-07-10","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average prison sentence was of an offender convicted of a religiously aggravated offence in each of the last five years by (a) type of offence and (b) the religious belief of the offender.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204652","204652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76497","2014-07-10","Home Office","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which the highest number of previous convictions for failing to comply with the notification requirements of the Sex Offenders Register for an individual convicted of a further such offence without being sent to prison was in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204661","204661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76498","2014-07-10","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the religious belief of the (a) offender and (b) victim of each religiously aggravated offence which resulted in a prison sentence was in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204653","204653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76499","2014-07-10","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of individual sentencing guidlines do not include the maximum sentence available to the court in the most serious offence range of the offence.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204662","204662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76500","2014-07-10","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average spending per head on prison libraries was for (a) male and (b) female prisoners in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204654","204654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76501","2014-07-10","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 14 May 2014, Official Report, column 689W, on the Employment Tribunal Service, what the nature was of the complaint in the cases of the highest compensation payments for race in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204681","204681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76502","2014-07-14","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 7 July 2014, Official Report, column 78W, on homicide, if he will require the Legal Aid Agency to record an offence type of homicide in future.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204664","204664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76503","2014-07-10","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 14 May 2014, Official Report, column 714W, on prison libraries, what the spending was by category of expenditure for HM Prison (a) Leeds and (b) Wakefield.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204680","204680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76504","2014-07-14","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 7 July 2014, Official Report, column 78W, on homicide: victim support schemes, which of the peer support groups within the original victim support bid cater specifically for those bereaved through homicide abroad.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204665","204665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76505","2014-07-14","Department for International Development","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 7 July 2014, Official Report, column 1W, on abortion, if she will withdraw her Department's policy position paper entitled Safe and Unsafe Abortion pending a free vote in the House on the use of UK aid to (a) campaign for more liberal abortion laws in other countries and (b) provide abortion services in other countries.","Biography information for Jim Dobbin","Jim Dobbin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204591","204591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76506","2014-07-10","Prime Minister","2014-07-08","To ask the Prime Minister, if he will make it policy that ministers should (a) answer to Parliament on the contents of leaked Government documents and (b) not comment on documents leaked from organisations outside Government.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204380","204380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76507","2014-07-10","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will replicate for victims and survivors of Northern Ireland-related acts of terrorism in Great Britain the support services available in Northern Ireland; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204452","204452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76508","2014-07-10","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what research the Government has commissioned on the educational, psychological, welfare, justice and related needs of victims and survivors of Northern Ireland-related acts of terrorism in Great Britain; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204451","204451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76509","2014-07-10","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what support the Government provides to victims and survivors of Northern Ireland-related acts of terrorism in Great Britain; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204449","204449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76510","2014-07-10","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate the Government has made of the number of victims and survivors of Northern Ireland-related acts of terrorism in Great Britain where such victims and survivors live in Great Britain; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204450","204450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76511","2014-07-10","Prime Minister","2014-07-08","To ask the Prime Minister, when he last met the Prime Minister of Jamaica; and when he next plans to meet her.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204495","204495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76512","2014-07-15","Department for Transport","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to require service stations to advertise their fuel prices so that they are visible from the highway so that motorists know them before leaving the public carriageway.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204488","204488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76513","2014-07-10","Department for Transport","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to ensure disabled rail users can access all platforms at rural stations.","Biography information for Richard Benyon","Richard Benyon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204417","204417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76514","2014-07-14","Department for Transport","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to improve rail connections from northern England to Scotland; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Iain McKenzie","Iain McKenzie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204599","204599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76515","2014-07-10","Department for Transport","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the (a) funding and (b) ownership arrangements are for the 17 new trains to be introduced on the Essex Thameside line under the terms of the new franchise agreement with NXET Trains Ltd; and what the deadline is for the introduction into service of the new fleet.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204534","204534"
