"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622655","2016-10-31","Home Office","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps the Government has taken in response to the recommendation in paragraph 4.1.4 of the Hutton review of forensic pathology in England and Wales on (a) introducing a publicly-funded salaried service for forensic pathologists and (b) job planning coronial autopsy sessions within NHS contracts.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50737","50737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622656","2016-10-31","Home Office","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the potential effect on (a) families and (b) businesses of the introduction of visa charges on travel to and from the UK after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50736","50736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622657","2016-10-31","Home Office","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps the Government has taken as a result of the recommendation made in the Hutton review of forensic pathology in England and Wales, submitted to the Minister of State for Crime and Prevention in March 2015, that non-forensic pathologists engaged in mass fatality incidents should work under the supervision of a Home Office Registered Forensic Pathologist.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50715","50715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622658","2016-11-04","Home Office","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the cost was to the public purse of (a) room hire, (b) food and (c) hot and cold drinks for the UK Visas and Immigration North West MP Account Manager Team Regional Event held at Manchester Civil Justice Centre on 16 September 2016.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50713","50713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622659","2016-10-31","Home Office","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps the Government has taken as a result of the recommendation made in the Hutton review of forensic pathology in England and Wales, submitted to the Minister of State for Crime and Prevention in March 2015, that the User Requirements for Forensic Pathology form the basis for more formal contractual arrangements with the police.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50773","50773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622660","2016-10-31","Home Office","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps the Government has taken as a result of the recommendations made in the Hutton review of forensic pathology in England and Wales, submitted to the Minister of State for Crime and Prevention in March 2015, that (a) there needs to be greater interchange between forensic and general pathology training systems and (b) the threshold for referring such cases up the supervisory ladder should be low.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50774","50774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622661","2016-10-31","Home Office","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many passports have been confiscated from Syrian citizens by UK officials in Turkey in 2016 on the basis of those passports having been stolen.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50784","50784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622662","2016-10-31","Home Office","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many arrests for knife crimes have taken place in (a) London and (b) Bethnal Green and Bow in each year since 2005.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50785","50785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622663","2016-10-31","Home Office","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many gun-related homicides have taken place in (a) London and (b) Bethnal Green and Bow in each year since 2005.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50786","50786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622664","2016-10-31","Home Office","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to counter threats of rape and sexual violence made through (a) social media networks, (b) Whatsapp and (c) Twitter.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50787","50787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622665","2016-10-31","Home Office","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps the Government has taken as a result of the recommendation made in the Hutton review of forensic pathology in England and Wales, submitted to the Minister of State for Crime and Prevention in March 2015, that as a temporary measure to ensure that sensitive material (such as notes, photographs and copy statements) from forensic autopsies are kept in secure locations, and all unused material should be stored with the police file as is normally the case with all other unused material.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50755","50755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622666","2016-10-31","Home Office","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Answer of 23 May 2012 to Question 106405 on asylum: young people, what the results of the dental x-ray pilot were.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50781","50781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622667","2016-10-31","Home Office","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many apprenticeships have been created in her Department in each region in each of the last five years; and how many participants in those apprenticeships subsequently secured a job within the Civil Service.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50811","50811"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622668","2016-10-31","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 12 October 2016 to Question 48562, how many of the families of the victims of the 61 prisoners (a) were offered the chance to receive information about key developments in the relevant prisoner's sentence and (b) took up the offer to receive such information.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50863","50863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622669","2016-10-31","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 12 October 2016 to Question 48562, how much notice was given to the family of each victim of the release on temporary licence of the offender.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50864","50864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622670","2016-10-31","Home Office","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps the Government has taken as a result of the recommendation made in the Hutton review of forensic pathology in England and Wales, submitted to the Minister of State for Crime and Prevention in March 2015, that (a) the Criminal Procedure Rules should be vigorously enforced in order to avoid costly and unnecessary challenges by experts for the prosecution and the defence in court and (b) the provision for a judge to allow experts to give evidence via video link could be utilised in order to encourage more-sub-speciality medical experts to engage in the criminal justice process.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50866","50866"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622671","2016-10-31","Home Office","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps the Government has taken as a result of the recommendation made in the Hutton review of forensic pathology in England and Wales, submitted to the Minister of State for Crime and Prevention in March 2015, that pathologists and other clinicians, police and coroners and their officers all need to be sensitive to the difficulties surrounding communication and understanding that arise in a multi-cultural society when death occurs in order to do what is possible to manage the situation.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50868","50868"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622672","2016-10-31","Home Office","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps the Government has taken as a result of the recommendation made in the Hutton review of forensic pathology in England and Wales, submitted to the Minister of State for Crime and Prevention in March 2015, that consideration should be given to the current fee structure payable for autopsies and possibly revised on the basis that you get what you pay for.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50865","50865"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622673","2016-10-31","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 12 October 2016 to Question 41032, how many prisoners convicted of murder had previously been released on temporary licence over a Christmas period; and, in each such case, how many times each of those prisoners had previously been released at Christmas.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50862","50862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622674","2016-10-31","Home Office","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the safety of unaccompanied refugee children who have not been placed in alternative accommodation or registered with the French authorities after the demolition of the camp in Calais; and what steps the Government is taking in conjunction with the French authorities to help ensure the safety of those children.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50860","50860"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622675","2016-11-08","Home Office","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the article, DVLA works with the police and HM Revenue and Customs to crack down on illegal foreign registered vehicles, published on the GOV.UK website on 30 January 2015, how many foreign-registered cars were seized and impounded by each constabulary in England in each month between 1 January 2015 and 30 September 2016.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50859","50859"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622676","2016-10-31","Department for International Development","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many apprenticeships have been created in her Department in each region in each of the last five years; and how many participants in those apprenticeships subsequently secured a job within the Civil Service.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50812","50812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622677","2016-10-31","Department for International Development","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent estimate she has made of the level of procurement of British steel by her Department in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50640","50640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622678","2016-10-31","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent estimate she has made of the level of procurement of British steel by her Department in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50641","50641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622679","2016-10-31","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent assessment her Department has made of the adequacy of the ratio of staff to young people at HMP Glen Parva in 2016; and what the adequacy of such ratios is up to 2020.","Biography information for Alberto Costa","Alberto Costa","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50652","50652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622682","2016-10-31","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many apprenticeships have been created in her Department in each region in each of the last five years; and how many participants in those apprenticeships subsequently secured a job within the Civil Service.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50813","50813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622683","2016-10-31","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many women were received into each prison under licence recall in the 12 months (a) prior to and (b) following the introduction of Transforming Rehabilitation.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50840","50840"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622684","2016-10-31","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of 14-day recalls for women who breach their licence conditions in reducing future offending.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50839","50839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622685","2016-10-31","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the findings of Her Majesty's Inspectorate of Probation, published in their report entitled A thematic inspection of the provision and quality of services in the community for women who offend, on 29 September 2016, whether she plans to re-establish dedicated funding for community services for women.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50848","50848"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622686","2016-10-31","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment she has made of the effect of changes to immigration and asylum tribunal fees on access to justice.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50783","50783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622687","2016-11-01","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if she will clarify the remit of the review into driving offences and penalties for drivers who cause death or serious injury to other people on the roads.","Biography information for Mr Mark Williams","Mr Mark Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50796","50796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622688","2016-11-01","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the timescale is for the review into driving offences and penalties for drivers who cause death or serious injury to other people on the roads.","Biography information for Mr Mark Williams","Mr Mark Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50797","50797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622689","2016-10-31","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if her Department's review of Transforming Rehabilitation addresses the effect of that policy on women; and when she plans to publish the findings of that review.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50718","50718"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622690","2016-11-01","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what discussions she has had with the President of the Family Division  on the issuance of new guidance on the anonymisation of judgments.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50745","50745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622691","2016-11-01","Department of Health","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of mental health support available for youth offenders in the criminal justice system.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50749","50749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622692","2016-10-31","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate she has made of the cost to her Department over the last 12 months of expanding recall eligibility to those released from short prison sentences.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50838","50838"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622693","2016-10-31","Northern Ireland Office","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many apprenticeships have been created in his Department in each region in each of the last five years; and how many participants in those apprenticeships subsequently secured a job within the Civil Service.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50814","50814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622694","2016-10-31","Northern Ireland Office","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what recent estimate he has made of the level of procurement of British steel by his Department in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50642","50642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622695","2016-10-31","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many EU laws, regulations and standards he plans to include in the planned Great Repeal Bill.","Biography information for Roger Mullin","Roger Mullin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50869","50869"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622696","2016-10-31","Scotland Office","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what recent estimate he has made of the level of procurement of British steel by his Department in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50643","50643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622697","2016-10-31","Scotland Office","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how many apprenticeships have been created in his Department in each region in each of the last five years; and how many participants in those apprenticeships subsequently secured a job within the Civil Service.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50815","50815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622698","2016-10-31","Department for Transport","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many apprenticeships have been created in his Department in each region in each of the last five years; and how many participants in those apprenticeships subsequently secured a job within the Civil Service.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50816","50816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622699","2016-11-01","Department for Transport","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to encourage commuters to use carbon-free public transport in (a) England and (b) Cumbria.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50799","50799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622700","2016-11-01","Department for Transport","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the oral statement on Airport Capacity of 25 October 2016, Official Report, column 163, on what evidential basis the figure of £61 billion was calculated for the economic benefit to the UK of expanding that airport; and what the reasons are for the difference between that figure and the £211 billion estimated by the Airports Commission.","Biography information for Dr Tania Mathias","Dr Tania Mathias","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50792","50792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622701","2016-10-31","Department for Transport","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the oral contribution of the Minister of State of 26 October 2016, Official Report, column 136WH, when he plans to begin consultation on the study of safety on the A34.","Biography information for Mr Edward Vaizey","Mr Edward Vaizey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50670","50670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622702","2016-10-31","Department for Transport","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent estimate he has made of the level of procurement of British steel by his Department in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50644","50644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622703","2016-11-01","Department for Transport","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 14 October 2016 to Question 48758, what steps have been taken to measure the effect of noise caused by flights going to and from London City Airport in Eltham constituency; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Clive Efford","Clive Efford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50646","50646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622704","2016-11-01","Department for Transport","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 19 October 2016 to Question 48759, what measures are in place to minimise the noise footprint around London City Airport; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Clive Efford","Clive Efford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50647","50647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622705","2016-10-31","Department for Transport","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department has made an assessment of the potential (a) economic merits and (b) benefits to passengers of a western rail link to Heathrow Airport.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50682","50682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622706","2016-11-01","Department for Transport","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what objectives his Department set for the Marine Environment Protection Committee of the International Maritime Organisation of 24 to 28 October 2016; and what progress was made against those objectives.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50666","50666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622707","2016-10-31","Department for Transport","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department has made an assessment of the potential economic effect of a third runway at Heathrow Airport on Swindon.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50683","50683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622708","2016-11-01","Department for Transport","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what progress has been made on the re-opening of the Ashley Hill railway station in Bristol West constituency.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50695","50695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622709","2016-11-01","Department for Transport","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department has taken to establish the best means by which high-polluting vehicles can be accurately and efficiently identified to facilitate enforcement action.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50702","50702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622710","2016-10-31","Department for Transport","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many responses his Department received during the public consultation on advanced driver assistance systems and automated vehicle technologies.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50669","50669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622711","2016-10-31","Wales Office","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how many apprenticeships have been created in his Department in each region in each of the last five years; and how many participants in those apprenticeships subsequently secured a job within the Civil Service.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50817","50817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622712","2016-11-01","Women and Equalities","2016-10-27","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what estimate she has made of the proportion of professional people working in STEM-related industries that are female.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50800","50800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622713","2016-10-31","Department for Education","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many apprenticeships have been created in the Government's Equalities Office in each region in each of the last five years; and how many participants in those apprenticeships subsequently secured a job within the Civil Service.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50809","50809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622714","2016-10-31","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps the Government plans to take to ensure the provision of specialist employment support to disabled jobseekers from 2017.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50690","50690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622715","2016-10-31","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether the Government plans to make additional funding available for specialist employment support for disabled jobseekers from 2017.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50691","50691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622716","2016-10-31","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessmenthis Department has made of the suitability of (a) phones and (b) laptops for use by claimants wishing to take an audio recording of a personal independence payment assessment.","Biography information for Holly Lynch","Holly Lynch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50667","50667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622717","2016-10-31","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, in what proportion of personal independence payment assessments the claimant makes a permitted audio recording of the assessment.","Biography information for Holly Lynch","Holly Lynch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50668","50668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622718","2016-10-31","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many disabled jobseekers his Department expects to be able to access specialist support through the proposed Work and Health programme.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50689","50689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622719","2016-10-31","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many personal independence payment decisions have been amended at the mandatory reconsideration state in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50625","50625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622720","2016-10-31","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many apprenticeships have been created in his Department in each region in each of the last five years; and how many participants in those apprenticeships subsequently secured a job within the Civil Service.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50818","50818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622721","2016-10-31","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and which local authorities his Department is investigating on the grounds of potential housing benefit fraud.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50846","50846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622722","2016-10-31","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate his Department has made of the cost to individual claimants of purchasing the audio recording equipment that is permitted for use during personal independence payment assessments.","Biography information for Holly Lynch","Holly Lynch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50721","50721"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622723","2016-10-31","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to ensure parity of treatment for people with physical and mental health issues when applying for benefits.","Biography information for Oliver Colvile","Oliver Colvile","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50730","50730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622724","2016-10-31","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people with Parkinson's disease receive personal independence payment at the (a) daily living standard, (b) daily living enhanced, (c) mobility standard and (d) mobility enhanced rate.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50850","50850"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622725","2016-11-01","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to Nissan's announcement of 27 October 2016 on the production of the next Qashqai and X-Trail models in the UK, what support and assurances the Government has offered to that company.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50793","50793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622726","2016-11-01","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the Answer of 17 October 2016 to Question LH2367, what steps his Department is taking to ensure small and medium-sized enterprises involved in the supply chain for the production of Nissan vehicles in the North East automotive sector remain competitive.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50794","50794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622727","2016-10-31","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many apprenticeships have been created in his Department in each region in each of the last five years; and how many participants in those apprenticeships subsequently secured a job within the Civil Service.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50801","50801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622728","2016-10-31","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will publish the evidence used to inform the range of the costs set out for alternative large-scale low carbon generation technologies in the 2020s in his Department's Hinkley Point C Value for Money Assessment.","Biography information for Callum McCaig","Callum McCaig","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50624","50624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622729","2016-10-31","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent estimate he has made of the level of procurement of British steel by his Department in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50630","50630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622730","2016-10-31","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, for what reasons the range of the costs for alternative large-scale low carbon generation technologies in the 2020s as set out in his Department's Hinkley Point C Value for Money Assessment differs from the assessment of the same technologies in the National Audit Office report on Nuclear power in the UK, published in July 2016.","Biography information for Callum McCaig","Callum McCaig","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50621","50621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622731","2016-10-31","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will publish the evidence used to inform the conclusion in the Hinkley Point C Value for Money Assessment that the same capacity of onshore wind and solar would require significant upgrades to the grid and increase the costs of keeping the system in balance.","Biography information for Callum McCaig","Callum McCaig","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50622","50622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622732","2016-10-31","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will publish the departmental report on which figures for the levelised cost of generating 1MWh with different technologies in 2025 in the National Audit Office report, Nuclear power in the UK, published in July 2016, are based.","Biography information for Callum McCaig","Callum McCaig","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50623","50623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622733","2016-10-31","Department for International Trade","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what recent estimate he has made of the level of procurement of British steel by his Department since it was established.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50627","50627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622734","2016-10-31","Department for International Trade","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, with which governments of non-EU countries he has discussed future trade agreements since his Department was created.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50688","50688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622735","2016-10-31","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what recent estimate he has made of the level of procurement of British steel by his Department since its creation.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50626","50626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622736","2016-10-31","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 13 October 2016 to Question 47485, whether member states will be bound by Article 1 of Protocol 1 of the European Convention on Human Rights, in respect of property rights, where the owner is a UK national, after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50779","50779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622737","2016-10-31","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many apprenticeships have been created in his Department in each region in each of the last five years; and how many participants in those apprenticeships subsequently secured a job within the Civil Service.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50807","50807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622738","2016-10-31","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, pursuant to the Answer of 13 October 2016 to Question 47485, if he will ensure the rights of UK owners of property in the EU to occupy that property (a) as a main residence while working, (b) as a main residence during retirement and (c) as an occasional residence, after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50789","50789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622739","2016-10-31","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether he plans to give domestic effect to the Acquired Rights Directive 2001/23/EC through the forthcoming Repeal Bill.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50829","50829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622740","2016-10-31","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether he plans to give domestic effect to the Collective Redundancies Directive 98/59/EC through the forthcoming Repeal Bill.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50831","50831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622741","2016-10-31","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether he plans to give domestic effect to the Agency Workers Directive 2008/104/EC through the forthcoming Repeal Bill.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50830","50830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622742","2016-10-31","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether he plans to give domestic effect to the European Works Council Directive 2006/109/EC through the forthcoming Repeal Bill.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50824","50824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622743","2016-10-31","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether he plans to give domestic effect to the Equal Treatment Directive 76/207/EC through the forthcoming Repeal Bill.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50825","50825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622744","2016-10-31","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether he plans to give domestic effect to the Young Workers Directive 94/33/EC through the forthcoming Repeal Bill.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50823","50823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622745","2016-10-31","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether he plans to give domestic effect to the Race Directive 2000/43/EC through the forthcoming Repeal Bill.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50826","50826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622746","2016-10-31","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether he plans to give domestic effect to the Working Time Directive 2003/88/EC through the forthcoming Repeal Bill.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50827","50827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622747","2016-10-31","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether he plans to give domestic effect to the Recast Gender Directive 2006/54/EC through the forthcoming Repeal Bill.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50828","50828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622748","2016-10-31","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether he plans to give domestic effect to the Part-Time Workers Directive 97/81/EC through the forthcoming Repeal Bill.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50819","50819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622749","2016-10-31","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether he plans to give domestic effect to the Parental Leave Directive 2010/18/EC through the forthcoming Repeal Bill.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50820","50820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622750","2016-10-31","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether he plans to give domestic effect to the Fixed-Term Workers Directive  99/70/EC through the forthcoming Repeal Bill.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50821","50821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622751","2016-10-31","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether he plans to give domestic effect to the Information and Consultation Directive 2002/14/EC through the forthcoming Repeal Bill.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50822","50822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622752","2016-10-31","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether he plans to give domestic effect to the Employment Framework Directive 89/391/EC through the forthcoming Repeal Bill.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50832","50832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622753","2016-10-31","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether he plans to give domestic effect to the Employer Insolvency Directive 2008/94/EC through the forthcoming Repeal Bill.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50833","50833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622754","2016-10-31","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether he plans to give domestic effect to the Employment Conditions Directive 91/533/EEC through the forthcoming Repeal Bill.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50867","50867"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622755","2016-11-04","Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster","2016-10-27","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster, how much has been donated by the Duchy of Lancaster Benevolent Fund in each of the last five years and in 2016; how much of that was donated to organisations and projects in Lancashire during each such year; and what use was made of those donations.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50664","50664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626904","2016-11-02","Cabinet Office","2016-10-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how his Department monitors the effectiveness of cross-cutting initiatives that involve more than one government department.","Biography information for John Pugh","John Pugh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 906983","906983"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626905","2016-11-02","Cabinet Office","2016-10-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what progress has been made on establishing the National Cyber Security Centre.","Biography information for Craig Williams","Craig Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 906987","906987"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626906","2016-11-02","Cabinet Office","2016-10-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will take steps to introduce automatic electoral registration.","Biography information for Callum McCaig","Callum McCaig","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 906990","906990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626907","2016-11-02","Cabinet Office","2016-10-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment he has made of the performance of the One Public Estate programme.","Biography information for Jo Churchill","Jo Churchill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 906984","906984"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626908","2016-11-02","Cabinet Office","2016-10-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when the Government plans to publish its initial findings from its audit to tackle racial disparities in public service outcomes.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 906985","906985"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626909","2016-11-02","Cabinet Office","2016-10-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what recent progress has been made on the use of digital technologies to improve public services.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 906988","906988"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621948","2016-10-31","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, when her Department plans to publish its consultation on regulatory reform of the commercial radio sector.","Biography information for Calum Kerr","Calum Kerr","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50454","50454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621949","2016-10-28","HM Treasury","2016-10-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what progress has been made in implementing the reforms set out in Fixing the foundations: creating a more prosperous nation, published in July 2015; and whether he plans to continue to monitor the recommendations set out in that document.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50486","50486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621950","2016-10-28","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the reasons are for the increase in costs of £1.6 billion by Cavendish Fluor Partnership for the clean-up project for 12 Magnox reactors.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50410","50410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621951","2016-10-28","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of management of the Nuclear Decommissioning Authority in response to the judgement arising from Energy Solutions EU Limited and the Nuclear Decommissioning Authority of 29 July 2016; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50560","50560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621952","2016-10-28","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the cost to the public purse was of the (a) legal and (b) associated costs in the case of EnergySolutions EU Limited and the Nuclear Decommissioning Authority.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50559","50559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621953","2016-10-28","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to improve the procurement process in the Nuclear Decommissioning Authority in response to the judgement arising from EnergySolutions EU Limited and the Nuclear Decommissioning Authority of 29 July 2016.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50561","50561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621954","2016-10-28","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what meetings (a) he and (b) other Ministers of his Department have had with representatives of the (i) aerospace, (ii) automotive, (iii) construction, (iv) life sciences and (v) tech sectors.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50430","50430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621955","2016-10-28","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, (a) how many and (b) what proportion of senior civil service graded posts in her Department classified as (i) deputy director, (ii) assistant director, (iii) team leader and (iv) policy manager have been based outside London in each year since 2014.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50396","50396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621956","2016-10-28","Attorney General","2016-10-26","To ask the Attorney General, (a) how many and (b) what proportion of senior civil service graded posts in the Law Officers' Departments classified as (i) deputy director, (ii) assistant director, (iii) team leader and (iv) policy manager have been based outside London in each year since 2014.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50394","50394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621957","2016-10-31","Cabinet Office","2016-10-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many male civil servants have applied for shared parental leave since April 2015; and whether his Department has made an estimate of the number of male civil servants eligible for such leave in that period.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50366","50366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621958","2016-10-31","Cabinet Office","2016-10-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, (a) how many and (b) what proportion of senior civil servants in his Department who are graded as (i) deputy director, (ii) assistant director, (iii) team leader or (iv) policy manager were based outside London in each year since 2014.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50326","50326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621959","2016-10-28","HM Treasury","2016-10-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, (a) how many and (b) what proportion of senior civil service graded posts in his Department classified as (i) deputy director, (ii) assistant director, (iii) team leader and (iv) policy manager have been based outside London in each year since 2014.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50408","50408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621960","2016-10-28","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, (a) how many and (b) what proportion of senior civil service graded posts in his Department classified as (i) deputy director, (ii) assistant director, (iii) team leader and (iv) policy manager have been based outside London in each year since 2014.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50395","50395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621961","2016-10-28","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, (a) how many and (b) what proportion of senior civil service graded posts in his Department classified as (i) deputy director, (ii) assistant director, (iii) team leader and (iv) policy manager have been based outside London in each year since 2014.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50397","50397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621962","2016-10-28","Department for Education","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, (a) how many and (b) what proportion of senior civil service graded posts in her Department classified as (i) deputy director, (ii) assistant director, (iii) team leader and (iv) policy manager have been based outside London in each year since 2014.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50398","50398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621963","2016-10-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, (a) how many and (b) what proportion of senior civil service graded posts in her Department classified as (i) deputy director, (ii) assistant director, (iii) team leader and (iv) policy manager have been based outside London in each year since 2014.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50399","50399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621964","2016-10-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, (a) how many and (b) what proportion of senior civil service graded posts in his Department classified as (i) deputy director, (ii) assistant director, (iii) team leader and (iv) policy manager have been based outside London in each year since 2014.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50400","50400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621965","2016-10-28","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, (a) how many and (b) what proportion of senior civil service graded posts in his Department classified as (i) deputy director, (ii) assistant director, (iii) team leader and (iv) policy manager have been based outside London in each year since 2014.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50393","50393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621966","2016-10-28","Scotland Office","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, (a) how many and (b) what proportion of senior civil service graded posts in his Department classified as (i) deputy director, (ii) assistant director, (iii) team leader and (iv) policy manager have been based outside London in each year since 2014.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50406","50406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621967","2016-10-28","Department for Transport","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, (a) how many and (b) what proportion of senior civil service graded posts in his Department classified as (i) deputy director, (ii) assistant director, (iii) team leader and (iv) policy manager have been based outside London in each year since 2014.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50407","50407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621968","2016-10-28","Wales Office","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, (a) how many and (b) what proportion of senior civil service graded posts in his Department classified as (i) deputy director, (ii) assistant director, (iii) team leader and (iv) policy manager have been based outside London in each year since 2014.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50409","50409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621969","2016-10-28","Department of Health","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which groups consulted on the Summary Documents produced for the prioritisation meeting of the Clinical Priorities Advisory Board.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50586","50586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621970","2016-10-28","Department of Health","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, (a) how many and (b) what proportion of senior civil service graded posts in his Department classified as (i) deputy director, (ii) assistant director, (iii) team leader and (iv) policy manager have been based outside London in each year since 2014.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50401","50401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621971","2016-10-28","Home Office","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, (a) how many and (b) what proportion of senior civil service graded posts in her Department classified as (i) deputy director, (ii) assistant director, (iii) team leader and (iv) policy manager have been based outside London in each year since 2014.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50402","50402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621972","2016-10-28","Department for International Development","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, (a) how many and (b) what proportion of senior civil service graded posts in her Department classified as (i) deputy director, (ii) assistant director, (iii) team leader and (iv) policy manager have been based outside London in each year since 2014.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50403","50403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621973","2016-10-28","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, (a) how many and (b) what proportion of senior civil service graded posts in her Department classified as (i) deputy director, (ii) assistant director, (iii) team leader and (iv) policy manager have been based outside London in each year since 2014.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50404","50404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621974","2016-10-28","Northern Ireland Office","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, (a) how many and (b) what proportion of senior civil service graded posts in his Department classified as (i) deputy director, (ii) assistant director, (iii) team leader and (iv) policy manager have been based outside London in each year since 2014.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50405","50405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621975","2016-10-28","Department of Health","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the innovative potential of PCSK9 inhibitor medicines for the treatment of high levels of cholesterol.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50562","50562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621976","2016-10-28","Department of Health","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to encourage the adoption of a personalised approach to medicines (a) in general and (b) in the treatment of familial hypercholesterolemia.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50611","50611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621977","2016-10-28","Department of Health","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he has made an assessment of the effect of the Cardiovascular Outcomes Strategy on patient outcomes since its publication.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50504","50504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621978","2016-10-28","Department for Education","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of Gypsy, Traveller and Roma pupils were excluded from school in each local authority area in 2014-15.","Biography information for John Pugh","John Pugh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50434","50434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621979","2016-10-28","Department for Education","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when she plans to form the expert panel for Gypsy, Traveller and Roma education; and who will be invited to participate in that panel.","Biography information for John Pugh","John Pugh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50435","50435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621980","2016-10-28","Department for Education","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of the potential effect of withdrawal of the archaeology A-level on the number of students taking that subject at undergraduate level.","Biography information for John Pugh","John Pugh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50436","50436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621981","2016-10-28","Department for Education","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of the potential effect of withdrawal of the history of art A-level on the number of students taking that subject at undergraduate level.","Biography information for John Pugh","John Pugh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50437","50437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621982","2016-10-28","Department for Education","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of recommendations made by the Bacc for the Future campaign before deciding which subjects to include in the English baccalaureate.","Biography information for John Pugh","John Pugh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50438","50438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621983","2016-10-28","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate she has made of the additional workforce requirement of commercial archaeology in England over the next five years.","Biography information for John Pugh","John Pugh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50426","50426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621984","2016-10-28","Department for Transport","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which of the Government's requirements for lifting the current flight ban between the UK and Sharm el-Sheikh have not been met by Egyptian authorities.","Biography information for John Pugh","John Pugh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50427","50427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621985","2016-10-31","Home Office","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people were (a) prosecuted and (b) convicted of offences relating to online hate content in each of the last three years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50369","50369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621986","2016-10-31","Home Office","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, on how many occasions laser pen type items have been seized in the vicinity of regional and international airports in the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50370","50370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621987","2016-10-31","HM Treasury","2016-10-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment the Government has made of the effect on (a) Liverpool City Region and (b) Wirral of not making up the shortfall in funding from the European Regional Development Fund and European Social Fund after the 2014 to 2020 programme has concluded.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50517","50517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621988","2016-10-31","HM Treasury","2016-10-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what forecast he had made of the potential amount of European Regional Development Fund and European Social Fund payments that (a) Liverpool City Region Local Enterprise Partnership and (b) Wirral would have been allocated in the 2021 to 2027 funding period.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50518","50518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621989","2016-10-31","HM Treasury","2016-10-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the Government plans to develop a system of regional funding as a long-term replacement for the European Social Fund and European Regional Development Fund.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50600","50600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621990","2016-10-31","HM Treasury","2016-10-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the Government is conducting a regional assessment of the effect of the UK leaving the EU on (a) Liverpool City Region and (b) Wirral.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50601","50601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621991","2016-10-31","Department of Health","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the progress that has been made in improving the recording of patients' status as armed forces veterans.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50602","50602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621992","2016-10-31","Department of Health","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of prioritising NHS treatment for armed forces veterans.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50620","50620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621993","2016-10-31","Department of Health","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what data his Department holds on the number of health care professionals who have completed the new NHS Healthcare for the Armed Forces e-learning module.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50603","50603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621994","2016-10-28","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many meetings Ministers of his Department have had with representatives of the Iraq Historic Allegations Team since June 2015.","Biography information for Sir Henry Bellingham","Sir Henry Bellingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50412","50412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621995","2016-10-28","HM Treasury","2016-10-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of the role of the carbon price floor in maintaining security of electricity supply.","Biography information for Callum McCaig","Callum McCaig","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50413","50413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621996","2016-10-28","HM Treasury","2016-10-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when his Department plans to provide an update on the future of the carbon price floor after 2021.","Biography information for Callum McCaig","Callum McCaig","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50417","50417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621997","2016-10-28","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the maximum number of releases on temporary licence a prisoner has been granted over their sentence while in custody was in the last five years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50418","50418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621998","2016-10-28","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 24 October 2016 to Question 48562, what the sentence length of each of the 61 people convicted of murder was; and at what point in that sentence those people were released on temporary licence during Christmas 2015.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50375","50375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/621999","2016-10-28","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 24 October 2016 to Question 48562, on prisoners' release, how many times representations have been made by the victim's family in respect of each of the people convicted of murder; and how many times the decision on release changed as a result of those representations.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50376","50376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622000","2016-10-28","Attorney General","2016-10-26","To ask the Attorney General, with reference to the Written Ministerial Statement of 6 December 2010, Official Report, column 7WS, what consideration the Law Officers' Departments have given to the articles of the UN Convention on the Rights of the Child when making new policy and legislation since May 2015.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50456","50456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622001","2016-10-31","Cabinet Office","2016-10-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the Written Ministerial Statement of 6 December 2010, Col 7WS, what consideration his Department has given to the articles of the UN Convention on the Rights of the Child when making new policy and legislation since May 2015.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50470","50470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622002","2016-10-28","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Written Ministerial Statement of 6 December 2010, Official Report, column 7WS, what consideration his Department has given to the articles of the UN Convention on the Rights of the Child when making new policy and legislation since May 2015.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50459","50459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622003","2016-10-28","HM Treasury","2016-10-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the Written Ministerial Statement of 6 December 2010, Official Report, column 7WS, what consideration his Department has given to the articles of the UN Convention on the Rights of the Child when making new policy and legislation since May 2015.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50468","50468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622004","2016-10-28","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Written Ministerial Statement of 6 December 2010, Official Report, column 7WS, what consideration his Department has given to the articles of the UN Convention on the Rights of the Child when making new policy and legislation since May 2015.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50457","50457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622005","2016-10-28","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to the Written Ministerial Statement of 6 December 2010, Official Report, column 7WS, what consideration her Department has given to the articles of the UN Convention on the Rights of the Child when making new policy and legislation since May 2015.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50458","50458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622006","2016-10-31","Department for Education","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Written Ministerial Statement of 6 December 2010, Col 7WS, what consideration her Department has given to the articles of the UN Convention on the Rights of the Child when making new policy and legislation since May 2015.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50471","50471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622007","2016-10-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the Written Ministerial Statement of 6 December 2010, Official Report, column 7WS, what consideration his Department has given to the articles of the UN Convention on the Rights of the Child when making new policy and legislation since May 2015.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50462","50462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622008","2016-10-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the Written Ministerial Statement of 6 December 2010, Official Report, column 7WS, what consideration her Department has given to the articles of the UN Convention on the Rights of the Child when making new policy and legislation since May 2015.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50460","50460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622009","2016-10-28","Department for International Development","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, with reference to the Written Ministerial Statement of 6 December 2010, Official Report, column 7WS, what consideration her Department has given to the articles of the UN Convention on the Rights of the Child when making new policy and legislation since May 2015.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50464","50464"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622010","2016-10-28","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the Written Ministerial Statement of 6 December 2010, Official Report, column 7WS, what consideration her Department has given to the articles of the UN Convention on the Rights of the Child when making new policy and legislation since May 2015.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50466","50466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622011","2016-10-28","Home Office","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Written Ministerial Statement of 6 December 2010, Official Report, column 7WS, what consideration her Department has given to the articles of the UN Convention on the Rights of the Child when making new policy and legislation since May 2015.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50463","50463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622012","2016-10-31","Department of Health","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Written Ministerial Statement of 6 December 2010, Col 7WS, what consideration his Department has given to the articles of the UN Convention on the Rights of the Child when making new policy and legislation since May 2015.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50472","50472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622013","2016-10-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Written Ministerial Statement of 6 December 2010, Official Report, column 7WS, what consideration his Department has given to the articles of the UN Convention on the Rights of the Child when making new policy and legislation since May 2015.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50469","50469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622014","2016-10-28","Department for Transport","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the Written Ministerial Statement of 6 December 2010, Official Report, column 7WS, what consideration his Department has given to the articles of the UN Convention on the Rights of the Child when making new policy and legislation since May 2015.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50467","50467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622015","2016-10-28","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to the Written Ministerial Statement of 6 December 2010, Official Report, column 7WS, what consideration his Department has given to the articles of the UN Convention on the Rights of the Child when making new policy and legislation since May 2015.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50461","50461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622016","2016-10-28","Department for International Trade","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, with reference to the Written Ministerial Statement of 6 December 2010, Official Report, column 7WS, what consideration his Department has given to the articles of the UN Convention on the Rights of the Child when making new policy and legislation since May 2015.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50465","50465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622017","2016-10-28","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the Written Ministerial Statement of 6 December 2010, Official Report, column 7WS, what consideration his Department has given to the articles of the UN Convention on the Rights of the Child when making new policy and legislation since May 2015.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50455","50455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622018","2016-11-02","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to prevent vexatious lawsuits being brought against British servicemen.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50358","50358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622019","2016-11-03","Department for Transport","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what proposals he has further to reduce traffic delays on the A46 Lincoln ring road; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50359","50359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622020","2016-10-31","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to provide local authorities with the appropriate facilities to enable them to recycle all kinds of plastics.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50320","50320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622021","2016-10-31","Home Office","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will provide statistics on the number of individuals rescued from people trafficking in the UK who have subsequently fallen back into trafficking for each year since 2010.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50319","50319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622022","2016-10-31","HM Treasury","2016-10-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will call on British newspapers to disclose their ownership structure and tax arrangements; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50452","50452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622023","2016-10-28","Department for Education","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 10 October 2016 to Question 46637, how the initial 14 schools were selected for that programme; and where the other 12 schools are situated.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50411","50411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622024","2016-10-28","Cabinet Office","2016-10-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will make an assessment of whether the Advisory Committee on Business Appointments takes sufficient account of the potential risk of (a) an employer gaining an improper advantage by appointing a former official who holds information about its competitors or about impending government policy and (b) a former official or Minister improperly exploiting privileged access to contacts in government.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50439","50439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622025","2016-10-31","HM Treasury","2016-10-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what meetings (a) he, (b) his advisers and (c) officials of his Department have had with representatives from the Bank of England to discuss the effect of quantitative easing on inequality since his appointment.","Biography information for Tristram Hunt","Tristram Hunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50318","50318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622026","2016-10-28","Department for Education","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what criteria were used to select the first six social mobility opportunity areas; and if she will publish the evidence that that decision was based on.","Biography information for Tristram Hunt","Tristram Hunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50295","50295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622027","2016-10-28","Department for Education","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what ranking her Department gave to Stoke-on-Trent relative to other local authority areas in the assessment made against criteria used to select the six social mobility opportunity areas.","Biography information for Tristram Hunt","Tristram Hunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50296","50296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622028","2016-10-31","Department for Education","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many members have joined the government-funded chartered College of Teaching since its inception.","Biography information for Tristram Hunt","Tristram Hunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50528","50528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622029","2016-10-31","Department for Education","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether the Department has had any discussions with the chartered College of Teaching about further Government funding.","Biography information for Tristram Hunt","Tristram Hunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50525","50525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622030","2016-10-31","Department for Education","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what meetings (a) she, (b) the Minister for Schools, (c) her advisers and (d) officials of her Department have had with representatives of the chartered College of Teaching since she took up her office.","Biography information for Tristram Hunt","Tristram Hunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50526","50526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622031","2016-10-31","Department for Education","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether her Department has received a formal request from the chartered College of Teaching for further public funding.","Biography information for Tristram Hunt","Tristram Hunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50527","50527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622032","2016-10-31","Department for Education","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent evaluation she has made of the capacity of childcare providers to provide 30 hours of free childcare from the eight pilot schemes that are piloting the new childcare entitlement; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50513","50513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622033","2016-10-31","Department for Education","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of funding from her Department for free childcare is retained by each local authority for central services.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50597","50597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622034","2016-10-28","Department for Education","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what mechanisms her Department has for ensuring that local authorities manage their childcare funding effectively.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50574","50574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622035","2016-10-31","Department for Education","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many childcare providers have breached her Department's statutory guidance issued in September 2014 that states that providers which charge for goods or services do not make this a condition of children accessing their place.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50563","50563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622036","2016-10-31","Department for Education","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she has taken to ensure that all local authorities are aware of their duty to clarify the complaints procedure for parents in relation to their entitlement to free childcare.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50564","50564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622037","2016-10-28","Department for Education","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many staff in her Department are engaged in measuring the effect of the new entitlement for free early years education and childcare.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50565","50565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622038","2016-10-28","Department for Education","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the cost to her Department was of commissioning Frontier Economics to develop a framework for measuring the impact of the new entitlement for free childcare.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50566","50566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622039","2016-10-28","Department for Education","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if her Department will publish the data that it is using to measure the effectiveness of the free childcare entitlement in increasing the employment rates of parents.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50567","50567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622040","2016-10-28","Department for Education","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many trainees were recruited to the National College of Teaching and Leadership's teacher training programme in each year since that programme was introduced.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50570","50570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622041","2016-10-28","Department for Education","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she has taken to ensure that local authorities are updating and improving access to their Family Information Service in preparation for introduction of the new childcare entitlement.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50571","50571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622042","2016-10-28","Department for Education","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she has taken to ensure that local authorities are aware of their duty to provide sufficient accessible information to parents on their entitlement to free childcare.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50572","50572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622043","2016-10-28","Department for Education","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if her Department will publish the data that it is using to measure the effect of the free childcare entitlement on disadvantaged children.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50568","50568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622044","2016-10-28","Department for Education","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to increase the number of qualified early years staff in preparation for the proposed changes to entitlement to free childcare places.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50569","50569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622045","2016-10-28","Department for Education","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she has taken to ensure that local authorities are aware of their statutory duty to ensure that childcare providers charge for any goods or services, this is not a condition of children accessing a free childcare place with that provider.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50573","50573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622046","2016-10-31","Department for Education","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will outline the methodology for evaluating the eight pilot schemes that are assessing the capacity of childcare providers to operate under new early years' funding rates.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50514","50514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622047","2016-10-28","HM Treasury","2016-10-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department is taking to review the terms of the Small Breweries' Relief scheme; and whether his Department has sought representations from all parts of that industry on the terms of that Relief scheme.","Biography information for Michael Gove","Michael Gove","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50360","50360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622048","2016-10-31","Department for International Development","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department has taken to ensure value for money when procuring medicines and other health technologies as part of its bilateral and multilateral spending on health.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50608","50608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622049","2016-10-31","Department for International Development","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether the price of HIV drugs procured by her Department has increased over the last five years; and whether her Department's overall spending on drug procurement has increased as a result.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50607","50607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622050","2016-10-28","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many times government ministers have met the Coal Authority in the last two years.","Biography information for Sir Alan Campbell","Mr Alan Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50553","50553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622051","2016-10-28","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many times the Secretary of State has exercised his powers to make payments above £15,000 under the House Loss Payments Scheme.","Biography information for Sir Alan Campbell","Mr Alan Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50554","50554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622052","2016-10-28","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how much the Coal Authority has spent on external legal advice in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sir Alan Campbell","Mr Alan Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50556","50556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622053","2016-10-28","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many people have been employed in the Coal Authority in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sir Alan Campbell","Mr Alan Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50555","50555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622054","2016-10-31","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much the Government has paid in compensation to farmers for animals culled in efforts to control bovine tuberculosis since 2010.","Biography information for Rob Marris","Rob Marris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50605","50605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622055","2016-10-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in (a) the UK and (b) resident in overseas countries over the age of 100 received the state pension in each of the last three years; and how many such people lived in  each such overseas country in each of those years.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50587","50587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622056","2016-10-31","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will request that the Human Rights Council begin an investigation into human rights abuses in Kashmir.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50331","50331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622057","2016-10-31","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 24 October 2016 to Question 49326, on Ilois: settlement, if he will provide an estimate of in-house costs associated with legal action.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50497","50497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622058","2016-10-31","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the oral contributions of the Minister of State on British Indian Ocean territory and the Chagos Islands, Official Report, column 77WH, and with reference to the further work being undertaken to refine policy options for resettlement considerations for the Chagos Islands, what the terms of reference for this work are; who is undertaking that work; who drew up the terms of reference and is overseeing that work; what the agreed timescales for completion of that work are; what consultations are being undertaken as part of that work; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50530","50530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622059","2016-10-31","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 20 October 2016 to Question 49732, on Trident submarines: iron and steel, what proportion of the BAE supply chain in the UK is based in Scotland.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50532","50532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622060","2016-10-31","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 25 October 2016 to Question 49731, on Trident submarines, what estimate he has made of the number of jobs to be created in (a) Scotland and (b) the rest of the UK from the investment in the Successor submarines.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50391","50391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622061","2016-10-31","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 25 October 2016 to Question 49731, on Trident submarines, what proportion of the total steel tonnage required for the Successor submarine programme will originate from (a) the UK, (b) France and (c) other countries.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50392","50392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622062","2016-10-31","Department for Transport","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Oral Statement on Airport Capacity of 25 October 2016, Official Report, column 179, whether any public transport upgrades or public infrastructure will be required to facilitate the proposed additional runway at Heathrow.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50531","50531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622063","2016-10-28","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if she will suspend the planned budget reductions to S4C until the review of that channel has been published.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50506","50506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622064","2016-10-31","Home Office","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what information her Department holds on the frequency and relative effect of the use of tasers on (a) people from the UK's Afro-Caribbean communities and (b) the general population.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50500","50500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622065","2016-10-31","Home Office","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 29 June 2016 to Question 41026, which police forces record the ethnicity, age, location and outcome of all serious uses of force by police officers, including the use of tasers, in accordance with the recommendations of Chief Constable David Shaw's review.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50510","50510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622066","2016-10-31","Home Office","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 29 June 2016 to Question 41026, when she plans to extend the recording of ethnicity, age, location and outcome of all serious uses of force by police officers, including the use of tasers, beyond the Pathfinder forces.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50511","50511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622067","2016-10-31","Home Office","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 29 June 2016 to Question 41026, for what reason the collection of information on the ethnicity, age, location and outcome of all serious uses of force by police officers, including the use of tasers, will not form part of the 2016-17 Home Office Annual Data Return; if she will make it her policy to bring forward the publication of that data; and if she will make it her policy to publish that data on a quarterly basis.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50512","50512"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622068","2016-10-31","Home Office","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will conduct an immediate review of the use of tasers (a) in mental health settings and (b) by the police more generally.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50317","50317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622070","2016-10-28","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many employers use the Output Work system set out in Chapter 4 of the National Minimum Wage Regulations 2015, SI 2015/621.","Biography information for Kevin Hollinrake","Kevin Hollinrake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50503","50503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622071","2016-10-28","Department for International Trade","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how much his Department has spent on consultancy from advertising companies since its establishment for (a) public campaigns and (b) other advice; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50508","50508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622072","2016-10-31","Department for International Trade","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what the cost to the public purse was of the UKTI British House project in Rio; what the aims of that project were; and what steps his Department has taken to assess its effectiveness towards those aims.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50357","50357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622073","2016-10-31","Department for Transport","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had on negotiation approaches with his EU counterparts in preparation for the Marine Environment Protection Committee of the International Maritime Organisation of 24 to 28 October 2016.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50356","50356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622074","2016-10-28","Department for Transport","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of implementing the measures in the Nautilus Charter for Jobs; and if he will review his Department's policies on training and education for UK seafarers in response to that charter.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50429","50429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622075","2016-10-31","Department for International Development","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 13 October 2016 to Question 47905, what proportion of her Department's spending those proven cases of fraud represented in each of those financial years.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50367","50367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622076","2016-10-31","Department for International Development","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 13 October 2016 to Question 47905, whether any of those instances of fraud were related to her Department's spending in (a) Israel and (b) the Occupied Palestinian Territories.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50368","50368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622077","2016-10-31","HM Treasury","2016-10-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect on the economy of a loss of permission to undertake euro-denominated clearing in the UK; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50444","50444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622078","2016-10-31","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the effect on funding for local authorities of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50491","50491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622079","2016-10-31","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his counterpart in Ethiopia on whether Mr Andargachew Tsege has received the legal advice promised by the Ethiopian Prime Minister on 1 June 2016.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50490","50490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622080","2016-10-31","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of universal credit in supporting people into self-employment.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50492","50492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622081","2016-10-31","Department for Education","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of children with disabilities that are eligible for the early education offer for disadvantaged two-year-olds have taken up that offer in (a) England, (b) each region of England and (c) each local authority.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50606","50606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622082","2016-10-31","Department for Education","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of two-year-olds eligible for free 15 hours early education are accessing care in settings that (a) are outstanding, (b) are good, (c) are satisfactory, (d) require improvement and (e) have not been inspected by Ofsted in (i) England, (ii) each region and (iii) each local authority.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50598","50598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622083","2016-10-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what account the Government has taken of the number of elephants killed for their ivory since 2010 in assessing the effectiveness of its ban on sales of ivory dating from 1947 to the present day.","Biography information for Mrs Pauline Latham","Pauline Latham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50488","50488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622084","2016-10-28","HM Treasury","2016-10-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment the Government has made of the potential merits of making changes to police pension regulations to equalise survivor benefits for people in same sex and heterosexual marriages.","Biography information for Kwasi  Kwarteng","Kwasi Kwarteng","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50428","50428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622085","2016-10-28","HM Treasury","2016-10-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what progress has been made on finding an alternative location for the HM Revenue and Customs Welsh Language Unit staff and needs enhanced service staff located at Ty Moelwyn in Porthmadog.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50300","50300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622086","2016-10-28","Home Office","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what alternatives her Department has considered for the income threshold of £18,600 for immigration of non-EEA partners of British citizens.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50301","50301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622087","2016-10-28","Home Office","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the effect on the health and wellbeing of children in families of their separation resulting from the income threshold for immigration of non-EEA partners of British citizens.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50299","50299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622088","2016-10-31","Department of Health","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many perinatal mental health specialist (a) doctors and (b) nurses were in place in (i) Liverpool Wavertree constituency, (ii) Liverpool, (iii) England and (iv) each region in each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50522","50522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622089","2016-10-31","Department of Health","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many mental health nurses were in place in (a) Liverpool Wavertree constituency, (b) Liverpool, (c) England and (d) each region in each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50523","50523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622090","2016-10-31","Department of Health","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make it his policy to re-categorise the Debt and Mental Health Evidence form as an NHS form.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50520","50520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622091","2016-10-31","Department of Health","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of support available to young people who are transitioning from child and adolescent mental health services to adult mental health services.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50524","50524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622092","2016-10-31","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he plans to publish the Life Chances Strategy.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50521","50521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622094","2016-10-31","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when she plans to update the safety in custody statistics.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50371","50371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622095","2016-10-31","Department of Health","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 24 October 2016 to Question 49464 and with reference to the Answer of 8 September 2014 to Question 208139, on incinerators: health hazards, what the reasons are for the time taken for the papers to be published.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50386","50386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622096","2016-10-31","Department of Health","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many representations he and officials of his Department have received from NHS managers and employees on the financial viability of NHS trusts and clinical commissioning groups; and if he will publish those representations.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50350","50350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622097","2016-10-28","Department of Health","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many GPs were full-time in (a) 2010 and (b) 2016.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50333","50333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622098","2016-10-31","Department for Transport","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he expects the Halton Curve to open.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50351","50351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622099","2016-10-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assistance her Department is providing to support farmers in utilising new technologies to increase productivity.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50372","50372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622100","2016-10-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assistance her Department is providing to support young people who wish to (a) pursue a career in farming and (b) acquire the rights to a farm.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50373","50373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622101","2016-10-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to work with local authorities to increase the number of successful prosecutions for fly-tipping.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50374","50374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622102","2016-10-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to develop export markets for British food products outside the EU.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50423","50423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622103","2016-10-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to reduce the burden of regulation on farmers.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50507","50507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622104","2016-10-28","Department for International Trade","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps his Department is taking to work with manufacturing businesses in West Yorkshire to strengthen their export links.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50422","50422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622105","2016-10-28","Department for International Trade","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps his Department is taking to work with the West Yorkshire Combined Authority to strengthen the export links of businesses in West Yorkshire.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50421","50421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622106","2016-10-28","Department of Health","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to improve the provision of mental health services in (a) Calderdale and (b) West Yorkshire.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50424","50424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622107","2016-10-28","Department of Health","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to assist young people experiencing mental health problems in Calderdale.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50425","50425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622108","2016-10-28","Department of Health","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to (a) prevent the late cancellation of appointments with GPs and (b) reduce the cost to GPs of cancelled appointments.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50420","50420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622109","2016-10-28","Department for Education","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what timetable has been set by her Department for the Government's response to the consultation on the new national funding formula.","Biography information for Michael Tomlinson","Michael Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50297","50297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622110","2016-10-28","Department for Education","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what timetable has been set by her Department for the implementation of the new national funding formula.","Biography information for Michael Tomlinson","Michael Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50298","50298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622111","2016-10-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 18 October 2016 to Question 47643, what estimate his Department has made of the number of times a new Royal Yacht would have to be used for trade promotion to represent a good return on investment.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50557","50557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622112","2016-10-28","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, pursuant to the Answer of 21 October 2016 to Answer 48518, which businesses in each sector his Department has consulted on reform after the UK has left the EU and the domestication of EU regulations.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50558","50558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622113","2016-10-31","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what information his Department holds on the number of staff working for ACAS who are (a) BME, (b) disabled, (c) female, (d) male and (e) over 50 years of age.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50496","50496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622114","2016-10-31","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what consultation process has taken place on the proposed reforms to ACAS and its staffing structure.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50495","50495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622115","2016-10-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average time taken was for a case to be fully investigated by the Independent Case Examiner from initial referral until final outcome in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50580","50580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622116","2016-10-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many employment and support allowance decisions have been amended at the mandatory reconsideration stage in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50575","50575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622117","2016-10-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many employment and support allowance decisions have been amended at the tribunal stage in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50576","50576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622118","2016-10-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of cases dealt with by the Independent Case Examiner have found in the claimant's favour in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50577","50577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622119","2016-10-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many cases have been dealt with by the Independent Case Examiner in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50578","50578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622120","2016-10-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the observation and effectiveness of the recent ceasefire in Yemen.","Biography information for Mrs Flick Drummond","Mrs Flick Drummond","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50377","50377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622121","2016-10-31","HM Treasury","2016-10-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the Government plans unilaterally to grant China market economy status in the event of the UK leaving the EU and its single market.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50493","50493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622122","2016-10-31","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what information his Department holds on the number of employers who have prevented migrant workers from joining a union during their time working in the UK.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50494","50494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622123","2016-10-31","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 20 October 2016 to Question 48990 and the correction to that Answer of 21 October 2016, whether he has received representations on migrant employees in the UK being forced to repay funds to their employers which had been paid to such employees as a result of shortfalls in wages upon return to their country of origin.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50502","50502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622124","2016-10-31","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when she plans to announce the sites for the Prisons Investment programme.","Biography information for Mr Peter Bone","Mr Peter Bone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50365","50365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622125","2016-10-28","HM Treasury","2016-10-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate his Department has made of how much of the tax credit savings to date were a result of erroneous decisions made by Concentrix against legitimate tax credit recipients.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50476","50476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622126","2016-10-28","HM Treasury","2016-10-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what timescale has been set for incorrect tax credit withdrawals by Concentrix to be remedied; and what plans he has to compensate clamants for any missing time periods.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50477","50477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622127","2016-10-28","HM Treasury","2016-10-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will publish any performance reviews of the Concentrix tax credit contract conducted by (a) HM Revenue and Customs and (b) his Department.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50478","50478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622128","2016-10-28","HM Treasury","2016-10-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will publish the dates of any meeting which were held between Concentrix and (a) HM Revenue and Customs and (b) his Department for the purposes of monitoring the performance of Concentrix.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50479","50479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622129","2016-10-28","HM Treasury","2016-10-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will conduct an official investigation into HM Revenue and Customs' conduct in relation to monitoring the performance of Concentrix since that company was awarded the tax credit contract in 2014.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50505","50505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622130","2016-10-28","HM Treasury","2016-10-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will publish the minutes of any meeting which were held between Concentrix and (a) HM Revenue and Customs and (b) his Department for the purposes of monitoring the performance of Concentrix.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50480","50480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622131","2016-10-28","HM Treasury","2016-10-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, who (a) in his Department and (b) at HM Revenue and Customs has the responsibility for monitoring the Concentrix tax credit contract.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50481","50481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622132","2016-10-28","HM Treasury","2016-10-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many HM Revenue and Customs (HMRC) staff at Cumbernauld Tax Office have been placed in the redeployment pool as a result of HMRC's decision to end its contract with Fujitsu early on that side.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50482","50482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622133","2016-10-28","HM Treasury","2016-10-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he plans to seek compensation from Concentrix to cover the cost of HM Revenue and Customs' staff resolving tax credit claims (a) to date and (b) for the remaining duration of the contract with Concentrix.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50440","50440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622134","2016-10-28","HM Treasury","2016-10-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what target his Department set for savings to the public purse from the contract with Concentrix; and what the evidential basis for that target was.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50443","50443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622135","2016-10-28","HM Treasury","2016-10-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the Government plans to seek payment from Concentrix to fund any remedial action on erroneous decisions made by Concentrix against legitimate tax credit recipients.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50442","50442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622136","2016-10-28","HM Treasury","2016-10-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, for what reasons (a) HM Revenue and Customs (HMRC) and (b) his Department have not investigated Concentrix's performance as required in Section 13.1 of the formal contract between HMRC and SYNNEX-Concentrix UK Limited.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50473","50473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622137","2016-10-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will conduct a review of all payment-by-results contracts in the welfare system; and if he will place a copy of the results of that review in the Library.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50474","50474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622138","2016-10-28","HM Treasury","2016-10-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether people with outstanding tax credit claims should contact Concentrix through their helpline or contact HM Revenue and Customs directly.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50475","50475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622139","2016-10-31","Department of Health","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether funding to the NHS will increase if inflation forecasts are revised upwards by the Office for Budget Responsibility.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50364","50364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622140","2016-10-31","Department of Health","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much has been received to the public purse through the Pharmaceutical Price Regulation Scheme rebate since its inception; and for what purposes that funding has been used.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50330","50330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622141","2016-10-28","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to his Answer of 25 October 2016 to Question 49170, how many checks Ofgem has carried out to ensure that Energy Company Obligation scheme requirements have been met in each of the last 12 months for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50441","50441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622142","2016-10-31","Department of Health","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how his Department assesses the value for money of health service contracts that are tendered by clinical commissioning groups; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Clive Efford","Clive Efford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50519","50519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622143","2016-10-31","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what progress the Government has made on the Healthy Relationships Fund.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50529","50529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622144","2016-10-31","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Early Intervention Foundation review, What works to enhance interparental relationships and improve children's outcomes, commissioned by his Department and published on 22 March 2016, what steps he is taking to increase investment for interventions aimed at supporting parental relationships in order to improve children's mental health and life chances.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50590","50590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622145","2016-10-31","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Early Intervention Foundation review, What works to enhance interparental relationships and improve children's outcomes, commissioned by his Department and published on 22 March 2016, what steps he is taking to strengthen the policymaker's role in promoting awareness of the effect of the quality of the relationship between parents on their children.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50589","50589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622146","2016-10-31","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Early Intervention Foundation review, What works to enhance interparental relationships and improve children's outcomes, commissioned by his Department and published on 22 March 2016, what assessment the Government has made of the (a) link between the quality of a parental relationship on a child's life chances and (b) effectiveness of targeted relationship support.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50588","50588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622147","2016-10-31","HM Treasury","2016-10-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he plans to pay Synnex-Concentrix UK Limited any compensation as a result of the early termination of the HM Revenue and Customs Benefits and Credits, Errors and Fraud Adding Capacity 444 contract.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50596","50596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622148","2016-10-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many care leavers identified through the self-identified marker used by his Department as being between the ages of 18 and 25 had their (a) jobseeker's allowance and (b) employment and support allowance sanctioned between October 2015 and March 2016.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50581","50581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622149","2016-10-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many care leavers aged between 18 and 25 as identified through the self-identified marker used by his Department had their sanctions overturned or reduced on reconsideration or appeal between October 2015 and March 2016.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50579","50579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622150","2016-10-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many applications from care leavers identified through the self-identified marker used by his Department as being between the ages of 18 and 25 submitted a request for reconsideration or appeal of a sanction decision between October 2015 and March 2016.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50582","50582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622151","2016-10-28","Department of Health","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to ensure that GPs do not charge people with mental health conditions for the provision of a doctor's note.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50361","50361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622152","2016-10-28","HM Treasury","2016-10-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans he has to review the 36H regulations under the Financial Services and Markets Act 2000 (Regulated Activities) (Amendment) (No.2) Order 2013.","Biography information for Julian Knight","Julian Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50614","50614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622153","2016-10-28","HM Treasury","2016-10-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will (a) review and (b) ease restrictions on intermediary balance sheet lending by platforms under 36H of the Financial Services and Markets Act 2000 (Regulated Activities) (Amendment) (No. 2) Order 2013.","Biography information for Julian Knight","Julian Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50509","50509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622154","2016-10-31","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will conduct a review of all payment-by-results contracts in the welfare system; and if he will place a copy of the results of that review in the Library.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50322","50322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622155","2016-10-31","HM Treasury","2016-10-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the number of tax credit cases awaiting consideration by Concentrix in (a) Hornsey and Wood Green constituency and (b) the London Borough of Haringey.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50323","50323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622156","2016-10-31","HM Treasury","2016-10-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people in (a) Hornsey and Wood Green constituency and (b) the London Borough of Haringey have had a tax credit claim stopped by Concentrix; and how many such claims were subsequently reinstated by HM Revenue and Customs.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50324","50324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622157","2016-10-31","HM Treasury","2016-10-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether (a) his Department, (b) HM Revenue and Customs and (c) Concentrix have issued a formal apology for each erroneous accusation made by Concentrix against legitimate tax credit recipients.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50325","50325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622158","2016-10-31","HM Treasury","2016-10-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to section 13.1 of the formal contract between HM Revenue and Customs (HMRC) and SYNNEX-Concentrix Ltd, for what reasons (a) HMRC and (b) his Department has not investigated Concentrix's performance.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50321","50321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622159","2016-10-28","HM Treasury","2016-10-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate his Department has made of the backlog of tax credit cases which need to be dealt with by Concentrix and HM Revenue and Customs.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50315","50315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622160","2016-10-28","HM Treasury","2016-10-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate his Department has made of tax credits savings to date which were as a result of erroneous accusations by Concentrix against legitimate tax credit recipients.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50316","50316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622161","2016-10-28","HM Treasury","2016-10-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, on what date (a) HM Revenue and Customs and (b) his Department first received representations that Concentrix was erroneously investigating legitimate tax credit claimants and halting their payments.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50305","50305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622162","2016-10-28","HM Treasury","2016-10-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what support and guidance has been provided by his Department and HM Revenue and Customs to ensure that (a) Concentrix and (b) any body working on behalf of HM Revenue and Customs are aware of their obligations under the Data Protection Act.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50306","50306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622163","2016-10-28","HM Treasury","2016-10-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will publish the minutes of meetings which were held between Concentrix and (a) HM Revenue and Customs and (b) his Department for the purposes of monitoring the performance of Concentrix.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50307","50307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622164","2016-10-28","HM Treasury","2016-10-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will publish the dates of meetings which were held between Concentrix and (a) HM Revenue and Customs and (b) his Department for the purposes of monitoring the performance of Concentrix.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50308","50308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622165","2016-10-28","HM Treasury","2016-10-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will publish performance reviews of the Concentrix tax credit contract conducted by (a) HM Revenue and Customs and (b) his Department.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50309","50309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622166","2016-10-28","HM Treasury","2016-10-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what timescale has been set for incorrect tax credit withdrawals by Concentrix to be remedied; and what plans he has to compensate claimants for any missing time periods.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50310","50310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622167","2016-10-28","HM Treasury","2016-10-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what target his Department had for savings to the public purse from the Concentrix contract; and what the evidential basis for that target was.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50311","50311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622168","2016-10-28","HM Treasury","2016-10-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he plans to seek compensation from Concentrix to cover the cost of HM Revenue and Customs staff having to resolve tax credit claims (a) to date and (b) for the remaining duration of the contract with Concentrix.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50312","50312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622169","2016-10-28","HM Treasury","2016-10-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the Government plans to seek payment from Concentrix to fund any remedial action on erroneous accusations made by Concentrix against legitimate tax credit recipients.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50313","50313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622170","2016-10-28","HM Treasury","2016-10-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how his Department plans to monitor the performance of Concentrix under its contract with HM Revenue and Customs until the end of its contract.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50314","50314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622171","2016-10-28","HM Treasury","2016-10-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what information his Department holds on the number of staff Concentrix has employed in the UK in each year since 2014.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50302","50302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622172","2016-10-28","HM Treasury","2016-10-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much tax Concentrix has paid in the UK in each year since 2014.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50303","50303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622173","2016-10-28","HM Treasury","2016-10-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, on what date his Department first received representations that Concentrix was not meeting its performance targets.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50304","50304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622174","2016-10-31","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of the implications of bringing into effect section 40 of the Crime and Courts Act 2013 for the protections and privileges granted under the Parliamentary Papers Act 1840; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50501","50501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622175","2016-10-31","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 24 October 2016 to Question 49479, whether all EU-derived employment rights will be retained in primary legislation.","Biography information for Jack Dromey","Jack Dromey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50615","50615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622176","2016-10-31","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what discussions he has had with Acas on proposed office closures and staffing reductions; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50593","50593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622177","2016-10-31","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what discussions have taken place between Acas and the PCS Union on the proposed closure of (a) the Liverpool office and (b) seven telephone helplines across England and Wales.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50594","50594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622178","2016-10-31","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the effect of proposed changes to Acas on (a) maintaining the functions of the service, (b) office closures and (c) job losses; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50592","50592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622179","2016-10-31","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether Acas has conducted an equality impact assessment on the proposed closure of its Liverpool office; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50591","50591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622180","2016-10-28","Northern Ireland Office","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, if he will make representations to the EU Exit and Trade Committee to examine the needs of UK citizens living along the border with the Republic of Ireland.","Biography information for Tom Elliott","Tom Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50610","50610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622181","2016-10-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to the government of Iran on the imprisonment of Kamal Foroughi.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50487","50487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622182","2016-10-28","Department for Education","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 18 October 2016 to Question 47306, what assessment she has made of whether the proportion of overseas fee income received over the next five years will remain at or be above the level received in 2014-15.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50332","50332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622183","2016-10-31","Home Office","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the efficacy of knife crime amnesty provisions in England and Wales.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50327","50327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622184","2016-10-31","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the political implications of alleged war crimes committed in Syria during the present conflict.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50450","50450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622185","2016-10-31","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many UK personnel have died on military operations in 2016 to date.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50499","50499"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622186","2016-10-31","Department of Health","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what forecast he has made of the amount per head of population that will be spent on the NHS in each year until 2020.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50387","50387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622187","2016-10-31","Prime Minister","2016-10-26","To ask the Prime Minister, what assessment she has made of whether the EU referendum result will lead to changes in any of the Government's previously-announced policies.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50449","50449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622188","2016-10-31","Department for International Trade","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether leaving the EU customs union is a prerequisite to signing trade agreements with non-EU countries.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50451","50451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622189","2016-10-31","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment her Department has made of the effect of the UK leaving the EU on the funding and operation of the National Citizen Service.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50445","50445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622190","2016-10-31","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what (a) salary and (b) expenses the Chair of Patrons at the National Citizen Service receives.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50446","50446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622191","2016-10-31","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to the provisions of the National Citizen Service Bill [Lords], what estimate her Department has made of the cost of writing to every 16 year old to promote the National Citizen Service.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50447","50447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622192","2016-10-31","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if she will publish a list of patrons of the National Citizen Service.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50448","50448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622193","2016-10-31","HM Treasury","2016-10-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many families in (a) Warrington and (b) Warrington North constituency are in receipt of tax credits for three or more children.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50619","50619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622194","2016-10-31","Department of Health","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the effect on the number of pharmacies in Warrington of proposed changes to pharmacy funding.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50595","50595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622195","2016-10-31","Department of Health","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to measure the effect on health outcomes of (a) restrictions on referral and (b) restrictive prescribing as a result of decisions taken by clinical commissioning groups.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50599","50599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622196","2016-10-31","Department of Health","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much the Government has spent on research into age-related macular degeneration in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50362","50362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622197","2016-10-31","Department of Health","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will estimate the cost to the NHS of conditions related to age-related macular degeneration in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50363","50363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622198","2016-10-28","HM Treasury","2016-10-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, which organisation is expected to meet the cost of redundancy payments to Fujitsu staff at Cumbernald Tax Office who will lose their jobs as a result of the decision of HM Revenue and Customs to end its contract early with Fujitsu at that site.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50483","50483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622199","2016-10-28","HM Treasury","2016-10-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, (a) what proportion of and (b) how many staff at the offices being replaced by the Croydon Regional Centre have been offered exit packages instead of transferring to that Regional Centre.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50485","50485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622200","2016-10-28","HM Treasury","2016-10-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when the most recent policy guidance from HM Revenue and Customs on managing poor attendance came into force.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50484","50484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622201","2016-10-31","Department for Education","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many learners have started more than one apprenticeship at the same level since April 2009.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Bailey","Mr Adrian Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50389","50389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622202","2016-10-31","Department for Education","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many (a) public and (b) private sector employers offered apprenticeships in West Bromwich West constituency in each year from 2010 to 2015.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Bailey","Mr Adrian Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50390","50390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622203","2016-10-31","Department for Education","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many people aged (a) 16 to 18, (b) 19 to 24 and (c) 25 and over are employed and training in apprenticeships in West Bromwich West constituency.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Bailey","Mr Adrian Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50388","50388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622204","2016-10-28","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions Ministers have had with the Gambling Commission on the National Lottery in the last year.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50344","50344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622205","2016-10-28","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what remuneration is received by members of the Board of Commissioners of the Gambling Commission; and how many days those members work in that capacity each year.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50345","50345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622206","2016-10-28","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what the duties of the Board of Commissioners of the Gambling Commission are in relation to the regulation of the National Lottery.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50346","50346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622207","2016-10-28","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what the duties of the Gambling Commission are in relation to the regulation of the National Lottery.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50347","50347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622208","2016-10-28","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps her Department is taking to increase participation in sport.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50348","50348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622209","2016-10-28","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many unpaid advisers left her Department in the last six months.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50349","50349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622210","2016-10-28","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many unpaid advisers are currently based in her Department.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50339","50339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622211","2016-10-28","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps she is taking to encourage low-income families to visit theatres.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50340","50340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622212","2016-10-28","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps she is taking to increase participation in drama among people from lower socio-economic backgrounds.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50341","50341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622213","2016-10-28","Home Office","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make an assessment of the potential effect on professional sport of applying to professional sportspeople from outside the UK the same immigration arrangements as those currently available to entertainers, artists and musicians from outside the EU after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50337","50337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622214","2016-10-28","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if she will make an assessment of the potential effect on professional sport of applying the same work permit rules which currently apply to non-EU sportspeople to all non-UK sportspeople after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50338","50338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622215","2016-10-28","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps she is taking to increase participation in sport among people from lower socio-economic backgrounds.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50342","50342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622216","2016-10-28","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if she will place the minutes of the 2016 meetings of the Gambling Commission's National Lottery Committee in the Library.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50343","50343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622217","2016-10-28","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate she has made of the annual funding received from the EU by arts organisations, programmes and projects in the UK in the last three years.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50334","50334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622218","2016-10-28","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether there are any extended ministerial offices in her Department.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50335","50335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622219","2016-10-28","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if she will make an assessment of the potential effect on professional sport of retaining free movement of workers between the UK and EU member states after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50336","50336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622220","2016-10-28","Department for Education","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of demand for school places for (a) boys and (b) girls in Luton in the next five years.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Mr Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50432","50432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622221","2016-10-28","Department for Education","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much her Department spent on developing and supporting the Saint Anne's High School for Girls free school project in Luton prior to its cancellation.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Mr Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50433","50433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622222","2016-10-28","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what recent assessment he has made of the extent of compliance with Part M of the building regulations for (a) dwellings and (b) non-dwellings (i) nationally and (ii) in each local authority area.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Mr Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50431","50431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622223","2016-10-31","Department of Health","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will bring forward regulations to give the Care Quality Commission (CQC) powers to demand that all contractors providing a service that requires regulation with the CQC notify the CQC of who their subcontractors are; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50498","50498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622224","2016-10-28","Home Office","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking further to reduce the number of fires in homes.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50382","50382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622225","2016-10-28","Home Office","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions she has had with stakeholders on fire safety in care homes and specialised housing.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50383","50383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622226","2016-10-28","Home Office","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of the Regulatory Reform (Fire Safety) Order 2005 in protecting heritage buildings.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50384","50384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622227","2016-10-28","Home Office","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions her Department has had with the Department for Education on automatic fire sprinkler systems in schools.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50385","50385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622228","2016-10-28","Home Office","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans she has to use the Fire Kills campaign to increase awareness of fires caused by electricity.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50414","50414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622229","2016-10-28","Home Office","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions she has had with fire and rescue services on including in the data collated by her Department the number of fires caused by (a) mobile telephone chargers and (b) e-cigarettes.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50415","50415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622230","2016-10-28","Home Office","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much her Department has spent on awareness raising campaigns on (a) fire safety and (b) electrical fires in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50416","50416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622231","2016-10-28","Home Office","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions she has had with the Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy on the fire risk from faulty white goods.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50381","50381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622232","2016-10-28","Home Office","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions she has had with the Secretary of State for Education on fire safety in school buildings.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50380","50380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622233","2016-10-28","Home Office","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate her Department has made of the average cost to the public purse of a school fire in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50613","50613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622234","2016-10-28","Home Office","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment the Government has made of the effect and cost of fires in the home caused by electricity.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50612","50612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622235","2016-10-28","Home Office","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps the Government is taking to promote the benefits of sprinkler systems.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50584","50584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622236","2016-10-28","Home Office","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent discussions her Department has had with (a) fire and rescue authorities, (b) the Fire Brigades Union and (c) other fire and rescue service stakeholders on the development of national professional standards and the establishment of a standards body to drive sector improvement.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50583","50583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622237","2016-10-28","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will make an assessment of the implications for the provision of his Department's services of the findings of the report entitled, Joining the Dots: the combined burden of violence, abuse and poverty in the lives of women, published by Agenda in September 2016; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50379","50379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622238","2016-10-28","Home Office","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make an assessment of the implications for the provision of her Department's services of the findings of the report entitled, Joining the Dots: the combined burden of violence, abuse and poverty in the lives of women, published by Agenda in September 2016; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50378","50378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622239","2016-10-31","Home Office","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average response time was for responding by Lancashire Constabulary to a burglary in each division of the county of Lancashire in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50604","50604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622240","2016-11-04","Women and Equalities","2016-10-26","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, how many staff of the Government Equalities office identify as (a) male, (b) female, (c) gay, (d) lesbian, (e) bisexual, (f) transgender, (g) gender fluid, (h) bi-gender, (i) non-binary, (j) gender queer, (k) gender non-conforming, (l) tri-gender, (m) all genders, (n) intersex and (o) another gender identity.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50609","50609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622241","2016-10-31","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what definition of moderate his Department uses when referring to Syrian opposition groups.","Biography information for Steven Paterson","Steven Paterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50515","50515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622242","2016-10-31","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what vetting process his Department applies to moderate Syrian opposition groups before they receive training from UK personnel.","Biography information for Steven Paterson","Steven Paterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50516","50516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622243","2016-10-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate his Department has made of the number of benefit claimants who are accommodated in domestic violence refuges whose overall benefit entitlement has reduced as a result of changes to the benefit cap level after housing benefit paid to households in supported accommodation has been disregarded from the benefit cap calculation.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50419","50419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622244","2016-10-28","Department of Health","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that NHS England is monitoring the performance of the contract awarded to Capita relating to primary care support; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50489","50489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622245","2016-10-31","Department of Health","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many full-time equivalent GP clinical staff there were in (a) Houghton and Sunderland South constituency, (b) the North East of England and (c) England in (i) 2013-14, (ii) 2014-15 and (iii) 2015-16; and how many such staff were working (A) part and (B) full-time.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50329","50329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622246","2016-10-31","Department of Health","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many full-time equivalent clinical staff there were in Houghton and Sunderland South constituency in 2015-16 in each GP practice in that area.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50328","50328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622247","2016-10-31","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 19 October 2016 to Question 48694, what steps his Department is taking to increase the range of statistics available for assessing the cost-effectiveness and efficiency of the Child Maintenance Service.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50618","50618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622248","2016-10-31","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 19 October 2016 to Question 48695, what recent assessment he has made of the efficiency and cost-effectiveness of the Child Maintenance Service for families that use that service.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50617","50617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622249","2016-10-31","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 19 October 2016 to Question 48696, what the timescale is for (a) implementing the published evaluation strategy for the child maintenance reforms and (b) considering the effect of the programme.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50616","50616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622250","2016-10-28","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many trained Army Reserve soldiers and officers there have been in each of the Army's regiments and corps in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50543","50543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622251","2016-10-28","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Spartan and CVR(T) vehicles are (a) in operational service, (b) used for training, (c) held in reserve, (d) undergoing the inspection and repair process and (e) mothballed or in storage.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50533","50533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622252","2016-10-28","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many trained soldiers and officers there have been in (a) the Queen's Royal Hussars, (b) the King's Royal Hussars, (c) the Royal Tank Regiment and (d) the Royal Wessex Yeomanry in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50544","50544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622253","2016-10-28","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Scimitar armoured reconnaissance vehicles are (a) in operational service, (b) used for training, (c) held in reserve (d) undergoing the inspection and repair process and (e) mothballed or in storage.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50534","50534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622254","2016-10-28","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many reserve Challenger 2 crew have passed Annual Crew tests on the platform at what level in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50545","50545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622255","2016-10-28","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many regular Challenger 2 crew have passed annual crew tests on the platform at what level in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50546","50546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622256","2016-10-28","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Stormer vehicles are (a) in operational service, (b) used for training, (c) held in reserve (d) undergoing the inspection and repair process and (e) mothballed or in storage.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50535","50535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622257","2016-10-28","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Bulldog and FV430 series vehicles are (a) in operational service, (b) used for training, (c) held in reserve, (d) undergoing the inspection and repair process and (e) mothballed or in storage.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50536","50536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622258","2016-10-28","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Warrior infantry fighting vehicles are (a) in operational service, (b) used for training, (c) held in reserve, (d) undergoing the inspection and repair process and (e) mothballed or in storage.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50537","50537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622259","2016-10-28","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans his Department has to reduce the number of regular armoured regiments that operate the Challenger 2 main battle tank; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50547","50547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622260","2016-10-28","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Challenger 2 main battle tanks are expected to go through the Challenger 2 Life Extension Programme.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50548","50548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622261","2016-10-28","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans his Department has to maximise the UK workshare in the P-8 Poseidon maritime patrol aircraft programme.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50538","50538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622262","2016-10-28","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Challenger 2 main battle tanks are (a) in operational service, (b) used for training, (c) held in reserve, (d) undergoing the inspection and repair process and (e) mothballed or in storage.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50549","50549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622263","2016-10-28","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department plans to procure the F-35A for the Royal Air Force; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50539","50539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622264","2016-10-28","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Army Reserve soldiers who started but did not complete either phase 1 or phase 2 training have been discharged in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50540","50540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622265","2016-10-28","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Army Reserve soldiers started but did not complete phase 2 training in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50541","50541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622266","2016-10-28","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many fully trained Army reservists were in the (a) Infantry, (b) Royal Artillery, (c) Royal Corps of Signals, (d) Army Medical Services, (e) Adjutant General's Corps, (f) Royal Armoured Corps, (g) Army Air Corps, (h) Royal Engineers, (i) Royal Logistics Corps, (j) Royal Electrical and Mechanical Engineers and (h) Intelligence Corps in each training year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50550","50550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622267","2016-10-28","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Army Reserve soldiers started but did not complete phase 1 training in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50542","50542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622268","2016-10-28","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Army reservists in the (a) Infantry, (b) Royal Artillery, (c) Royal Corps of Signals, (d) Army Medical Services, (e) Adjutant General's Corps, (f) Royal Armoured Corps, (g) Army Air Corps, (h) Royal Engineers, (i) Royal Logistics Corps, (j) Royal Electrical and Mechanical Engineers and (h) Intelligence Corps successfully passed the annual mandatory training tests in each training year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50551","50551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622269","2016-10-28","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Jackal 2 armoured vehicles are (a) in operational service, (b) used for training, (c) held in reserve, (d) undergoing the inspection and repair process and (e) mothballed or in storage.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50552","50552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622270","2016-10-31","HM Treasury","2016-10-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of the financial effect of incorrect assessments carried out by Concentrix on people (a) in Bristol West constituency, (b) in the UK and (c) who are victims of domestic violence; and if he will make an assessment of the other effects of such incorrect assessments on such people.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50453","50453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622271","2016-10-31","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate her Department has made of the average cost in the last 12 months of an asylum appeal in the (a) First-tier and (b) Upper-tier Tribunal.","Biography information for Dr Tania Mathias","Dr Tania Mathias","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50355","50355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622272","2016-10-31","Home Office","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average weekly cost of accommodating an asylum seeker on (a) section 4 and (b) section 95 support was in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Dr Tania Mathias","Dr Tania Mathias","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50354","50354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622273","2016-10-31","Home Office","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what qualifications are required for an asylum caseworker to be employed by her Department.","Biography information for Dr Tania Mathias","Dr Tania Mathias","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50353","50353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622274","2016-10-31","Home Office","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many days training an asylum caseworker receives; and how many days of mentoring those caseworkers receive after starting that role.","Biography information for Dr Tania Mathias","Dr Tania Mathias","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50352","50352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622680","2016-11-01","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether it is her Department's policy to maintain current transfer arrangements for foreign national offenders with EU member states after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 906950","906950"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622681","2016-11-01","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps she is taking to tackle drug use in prisons.","Biography information for Neil Carmichael","Neil Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 906958","906958"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626193","2016-11-01","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps she is taking to reduce re-offending rates.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 906956","906956"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626194","2016-11-01","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps she is taking to increase prison staffing numbers.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 906961","906961"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626195","2016-11-01","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment she has made of the effect of employment tribunal fees on access to justice.","Biography information for Gerald Jones","Gerald Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 906959","906959"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626196","2016-11-01","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if she will take steps to ensure that British men accused of rape abroad can be brought to trial in the UK if they cannot be tried overseas.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 906955","906955"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620831","2016-10-27","Attorney General","2016-10-25","To ask the Attorney General, how many times (a) police and (b) police community support officer defendants have been convicted since the Crown Prosecution Service's victims' right to review in June 2013.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50150","50150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620832","2016-10-27","Attorney General","2016-10-25","To ask the Attorney General, how many times a victim has sought a review of a Crown Prosecution Service decision to leave all charges in the proceedings to lie on file since June 2013; how many such cases have related to a police officer or a police community support officer (PCSO); how many reviews have led to a reversal; and how many cases which resulted in reversal have related to a police officer or a PCSO.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50151","50151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620833","2016-10-27","Attorney General","2016-10-25","To ask the Attorney General, how many times a victim has sought a review of a Crown Prosecution Service decision to end all proceedings since June 2013; how many such cases related to a police officer or a police community support officer (PCSO); how many reviews have led to a reversal; and how many cases which resulted in reversal have related to a police officer or a PCSO.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50152","50152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620834","2016-10-27","Attorney General","2016-10-25","To ask the Attorney General, how many times a victim has sought a review of a Crown Prosecution Service decision to offer no evidence in all proceedings since June 2013; how many such cases related to a police officer or a police community support officer (PCSO); how many reviews have led to a reversal; and how many cases which resulted in reversal have related to a police officer or a PCSO.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50153","50153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620835","2016-10-27","Attorney General","2016-10-25","To ask the Attorney General, how many times since June 2013 a review has been requested of a Crown Prosecution Service decision not to prosecute; how many of those requests related to a police officer or a police community support officer (PCSO); how many of those decisions were reversed; and how many of those that were reversed related to a police officer or a PCSO.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50154","50154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620836","2016-10-28","Attorney General","2016-10-25","To ask the Attorney General, what role he expects his Department to play in the negotiations on the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Mr Peter Bone","Mr Peter Bone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50179","50179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620837","2016-10-28","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to the Answer of 10 February 2016 to Question 26796, how the figure of (a) £1,500 allocated to each young person and (b) cost of running the NCS Trust was calculated.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50176","50176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620838","2016-10-28","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 10 February 2016 to Question 26796, whether the return of £3.98 for every £1 spent on the National Citizen Service is calculated on the basis of the cost of (a) delivery and (b) running the National Citizen Service Trust.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50181","50181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620839","2016-10-28","Cabinet Office","2016-10-25","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many regional roundtables with employers his Department has held to develop new measures of socio-economic background.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50205","50205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620840","2016-10-27","Cabinet Office","2016-10-25","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will provide guidance to Government departments on the Government's current definition of the prerogative power.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50060","50060"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620841","2016-10-27","Cabinet Office","2016-10-25","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps the Government is taking to monitor copycat websites that offer government services.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50062","50062"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620842","2016-10-27","HM Treasury","2016-10-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, for what reasons the National Infrastructure Commission is to be established as an executive agency rather than as a non-departmental public body.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50070","50070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620843","2016-10-27","HM Treasury","2016-10-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if his Department will carry out an impact assessment on the effect on child poverty levels of limiting tax credit payments to two children.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50046","50046"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620844","2016-10-27","HM Treasury","2016-10-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what proportion of staff being relocated to Croydon regional centre by HM Revenue and Customs have been deemed as living within reasonable daily travel of the centre; and what the basis was for that assessment.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50101","50101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620845","2016-10-27","HM Treasury","2016-10-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many HM Revenue and Customs' staff have been dismissed in each year since 2006; and what proportion of those staff were disabled.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50102","50102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620846","2016-10-27","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when he plans to announce a decision on the Swansea Bay Tidal Lagoon.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50103","50103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620847","2016-10-27","HM Treasury","2016-10-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans are in place to mitigate the potential economic effect of the proposal to close HM Revenue and Custom's Cumbernauld tax office.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50139","50139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620848","2016-10-27","HM Treasury","2016-10-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will publish the detailed estimate his Department has made of the potential costs and savings of the proposed relocation of staff from Cumbernauld tax office to a new site in Glasgow.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50140","50140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620849","2016-10-28","HM Treasury","2016-10-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will increase the Local Majors Fund.","Biography information for Mims Davies","Mims Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50185","50185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620850","2016-10-28","HM Treasury","2016-10-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the economic effect on small and new-entrant producers of the introduction of the standard charge imposed by HM Revenue and Customs under the Spirit Drinks Verification Scheme; and what reports he has received of whether the standard charge is a barrier to entry for small and new-entrant producers and a restraint on trade.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50189","50189"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620851","2016-10-27","HM Treasury","2016-10-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the Answer of 26 October 2015 to Question 12759, if he will publish assessments made by HM Revenue and Customs of the local economic issues, business requirements, impact on current workforce and location principles in relation to the decision to close Cumbernauld tax office.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50269","50269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620852","2016-10-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the effect of devolution of attendance allowance to local authorities on the future expenditure on that benefit; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50282","50282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620853","2016-10-28","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the devolution of attendance allowance to local authorities on future regional variations in that allowance; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50216","50216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620854","2016-10-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the potential uptake of social care precept by councils in each year to 2020-21.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50100","50100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620855","2016-10-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of online retailers on small high street businesses.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50088","50088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620856","2016-10-28","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what guidance his Department issues to social landlords on transfer of tenancy agreements to victims of domestic violence when that person's relationship with their abusive partner ends and the victim remains the sole adult tenant after the ex-partner moves out.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50080","50080"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620857","2016-10-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what guidance his Department issues to local authorities on budget setting processes to ensure (a) value for money for residents and (b) the delivery of core frontline services.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50063","50063"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620858","2016-10-28","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 24 October 2016 to Question 49394, on communication: competition, whether Ofcom has responsibility relating to the regulation of the advertising sector in relation to communications markets.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50077","50077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620859","2016-10-28","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what the level of arts spending per head in each of the regions of England has been in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50091","50091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620860","2016-10-28","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many people have participated in the National Citizen Service from each local authority area in each year since that service was introduced.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50092","50092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620861","2016-10-28","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many participants in the National Citizen Service have been eligible for free school meals in each year since that service was introduced.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50093","50093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620862","2016-10-28","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what (a) financial and (b) other support her Department has provided for Gaelic Athletic Association activities in England.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50094","50094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620863","2016-10-27","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what her policy is on devolving responsibility for (a) S4C and (b) all aspects of broadcasting to the National Assembly for Wales.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50131","50131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620864","2016-10-31","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions she has had with the Welsh Office on the Government's review of S4C.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50290","50290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620865","2016-10-31","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how she plans to ensure that the review of S4C is independent.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50291","50291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620866","2016-10-31","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, when she plans to make an announcement as to who will lead the independent review of S4C.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50292","50292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620867","2016-10-31","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions she has had with the Welsh Government on the review of S4C.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50293","50293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620868","2016-10-28","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether she will be obliged to put into effect recommendations arising from the Independent Review of S4C.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50194","50194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620869","2016-10-28","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether the Independent Review of S4C will include an assessment of the channel's impact in Wales in areas of language use, culture, employment and communities.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50193","50193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620870","2016-10-28","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps she plans to take to ensure that the needs of the independent television sector are taken on board during the review of S4C.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50196","50196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620871","2016-10-28","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps she plans to take to ensure that the review of S4C takes on board the views of the Welsh public.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50197","50197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620872","2016-10-27","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how she plans to ensure that the Independent Review into S4C's recommendations are published in time to be incorporated into the final BBC charter documentation.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50264","50264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620873","2016-10-28","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether she will take steps to ensure the return of £425m of Big Lottery Fund money which was used to subsidise West Ham United's lease of the Olympic Stadium.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50167","50167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620874","2016-10-27","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many submissions from (a) employees of media companies and organisations and (b) from those not employed by media companies and organisations, in response to (i) the BBC Charter Review public consultation that closed on 8 October 2015 and (ii) her Department's research since October 2016, expressed (A) support for and (B) opposition to the proposal for 60 per cent tendering in BBC radio.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50248","50248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620875","2016-10-27","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on the (a) effectiveness and (b) scope of the work undertaken by the EU Military Committee of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50275","50275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620876","2016-10-27","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department (a) has directly employed and (b) plans to directly employ additional staff as a result of the decision of the UK to leave the EU.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50276","50276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620877","2016-10-27","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much his Department has allocated for consultants to work on the defence implications of the UK exiting the EU; how many such contracts his Department has tendered to date; and what the aggregate value is of such contracts.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50271","50271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620878","2016-10-27","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department (a) has employed or (b) plans to employ additional staff on secondment from organisations and businesses based outside the UK after the vote for the UK to leave the EU.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50272","50272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620879","2016-10-27","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department (a) has employed or (b) plans to employ additional staff on secondment from (i) non-governmental organisations and (ii) private sector companies after the vote for the UK to leave the EU.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50273","50273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620880","2016-10-28","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if his Department will review the proposal to close the defined benefit pension scheme at the Atomic Weapons Establishment.","Biography information for Patricia Gibson","Patricia Gibson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50224","50224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620881","2016-10-28","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to resolve the current impasse between parties on proposals to close the defined benefit pension scheme at the Atomic Weapons Establishment.","Biography information for Patricia Gibson","Patricia Gibson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50223","50223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620882","2016-10-28","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the National Audit Office report, Departmental Overview 2015-16, Ministry of Defence, published 21 October 2016, page 37, what steps he is taking to address dissatisfaction among service personnel regarding the quality of repairs to service accommodation.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50161","50161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620883","2016-10-28","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the National Audit Office report, Departmental Overview 2015-16, Ministry of Defence, published 21 October 2016, page 17, what steps he is taking to reduce the number of complaints made to CarillionAmey about service families' accommodation.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50162","50162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620884","2016-10-28","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the National Audit Office report, Departmental Overview 2015-16, Ministry of Defence, published 21 October 2016, page 17, if he will review the contract with CarillionAmey to provide service families' accommodation.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50163","50163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620885","2016-10-28","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the National Audit Office report, Departmental Overview 2015-16, Ministry of Defence, published 21 October 2016, page 37, what steps he is taking to address the decrease in satisfaction with the overall standard of service accommodation among service personnel.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50164","50164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620886","2016-10-27","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that the procurement decisions it makes benefits from the research and development work undertaken by companies in the UK.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50112","50112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620887","2016-10-27","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to increase the use of locally produced food in defence establishments.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50137","50137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620888","2016-10-27","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department takes to assess the social and economic effect of closures of military bases and other defence establishments in rural areas.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50138","50138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620889","2016-10-27","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to prepare and improve ground-to-air defences for use by the armed forces.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50111","50111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620890","2016-10-27","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent assessment his Department has made of the trends in the level of cyber attacks originating from outside the UK from (a) government and (b) private sources.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50142","50142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620891","2016-10-27","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of Royal Navy staffing levels.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50047","50047"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620892","2016-10-27","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he has taken to monitor (a) staffing levels and (b) training of Royal Naval Reservists.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50048","50048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620893","2016-10-28","Department for Education","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what information her Department holds on which regions the teachers who have signed up to take part in the North West National Teaching Service pilot had previously been working in.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50084","50084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/620894","2016-10-28","Department for Education","2016-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, in which (a) schools and (b) local authorities National Teaching Service teachers are due to be working in the North West when that scheme begins in January 2017.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50085","50085"
