"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638128","2016-11-18","Department for Transport","2016-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans he has for future investment in the (a) West Sussex and (b) Mid Sussex transport network.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53438","53438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638129","2016-11-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether his Department has made an assessment of the potential merits of collating official statistics on (a) the number of foodbanks in the UK, (b) dependency on foodbanks, (c) use of foodbanks and (d) foodbank referral causes; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53439","53439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638130","2016-11-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many former Crown post office premises the Post Office has sold since 2014 after franchising a Crown office; and for how much such premises have been sold.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53409","53409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638131","2016-11-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant the Answer of 14 November 2016 to Question 52126, what the timetable is for the completion of work to make SMETS1 meters interoperable.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53430","53430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638132","2016-11-21","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, pursuant to the Answer of 16 November 2016 to Question 52723, when he plans to publish his Department's next Quarterly Transparency Returns on gov.uk.","Biography information for Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53427","53427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638133","2016-11-18","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what the Government's policy is on the maximum contribution the UK is willing to make to the EU budget in order to gain access to the Single market.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53480","53480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641458","2016-11-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the strength of diplomatic and economic relations between India and the UK.","Biography information for Bob Blackman","Bob Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 907420","907420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641459","2016-11-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his Russian counterparts on the sovereignty of the Baltic States.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 907424","907424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641460","2016-11-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with the incoming US administration on its policy on the conflict in Syria.","Biography information for Kate Hollern","Kate Hollern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 907422","907422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641461","2016-11-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the progress of recent talks on the future of Cyprus.","Biography information for Martin Vickers","Martin Vickers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 907425","907425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641462","2016-11-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with the incoming US administration on its policy on Article 5 of the NATO treaty.","Biography information for Stephen Pound","Stephen Pound","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 907419","907419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636975","2016-11-18","Cabinet Office","2016-11-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when the Government plans to publish its response to the report by the right hon. Sir Eric Pickles on his review into electoral fraud.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52949","52949"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636976","2016-11-18","Cabinet Office","2016-11-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much the Government has spent on advertising in (a) The Times, (b) The Sunday Times, (c) The Mail on Sunday, (d) The Sun, (e) The Sun on Sunday, (f) The Huffington Post, (g) Mail Online, (h) Daily Mail, (i) The Guardian and (j) Trinity Mirror newspapers in each Department in the last six years.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53019","53019"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636977","2016-11-17","Cabinet Office","2016-11-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the cost of the Main Honours Advisory Committee has been in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53010","53010"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636978","2016-11-17","Cabinet Office","2016-11-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the cost of the Advisory Committee on Business Appointments has been in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53011","53011"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636979","2016-11-17","Cabinet Office","2016-11-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what performance data the Crown Commercial Services (a) collects and (b) recommends be collected from public sector fleet operators in relation to the Government's air quality targets.","Biography information for Drew Hendry","Drew Hendry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53122","53122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636980","2016-11-17","Cabinet Office","2016-11-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the cost of funding the House of Lords Appointments Commission has been in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53132","53132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636981","2016-11-17","HM Treasury","2016-11-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 14 November 2016 to Question 51941, when the new Customs Declaration Service will come into effect; and what estimate he has made of how long an Economic Operator Registration Identification  application will take to process under that service.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53134","53134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636982","2016-11-17","HM Treasury","2016-11-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to Written Statement of 15 November 2016, HCWS251, Update on HM Revenue and Customs' contract with Concentrix, for what reasons HM Revenue and Customs paid £500,000 towards some of Concentrix's exit costs from its subcontracts; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53117","53117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636983","2016-11-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much and what proportion of business rate revenue in (a) Hull City Council area and (b) England came from local pharmacies in the last three years.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53127","53127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636984","2016-11-17","HM Treasury","2016-11-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to Written Statement of 15 November 2016, HCWS251, Update on HM Revenue and Customs' contract with Concentrix, what the costs have been to HM Revenue and Customs of taking over cases from Concentrix prior to the early close of the contract.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53118","53118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636985","2016-11-17","HM Treasury","2016-11-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the Work and Pensions Committee evidence session of 13 October 2016 on Concentrix and Tax Credits Q99, and to the Written Statement of 15 November 2016, HCWS 251, Update on HM Revenue and Customs' contract with Concentrix: Written statement, what the reasons are for the difference between the figure for the estimated saving to the Exchequer from reducing fraud and error as a result of this contract of £270 million given by the Chief Executive of HM Revenue and Customs in the evidence and the figure of £193 million given by the Minister in the written statement; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53144","53144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636986","2016-11-18","HM Treasury","2016-11-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the European Commission's proposals for Eurozone public country-by-country reporting for tackling multi-national tax avoidance.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53035","53035"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636987","2016-11-18","HM Treasury","2016-11-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to encourage mortgage providers to develop financial products which support shared equity affordable housing; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stewart Jackson","Mr Stewart Jackson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53048","53048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636988","2016-11-17","HM Treasury","2016-11-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many working days were lost due to mental illness in his Department in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53077","53077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636989","2016-11-17","HM Treasury","2016-11-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much on average has been paid to claimants relating to the maladministration of tax credits in the last (a) year and (b) three months.","Biography information for Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53091","53091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636990","2016-11-17","HM Treasury","2016-11-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, in how many cases relating to the maladministration of tax credits have compensation payments been made in the last (a) year and (b) three months.","Biography information for Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53094","53094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636991","2016-11-17","HM Treasury","2016-11-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, in how many cases relating to the maladministration of tax credits have compensation payments been offered in the last (a) year and (b) three months.","Biography information for Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53095","53095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636992","2016-11-17","HM Treasury","2016-11-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many hardship payments have been (a) offered and (b) withheld following tax credits decisions in 2016.","Biography information for Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53092","53092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636993","2016-11-17","HM Treasury","2016-11-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what targets his Department has set for the number of mandatory reconsiderations (a) requested and (b) upheld in relation to tax credits decisions in 2016.","Biography information for Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53093","53093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636994","2016-11-17","HM Treasury","2016-11-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what meetings he or his predecessor have held with his EU counterparts during 2016 to discuss the European Commission proposals for public country-by-country reporting.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53013","53013"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636995","2016-11-17","HM Treasury","2016-11-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment he has made of the effect of reductions in beer duty on (a) the number of jobs and (b) the level of investment in the beer and pub industry.","Biography information for Graham Evans","Graham Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53000","53000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636996","2016-11-18","HM Treasury","2016-11-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will publish details of the guidance given to HM Revenue and Customs staff on the offer of hardship payments to people who have had tax credit payments stopped in the last four months.","Biography information for Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52933","52933"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636997","2016-11-18","HM Treasury","2016-11-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans his Department has to review all tax credit cases taken back in-house from Concentrix to ensure that policy and procedures have been correctly applied.","Biography information for Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52934","52934"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636998","2016-11-18","HM Treasury","2016-11-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what proportion of mandatory reconsiderations of cases taken back by HM Revenue and Customs from Concentrix in the last three months have been upheld.","Biography information for Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52935","52935"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636999","2016-11-18","HM Treasury","2016-11-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the average time taken by HM Revenue and Customs staff was to process mandatory reconsiderations requested in relation to tax credit decisions from the point of the request to the final decision in the last three months.","Biography information for Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52936","52936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637000","2016-11-17","HM Treasury","2016-11-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much was raised for the public purse from (a) Vehicle Excise Duty and (b) Fuel Duty in each year since 2011-12.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52982","52982"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637001","2016-11-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when his Department plans to publish the report commissioned from AECOM and Fourwalls in 2015 to monitor air tightness in 55 homes and compliance with Approved Document F in the Building Regulations (Contract Number CPD/004/109/132).","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52906","52906"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637002","2016-11-18","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much his Department has spent to limit excess winter deaths in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52940","52940"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637003","2016-11-18","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 14 November 2016 to Question 52130, what criteria the Government applies when considering its approach to council tax equalisation; and whether the Government has issued advice on that subject to local authorities considering proposals for reorganisation.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52950","52950"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637004","2016-11-18","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if the Government will bring forward legislative proposals to enable the establishment of combined authorities which have the power for extending their functions beyond those initially authorised; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52954","52954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637005","2016-11-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much has been spent on training and resources to enable local emergency services to better respond to possible incidents involving transport of nuclear warheads and high level nuclear waste passing through their areas in the last five years.","Biography information for Jeff Smith","Jeff Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53089","53089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637006","2016-11-18","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many properties there are in the private rented sector in each energy efficiency rating.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53045","53045"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637007","2016-11-18","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to enable private sector providers of affordable housing which are not housing associations to be permitted to supply shared equity and other non-traditional housing tenures; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stewart Jackson","Mr Stewart Jackson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53049","53049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637008","2016-11-18","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what discussions he has had with the Homes and Communities Agency on funding support for private providers of affordable homes which are not classified as registered providers; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stewart Jackson","Mr Stewart Jackson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53042","53042"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637009","2016-11-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what number of working days were lost due to mental illness in his Department in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53064","53064"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637010","2016-11-18","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what progress has been made on ensuring that all registered social housing association tenants have the right to buy their own homes since the conclusion of the pilot scheme.","Biography information for Oliver Colvile","Oliver Colvile","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53037","53037"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637011","2016-11-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect of devolution of the adult skills budget on reducing the skills shortage in the North of England.","Biography information for Graham Evans","Graham Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53016","53016"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637012","2016-11-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the timetable is for the roll-out of the Right to Buy scheme nationally.","Biography information for Michael Tomlinson","Michael Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53128","53128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637013","2016-11-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what notice is given to local government emergency services on nuclear warhead convoys and consignments of high level nuclear waste passing through their areas.","Biography information for Jeff Smith","Jeff Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53088","53088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637014","2016-11-18","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how her Department monitors the Football Association's effectiveness in maintaining participation numbers of people playing football; and what account her Department takes of such numbers in future funding decisions.","Biography information for Richard Graham","Richard Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53057","53057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637015","2016-11-18","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether the Government plans to undertake any further action to prevent corruption within football.","Biography information for Richard Graham","Richard Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53058","53058"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637016","2016-11-17","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many working days were lost due to mental illness in her Department in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53065","53065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637017","2016-11-18","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of the effect of restricting High in Fat, Salt or Sugar (HFSS) food advertising during all programmes before the 9pm watershed relative to existing restrictions on such advertising on (a) children's exposure to HFSS food and (b) children's obesity rates.","Biography information for Jeff Smith","Jeff Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53041","53041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637018","2016-11-18","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if she will discuss with the BBC Trust what steps it plans to take to support people with visual impairments to register for the BBC iPlayer service ahead of the new registration requirement expected to be introduced in 2017.","Biography information for Dr Alasdair McDonnell","Dr Alasdair McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52930","52930"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637019","2016-11-18","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what progress the Dormant Assets Commission has made since it was established in March 2016.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52931","52931"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637020","2016-11-18","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment his Department has made of the (a) effectiveness and (b) cost efficiency of the system for repair of defects on the UK's Type 45 destroyers; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52945","52945"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637021","2016-11-18","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether it is his policy that Royal Navy warships should always escort ships of the Russian Navy when they are within UK waters.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52944","52944"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637022","2016-11-18","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to support BAME veterans into employment.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52941","52941"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637023","2016-11-17","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assistance the Government is providing to the Afghan National Army for (a) equipment and (b) accommodation in Afghanistan.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52903","52903"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637024","2016-11-17","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what he expects the role of the Royal Irish Regiment to be when that Regiment is in Afghanistan in 2017.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52904","52904"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637025","2016-11-17","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether recruitment to posts in his Department have included Welsh language skills as an essential or desirable criteria.","Biography information for Chris Elmore","Chris Elmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52958","52958"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637026","2016-11-18","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department has made an assessment of the potential merits of closing the barracks at Brecon before the assessment which led to the decision announced on 7 November 2016 during the last 10 years.","Biography information for Chris Davies","Chris Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53059","53059"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637027","2016-11-17","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 15 November 2016 to Question 52406 and with reference to the speech delivered by the Secretary of State for Defence on 15 April 2014 at Thales, whether it is still his Department's policy to base 12,500 regular armed forces personnel in Scotland by 2020.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52968","52968"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637028","2016-11-18","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to his Department's report, a Better Defence Estate, published in November 2016, how the figure of £140 million running costs saving over 10 years, rising to nearly £3 billion in total to 2040 was calculated.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53020","53020"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637029","2016-11-18","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the National Audit Office report, Delivering the defence estate, published 15 November 2016, page 8, paragraph 17, what key performance indicators are in place to measure the Defence Infrastructure Organisation's performance; and how many key performance indicators in this area are not set in place.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53021","53021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637030","2016-11-18","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the his Department's report, a Better Defence Estate, published in November 2016, which projects and programmes are projected to be included within his Department's estimate of £4 billion worth of new investment in the estate over the next 10 years.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53022","53022"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637031","2016-11-17","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 26 July 2016 to Question 43260, what progress has been made on the development of Coalition policy on investigating civilian casualties.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52985","52985"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637032","2016-11-17","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to his oral contribution of 7 November 2016, Official Report, column 1240, whether he plans to discuss the Coalition policy on investigating civilian casualties at the meeting of the counter-Daesh coalition to be chaired by the UK in London in December 2016.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52986","52986"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637033","2016-11-17","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many working days were lost due to mental illness in his Department in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53066","53066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637034","2016-11-17","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to his Department's report, a Better Defence Estate, published in November 2016, what the annual running costs are of each of the 91 most expensive sites planned for disposal.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53112","53112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637035","2016-11-17","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to his Department's report, a Better Defence Estate, published November 2016, how the £140 million running costs saving over 10 years was calculated.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53145","53145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637036","2016-11-18","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the average rental price paid by his Department was for Annington Homes-managed properties in each year since 1996.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53168","53168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637037","2016-11-17","Department for Education","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many citizens of other EU countries in each (a) region and (b) nation of the UK work as (i) teachers, (ii) teaching assistants and (iii) school support staff.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53141","53141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637038","2016-11-17","Department for Education","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to her Department's report Cost of school uniform 2015, published in June 2015, what steps she is taking to reduce the financial hardship reported by parents and carers as a result of purchasing their child's school uniform; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53124","53124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637039","2016-11-17","Department for Education","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what mechanism her Department uses to monitor the number of nursery workers referred to local authorities for responsible incidents; and how many such referrals there have been in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53139","53139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637040","2016-11-17","Department for Education","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much the Government has spent on advertising in each of the last six years with (a) The Times, (b) The Sunday Times, (c) The Mail on Sunday, (d) The Sun, (e) The Sun on Sunday, (f) The Huffington Post, (g) Mail Online, (h) Daily Mail, (i) The Guardian and (j) Trinity Mirror.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53137","53137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637041","2016-11-17","Department for Education","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what mechanism her Department uses to monitor the number of reportable incidents recorded in (a) nurseries and (b) other non-domestic childcare settings across local authorities in England.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53115","53115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637042","2016-11-17","Department for Education","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what budget was allocated to Ofsted's inspection team for early years settings in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53116","53116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637043","2016-11-17","Department for Education","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many working days were lost due to mental illness in her Department in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53067","53067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637044","2016-11-17","Department for Education","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many students have studied at least two arts subjects at GCSE level in York in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52977","52977"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637045","2016-11-18","Department for Education","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will make it her policy to commit to maintaining funding for Scottish and UK higher education institutions from EU sources at or above current levels after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53029","53029"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637046","2016-11-17","Department for Education","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when she plans to answer Questions 51314 and 51315, tabled by the hon. Member for Manchester Central on 1 November 2016 for Answer on 4 November 2016.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53090","53090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637047","2016-11-17","Department for Education","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children for whom hearing impairment is a primary need and who attended a grammar school achieved five GCSEs including English and mathematics at grades A* to C in 2015-16.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53096","53096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637048","2016-11-17","Department for Education","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children for whom hearing impairment is a primary special educational need attended a grammar school in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53097","53097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637049","2016-11-17","Department for Education","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 14 November 2016 to Question 52486, what estimate she has made of the number of independent faith schools in Oldham; and what steps her Department is taking to encourage community cohesion and integration in such schools.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53102","53102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637050","2016-11-18","Department for Education","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the timetable is for a decision to be taken on the future of the Rock Ferry High School site.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53051","53051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637051","2016-11-17","Department for Education","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will set a publication date for the Early Years Workforce strategy.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53105","53105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637052","2016-11-17","Department for Education","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many GCSE entries for arts subjects there were from students in York in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52978","52978"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637053","2016-11-17","Department for Education","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many students studied music at GCSE level in York in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52979","52979"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637054","2016-11-17","Department for Education","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when she plans for the Early Years Workforce Strategy to be published.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52970","52970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637055","2016-11-18","Department for Education","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many Ofsted-registered childcare providers have been inspected by Ofsted in the last (a) one, (b) two, (c) three and (d) four years.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53024","53024"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637056","2016-11-18","Department for Education","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many Ofsted-registered childcare providers there were in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53025","53025"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637057","2016-11-18","Department for Education","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many inspections have been carried out by Ofsted arising from information given to Ofsted by managers of childcare providers in each year since 2010; and how many providers have lost their registration as a result of inspections arising from such information.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53027","53027"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637058","2016-11-18","Department for Education","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many Ofsted-registered childcare providers were rated (a) outstanding, (b) good, (c) satisfactory and (d) inadequate in each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53028","53028"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637059","2016-11-17","Department for Education","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether additional support will be available for providers who are negatively financially impacted as a result of the introduction of 30 hours of free childcare policy.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52964","52964"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637060","2016-11-17","Department for Education","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to ensure that providers receive the adequate level of funding to deliver the 30 hours of free childcare policy.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52965","52965"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637061","2016-11-18","Department for Education","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the average number of children with special educational needs and disabilities attending non-selective schools is in (a) partially selective, (b) fully selective and (c) non-selective local education authority areas.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52948","52948"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637062","2016-11-18","Department for Education","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of children (a) with special education needs, (b) in care and (c) on a child protection plan attend (i) maintained nursery schools, (ii) nursery classes and (iii) private, voluntary and independent early years provision.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52947","52947"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637063","2016-11-18","Department for Education","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether her Department plans to make support available to parents and carers who are required to purchase new school uniform due to academisation; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52897","52897"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637064","2016-11-18","Department for Education","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to reduce any financial hardship which parents and carers may face when purchasing school uniforms; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52898","52898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637065","2016-11-17","Department for Education","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many students took (a) a GCSE and (b) an AS/A2 Level in Panjabi in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52928","52928"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637066","2016-11-17","Department for Education","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many students took (a) a GCSE and (b) an AS/A2 Level in Polish in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52926","52926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637067","2016-11-17","Department for Education","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many students took (a) a GCSE and (b) an AS/A2 Level in Urdu in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52927","52927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637068","2016-11-17","Department for Education","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many students took (a) a GCSE and (b) an AS/A2 Level in Turkish in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52922","52922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637069","2016-11-17","Department for Education","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many students took (a) a GCSE and (b) an AS/A2 Level in Mandarin Chinese in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52923","52923"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637070","2016-11-17","Department for Education","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many students took (a) a GCSE and (b) an AS/A2 Level in Bengali in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52924","52924"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637071","2016-11-17","Department for Education","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many students took (a) a GCSE and (b) an AS/A2 Level in Modern Hebrew in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52925","52925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637072","2016-11-18","Department for Education","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of children in receipt of free school meals attend each grammar school in each local education authority area with a fully or partially selective system.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52946","52946"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637073","2016-11-18","Department for Education","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to work with West Sussex County Council to improve education results in that area.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52932","52932"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637074","2016-11-18","Department for Education","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to encourage the uptake of modern foreign language qualifications.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52918","52918"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637075","2016-11-17","Department for Education","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many students took (a) a GCSE and (b) an AS/A2 Level in Modern Greek in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52920","52920"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637076","2016-11-17","Department for Education","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many students took (a) a GCSE and (b) an AS/A2 Level in Italian in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52921","52921"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637077","2016-11-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the deterrent effect that increased maximum sentences for cruelty against animals have had in Northern Ireland; and whether she has made an assessment of the implications of those effects for her Department's policies.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52929","52929"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637078","2016-11-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the timetable is for publication of her Department's proposed consultation on Proposals to regulate generators with high NOx emissions; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52901","52901"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637079","2016-11-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many inspections Trading Standards has undertaken of animals during transit for slaughter abroad in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Mr Mark Williams","Mr Mark Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52956","52956"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637080","2016-11-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she made of the potential merits of the regulation of commercial cat breeding to improve safeguards for cat welfare through the introduction of cat breeding licensing, welfare conditions and standards and an inspection process.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52969","52969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637081","2016-11-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many working days were lost due to mental illness in her Department in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53068","53068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637082","2016-11-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many new incidents of bovine TB there have been in each month in each of the last five years; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53162","53162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637083","2016-11-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate she has made of the total application of (a) nitrogen, (b) phosphate, (c) potash and (d) sulphur on farmland across the UK in each of the last five years; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53157","53157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637084","2016-11-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to ensure that British Muslims wishing to travel to the US can do so within normal terms applied to non-Muslims and not prescribed by the comments of President-Elect Trump on 7 December 2015.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53148","53148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637085","2016-11-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 29 June 2016 to Question 41097, what further information he has on the progress being made by the Danish authorities on the re-opened inquest into the death of Stephen O'Malley; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Mrs Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53163","53163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637086","2016-11-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the UK ambassador to Egypt has made representations to the government of Egypt on the practice of female genital mutilation.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53152","53152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637087","2016-11-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that BP operations in the Bintuni Bay area in West Papua recently authorised by the Indonesian government are undertaken in accordance with (a) UK and international human rights law and (b) the OECD Guidelines for Multinational Enterprises.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53120","53120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637088","2016-11-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many working days were lost due to mental illness in his Department in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53069","53069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637089","2016-11-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to discourage illegal settlements in Palestine.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53030","53030"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637090","2016-11-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has made representations to the Indonesian government on the reported arrest and detention of protestors this summer in West Papua.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53007","53007"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637091","2016-11-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his international counterparts on reports of recent massacres in Beni and the North Kivu region in the Democratic Republic of Congo.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53002","53002"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637092","2016-11-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his international counterparts on improving diplomatic co-ordination against Daesh.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53003","53003"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637093","2016-11-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will raise with his counterpart in Indonesia the appointment of General Wiranto as that country's security minister.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53004","53004"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637094","2016-11-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the UK's decision to leave the EU on UK bilateral relations with (a) other EU and (b) non-EU countries.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53005","53005"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637095","2016-11-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the Israeli government on the overnight detention of Palestinian minors.","Biography information for Dr Alasdair McDonnell","Dr Alasdair McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53046","53046"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637096","2016-11-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what criteria the Government uses in order to assess whether the recognition of Palestinian statehood would be conducive to peace in that region.","Biography information for Dr Alasdair McDonnell","Dr Alasdair McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53047","53047"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637097","2016-11-18","Department for International Trade","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether public bodies are covered by the advice on the UK Trade and Investment website not to trade with illegal settlements in the West Bank.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53026","53026"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637098","2016-11-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many times he has met Ministers of the Scottish Government since July 2016.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53001","53001"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637099","2016-11-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the UK Ambassador to Guinea has made representations to the government of Guinea on the practice of female genital mutilation.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52997","52997"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637100","2016-11-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the UK Ambassador to Burkina Faso has made representations to the government of Burkina Faso on the practice of female genital mutilation.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52998","52998"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637101","2016-11-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the UK Ambassador to Mali Faso has made representations to the government of Mali on the practice of female genital mutilation.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52999","52999"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637102","2016-11-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the UK Ambassador to Ethiopia has made representations on the practice of female genital mutilation to the government of Ethiopia.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52971","52971"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637103","2016-11-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions are taking place with the US administration on its continuing role in NATO; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52992","52992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637104","2016-11-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the UK Ambassador to Djibouti has made representations to the government of Djibouti on the practice of female genital mutilation.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52993","52993"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637105","2016-11-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the UK Ambassador to Eritrea has made representations to the government of Eritrea on the practice of female genital mutilation.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52994","52994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637106","2016-11-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the UK Ambassador to Somalia has made representations to the government of Somalia on the practice of female genital mutilation.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52995","52995"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637107","2016-11-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the UK Ambassador to Sudan has made representations to the government of Sudan on the practice of female genital mutilation.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52996","52996"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637108","2016-11-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to the Turkish government on the death penalty.","Biography information for Chris Elmore","Chris Elmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52957","52957"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637109","2016-11-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions the Government has had with the Indian government on the continued imprisonment of six UK ex-servicemen who had been working on an anti-piracy ship; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52963","52963"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637110","2016-11-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many representations he has made to his Israeli counterpart on the building of settlements on Palestinian land since he took office.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52976","52976"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637111","2016-11-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, where he plans to hold the Commonwealth Heads of Government meeting in the UK in 2018.","Biography information for James Duddridge","James Duddridge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53060","53060"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637112","2016-11-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the oral contribution of the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs of 18 October 2016, Official Report, column 653, what discussions he has had with his counterpart in India on the review of the use of pellet guns and the proposed alternative methods of crowd control.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52937","52937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637113","2016-11-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his counterpart in India on the use of pellet ammunition by Indian troops in Kashmir.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52938","52938"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637114","2016-11-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his Department has requested a copy of the extradition agreement or security agreement from either the Yemeni or Ethiopian governments which was reported to exist between the two countries at the time of Andargachew Tsege's kidnap in 2014.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52902","52902"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637115","2016-11-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many people are employed in the UK Permanent Representation to the EU.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52887","52887"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637116","2016-11-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many civil servants in his Department have responsibilities which include EU-related matters.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52888","52888"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637117","2016-11-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what information his Department holds on the number of people (a) killed, (b) blinded and (c) otherwise seriously injured during recent disturbances in Kashmir.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52939","52939"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637118","2016-11-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has met representatives from (a) Hong Kong pro-democracy groups and (b) the Hong Kong Democratic Party since taking office.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52914","52914"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637119","2016-11-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has made representations to his Chinese counterpart on the banning of Yau Wai-ching and Baggio Sixtus Leung from taking office in the Hong Kong Legislative Council by the Chinese government.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52916","52916"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637120","2016-11-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has met his Chinese counterpart to discuss the banning of Yau Wai-ching and Baggio Sixtus Leung from taking office in the Hong Kong Legislative Council by the Chinese government.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52917","52917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637121","2016-11-17","Department of Health","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the Committee on the Medical Effects of Air Pollutants has been instructed to concentrate on ambient air pollution and not to carry out any work on indoor air pollution.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52907","52907"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637122","2016-11-17","Department of Health","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the level of future funding for local health services in Kirklees.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52908","52908"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637123","2016-11-17","Department of Health","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department has taken to ensure a sustainable level of hospital bed provision in Kirklees.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52909","52909"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637124","2016-11-18","Department of Health","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much his Department has spent to limit excess winter deaths in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52943","52943"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637125","2016-11-18","Department of Health","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many officials work in his Department's Exiting the EU team.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52889","52889"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637126","2016-11-17","Department of Health","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much the NHS spent on branded drugs after the rebate from the Pharmaceutical Price Regulation Scheme as a proportion of total expenditure in (a) 2010-11 and (b) 2015-16.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52905","52905"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637127","2016-11-17","Department of Health","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much of the estimated £2.4 billion funding by 2020-21 for the General Practice Forward View is planned to be allocated to support GPs in Bristol; and by what method that allocation will be distributed.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52959","52959"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637128","2016-11-17","Department of Health","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress NHS Property Services has made on reducing its level of debt to his Department in the last two years.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52960","52960"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637129","2016-11-17","Department of Health","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what representations have been made by health bodies to NHS Property Services on the quality of the services its provides.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52961","52961"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637130","2016-11-18","Department of Health","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 14 November 2016 to Question 52127, on the WHO Framework Convention on Tobacco Control, which countries are receiving direct country support; what the cost to the Exchequer is of that support; and which countries meet the criterion of being low and middle income countries for the purposes of training and guidance.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52951","52951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637131","2016-11-18","Department of Health","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 14 November 2016 to Question 52428, for what reason there is no information given in that Answer on the proportion of patients being referred to hospital emergency departments by South West Ambulance and ambulance services in London and North West England; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52952","52952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637132","2016-11-17","Department of Health","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect of recent currency exchange rate changes on the import costs of (a) medicines and (b) equipment for the NHS.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52966","52966"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637133","2016-11-17","Department of Health","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect of recent currency exchange rate changes on the ability of the NHS to attract overseas workers.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52967","52967"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637134","2016-11-17","Department of Health","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if the Nursing and Midwifery Council will include mandatory bowel and bladder care training for pre- and post-registration nurses in the new revised curriculum.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52962","52962"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637135","2016-11-17","Department of Health","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of the risks posed by WiFi and related electromagnetic fields to children.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52981","52981"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637136","2016-11-18","Department of Health","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) hospitals and (b) care homes inspected by the Care Quality Commission in each of the last six years did not meet the requirements set out in Regulation 14 of the Health and Social Care Act 2008 (Regulated Activities) Regulations 2014.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53061","53061"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637137","2016-11-17","Department of Health","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which Clinical Commissioning Groups have put into practice the NHS England Excellence in continence care guidelines published in November 2015.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52987","52987"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637138","2016-11-17","Department of Health","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps NHS England has taken to promote the Excellence in continence care guidelines to (a) clinical commissioning groups, (b) patient groups and (c) the general public.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53012","53012"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637139","2016-11-18","Department of Health","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many NHS staff have (a) taken medical severance, (b) taken early retirement on health grounds and (c) been redeployed due to work-related injury or illness in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53040","53040"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637140","2016-11-17","Department of Health","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions Ministers and officials of his Department have had with NHS England on the expiry of the National Stroke Strategy in December 2016.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53100","53100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637141","2016-11-17","Department of Health","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what meetings Ministers and officials of his Department have had on the National Stroke Strategy since October 2016.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53101","53101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637142","2016-11-17","Department of Health","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which NHS Trusts that provide both adult and paediatric audiology services have received accreditation for their adult service alone.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53098","53098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637143","2016-11-17","Department of Health","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which NHS Trusts have gained accreditation for paediatric audiology services.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53099","53099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637144","2016-11-17","Department of Health","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many working days were lost due to mental illness in his Department in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53070","53070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637145","2016-11-17","Department of Health","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the take-up rate has been for Meningococcal ACWY vaccine by each clinical commissioning group in England in each year since 2015.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53008","53008"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637146","2016-11-17","Department of Health","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patient referrals (a) GPs and (b) other NHS bodies received from pharmacies in each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53109","53109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637147","2016-11-17","Department of Health","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if his Department will take steps to improve consumer access to food hygiene ratings through online food ordering platforms.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Mr David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53131","53131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637148","2016-11-18","Department of Health","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many delayed transfers of care there have been in West Sussex in each of the last three years; what steps he is taking to reduce the number of such transfers; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53050","53050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637149","2016-11-17","Department of Health","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will publish all correspondence between NHS England and (a) Hull City Council, (b) Hull Clinical Commissioning Group and (c) Hull and East Yorkshire Hospitals NHS Trust on Sustainability and Transformation Plans.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53106","53106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637150","2016-11-17","Department of Health","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will estimate the number of pharmacies in Hull which are at risk of closure in (a) 2016-17 and (b) 2017-18 as a result of planned changes to community pharmacy funding.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53107","53107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637151","2016-11-17","Department of Health","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many Healthy Living Pharmacies there were in (a) Hull and (b) England in each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53108","53108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637152","2016-11-17","Department of Health","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 7 November 2016 to Question 51260, where an error in a recommendation made by NHS England's Clinical Priorities Advisory Group is found following investigation by the Director of Specialised Commissioning, what process would be followed for reconsideration of that recommendation.","Biography information for Crispin Blunt","Crispin Blunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53125","53125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637153","2016-11-17","Department of Health","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people under the age of 16 were admitted to hospital with malnutrition in each (a) English region and (b) parliamentary constituency in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53136","53136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637154","2016-11-17","Department of Health","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of the planned changes in community pharmacy funding in (a) 2016-17 and (b) 2017-18 will fall on pharmacies based in each deprivation decile Lower-Layer Super Output Areas.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53111","53111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637155","2016-11-17","Department of Health","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of the planned funding from the Pharmacy Access Scheme will go to pharmacies based in each deprivation decile Lower-Layer Super Output Areas in (a) England and (b) Hull.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53110","53110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637156","2016-11-18","Department of Health","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much his Department has spent on advertising in each of the last six years in (a) The Sunday Times, (b) The Times, (c) The Mail on Sunday, (d) The Sun, (e) The Sun on Sunday, (f) The Huffington Post, (g) Mail Online, (h) Daily Mail, (i) The Guardian and (j) Trinity Mirror.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53154","53154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637157","2016-11-17","Department of Health","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which key indicators defined as important in the National Stroke Strategy are not currently measured by the sentinel stroke national audit programme.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53151","53151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637158","2016-11-17","Department of Health","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the number of delayed transfers of care attributable to patients awaiting a care package in their own home; and what steps he is taking to reduce the number of such delays.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53146","53146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637159","2016-11-17","Department of Health","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many pregnant women were admitted to hospital with malnutrition in each (a) English region and (b) parliamentary constituency in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53150","53150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637160","2016-11-17","Department of Health","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had on enhancing consultation with stakeholders on the Pharmaceutical Price Regulation in the preparation and conduct of the forthcoming negotiations on the next such Scheme, in particular with industry bodies representing companies directly affected through their participation in the Scheme.","Biography information for Crispin Blunt","Crispin Blunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53147","53147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637161","2016-11-18","Department of Health","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 20 July 2016 to Question 42560, if he will provide the figures in that Answer by each (a) English region and (b) parliamentary constituency.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53158","53158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637162","2016-11-17","Department of Health","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of delayed transfers of care attributable to patients awaiting either a nursing or residential care placement; and what steps he is taking to reduce the number of such delays.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53149","53149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637163","2016-11-18","Department of Health","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many bed days in hospitals were for people with (a) a primary diagnosis for malnutrition and (b) a secondary diagnosis of malnutrition in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53159","53159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637164","2016-11-18","Department of Health","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of the (a) number and (b) proportion of care home residents who are malnourished; what steps his Department is taking to improve nutrition in care homes; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53160","53160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637165","2016-11-18","Department of Health","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much remains in the budget of the Cancer Drugs Fund; and how the monies available to that Fund have been allocated.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53166","53166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637166","2016-11-18","Home Office","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many students detained under section 10 of the Immigration and Asylum Act (1999) had their visas revoked as a result of investigations into the Test of English for International Communication operations of Educational Testing Services.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53164","53164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637167","2016-11-18","Home Office","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many students have submitted appeals from (a) inside the UK and (b) outside the UK after revocation of their visas as a result of investigations into the Test of English for International Communication operations of Educational Testing Services.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53032","53032"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637168","2016-11-17","Home Office","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many working days were lost due to mental illness in her Department in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53071","53071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637169","2016-11-18","Home Office","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she plans to respond to the letter from the hon. Member for Wolverhampton South West of 23 August 2016, reference ZA3542.","Biography information for Rob Marris","Rob Marris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53023","53023"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637170","2016-11-17","Home Office","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she plans the second round of bids to open in the Places of worship: security funding scheme; and how much funding she plans to make available (a) in total and (b) for each bid.","Biography information for Richard Graham","Richard Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52975","52975"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637171","2016-11-17","Department for International Development","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what (a) countries and (b) programmes will receive the additional funding announced by the Prime Minister on 21 September 2016.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52980","52980"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637172","2016-11-17","Department for International Development","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many working days were lost due to mental illness in her Department in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53072","53072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637173","2016-11-17","Department for International Development","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what estimate she has made of how much of the funding provided by her Department for projects in Burma is administered by companies which are owned by the Burmese Army.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53018","53018"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637174","2016-11-17","Department for International Development","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what discussions she has had with her counterpart in Burma on the suicide rates of internally displaced people in camps in that country.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53017","53017"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637175","2016-11-17","Department for International Development","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the availability of access to (a) clean water and (b) medical supplies in (i) Gaza and (ii) the West Bank; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53087","53087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637176","2016-11-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will estimate the number of Palestinian people displaced from their homes through Israeli settlement building in the last 12 months; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53085","53085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637177","2016-11-17","Department for International Development","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to increase investment in decentralised renewable energy in developing countries.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53140","53140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637178","2016-11-17","Department for International Development","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what proportion of her Department's allocated aid for Burma will be administered by the Department for International Trade (a) in this financial year and (b) in the next three financial years.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53138","53138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637179","2016-11-17","Department for International Development","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to support adolescent girls into secondary education in Democratic Republic of Congo (DRC); which programmes her Department supports that address access to secondary education in DRC; and how many girls have been assisted to engage in and to complete secondary schooling as a result of such work in the last five years.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53126","53126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637180","2016-11-17","Department for International Development","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to increase provision of decentralised renewable energy in developing countries.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53123","53123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637181","2016-11-17","Department for International Development","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will offer assistance to New Zealand to manage the effects of the recent earthquakes in that country.","Biography information for Oliver Colvile","Oliver Colvile","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53130","53130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637182","2016-11-17","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 11 November 2016 to Question 51837, what steps her Department plans to take to reduce the difference between Gypsy, Romany or Traveller understanding of written English in young offender institutions and that of other young males.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53135","53135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637183","2016-11-17","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many working days were lost due to mental illness in her Department in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53073","53073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637184","2016-11-18","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many assaults on prison officers there were in South Yorkshire prisons in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53036","53036"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637185","2016-11-17","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to her oral contribution of 3 November 2016, Official Report, column 1071, what the (a) remit, (b) membership and (c) date of the last meeting is of the Government taskforce to address the issue of drone use and prisons.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52984","52984"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637186","2016-11-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many prosecutions there have been for breaches of the animal welfare regulations governing live animal exports in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Mr Mark Williams","Mr Mark Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52955","52955"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637187","2016-11-17","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what discussions she had with the (a) Law Society and (b) Bar Council before those organisations introduced training for their members on improving the courtroom experience for (i) vulnerable witnesses and (ii) children who have experienced sexual abuse.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52912","52912"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637188","2016-11-17","Northern Ireland Office","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many working days were lost due to mental illness in his Department in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53074","53074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637189","2016-11-18","Prime Minister","2016-11-15","To ask the Prime Minister, whether during her recent visit to India she discussed the cases of Indian nationals who had their visas curtailed following investigations into the Test of English for International Communication operations of Educational Testing Services; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53033","53033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637190","2016-11-18","Cabinet Office","2016-11-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the cost of appointing peers to the House of Lords has been for the period between May 2010 and November 2016.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53169","53169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637191","2016-11-17","Scotland Office","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what recent discussions he has had with the Chancellor of the Exchequer on future funding for the Scottish Government.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53121","53121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637192","2016-11-17","Scotland Office","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how many working days were lost due to mental illness in his Department in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53075","53075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637193","2016-11-17","Department for Transport","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many working days were lost due to mental illness in his Department in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53076","53076"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637194","2016-11-17","Department for Transport","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent estimate he has made of the total cost of the High Speed 2 project; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53086","53086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637195","2016-11-17","Department for Transport","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much his Department has spent on research conducted by (a) private bodies and (b) public bodies in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53084","53084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637196","2016-11-17","Department for Transport","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many full-time equivalent civil servants employed by his Department work in support of research projects funded by his Department; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53080","53080"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637197","2016-11-17","Department for Transport","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much has been spent on (a) highway maintenance and (b) transport infrastructure in each year since 2011.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53103","53103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637198","2016-11-18","Department for Transport","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the total electrical output from electrical vehicle chargepoints in the UK in each of the last three years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53161","53161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637199","2016-11-18","Department for Transport","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to reduce the level of greenhouse gas emissions from heavy goods vehicles; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53156","53156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637200","2016-11-18","Department for Transport","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the number of ultra-low emissions vehicles registered in each of the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53155","53155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637201","2016-11-17","Department for Transport","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will take steps to improve rail links with Cardiff.","Biography information for Craig Williams","Craig Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53129","53129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637202","2016-11-17","Department for Transport","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to reduce noise emissions from (a) motorcycles, (b) cars and (c) commercial vehicles; and what targets he has set to reduce each such type of noise emission.","Biography information for Sir Hugo Swire","Sir Hugo Swire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52910","52910"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637203","2016-11-17","Department for Transport","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what research his Department has conducted on the effectiveness of noise-reducing road surfaces.","Biography information for Sir Hugo Swire","Sir Hugo Swire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52911","52911"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637204","2016-11-17","Department for Transport","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many applications from bus companies based in Wales were submitted for the low emission bus scheme; and how many of those applications were successful.","Biography information for Craig Williams","Craig Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52919","52919"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637206","2016-11-18","Department for Transport","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the Govia Thameslink Railway (GTR) franchise agreement that stipulates as to whether it is in default of its franchise agreement for cancellations relates to (a) GTR as a whole, (b) Thameslink, Southern, Gatwick Express and Great Northern individually or (c) is at the discretion of the Secretary of State.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52890","52890"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637207","2016-11-18","Department for Transport","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the actual level of cancellations was compared to the default threshold cancellation level for the southern section of the Govia Thameslink Railway (GTR) franchise, as amended by the GTR remedial plan, for each monthly period since the beginning of 2016.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52891","52891"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637208","2016-11-18","Department for Transport","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the actual number of train cancellations was compared to the default threshold number of train cancellations for the southern section of the Govia Thameslink Railway (GTR) franchise as amended by the GTR remedial plan for each monthly period since the beginning of 2016.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52892","52892"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637209","2016-11-18","Department for Transport","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the actual percentage level of cancellations was compared to the default percentage threshold cancellation level for the Govia Thameslink Railway (GTR) franchise, as amended by the GTR remedial plan, for each monthly period since the beginning of 2016.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52894","52894"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637210","2016-11-18","Department for Transport","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the actual number of train cancellations was compared to the default threshold number of train cancellations for the Govia Thameslink Railway (GTR) franchise, as amended by the GTR remedial plan, for each monthly period since the beginning of 2016.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52893","52893"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637211","2016-11-18","HM Treasury","2016-11-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the funding formula implications for Scotland are of the £2.1 billion increase in the estimated cost of the modernisation of the Great Western railway network in England and Wales.","Biography information for Drew Hendry","Drew Hendry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52895","52895"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637212","2016-11-18","Department for Transport","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking with the Cabinet Office to ensure that public sector fleet operators utilise alternative fuels such as LPG in order to achieve local air quality targets.","Biography information for Drew Hendry","Drew Hendry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52896","52896"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637213","2016-11-17","Department for Transport","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 15 June 2016 to Question 40015, if he will now place in the Library a redacted summary of the risk assessments commissioned by the Cross-Government Working Group on remotely piloted aircraft system on the use of drones for criminal purposes.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52972","52972"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637214","2016-11-18","Department for Transport","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 14 November 2016 to Question 52128, if the Government will reject any new proposals for further regulation of new Implementing Rules (Prototype) Regulations which are not proportionate to the risk and undermine the activities of modal aircraft clubs.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52953","52953"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637215","2016-11-17","Department for Transport","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the Answer of 27 May 2016 to Question 38311, what the outcome was of the Government's consultation on measures to regulate the use of drones.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52973","52973"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637216","2016-11-21","Department for Transport","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the timetable is for work to commence on uprating the A12 to a three lane road from (a) the M25 to Margaretting and (b) Boreham Interchange to Colchester; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Simon Burns","Sir Simon Burns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53062","53062"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637217","2016-11-17","Wales Office","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how many working days were lost due to mental illness in his Department in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53078","53078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637218","2016-11-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many working days were lost due to mental illness in his Department in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53079","53079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637219","2016-11-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate his Department has made of how many properties have been released for letting in Peterborough since the introduction of changes in the spare room subsidy regime; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stewart Jackson","Mr Stewart Jackson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53043","53043"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637220","2016-11-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the cost to the public purse has been of Government legal action in respect of the case brought by the Rutherford family on the spare room subsidy.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53044","53044"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637221","2016-11-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what representations he has made to the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy on (a) the link between increased productivity and good safety and health management and (b) that link forming part of the Government's new industrial strategy.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53039","53039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637222","2016-11-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he plans to respond to the letter dated 23 September 2016 from the hon. Member for Gordon on toilet facilities in Ebury House, Aberdeen.","Biography information for Alex Salmond","Alex Salmond","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53143","53143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637223","2016-11-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much his Department has spent on advertising in each of the last six years in (a) The Sun, (b) The Sunday Times, (c) The Mail on Sunday, (d) The Times, (e) The Sun on Sunday, (f) The Huffington Post, (g) Mail Online, (h) Daily Mail, (i) The Guardian and (j) Trinity Mirror.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53153","53153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637224","2016-11-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he plans to respond to the letter from the hon. Member for Glasgow Central of 25 October 2016, requesting that the Government's consultation on tax credit payments be extended.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53133","53133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637225","2016-11-17","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many cases before employment tribunals were from claimants with cancer in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53113","53113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637226","2016-11-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make it his policy to end the requirement for re-assessments for those with long-term medical conditions who are receiving personal independence payments.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53014","53014"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637227","2016-11-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many appointments for claimants transferring from disability living allowance to personal independence payments have been rearranged or cancelled at the request of a person other than the claimant in (a) Plymouth and (b) the South West in the last 12 months; and of those rearranged appointments how many claimants received (i) one strike and (ii) two strikes as a result.","Biography information for Johnny Mercer","Johnny Mercer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52915","52915"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637228","2016-11-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of social security claimants who were sanctioned for late arrival to advisory meetings in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52913","52913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637229","2016-11-18","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how much his Department has spent to limit excess winter deaths in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52942","52942"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637230","2016-11-18","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate he has made of the likely proportion of capacity that diesel generation could make up in the Capacity Market T-4 auction in winter 2016-17; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52899","52899"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637231","2016-11-18","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate he has made of the likely amount of investment in new large-scale gas power stations that will be delivered through the Capacity Market T-4 auction in winter 2016-17; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52900","52900"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637232","2016-11-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department is taking to (a) encourage graduates from North West universities to remain in the North West after graduation and (b) attract graduates from across the country to the North West.","Biography information for Graham Evans","Graham Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53015","53015"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637233","2016-11-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department is taking to support businesses which are threatened with legal action from previous employees affected by asbestosis but which cannot trace any relevant Employer's Liability insurance policy.","Biography information for Ms Nusrat Ghani","Nusrat Ghani","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52974","52974"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637234","2016-11-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many people were on pre-payment meters in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52983","52983"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637235","2016-11-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will take steps to ensure that energy consumers with cancer are protected by a price cap.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53114","53114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637236","2016-11-18","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many responses the Post Office has received to its consultation on proposals to franchise Crown post office branches since January 2014; and how many of those responses were opposed to those proposals.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53056","53056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637237","2016-11-18","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the timetable is for the publication of the Post Office Network Report for 2016 pursuant to section 11 of the Postal Services Act 2011.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53055","53055"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637238","2016-11-18","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many Crown post offices which the Post Office is proposing to franchise in 2016 are in (a) urban deprived, (b) urban and (c) rural areas.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53054","53054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637239","2016-11-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what support his Department makes available for the establishment of new cooperatives in the UK.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53104","53104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637240","2016-11-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent progress has been made on introducing a cap on the cost of energy supplied through prepayment meters.","Biography information for Dawn Butler","Dawn Butler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53119","53119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637241","2016-11-18","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when he plans to respond to the recommendations by the Low Pay Commission made in the National Minimum Wage: Low Pay Commission Report, Spring 2016, published in March 2016.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53165","53165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637242","2016-11-18","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what plans he has to transpose the EU Non-Financial Reporting Directive into UK Law.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53038","53038"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637243","2016-11-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what support his Department provides to energy-intensive users in the manufacturing and engineering sectors.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53009","53009"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637244","2016-11-18","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what plans his Department has to improve the energy efficiency of non-domestic premises.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53034","53034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637245","2016-11-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many working days were lost due to mental illness in his Department and its predecessor in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53006","53006"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637246","2016-11-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how much he plans for his Department to contribute towards the Economic and Social Research Council grant programme, UK in a Changing Europe.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53082","53082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637247","2016-11-18","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how much has been spent since January 2010 from the public purse on refurbishment of Crown post offices which are proposed to be franchised in July 2016.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53052","53052"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637248","2016-11-18","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how much has been spent since January 2010 from the public purse on each of the branches which the Post Office has announced will be franchised in 2016.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53053","53053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637249","2016-11-17","Department for International Trade","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many meetings he has had with representatives from Commonwealth countries since his Department was created; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53083","53083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637250","2016-11-18","Department for International Trade","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether public bodies are covered by the advice on the UK Trade and Investment website not to trade with illegal settlements in the West Bank.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53031","53031"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637251","2016-11-22","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when her Department plans to make a decision on the entrustment to facilitate a trade agreement between Jersey and Rwanda.","Biography information for James Duddridge","James Duddridge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53063","53063"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637252","2016-11-17","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what recent assessment he has made of the scale of work generated by the UK's decision to leave the EU.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52989","52989"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637253","2016-11-17","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what assessment he has made of whether the staffing levels of (a) his Department and (b) other Government departments are sufficient to deal with the work generated by the UK's exit of the EU.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52990","52990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637254","2016-11-17","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether his Department has a common strategy for co-ordinating consistent approaches to the UK's exit of the EU between departments.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52988","52988"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637255","2016-11-17","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many projects in operation in his Department deal with the UK's exit of the EU.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52991","52991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637256","2016-11-17","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many meetings he has had with representatives from Commonwealth countries since his Department was created; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53081","53081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637257","2016-11-17","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, when his Department expects the final EU Structural Fund payments to be made to Wales.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53142","53142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/640523","2016-11-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that people with mental health conditions are properly supported into work.","Biography information for Mr Marcus Fysh","Marcus Fysh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 907336","907336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/642473","2016-11-23","Scotland Office","2016-11-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy on the potential merits of locating a space port in Scotland.","Biography information for Stephen Metcalfe","Stephen Metcalfe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 907328","907328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636153","2016-11-16","Cabinet Office","2016-11-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 19 October 2016 to Question 47797, whether the Gulf Strategy Integrated Delivery Team's remit includes co-ordinating the Government's strategic policy on the size of the UK's permanent military presence in the Gulf states.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52851","52851"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636154","2016-11-17","HM Treasury","2016-11-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate his Department has made of the number of towns and villages which have been left without a bank in the last five years due to local branch closures.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52877","52877"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636155","2016-11-16","HM Treasury","2016-11-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of the potential contribution of the system due to replace Customs CHIEF to a more-intelligence led, frictionless border.","Biography information for Charlie Elphicke","Charlie Elphicke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52733","52733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636156","2016-11-16","HM Treasury","2016-11-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when his Department concluded its agreement with Concentrix to end the contract with that company to administer tax credits on behalf of HM Revenue and Customs; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52750","52750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636157","2016-11-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many EU nationals who live abroad claim UK state pension in each non-UK EU country; and what the total value is of these payments annually.","Biography information for Naz Shah","Naz Shah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52796","52796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636158","2016-11-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many UK pensioners who live outside the UK receive pensions from other EU countries; and how many receive such entitlements from each other EU country.","Biography information for Naz Shah","Naz Shah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52797","52797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636159","2016-11-16","HM Treasury","2016-11-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what Freedom of Information requests his Department has received in respect of requests for documents relating to meetings held between the oil and gas sector and Ministers and officials of his Department; what response his Department provided to those requests; and what the reasons were for each such response.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52816","52816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636160","2016-11-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many full-time equivalent civil servants employed by his Department work in support of the West Midlands Combined Authority; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52835","52835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636161","2016-11-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what guidance his Department provides on the design and construction of affordable housing.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52775","52775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636162","2016-11-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the amount in devolved business rates which will be collected by each combined authority in each of the next three years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52866","52866"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636163","2016-11-17","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether she plans to set up a commission to assess the potential merits of introducing a new legal status to recognise participation in long-term volunteering programmes.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52880","52880"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636164","2016-11-16","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Maritime Patrol Aircraft are based in the UK; and where those aircraft are based.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52864","52864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636165","2016-11-16","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which Ministry of Defence contractors have signed the community covenant.","Biography information for Oliver Colvile","Oliver Colvile","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52865","52865"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636166","2016-11-17","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 14 November 2016 to Question 52316, whether he intends to meet the Burmese military, Tatmadaw, to discuss democratic accountability and adherence to international law and human rights.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52883","52883"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636167","2016-11-16","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many residential properties there are on the Dale barracks site in Chester; and how many such properties are (a) occupied by servicemen, servicewomen or service families, (b) unoccupied and (c) privately owned.","Biography information for Christian Matheson","Christian Matheson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52831","52831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636168","2016-11-17","Department for Education","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many free schools that opened in (a) 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012 and (d) 2013 are in temporary buildings.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52833","52833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636169","2016-11-17","Department for Education","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the longest period is for which a free school has remained in temporary accommodation.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52834","52834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636170","2016-11-17","Department for Education","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many pupils were in (a) selective and (b) non-selective state schools in Year 7 in each of the last five years; and what proportion of those were (i) boys, (ii) boys eligible for free school meals, (iii) girls and (iv) girls eligible for free school meals.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52778","52778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636171","2016-11-17","Department for Education","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many students took (a) a GCSE and (b) an AS/A2 Level in Spanish in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52779","52779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636172","2016-11-17","Department for Education","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many students took (a) a GCSE and (b) an AS/A2 Level in German in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52780","52780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636173","2016-11-17","Department for Education","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many students took (a) a GCSE and (b) an AS/A2 Level in French in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52781","52781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636174","2016-11-16","Department for Education","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when she last met representatives of the Russell Group of universities; and what subjects were discussed at that meeting.","Biography information for Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52795","52795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636175","2016-11-16","Department for Education","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment her Department has made of the implications for her policy on faith schools of (a) the Populus Poll commissioned by the Accord Coalition, published on 2 November 2016 and (b) the 2011 research paper entitled Faith Primary Schools: Better Schools or Better Pupils, written by Steve Gibbons and Olmo Silva.","Biography information for Mr Graham Allen","Mr Graham Allen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52815","52815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636176","2016-11-17","HM Treasury","2016-11-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many (a) primary and (b) secondary schools will be obliged to pay the apprenticeship levy.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52832","52832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636177","2016-11-16","Home Office","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate her Department has made of the potential financial benefits to universities involved in the introduction of the Tier 4 visa pilot scheme.","Biography information for Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52798","52798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636178","2016-11-17","Department for Education","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 2 November 2016 to Question 48790, how many children in Year 7 whose ethnic backgrounds were (a) white British, (b) white British eligible for free school meals, (c) white non-British, (d) white non-British eligible for free school meals, (e) black, (f) black eligible for free school meals, (g) Indian, (h) Indian eligible for free school meals, (i) Chinese, (j) Chinese eligible for free school meals, (k) Bangladeshi, (l) Bangladeshi eligible for free school meals, (m) Pakistani, (n) Pakistani eligible for free school meals, (o) other Asian, (p) other Asian eligible for free school meals, (q) any other ethnicity and (r) any other ethnicity eligible for free school meals received a place in a grammar school in each of the last five years; and what the total number was of Year 7 pupils and the total number was of Year 7 pupils eligible for free school meals in each of those ethnic groups in each of those years.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52769","52769"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636179","2016-11-17","Department for Education","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 2 November 2016 to Question 48789, how many and what proportion of boys in Year 7 whose ethnic backgrounds were (a) white British, (b) white British eligible for free school meals, (c) white non-British, (d) white non-British eligible for free school meals, (e) black, (f) black eligible for free school meals, (g) Indian, (h) Indian eligible for free school meals, (i) Chinese, (j) Chinese eligible for free school meals, (k) Bangladeshi, (l) Bangladeshi eligible for free school meals, (m) Pakistani, (n) Pakistani eligible for free school meals, (o) other Asian, (p) other Asian eligible for free school meals, (q) any other ethnicity and (r) any other ethnicity eligible for free school meals received a place in a grammar school in each of the last five years; and what the total number was of Year 7 male pupils and the total number was of Year 7 male pupils eligible for free school meals in each of those ethnic groups in each of those years.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52770","52770"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636180","2016-11-17","Department for Education","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 2 November 2016 to Question 48788, how many and what proportion of girls in Year 7 whose ethnic backgrounds were (a) white British, (b) white British eligible for free school meals, (c) white non-British, (d) white non-British eligible for free school meals, (e) black, (f) black eligible for free school meals, (g) Indian, (h) Indian eligible for free school meals, (i) Chinese, (j) Chinese eligible for free school meals, (k) Bangladeshi, (l) Bangladeshi eligible for free school meals, (m) Pakistani, (n) Pakistani eligible for free school meals, (o) other Asian, (p) other Asian eligible for free school meals, (q) any other ethnicity and (r) any other ethnicity eligible for free school meals received a place in a grammar school in each of the last five years; and what the total number was of Year 7 female pupils and the total number was of Year 7 female pupils eligible for free school meals in each of those ethnic groups in each of those years.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52771","52771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636181","2016-11-16","Department of Health","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many local authorities have published an autism strategy; and what steps the Government is taking to ensure that all local authorities are producing such strategies.","Biography information for Oliver Colvile","Oliver Colvile","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52749","52749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636182","2016-11-16","Department for Education","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how often she plans to review the per hour funding allocated to providers as part of the 30 hours free childcare entitlement.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52741","52741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636183","2016-11-16","Department for Education","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children are receiving 30 hours of free childcare under the pilot of that policy.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52742","52742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636184","2016-11-16","Department for Education","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment her Department has made of the pilot of the 30 hours free childcare entitlement.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52743","52743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636185","2016-11-17","Department for Education","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 14 November 2016 to Question 49975, which academy trusts had schools removed and rebrokered to other trusts; which schools were so removed and rebrokered; and how many schools each academy trust that received a financial notice to improve ran prior to receiving a notice from the Education Funding Agency.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52871","52871"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636186","2016-11-17","Department for Education","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Schools that work for everyone Government consultation, published in September 2016, page 7, paragraph 10, what the evidential basis is for the statement that the 50 per cent cap on faith-based admissions does not achieve inclusivity.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52884","52884"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636187","2016-11-17","Department for Education","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many people have qualified as teachers on the Troops to Teachers scheme since that scheme began.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52876","52876"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636188","2016-11-17","Department for Education","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much funding per head (a) was allocated for childcare in each constituency in the financial year 2010-11 and (b) is expected to be allocated for childcare in each constituency in the financial year 2017-18.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52870","52870"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636189","2016-11-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what advice her Department (a) has issued and (b) is planning to issue to minimise the risk of an outbreak of avian flu in the winter of 2016-17; what other steps she is taking to minimise the risk of such an outbreak; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52886","52886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636190","2016-11-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what funding her Department has allocated specifically for natural flood management projects; what proportion of the additional funding referred to in paragraphs 1.242 and 1.301 Budget 2016, HC 901, for flood risk management has been allocated to natural flood management projects; and which Department will have lead responsibility for the dispersal of that funding.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52818","52818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636191","2016-11-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to protect farmers from fluctuating energy costs; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52826","52826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636192","2016-11-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what her Department's most recent assessment is of the extent of the spread of ash dieback disease across UK woodland; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52827","52827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636193","2016-11-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what contingency funding was made available by her Department for flooding in each of the last five years; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52825","52825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636194","2016-11-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the combatibility of the UN negotiations to ban nuclear weapons with the Nuclear Non-Proliferation Treaty.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52808","52808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636195","2016-11-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports his Department has received on the demonstrations over economic policy proposals in Egypt on 11 November 2016.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52809","52809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636196","2016-11-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the Iranian Ambassador to the UK in relation to the murder of Farhang Amiri in Yazd on 26 September 2016; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Mrs Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52774","52774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636197","2016-11-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his counterparts in Guyana and Venezuela on the steps they are taking to resolve the border dispute between those two countries; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52731","52731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636198","2016-11-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent estimate his Department has made of the number of settlement structures in Amona, West Bank.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52735","52735"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636199","2016-11-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has made representations to his Iranian counterpart on the detention of Roya Saberinejad Nobakht.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52754","52754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636200","2016-11-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the cohesiveness and unity of purpose of the various groups within the Syrian opposition.","Biography information for Tom Elliott","Tom Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52785","52785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636201","2016-11-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his counterpart in the Israeli government on the effect on the number of outpost structures in the West Bank of the Israeli High Court ruling of 2014.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52772","52772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636202","2016-11-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his counterparts in Estonia, Latvia and Lithuania on the build-up of Russian forces on Russia's southern and western frontiers.","Biography information for Tom Elliott","Tom Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52786","52786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636203","2016-11-16","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to prevent the illegal hunting of wildlife on the Akrotiri and Dhekelia British Sovereign Bases Areas in Cyprus.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52801","52801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636204","2016-11-16","Department of Health","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many emergency admissions there were in the Lewisham and Greenwich NHS Trust in (a) 2013-14, (b) 2014-15 and (c) 2015-16.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52799","52799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636205","2016-11-16","Department of Health","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many elective admissions there were in the Lewisham and Greenwich NHS Trust in (a) 2013-14, (b) 2014-15 and (c) 2015-16.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52800","52800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636206","2016-11-21","Department of Health","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what representations his Department has received on the quality of congenital heart disease services at the Royal Brampton Hospital.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52784","52784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636207","2016-11-17","Department of Health","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many inpatient beds there were at Sherwood Forest Hospitals NHS Foundation Trust in (a) 2015-16 and (b) 2009-10.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52761","52761"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636208","2016-11-17","Department of Health","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 8 November 2016 to Question 51758, what discussions he has had with representatives of GPs to encourage them to prescribe non-branded drugs wherever possible; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52777","52777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636209","2016-11-17","Department of Health","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 7 November 2016 to Question 51566, what discussion he has had with the (a) Chancellor of the Exchequer, (b) Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy and (c) Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government on whether an assessment should be made of the potential additional cost pressures of the National Living Wage on learning disability service providers' wage budgets in relation to sleep-in shifts.","Biography information for Peter Aldous","Peter Aldous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52773","52773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636210","2016-11-16","Department of Health","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make an assessment of the achievements of the (a) Cardiovascular disease (CVD) outcomes strategy and (b) CVD expert forum since their establishment.","Biography information for Mr Graham Allen","Mr Graham Allen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52787","52787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636211","2016-11-16","Department of Health","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the lack of direct guidance to GPs on suspected cases of metastatic cancers in the NICE guideline Suspected cancer: recognition and referral on the (a) time taken for the diagnosis, (b) accuracy of diagnosis and (c) number of cases of such cancers.","Biography information for Craig Tracey","Craig Tracey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52807","52807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636212","2016-11-16","Department of Health","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will provide the equivalent information given in the Answers of 15 October 2015 to Question (a) 11427 and (b) 11428 for fiscal years 2009-10 and 2015-16.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52812","52812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636213","2016-11-17","Department of Health","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many and what proportion of local authorities in England have a (a) local suicide prevention plan and (b) local multi-agency suicide prevention group.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52841","52841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636214","2016-11-16","Department of Health","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of the financial health of the Coventry and Warwickshire Partnership NHS Trust; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52821","52821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636215","2016-11-16","Department of Health","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent steps he has taken to improve the financial situation of NHS trusts across England and Wales; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52822","52822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636216","2016-11-16","Department of Health","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that funding for NHS trusts remains in line with projected demand for services; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52823","52823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636217","2016-11-21","Department of Health","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what detailed analysis have been undertaken into current and projected congenital heart disease  patient flows in (a) London and (b) the South East and East of England and into the capacity of units in London to meet those flows.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52847","52847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636218","2016-11-17","Department of Health","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which body is responsible for centrally monitoring the effectiveness of (a) local suicide prevention plans and (b) local multi-agency suicide prevention groups in England.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52838","52838"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636219","2016-11-17","Department of Health","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, (a) how many and (b) what proportion of accident and emergency departments in England have 24-hour access to a mental health liaison service.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52839","52839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636220","2016-11-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many social security claims in England were terminated because the individual in receipt of the benefits took their own life in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52840","52840"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636221","2016-11-17","Department of Health","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidance his Department issues on which agencies within local authorities should have responsibility for overall leadership of local suicide prevention plans.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52842","52842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636222","2016-11-16","Department of Health","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 11 October 2016 to Question 46460, who the members of the Cardiovascular Disease expert forum are; and how regularly that forum meets.","Biography information for Mr Graham Allen","Mr Graham Allen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52854","52854"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636223","2016-11-16","Department of Health","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the estimated cost implications are of the proposed closure of congenital heart disease services at Royal Brompton Hospital, including (a) the cost of expanding provision elsewhere and (b) transferring staff and services.","Biography information for Mark Field","Mark Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52860","52860"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636224","2016-11-16","Department of Health","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to item 7 of the substantive hearing of the Conduct and Competence Committee at the Nursing and Midwifery Council of 13 and 14 September 2016 on Pauline Cafferkey that found that the evidence indicates that PHE Screening staff were not properly prepared to receive so many travellers from at risk countries, whether he has made an assessment of the implications for his policies of that finding; and what steps he plans to take to ensure health screening of such travellers is adequately planned for and resourced in future.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 528601","528601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636225","2016-11-16","Department of Health","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 13 July 2016 to Question 42224, what the remit of the Cardiovascular Disease collaborative group is; and how regularly that group meets.","Biography information for Mr Graham Allen","Mr Graham Allen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52855","52855"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636226","2016-11-16","Department of Health","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 11 October 2016 to Question 46460, what the stroke-specific aims and objectives of the Cardiovascular Disease expert forum are.","Biography information for Mr Graham Allen","Mr Graham Allen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52853","52853"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636227","2016-11-16","Department of Health","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many paediatric intensive care unit beds there are in central London; and how many of those beds are at the Royal Brompton Hospital.","Biography information for Mark Field","Mark Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52859","52859"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636228","2016-11-16","Department of Health","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the proportion of NHS trusts which were in financial deficit in each of the last six years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52867","52867"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636229","2016-11-16","Department of Health","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average waiting time is for people accessing psychological and specialist neuropsychological assessments for the diagnosis of dementia.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52868","52868"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636230","2016-11-16","Department of Health","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he plans to take to ensure families and carers are fully involved in the planning of care for the people experiencing dementia.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52869","52869"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636231","2016-11-17","Department of Health","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans his Department has to publish the draft sustainability and transformation plan for Croydon.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52879","52879"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636232","2016-11-16","Home Office","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions Ministers of her Department have had with Leicestershire County Council on the level of central government grant funding required per unaccompanied asylum seeking child to fully cover all costs incurred by that council since the inception of the unaccompanied asylum seeking children scheme.","Biography information for Edward Argar","Edward Argar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52857","52857"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636233","2016-11-16","Home Office","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions Ministers of her Department have had with Leicestershire County Council on its participation in the unaccompanied asylum seeking children scheme since that council announced its intention to withdraw from that scheme in October 2016.","Biography information for Edward Argar","Edward Argar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52858","52858"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636234","2016-11-16","Home Office","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Answer of 15 April 2016 to Question 34251, how many decisions on international protection her Department made from 1 April 2016 to 30 September 2016 with further submissions lodged under rule 353 of the Immigration Rules in respect of (a) grants on protection grounds, (b) grants on non-protection grounds, (c) decisions to treat as a fresh claim and then refused, (d) further submissions refused, (e) further submissions rejected as not in correct format or (f) further submissions withdrawn before any decision made.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52829","52829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636235","2016-11-16","Home Office","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will list the documents that her Department considered prior to her decision not to pursue an inquiry into alleged South Yorkshire police malpractice at Orgreave in 1984.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52830","52830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636236","2016-11-17","Home Office","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what decisions her Department has taken on extending compass asylum accommodation contracts; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52872","52872"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636237","2016-11-17","Home Office","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many Afghan nationals living in the UK who worked as interpreters in Afghanistan for UK forces have had their asylum application rejected by her Department in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52873","52873"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636238","2016-11-16","Home Office","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department has made an assessment of the potential merits of establishing an independent inquiry into alleged police malpractice in Scotland and Wales during the 1984-85 Miners' Strike.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52820","52820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636239","2016-11-16","Home Office","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department assessed the evidence held by South Yorkshire Police on its operations at Orgreave during the Miners' Strike in 1984 before making a decision on whether to hold an inquiry into events at Orgreave.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52817","52817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636240","2016-11-16","Home Office","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 11 November 2016 to Question 50781, on asylum: young people, for what reasons the planned trial of the use of voluntary dental x-rays did not go ahead in 2012.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52848","52848"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636241","2016-11-16","Home Office","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to her oral statement on Calais of 24 October 2016, Official Report, columns 64-5, if she will take steps to put in place a new joint agreement with France on tackling (a) people trafficking and (b) violence against refugees in the areas to which refugees have been dispersed since the closure of the Calais camp.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52849","52849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636242","2016-11-16","Home Office","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many ePassport gates were not in operation at any time on 12 November 2016 at (a) Heathrow, (b) Gatwick, (c) Stansted and (d) Luton Airports.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52788","52788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636243","2016-11-16","Home Office","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department has provided guidance to the Independent Inquiry into Child Sex Abuse on supporting victims of historic child sex abuse in evidence gathering sessions.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52794","52794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636244","2016-11-16","Home Office","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, on how many occasions the Disclosure and Barring Service used information from the European Criminal Records Information System to make checks on people applying to work with (a) adults and (b) children since 2012.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52810","52810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636245","2016-11-16","Home Office","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) Dutch and (b) Latvian nationals applying to work with (i) adults and (ii) children failed the enhanced Disclosure and Barring Service checks during the EU check pilot that ran from November 2015 to April 2016.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52811","52811"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636246","2016-11-16","Home Office","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will use her powers under subsections 6 to 8 of section 166 of the Criminal Justice and Public Order Act 1994 to outlaw ticket touting for (a) events related to Hull City of Culture 2017, (b) musical events and (c) cultural events.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52806","52806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636247","2016-11-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of introducing (a) guidance on and (b) legislative proposals for making mandatory noiseless fireworks at major public events in the interests of the safety of (i) live stock animals and (ii) people with post-traumatic stress syndrome.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52732","52732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636248","2016-11-17","Home Office","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people who have applied under the statelessness determination procedure have not yet received a decision; and how many such people have waited over (a) six months, (b) a year, (c) two years and (d) three years from their application.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52758","52758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636249","2016-11-17","Home Office","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people who have applied under the statelessness determination procedure since it was established in 2013 have received a decision (a) in total, (b) between six months and a year after their application, (c) between one and two years after their application, (d) between two and three years after their application and (e) more than three years after their application.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52759","52759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636250","2016-11-16","Home Office","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many visit visa applications from Pakistan for applicants wishing to visit the UK were (a) made, (b) accepted and (c) refused in (i) 2012, (ii) 2013, (iii) 2014 and (iv) 2015.","Biography information for Naz Shah","Naz Shah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52752","52752"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636251","2016-11-16","Home Office","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much compensation her Department paid due to errors made on applications for (a) indefinite leave to remain, (b) limited leave to remain, (c) marriage visas and (d) visit visas in (i) 2012, (ii) 2013, (iii) 2014 and (iv) 2015.","Biography information for Naz Shah","Naz Shah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52753","52753"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636252","2016-11-17","Department for International Development","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of her Department's progress on tackling malaria in developing countries.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52764","52764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636253","2016-11-17","Department for International Development","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much Government overseas development assistance expenditure is spent directly or indirectly on low-fee, for profit private schools in (a) Nigeria, (b) Pakistan, (c) Kenya and (d) Uganda.","Biography information for Mr Mark Williams","Mr Mark Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52765","52765"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636254","2016-11-17","Department for International Development","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she has taken to respond to the recent recommendations by the UN Committee on the Rights of the Child on privatisation and the right to education.","Biography information for Mr Mark Williams","Mr Mark Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52766","52766"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636255","2016-11-17","Department for International Development","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, when her Department plans to publish a new global education strategy setting out how the UK will help to meet Sustainable Development Goal 4.","Biography information for Mr Mark Williams","Mr Mark Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52767","52767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636256","2016-11-16","Department for International Development","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she has taken to ensure that her Department's education spending delivers the best learning outcomes.","Biography information for Mr Mark Williams","Mr Mark Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52755","52755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636257","2016-11-17","Department for International Development","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what discussions she has had with her counterpart in Ukraine on assistance for internally displaced people in that country.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52738","52738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636258","2016-11-17","Department for International Development","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the effect of direct or indirect Government overseas development assistance expenditure on low-fee, for profit private schools on the performance of those schools.","Biography information for Mr Mark Williams","Mr Mark Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52843","52843"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636259","2016-11-17","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what her Department's policy is on the future availability of legal aid funding for inquests.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52763","52763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636260","2016-11-16","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether supervision for an offender who is subject to two or more community orders or parole licences in the same or different areas is undertaken by one or more offender managers.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52789","52789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636261","2016-11-16","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether the contents or findings of a Serious Further Offence review involving probation services in England and Wales are (a) given to or (b) discussed with the victim or victim's family; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52791","52791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636262","2016-11-16","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether the number of offenders who have breached and subsequently not completed their community orders affects level payments made by the Department to the company responsible for those orders.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52790","52790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636263","2016-11-16","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what information her Department holds on whether any community rehabilitation companies in England or Wales are using or plan to use virtual supervision in undertaking the supervision of offenders.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52792","52792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636264","2016-11-16","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if she will investigate the failure of the prisoner transport constructor GeoAmey to deliver three defendants to Plymouth Crown Court on 28 October 2016; and what the cost to the public purse was of that failure.","Biography information for Mr Geoffrey Cox","Mr Geoffrey Cox","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52734","52734"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636265","2016-11-17","Northern Ireland Office","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what estimate he has made of the potential effect on funding for the Police Service of Northern Ireland to 2023 of the Northern Ireland Executive's plan to remove all peace walls in Northern Ireland by that date.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52740","52740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636266","2016-11-17","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many police cautions have been issued for offences of (a) rape, (b) sexual assault, (c) robbery and (d) burglary in each (i) year between 2014 and 2016 and (ii) month since January 2016.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52874","52874"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636267","2016-11-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many UK citizens have been charged with sexual abuse against children by jurisdictions outside the UK in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52875","52875"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636268","2016-11-17","Northern Ireland Office","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what discussions he has had with the Northern Ireland Executive on its plans to remove all peace walls in Northern Ireland by 2023.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52739","52739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636269","2016-11-16","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what contingency planning the Government has undertaken on the role of the three devolved national parliaments in voting to trigger the Article 50 process.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52828","52828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636270","2016-11-17","Scotland Office","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what progress has been made on the Edinburgh and South East Scotland City Region Deal; when he expects that deal to be concluded; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52844","52844"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636271","2016-11-16","Scotland Office","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, if he will meet representatives of the Women Against State Pension Inequality campaign.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52856","52856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636272","2016-11-17","Department for Transport","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the comments by the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Transport to the Transport Select Committee on 7 November 2016, Question 347, that he was looking at making in-franchise charges to existing rail franchises, whether he has made an assessment of the potential merits of introducing DelayRepay on all rail franchises via in-franchise changes rather than waiting for the commencement of the next round of the franchises.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52881","52881"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636273","2016-11-16","Department for Transport","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much steel is expected to be used in the High Speed 2 project; how much of that steel is expected to be British steel; what the value of that steel is expected to be; and how much of that steel has been ordered.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52863","52863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636274","2016-11-16","Department for Transport","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he plans to amend the Road Vehicles (Construction and Use) Regulations 1986 to proscribe the use of blue coloured decorative lights on HGV vehicles.","Biography information for Christian Matheson","Christian Matheson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52862","52862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636275","2016-11-17","Department for Transport","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 14 November 2016 to Question 52466, at which stations the additional staff paid for by the Rail Reparation Fund have been based.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52882","52882"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636276","2016-11-17","Department for Transport","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect of the non-availability of conductors or guards on train service delays.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52837","52837"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636277","2016-11-17","Department for Transport","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many full-time equivalent civil servants employed by his Department work in support of the West Midlands Combined Authority; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52836","52836"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636278","2016-11-17","Department for Transport","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many vehicles of which type were used by the Government Car Service for each year from 2011-12; how many vehicles of which type were allocated for the use of each (a) Minister and (b) Department for each year from 2006-07; for those Departments which have their own car pool, for how long that arrangement has been in place; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52846","52846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636279","2016-11-17","Department for Transport","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he has had discussions with the Chancellor of the Exchequer on waiving stamp duty for private residents choosing to relocate away from Heathrow Airport after the construction of a third runway.","Biography information for Dr Tania Mathias","Dr Tania Mathias","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52813","52813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636280","2016-11-17","Department for Transport","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what proportion of claims of force majeure made by Govia Thameslink Rail are related to (a) official industrial and (b) unofficial action.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52776","52776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636281","2016-11-16","Department for Transport","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of establishing an Independent Aviation Noise Authority.","Biography information for George Kerevan","George Kerevan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52805","52805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636282","2016-11-16","Department for Transport","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans he has to issue a consultation on night noise and night flying restrictions at Heathrow, Gatwick and Stansted Airports.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52730","52730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636283","2016-11-17","Department for Transport","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many Govia Thameslink Railway trains have been short formed in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52736","52736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636284","2016-11-17","Department for Transport","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what reasons Govia Thameslink Railway has given to his Department for short train formations in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52737","52737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636285","2016-11-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what discussions he has had with the Department for Communities and Local Government on the potential effect of forthcoming changes to support for housing costs for (a) people under 35 living in social housing and (b) 18 to 21 year olds on the Government's homelessness prevention agenda.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52757","52757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636286","2016-11-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the budget is for DWP Digital for financial year 2016-17.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52768","52768"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636287","2016-11-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many working households in (a) Ashfield constituency, (b) the East Midlands and (c) the UK were classed as being in poverty in the most recent year for which data is available and in each of the two previous years.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52760","52760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636288","2016-11-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many working households in (a) Ashfield constituency, (b) the East Midlands and (c) the UK were in receipt of housing benefit in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52762","52762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636289","2016-11-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what guidance he has provided to local authorities on allocating discretionary housing payments to claimants accommodated within domestic violence refuges who have been notified that their benefit entitlement will reduce as a result of changes to the benefit cap.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52802","52802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636290","2016-11-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the recent reduction in the benefit cap on the time taken for specialist domestic abuse refuges to secure move-on accommodation for claimants whose benefit entitlements will decrease.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52803","52803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636291","2016-11-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the recent reduction in the benefit cap on the affordability of housing for claimants who have recently left refuge or temporary accommodation in the (a) social rented sector and (b) private rented sector.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52804","52804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636292","2016-11-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate his Department has made of the number of households to be affected in Ashfield constituency by the introduction of the lower cap on the amount which working households are entitled to receive in benefits.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52845","52845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636293","2016-11-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment he has made of the potential causal link between social security sanctions and the deaths of vulnerable claimants.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52819","52819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636294","2016-11-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate she has made of the potential cost to the UK economy of a changing climate over the next 20 years; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52824","52824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636295","2016-11-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will make an assessment of the implications for his Department's policies in England of the conclusions of the report of Health Protection Scotland, entitled A Health Impact Assessment of Unconventional Oil and Gas in Scotland, published on 8 November 2016.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52814","52814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636296","2016-11-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the remaining potential carbon emission savings from residential buildings.","Biography information for Peter Aldous","Peter Aldous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52751","52751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636297","2016-11-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of progress on the Wolstenholme review of cash retentions in the construction industry; when he expects that review to be completed; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52756","52756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636298","2016-11-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what plans the Government has to increase the uptake of energy efficiency measures in non-fuel poor households.","Biography information for Peter Aldous","Peter Aldous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52744","52744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636299","2016-11-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether the Government plans to introduce minimum performance regulation to increase the energy efficiency of housing stock.","Biography information for Peter Aldous","Peter Aldous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52745","52745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636300","2016-11-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will ensure that a public consultation is conducted with groups representing mesothelioma victims and other relevant stakeholders before decisions are made about changing current policies and protocols for retaining records on dissolved companies by Companies House.","Biography information for Martin Docherty-Hughes","Martin Docherty-Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52746","52746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636301","2016-11-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will ensure that there is no further destruction of records on dissolved companies held by Companies House before a public consultation is held with relevant stakeholders about changes to current policies and protocols for retaining data.","Biography information for Martin Docherty-Hughes","Martin Docherty-Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52747","52747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636302","2016-11-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will publish the criteria currently used by Companies House when deciding whether to retain or destroy records held of dissolved companies.","Biography information for Martin Docherty-Hughes","Martin Docherty-Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52748","52748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636303","2016-11-16","Department for International Trade","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what proportion of trade in Welsh goods and services was undertaken on a tariff-free basis in accordance with free-trade agreements negotiated through the EU in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52793","52793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636304","2016-11-17","Department for International Trade","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether Ministers or officials of his Department have had discussions with Nigel Farage MEP or his representatives on the UK's international trade policy in the last three months.","Biography information for Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52783","52783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636305","2016-11-17","Department for International Trade","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, which Ministers or officials of his Department plan to speak or meet with Nigel Farage MEP or his representatives to discuss the UK's international trade policy.","Biography information for Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52782","52782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636306","2016-11-17","Department for International Trade","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether he plans to oppose the EU decision in the event that the EU grants Generalised System of Preferences Plus status to trade between the EU and Sri Lanka; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52885","52885"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636307","2016-11-16","Department for International Trade","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, with reference to Airbus Group's press release, entitled Airbus Group announcement on UK Export Credit Financing, published on 1 April 2016, if UK Export Finance will take steps to review its anti-corruption procedures to take account of the findings by Airbus that there were inaccuracies relating to applications for export credit financing for Airbus customers.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52852","52852"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636308","2016-11-17","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what estimate he has made of the total expenditure by his Department on dedicated legal support pertaining to the court case R (Miller) v the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, relating to Article 50.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52878","52878"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/636309","2016-11-16","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, if he will publish Britain's net contribution to the EU budget by NUTS 1 region for the latest fiscal year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52850","52850"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/637205","2016-11-17","Department for Transport","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the economic implications of the recent announcement on airport capacity for the North West.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 907303","907303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638216","2016-11-17","Department for Transport","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of trends in the level of Government investment in the road network.","Biography information for Chris Davies","Chris Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 907310","907310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638217","2016-11-17","Department for Transport","2016-11-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he has had discussions with the Chancellor of the Exchequer on provision for alternative fuels.","Biography information for Callum McCaig","Callum McCaig","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 907312","907312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/634006","2016-11-15","Attorney General","2016-11-11","To ask the Attorney General, what meetings he has had with ministerial colleagues to discuss the Serious Fraud Office's investigation of Rolls Royce.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52516","52516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/634007","2016-11-15","Cabinet Office","2016-11-11","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, which five government departments in (a) poll number and (b) cost terms make most use of opinion poll companies; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52549","52549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/634008","2016-11-15","Cabinet Office","2016-11-11","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many deaths were caused by alcoholic liver disease in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52573","52573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/634009","2016-11-16","Cabinet Office","2016-11-11","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what proportion of women are employed by his Department on non-London pay structures in the following pay grades (a) Administrative Assistant, (b) Administrative Officer, (c) Executive Officer, (d) Higher Executive Officer, (e) Fast Streamer, (f) Senior Executive Officer, (g) Grade Seven, (h) Grade Six, (i) Senior Civil Service Band 1, (j) Senior Civil Service Band 1A, (k) Senior Civil Service Band 2 and (l) Senior Civil Service Band 3.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52632","52632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/634010","2016-11-15","Cabinet Office","2016-11-11","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much the Cabinet Office has spent on purchasing vellum in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52698","52698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/634011","2016-11-15","HM Treasury","2016-11-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the Government's strategy is for reducing the tax gap on import taxes, levies and VAT.","Biography information for Charlie Elphicke","Charlie Elphicke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52708","52708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/634012","2016-11-15","HM Treasury","2016-11-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the tax gap for import duties.","Biography information for Charlie Elphicke","Charlie Elphicke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52709","52709"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/634013","2016-11-15","HM Treasury","2016-11-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the tax gap for customs duties on goods imported from outside the EU.","Biography information for Charlie Elphicke","Charlie Elphicke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52710","52710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/634014","2016-11-15","HM Treasury","2016-11-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether there is a memorandum of understanding or other form of agreement between HM Revenue and Customs and the Home Office for securing the collection of and compliance with import taxation.","Biography information for Charlie Elphicke","Charlie Elphicke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52712","52712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/634015","2016-11-15","HM Treasury","2016-11-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what progress has been made on the replacement of the Customs CHIEF system; and when that replacement is expected to be introduced.","Biography information for Charlie Elphicke","Charlie Elphicke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52711","52711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/634016","2016-11-17","HM Treasury","2016-11-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment the Government has made of the effect of the relative devaluation of the pound on the UK's wine industry.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52727","52727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/634017","2016-11-17","HM Treasury","2016-11-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the forecast rise in inflation on the Government's projections for wine duty income over the next five years.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52729","52729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/634018","2016-11-24","HM Treasury","2016-11-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what reciprocal arrangements are in place to allow UK citizens who have worked in Australia to import the pension contributions that they paid while working abroad.","Biography information for Kevin Foster","Kevin Foster","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52643","52643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/634019","2016-11-15","HM Treasury","2016-11-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate his Department has made of the tax gap for import VAT.","Biography information for Charlie Elphicke","Charlie Elphicke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52700","52700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/634020","2016-11-15","HM Treasury","2016-11-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he plans to publish draft legislation on introducing a minimum tobacco tax to tackle the growth of cheaper cigarettes and protect revenues.","Biography information for Simon Hart","Simon Hart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52612","52612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/634021","2016-11-15","Church Commissioners","2016-11-11","To ask the right hon. Member for Meriden, representing the Church Commissioners, what the timetable is for the exchange of contracts on the sale of Phase 2 of the Paston Reserve residential site in Peterborough; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stewart Jackson","Mr Stewart Jackson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52646","52646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/634022","2016-11-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-11-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to prevent developers from making repeat applications to build on land unfit for development.","Biography information for Sir Hugo Swire","Sir Hugo Swire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52635","52635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/634023","2016-11-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-11-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much processing unsuccessful planning applications has cost local authorities in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sir Hugo Swire","Sir Hugo Swire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52636","52636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/634024","2016-11-16","Home Office","2016-11-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when the Government plans to publish the National Statement of Expectations to provide a framework for the local commissioning of services relating to violence against women and girls.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52629","52629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/634025","2016-11-15","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-11-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what support his Department makes available for renewal for coastal towns with a significant tourism industry.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52693","52693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/634026","2016-11-15","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-11-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what role the Government plans that local government will play in the negotiations on the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52705","52705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/634027","2016-11-15","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-11-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the Institute for Public Research report on Roma communities and Brexit: integrating and empowering Roma communities in the UK, published on 24 October 2016.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52675","52675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/634028","2016-11-15","Department of Health","2016-11-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of the future level of demand for social care; and what steps he is taking to ensure that that level of demand can be met.","Biography information for Teresa Pearce","Teresa Pearce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52670","52670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/634029","2016-11-15","Department of Health","2016-11-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of the effect of the funding gap in social care on the adequate provision of appropriate social care.","Biography information for Teresa Pearce","Teresa Pearce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52671","52671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/634030","2016-11-15","Department of Health","2016-11-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the UK leaving the EU on the number of social care workers over the next five years.","Biography information for Teresa Pearce","Teresa Pearce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52672","52672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/634031","2016-11-15","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-11-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, by which formula the £150 million transition grant was allocated to local authorities; and what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of that grant in achieving its aims.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52707","52707"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/634032","2016-11-15","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-11-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, which local authorities have agreed to be part of the Syrian Resettlement Programme.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52691","52691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/634033","2016-11-15","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-11-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, which local authorities (a) have and (b) have not made applications for a multi-year financial settlement.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52692","52692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/634034","2016-11-15","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-11-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what his Department's policy is on establishing new city region mayors after May 2017.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52503","52503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/634035","2016-11-15","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-11-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what information local authorities are required to hold on tenants of their properties who receive assistance under the cavity insulation guarantee scheme.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52521","52521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/634036","2016-11-16","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-11-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps the Government takes to monitor how BT complies with Ofcom regulations in maintaining public telephone boxes and ensuring that those telephone boxes remain operational.","Biography information for Dr Alasdair McDonnell","Dr Alasdair McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52533","52533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/634037","2016-11-15","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-11-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what progress has been made on the roll-out of superfast broadband in (a) Enfield North constituency and (b) the London Borough of Enfield.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52544","52544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/634038","2016-11-16","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-11-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many National Citizen Service 2015 graduates were eligible for free school meals.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52581","52581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/634039","2016-11-16","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-11-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment her Department has made of the potential economic effects on the North of England of increased inbound tourism as a result of Heathrow Airport expansion.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52624","52624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/634040","2016-11-16","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many civilian jobs will be attached to Leuchars on completion of the Better Defence Estate review, published in November 2016.","Biography information for Owen Thompson","Owen Thompson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52660","52660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/634041","2016-11-16","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many service personnel will be based at Leuchars on completion of the Better Defence Estate review, published in November 2016.","Biography information for Owen Thompson","Owen Thompson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52659","52659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/634042","2016-11-15","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will provide a breakdown of the £20.8 million paid to Red Snapper since 2013.","Biography information for Sir Henry Bellingham","Sir Henry Bellingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52665","52665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/634043","2016-11-15","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether Red Snapper has received any additional payments from his Department for travel or accommodation expenses.","Biography information for Sir Henry Bellingham","Sir Henry Bellingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52666","52666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/634044","2016-11-16","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what projections he has made of the size of the (a) Army, (b) Royal Navy and (c) Royal Air Force in 2017-18.","Biography information for Wayne David","Wayne David","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52661","52661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/634045","2016-11-15","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Written Statement of 8 November 2016, WS 246, on which date Ministers of his Department were informed of the shortfall in funding for the Armed Forces Pension Scheme.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52701","52701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/634046","2016-11-15","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much from the public purse has been claimed by the 127 investigators recruited by Red Snapper to date.","Biography information for Sir Henry Bellingham","Sir Henry Bellingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52667","52667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/634047","2016-11-15","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much from the public purse has been paid by the 127 investigators recruited by Red Snapper to date.","Biography information for Sir Henry Bellingham","Sir Henry Bellingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52668","52668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/634048","2016-11-15","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many recruiters at Red Snapper are employed under the contract awarded by the Iraq Historic Allegations Team.","Biography information for Sir Henry Bellingham","Sir Henry Bellingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52669","52669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/634049","2016-11-15","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Written Statement of 8 November 2016, WS 249, whether the error referred to in that Statement has led to shortfalls in funding for other services provided by his Department.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52702","52702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/634050","2016-11-15","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department's recent shortfall in funding for the Armed Forces Pension Scheme (AFPS) has prohibited AFPS recipients from drawing on their pension.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 52703","52703"
