"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9279","2013-06-10","Department for Transport","2013-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether in its negotiations on the European Commission's Fourth Railway Package, his Department will seek to ensure that alliances and other forms of joint working between Network Rail and train operators are not prohibited or unduly restricted by EU legislation.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158988","158988"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9280","2013-06-10","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if her Department will carry out an assessment of the performance of the Suffolk Libraries Industrial and Provident Society.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158989","158989"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/93","2013-06-10","Ministry of Defence","2013-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent discussions he has had with his German counterpart on whether intelligence supplied by the UK will be used for drone strikes by Germany.","Biography information for Anas Sarwar","Anas Sarwar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158939","158939"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9389","2013-06-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many people were attacked by each breed of dog in each of the last five years for which figures are available; and what recent consideration his Department has given to expanding the register of prohibited dogs.","Biography information for Sir Graham Brady","Mr Graham Brady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158845","158845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9749","2013-06-10","Home Office","2013-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Answer of 15 November 2010, Official Report, column 549W, on drugs, what progress she has made in producing the evaluation framework to support assessments of the new drugs strategy.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158934","158934"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9866","2013-06-10","Department for Education","2013-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will take steps to prohibit the imposition of gagging orders on headteachers who leave their jobs when their school is required to become an academy.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158928","158928"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10142","2013-06-06","Ministry of Defence","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what progress has been made with the development of technology to allow radar to function effectively with wind turbines in line of sight situations; what plans he has to roll out such technology; and when he anticipates the installations of such technology in the Hebrides Range.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Mr Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158699","158699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10143","2013-06-06","Ministry of Defence","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what guidance his Department gives on wind turbine applications.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Mr Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158696","158696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10144","2013-06-06","Ministry of Defence","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the operation of the radar at Rangehead is for test facility or for national security.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Mr Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158697","158697"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10154","2013-06-06","Ministry of Defence","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the effects on the radar at Cletraval, Uist, of small domestic turbines in the machair.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Mr Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158698","158698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10155","2013-06-06","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps she has taken to encourage the sharing of mobile telephone mast sites between mobile network operators; and to what extent such sharing will be promoted in rural and island areas in the forthcoming review of the Electronic Communications Code.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Mr Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158787","158787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10234","2013-06-10","Department for Education","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what agreements he has signed setting up Academy schools in North Tyneside since May 2010.","Biography information for Sir Alan Campbell","Mr Alan Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158574","158574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10235","2013-06-10","Department for Education","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when he intends to sign-off the agreement setting up the Kings Priory Academy.","Biography information for Sir Alan Campbell","Mr Alan Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158573","158573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10358","2013-06-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many learners aged 19 to 23 years old achieved a Level 3 qualificaiton through their statutory entitlement to a fully funded first full level 3 qualification in academic year (a) 2009-10, (b) 2010-11 and (c) 2011-12.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158801","158801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10359","2013-06-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many learners aged 24 years and over achieved Level 2 qualifications in academic year (a) 2009-10, (b) 2010-11 and (c) 2011-12.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158802","158802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10360","2013-06-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many learners aged 19 to 24 years old achieved Level 2 qualifications through their statutory entitlement to a fully funded first full level 2 qualification in academic year (a) 2009-10, (b) 2010-11 and (c) 2011-12.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158803","158803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10362","2013-06-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to his Department's publication entitled, Rigour and Responsiveness in Skills, when he will confirm the appointment of the FE Commissioner.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158804","158804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10384","2013-06-06","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department is taking to encourage employers to offer industrial placements to (a) science undergraduates and (b) chemistry undergraduates.","Biography information for Graham Evans","Graham Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158554","158554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10385","2013-06-06","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what consideration he has given to extending the chemistry initial teacher training scholarship scheme to primary school initial teacher training.","Biography information for Graham Evans","Graham Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158555","158555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10386","2013-06-06","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to (a) ensure the future skills needs of Science, Technology, Engineering and Mathematics (STEM) based industries are met and (b) ensure graduates in STEM subjects are equipped with the skills employers need.","Biography information for Graham Evans","Graham Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158556","158556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10592","2013-06-06","Ministry of Justice","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, on how many occasions each prison reception in the UK has had to remain open due to the late arrival of offenders from courts in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame M. Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158454","158454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10595","2013-06-06","Ministry of Justice","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what value of fines have been paid under each privately-operated prisoner escort contract in each of the last 12 months; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame M. Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158448","158448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10596","2013-06-06","Ministry of Justice","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what fines can be levied against  each privately-operated prisoner escort contract for (a) late delivery to court of offenders and (b) late delivery of offenders at prison establishments; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame M. Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158449","158449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10869","2013-06-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the 20 highest amounts paid for external legal advice by his Department were in (a) 2010, (b) 2011 and (c) 2012; to whom such payments were paid; and for what reasons the legal advice was sought.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158617","158617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10870","2013-06-06","Cabinet Office","2013-06-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much the Deputy Prime Minister's Office spent on external legal advice from Queen's Counsel (a) between 7 May 2010 and 4 September 2012 and (b) since 4 September 2012.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158636","158636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10871","2013-06-06","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the highest day rate paid for external legal advice by his Department since 7 May 2010 was.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158673","158673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10872","2013-06-06","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the 20 highest amounts paid for external legal advice by his Department were in (a) 2010, (b) 2011 and (c) 2012; to whom such sums were paid; and for what reasons the legal advice was sought.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158631","158631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10873","2013-06-06","Speaker's Committee for Independent Parliamentary Standards Authority","2013-06-04","To ask the hon. Member for Broxbourne, representing the Speaker's Committee for the Independent Parliamentary Standards Authority, how much the Independent Parliamentary Standards Authority has spent on external legal advice (a) between 7 May 2010 and 4 September 2012 and (b) since 4 September 2012.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158705","158705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10874","2013-06-06","Speaker's Committee on the Electorial Commission","2013-06-04","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, how much the Electoral Commission has spent on external legal advice (a) between 7 May 2010 and 4 September 2012 and (b) since 4 September 2012.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158706","158706"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10875","2013-06-06","Public Accounts Commission","2013-06-04","To ask the Chairman of the Public Accounts Commission, how much the Public Accounts Commission has spent on external legal advice (a) between 7 May 2010 and 4 September 2012 and (b) since 4 September 2012.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158707","158707"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10876","2013-06-06","Speaker's Committee for Independent Parliamentary Standards Authority","2013-06-04","To ask the hon. Member for Broxbourne, representing the Speaker's Committee for the Independent Parliamentary Standards Authority, how much the Independent Parliamentary Standards Authority has spent on external legal advice from Queen's Counsel (a) between 7 May 2010 and 4 September 2012 and (b) since 4 September 2012.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158708","158708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10877","2013-06-06","Speaker's Committee on the Electorial Commission","2013-06-04","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, how much the Electoral Commission has spent on external legal advice from Queen's Counsel (a) between 7 May 2010 and 4 September 2012 and (b) since 4 September 2012.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158709","158709"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10878","2013-06-06","Public Accounts Commission","2013-06-04","To ask the Chairman of the Public Accounts Commission, how much the Public Accounts Commission has spent on external legal advice from Queen's Counsels (a) between 7 May 2010 and 4 September 2012 and (b) since 4 September 2012.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158710","158710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10879","2013-06-06","Speaker's Committee for Independent Parliamentary Standards Authority","2013-06-04","To ask the hon. Member for Broxbourne, representing the Speaker's Committee for the Independent Parliamentary Standards Authority, what the highest day rate paid for external legal advice by the Independent Parliamentary Standards Authority since 7 May 2010 has been.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158711","158711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10880","2013-06-06","Speaker's Committee on the Electorial Commission","2013-06-04","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what the highest day rate paid for external legal advice by the Electoral Commission since 7 May 2010 has been.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158712","158712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10881","2013-06-06","Public Accounts Commission","2013-06-04","To ask the Chairman of the Public Accounts Commission, what the highest day rate paid for external legal advice by the Public Accounts Commission since 7 May 2010 has been.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158713","158713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10882","2013-06-06","Speaker's Committee for Independent Parliamentary Standards Authority","2013-06-04","To ask the hon. Member for Broxbourne, representing the Speaker's Committee for the Independent Parliamentary Standards Authority, what the 20 highest amounts paid for external legal advice by the Independent Parliamentary Standards Authority in (a) 2010, (b) 2011 and (c) 2012 were; to whom such payments were made; and for what reasons the legal advice was sought.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158714","158714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10883","2013-06-06","Public Accounts Commission","2013-06-04","To ask the Chairman of the Public Accounts Commission, what the 20 highest amounts paid for external legal advice by the Public Accounts Commission in (a) 2010, (b) 2011 and (c) 2012 were; to whom such payments were made; and for what reasons the legal advice was sought.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158715","158715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10884","2013-06-06","Speaker's Committee on the Electorial Commission","2013-06-04","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what the 20 highest amounts paid for external legal advice by the Electoral Commission in (a) 2010, (b) 2011 and (c) 2012 were; to whom such payments were made; and for what reasons the legal advice was sought.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158716","158716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10885","2013-06-06","Department for Education","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much his Department spent on external legal advice from Queen's Counsel (a) between 7 May 2010 and 4 September 2012 and (b) since 4 September 2012.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158637","158637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10886","2013-06-06","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how much his Department spent on external legal advice from Queen's Counsel (a) between 7 May 2010 and 4 September 2012 and (b) since 4 September 2012.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158638","158638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10887","2013-06-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much his Department spent on external legal advice from Queen's Counsel (a) between 7 May 2010 and 4 September 2012 and (b) since 4 September 2012.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158639","158639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10888","2013-06-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how much his Department spent on external legal advice from Queen's Counsel (a) between 7 May 2010 and 4 September 2012 and (b) since 4 September 2012.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158640","158640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10889","2013-06-06","Department of Health","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much his Department spent on external legal advice from Queen's Counsel (a) between 7 May 2010 and 4 September 2012 and (b) since 4 September 2012.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158642","158642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10890","2013-06-06","Cabinet Office","2013-06-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the 20 highest amounts paid for external legal advice by the Deputy Prime Minister's Office were in (a) 2010, (b) 2011 and (c) 2012; to whom such sums were paid; and for what reasons the legal advice was sought.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158629","158629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10902","2013-06-06","Cabinet Office","2013-06-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much the Deputy Prime Minister's Office spent on external legal advice (a) between 7 May 2010 and 4 September 2012 and (b) since 4 September 2012.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158654","158654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10908","2013-06-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much his Department spent on external legal advice from Queen's Counsel (a) between 7 May 2010 and 4 September 2012 and (b) since 4 September 2012.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158653","158653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10909","2013-06-06","Women and Equalities","2013-06-04","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, how much the Government Equalities Office spent on external legal advice from Queen's Counsel (a) between 7 May 2010 and 4 September 2012 and (b) since 4 September 2012.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158641","158641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10910","2013-06-06","House of Commons Commission","2013-06-04","To ask the hon. Member for Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross, representing the House of Commons Commission, how much the House of Commons Commission spent on external legal advice from Queen's Counsel (a) between 7 May 2010 and 4 September 2012 and (b) since 4 September 2012.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158644","158644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10911","2013-06-06","Cabinet Office","2013-06-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much No. 10 Downing Street spent on external legal advice from Queen's Counsel (a) between 7 May 2010 and 4 September 2012 and (b) since 4 September 2012.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158648","158648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10912","2013-06-06","Department for Education","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the highest day rate paid for external legal advice by his Department since 7 May 2010 was.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158672","158672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10913","2013-06-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the highest day rate paid for external legal advice by his Department since 7 May 2010 was.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158674","158674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10914","2013-06-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the highest day rate paid for external legal advice by his Department since 7 May 2010 was.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158675","158675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10915","2013-06-06","Department of Health","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the highest day rate paid for external legal advice by his Department since 7 May 2010 was.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158677","158677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10916","2013-06-06","Home Office","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the highest day rate paid for external legal advice by her Department since 7 May 2010 was.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158678","158678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10917","2013-06-06","Department for International Development","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what the highest day rate paid for external legal advice by her Department since 7 May 2010 was.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158680","158680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10918","2013-06-06","Northern Ireland Office","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what the highest day rate paid for external legal advice by her Department since 7 May 2010 was.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158682","158682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10919","2013-06-06","Scotland Office","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what the highest day rate paid for external legal advice by his Department since 7 May 2010 was.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158684","158684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10920","2013-06-06","Department for Transport","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the highest day rate paid for external legal advice by his Department since 7 May 2010 was.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158685","158685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10921","2013-06-06","HM Treasury","2013-06-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the highest day rate paid for external legal advice by his Department since 7 May 2010 was.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158686","158686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10922","2013-06-06","Wales Office","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what the highest day rate paid for external legal advice by his Department since 7 May 2010 was.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158687","158687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10923","2013-06-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the highest day rate paid for external legal advice by his Department since 7 May 2010 was.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158688","158688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10924","2013-06-06","Cabinet Office","2013-06-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the highest day rate paid for external legal advice by the Deputy Prime Minister's Office since 7 May 2010 was.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158671","158671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10925","2013-06-06","Women and Equalities","2013-06-04","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what the highest day rate paid for external legal advice by the Government Equalities Office since 7 May 2010 was.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158676","158676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10926","2013-06-06","House of Commons Commission","2013-06-04","To ask the hon. Member for Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross, representing the House of Commons Commission, what the highest day rate paid for external legal advice by the House of Commons Commission since 7 May 2010 was.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158679","158679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10927","2013-06-06","Cabinet Office","2013-06-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the highest day rate paid for external legal advice by No. 10 Downing Street since 7 May 2010 was.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158683","158683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10930","2013-06-06","Department for Education","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much his Department spent on external legal advice (a) between 7 May 2010 and 4 September 2012 and (b) since 4 September 2012.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158655","158655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10940","2013-06-06","Home Office","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much her Department spent on external legal advice from Queen's Counsel (a) between 7 May 2010 and 4 September 2012 and (b) since 4 September 2012.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158643","158643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10944","2013-06-06","Department for International Development","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much her Department spent on external legal advice from Queen's Counsel (a) between 7 May 2010 and 4 September 2012 and (b) since 4 September 2012.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158645","158645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10945","2013-06-06","Department for Education","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the 20 highest amounts paid for external legal advice by his Department were in (a) 2010, (b) 2011 and (c) 2012; to whom such sums were paid; and for what reasons the legal advice was sought.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158630","158630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10946","2013-06-06","Northern Ireland Office","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how much her Department spent on external legal advice from Queen's Counsel (a) between 7 May 2010 and 4 September 2012 and (b) since 4 September 2012.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158647","158647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10947","2013-06-06","Department for International Development","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what the 20 highest amounts paid for external legal advice by her Department were in (a) 2010, (b) 2011 and (c) 2012; to whom such sums were paid; and for what reasons the legal advice was sought.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158632","158632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10948","2013-06-06","Scotland Office","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how much his Department spent on external legal advice from Queen's Counsel (a) between 7 May 2010 and 4 September 2012 and (b) since 4 September 2012.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158649","158649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10949","2013-06-06","Ministry of Justice","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the 20 highest amounts paid for external legal advice by his Department were in (a) 2010, (b) 2011 and (c) 2012; to whom such sums were paid; and for what reasons the legal advice was sought.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158633","158633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10950","2013-06-06","Department for Transport","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much his Department spent on external legal advice from Queen's Counsel (a) between 7 May 2010 and 4 September 2012 and (b) since 4 September 2012.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158650","158650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10951","2013-06-06","HM Treasury","2013-06-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much his Department spent on external legal advice from Queen's Counsel (a) between 7 May 2010 and 4 September 2012 and (b) since 4 September 2012.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158651","158651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10952","2013-06-06","Wales Office","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how much his Department spent on external legal advice from Queen's Counsel (a) between 7 May 2010 and 4 September 2012 and (b) since 4 September 2012.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158652","158652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10953","2013-06-06","HM Treasury","2013-06-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the 20 highest amounts paid for external legal advice by his Department were in (a) 2010, (b) 2011 and (c) 2012; to whom such sums were paid; and for what reasons the legal advice was sought.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158635","158635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11022","2013-06-06","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how much his Department spent on external legal advice (a) between 7 May 2010 and 4 September 2012 and (b) since 4 September 2012.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158656","158656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11023","2013-06-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much his Department spent on external legal advice (a) between 7 May 2010 and 4 September 2012 and (b) since 4 September 2012.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158657","158657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11024","2013-06-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how much his Department spent on external legal advice (a) between 7 May 2010 and 4 September 2012 and (b) since 4 September 2012.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158658","158658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11025","2013-06-06","Women and Equalities","2013-06-04","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, how much the Government Equalities Office spent on external legal advice (a) between 7 May 2010 and 4 September 2012 and (b) since 4 September 2012.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158659","158659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11026","2013-06-06","Department of Health","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much his Department spent on external legal advice (a) between 7 May 2010 and 4 September 2012 and (b) since 4 September 2012.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158660","158660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11027","2013-06-06","Home Office","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much her Department spent on external legal advice (a) between 7 May 2010 and 4 September 2012 and (b) since 4 September 2012.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158661","158661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11028","2013-06-06","House of Commons Commission","2013-06-04","To ask the hon. Member for Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross, representing the House of Commons Commission, how much the House of Commons Commission spent on external legal advice (a) between 7 May 2010 and 4 September 2012 and (b) since 4 September 2012.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158662","158662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11029","2013-06-06","Department for International Development","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much her Department spent on external legal advice (a) between 7 May 2010 and 4 September 2012 and (b) since 4 September 2012.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158663","158663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11030","2013-06-06","Northern Ireland Office","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how much her Department spent on external legal advice (a) between 7 May 2010 and 4 September 2012 and (b) since 4 September 2012.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158665","158665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11031","2013-06-06","Cabinet Office","2013-06-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much No. 10 Downing Street spent on external legal advice (a) between 7 May 2010 and 4 September 2012 and (b) since 4 September 2012.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158666","158666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11032","2013-06-06","Scotland Office","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how much his Department spent on external legal advice (a) between 7 May 2010 and 4 September 2012 and (b) since 4 September 2012.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158667","158667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11033","2013-06-06","Department for Transport","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much his Department spent on external legal advice (a) between 7 May 2010 and 4 September 2012 and (b) since 4 September 2012.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158668","158668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11034","2013-06-06","HM Treasury","2013-06-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much his Department spent on external legal advice (a) between 7 May 2010 and 4 September 2012 and (b) since 4 September 2012.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158669","158669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11035","2013-06-06","Wales Office","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how much his Department spent on external legal advice (a) between 7 May 2010 and 4 September 2012 and (b) since 4 September 2012.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158670","158670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11036","2013-06-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the 20 highest amounts paid for external legal advice by his Department were in (a) 2010, (b) 2011 and (c) 2012; to whom such payments were paid; and for what reasons the legal advice was sought.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158618","158618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11037","2013-06-06","Women and Equalities","2013-06-04","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what the 20 highest amounts paid for external legal advice by the Government Equalities Office were in (a) 2010, (b) 2011 and (c) 2012; to whom such payments were paid; and for what reasons the legal advice was sought.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158619","158619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11038","2013-06-06","Department of Health","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the 20 highest amounts paid for external legal advice by his Department were in (a) 2010, (b) 2011 and (c) 2012; to whom such payments were paid; and for what reasons the legal advice was sought.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158620","158620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11039","2013-06-06","Home Office","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the 20 highest amounts paid for external legal advice by her Department were in (a) 2010, (b) 2011 and (c) 2012; to whom such payments were paid; and for what reasons the legal advice was sought.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158621","158621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11040","2013-06-06","House of Commons Commission","2013-06-04","To ask the hon. Member for Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross, representing the House of Commons Commission, what the 20 highest amounts paid for external legal advice by the House of Commons Commission were in (a) 2010, (b) 2011 and (c) 2012; to whom such payments were paid; and for what reasons the legal advice was sought.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158622","158622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11041","2013-06-06","Northern Ireland Office","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what the 20 highest amounts paid for external legal advice by her Department were in (a) 2010, (b) 2011 and (c) 2012; to whom such payments were paid; and for what reasons the legal advice was sought.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158623","158623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11042","2013-06-06","Cabinet Office","2013-06-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the 20 highest amounts paid for external legal advice by No. 10 Downing Street were in (a) 2010, (b) 2011 and (c) 2012; to whom such payments were paid; and for what reasons the legal advice was sought.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158624","158624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11043","2013-06-06","Scotland Office","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what the 20 highest amounts paid for external legal advice by his Department were in (a) 2010, (b) 2011 and (c) 2012; to whom such payments were paid; and for what reasons the legal advice was sought.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158625","158625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11044","2013-06-06","Department for Transport","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the 20 highest amounts paid for external legal advice by his Department were in (a) 2010, (b) 2011 and (c) 2012; to whom such payments were paid; and for what reasons the legal advice was sought.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158626","158626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11045","2013-06-06","Wales Office","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what the 20 highest amounts paid for external legal advice by his Department were in (a) 2010, (b) 2011 and (c) 2012; to whom such payments were paid; and for what reasons the legal advice was sought.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158627","158627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11046","2013-06-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the 20 highest amounts paid for external legal advice by his Department were in (a) 2010, (b) 2011 and (c) 2012; to whom such payments were paid; and for what reasons the legal advice was sought.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158628","158628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11319","2013-06-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether he is confident that his plan for the mutualisation of the fire service will not lead to its privatisation.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158597","158597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11374","2013-06-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will publish (a) all correspondence, (b) market research, (c) the business case and (d) the impact assessment produced by his Department in the last 12 months with regards to privatising the Land Registry.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158577","158577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11375","2013-06-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what recent discussions he has had with his ministerial counterparts on the Land Registry prototype for the provision of local land charges.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158581","158581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11378","2013-06-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what discussions he has had with (a) trades unions and (b) local authorities with regards to TUPE arrangements in the event of the privatisation of the Land Registry.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158821","158821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11379","2013-06-10","Ministry of Justice","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether he has plans to bring forward legislative proposals to amend current legislation relating to Public Sector Information Re-use and the Environmental Information regulations.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158822","158822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11380","2013-06-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what recent correspondence he has had with (a) Lord McNally and (b) other Ministers in the Ministry of Justice on the prototype of the Provision of Local Land Charges.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158823","158823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11503","2013-06-06","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent measures he has put in place to help start-up businesses survive and expand.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158741","158741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11504","2013-06-06","Department for Education","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department has taken to assist and encourage charitable organisations in educating school pupils about business and associated skills.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158742","158742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11505","2013-06-06","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department is taking to support business societies at UK universities.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158743","158743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11506","2013-06-06","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent steps he has taken to encourage entrepreneurship amongst 16 to 25 year olds.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158744","158744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11507","2013-06-06","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to encourage nations outside the EU to purchase UK-manufactured goods.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158745","158745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11508","2013-06-06","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent steps his Department has taken to encourage growth in the manufacturing sector.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158746","158746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11509","2013-06-06","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the importance of the manufacturing sector to the UK economy.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158747","158747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11510","2013-06-06","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Education on improving technological skills training in secondary schools.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158748","158748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11511","2013-06-06","Department for Transport","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent meetings (a) heand (b) Ministers in his Department have had with the Post Office to discuss the implementation of new digital technology to process driving licence applications in post offices.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158749","158749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11512","2013-06-06","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the economic effect of new cogent digital camera technology has been on smaller sub-post offices.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158750","158750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11513","2013-06-06","Ministry of Defence","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the recent Joint Warrior training exercises and their effect in preparing troops for combat; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158730","158730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11616","2013-06-06","Ministry of Defence","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the use of the Black Hornet Nano unmanned air vehicle in operations; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158731","158731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11617","2013-06-06","Ministry of Defence","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the use of Urban Warrior 5 technology in recent training exercises; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158732","158732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11618","2013-06-06","Ministry of Defence","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to ensure that his Department's new Operating Model is being implemented and the desired effects are achieved.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158733","158733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11619","2013-06-06","Ministry of Defence","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what strategic advantages the use of the Wildcat helicopter in maritime operations brings; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158735","158735"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11620","2013-06-06","Ministry of Defence","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what role the Joint Forces Command will have in ensuring robust financial management in the armed forces.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158736","158736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11621","2013-06-06","Ministry of Defence","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how the new Operating Model will affect his Department; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158737","158737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11622","2013-06-06","Ministry of Defence","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the standards of training being given by the newly commissioned Defence Explosives Ordnance Disposal, Munitions and Search Training Regiment; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158738","158738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11623","2013-06-06","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs about the potential for improving the UK's bilateral trading relationship with countries in Central America.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158739","158739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11624","2013-06-06","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the importance of improving bilateral trading relationships with the BRIC countries.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158740","158740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11733","2013-06-10","Department for International Development","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent reports she has received on the holding of free and fair elections in Zimbabwe.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158795","158795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11734","2013-06-10","Department for International Development","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will provide advice and support to the First and Deputy First Minister from Northern Ireland following their recent visit to China to ascertain the viability of establishing a bureau in China to help foster good relations and promote inward investment.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158796","158796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11805","2013-06-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has received about the case of Redha al Gasra in Bahrain; and what assessment he has made of the legal proceedings being taken against him in that country.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158540","158540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11810","2013-06-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will take steps to secure the release of Mahdi 'Issa Mahdi Abu Dheeb in Bahrain.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158544","158544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11811","2013-06-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the level of trades union freedom in Bahrain.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158545","158545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11812","2013-06-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the trial and detention of Mahdi 'Issa Mahdi Abu Dheeb in Bahrain.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158546","158546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11918","2013-06-06","Home Office","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the implications of 3D printers in the UK producing plastic firearms.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158566","158566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11919","2013-06-06","Cabinet Office","2013-06-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people are working on zero hours contracts in (a) Gillingham and Rainham constituency and (b) Medway.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158700","158700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11920","2013-06-06","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many apprenticeships commenced in each sector in (a) Gillingham and Rainham constituency and (b) Medway in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158701","158701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11947","2013-06-06","Department for Transport","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the number of passengers on trains to London from (a) Gillingham station and (b) Rainham station in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158773","158773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11973","2013-06-06","Department of Health","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what incentives he has given to health and well-being boards to encourage them to invest in drug and alcohol prevention work aimed at young people.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158528","158528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11974","2013-06-06","Home Office","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the Children's Society report into asylum support for children and young people, published in January 2013; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158539","158539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11975","2013-06-06","Department of Health","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent steps he has taken to ensure that Public Health England works with health and well-being boards to promote health awareness in young people; and what steps he is taking to monitor progress in this area.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158527","158527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11976","2013-06-06","Department of Health","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidance his Department has given to clinical commissioning groups and health and well-being boards on coordinating health commissioning for people with (a) alcohol addiction, (b) drugs addiction and (c) dual-diagnosis mental health and addiction problems.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158529","158529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11977","2013-06-06","Department for Education","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans he has to alter the school calendar and school day; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158530","158530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/12011","2013-06-06","Department of Health","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many job descriptions for directors of public health to be appointed by health and well-being boards his Department has approved to date; and how many such appointees are currently in post.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158772","158772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/121","2013-06-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the implications of recent price movements in the Consumer Price Index for (a) food and non-alcoholic beverages and (b) vegetable products for people's dietary choices.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158532","158532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14414","2013-06-06","Leader of the House","2013-06-04","To ask the Leader of the House, how much his Office spent on external legal advice from Queen's Counsels (a) between 7 May 2010 and 4 September 2012 and (b) since 4 September 2012.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158646","158646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14415","2013-06-06","Leader of the House","2013-06-04","To ask the Leader of the House, what the highest day rate paid for external legal advice by his Office since 7 May 2010 was.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158681","158681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14416","2013-06-06","Leader of the House","2013-06-04","To ask the Leader of the House, what the 20 highest amounts paid for external legal advice by his Office were in (a) 2010, (b) 2011 and (c) 2012; to whom such sums were paid; and for what reasons the legal advice was sought.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158634","158634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14417","2013-06-10","Leader of the House","2013-06-04","To ask the Leader of the House, if he will ensure that Ministers attending the Bilderberg Conference at Watford on 6-9 June make a statement to the House afterwards reporting on the proceedings and the implications for Government policy.","Biography information for Mr Michael Meacher","Mr Michael Meacher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158531","158531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/14419","2013-06-06","Leader of the House","2013-06-04","To ask the Leader of the House, how much his Office spent on external legal advice (a) between 7 May 2010 and 4 September 2012 and (b) since 4 September 2012.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158664","158664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2051","2013-06-10","Home Office","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) non-complex cases and (b) complex cases an immigration caseworker completes in an average month.","Biography information for Mr David Ward","Mr David Ward","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158824","158824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2143","2013-06-06","Ministry of Defence","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the airworthiness of the Grob 115E training aircraft; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Tobias Ellwood","Mr Tobias Ellwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158446","158446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2144","2013-06-06","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, when the UK's new fleet of nuclear power stations will come on line; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Tobias Ellwood","Mr Tobias Ellwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158451","158451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2147","2013-06-10","Department of Health","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when a decision will be made on whether NHS England will commission the auto-islet transplant procedure; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Pauline Latham","Pauline Latham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158481","158481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2148","2013-06-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received on how many Palestinian homes are currently at risk of demolition in the Occupied Palestinian Territories in (a) East Jerusalem, (b) Areas A and B and (c) Area C.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158533","158533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2149","2013-06-10","Department for Transport","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he expects HS2 Ltd to complete and publish the research it commissioned in August 2012 into the potential effect of High Speed 2 on regional economies.","Biography information for Andrea Leadsom","Andrea Leadsom","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158578","158578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2150","2013-06-10","Department of Health","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people are employed by his Department to investigate whistleblowing cases in the NHS.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158570","158570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2151","2013-06-10","Department for Transport","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he expects to reach a decision on how rolling stock for phase one of High Speed 2 will be financed.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158596","158596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2152","2013-06-06","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to ban the advertising of payday loans on television.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158690","158690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2153","2013-06-06","Home Office","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the potential consequences of withdrawing from the EU on (a) EU economic migrants residing in the UK and (b) the future of UK citizens working in other EU countries.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158691","158691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2170","2013-06-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what research, surveys, studies or data gathering on pub closures his Department has (a) commissioned and (b) subscribed to.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158613","158613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2171","2013-06-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many jobs would have been created and how much investment would have been generated by each bid to the Regional Growth Fund which has been withdrawn to date had the project gone ahead.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158614","158614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2172","2013-06-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, for which industry sectors collaborative strategic partnerships are due to be published during this Parliament; and what timetable he has set for the publication of each.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158615","158615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2174","2013-06-06","Department of Health","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much his Department has spent on (a) clinical and (b) non-clinical pensions in the NHS since 2005.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158534","158534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2175","2013-06-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will assess the strength of the evidence base for the accusations made by the Colombian government that the March for Peace, held across Colombia on 9 April 2013, had been partly organised with money from FARC; and if he will make a statement on the implications for human rights in that country, particularly freedom of association.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Love","Mr Andrew Love","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158535","158535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2176","2013-06-06","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many households in the UK were disconnected by their (a) energy and (b) gas supplier in 2010-11.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158536","158536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2177","2013-06-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the cumulative effect of Government schemes to increase house building.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158537","158537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2178","2013-06-06","Deputy Prime Minister","2013-06-04","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what his most recent estimate is of the number of unregistered voters.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158538","158538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2179","2013-06-06","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what onshore wind energy generation capacity (a) had been installed, (b) had gained planning consent and (c) was seeking planning permission on 1 June 2013.","Biography information for Chris Heaton-Harris","Chris Heaton-Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158541","158541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2180","2013-06-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many employment and support allowance claimants referred to prime contractors in the last six months have had (a) zero, (b) one, (c) two, (d) three and (e) four or more interviews.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158543","158543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2181","2013-06-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what priority has been given by his Department to women's rights in Afghanistan.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158564","158564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2182","2013-06-06","Ministry of Justice","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much was paid in legal aid fees to (a) Mr Mohammed Tayyab Khan and (b) Mr Dean Kershaw; and what the total amount paid in legal aid fees was arising from the case of Crown v Ali and Others held at Stafford Crown Court between May and September 2011.","Biography information for David Mowat","David Mowat","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158565","158565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2183","2013-06-06","Department of Health","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the Risk-Sharing Scheme (RSS) that makes disease-modifying treatments available to those with multiple sclerosis; what steps he is taking to ensure there is a review of the RSS pending publication of 10-year data; and what steps he is taking to ensure that the provision of treatment of multiple sclerosis meet its associated care, support costs and ensures that new treatments for multiple sclerosis are made available to patients.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158689","158689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2184","2013-06-06","HM Treasury","2013-06-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will estimate the cost of bringing Midland Expressway Limited into public ownership.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158702","158702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2185","2013-06-06","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many applicants to the Regional Growth Fund in the North West have received funds from the Regional Growth Fund to date; and when such payments were made.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158703","158703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2186","2013-06-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many new housing starts began in (a) Tameside Metropolitan Borough and (b) Stalybridge and Hyde constituency in 2012-13.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158704","158704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2187","2013-06-06","Cabinet Office","2013-06-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the employment rate was in (a) Paisley and Renfrewshire North constituency, (b) Scotland and (c) the UK in each year since 2007.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158719","158719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2188","2013-06-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to help unemployed people over the age of 64 years in (a) Paisley and Renfrewshire North constituency, (b) Scotland and (c) the UK return to work.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158720","158720"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2196","2013-06-10","HM Treasury","2013-06-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 3 June 2013, Official Report, column 828W, on VAT High Speed 2 (HS2) railway line, when he expects HM Revenue and Customs to make a decision on whether the HS2 project will be subject to VAT.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158594","158594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2197","2013-06-10","Department for Transport","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans his Department has to analyse the effect of premium pricing on forecast (a) passenger demand, (b) revenues and (c) benefit to cost ratios for High Speed 2; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158595","158595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2198","2013-06-06","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps the Government is taking to ensure access to free and subsidised insulation schemes for people who live in park homes as part of the Green Deal.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158552","158552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2199","2013-06-06","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 16 May 2013, Official Report, column 358W, on fracking, what plans he has to commission further studies on the volume of shale gas in place to determine a total UK shale gas resource.","Biography information for Dan Byles","Dan Byles","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158553","158553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2200","2013-06-06","Cabinet Office","2013-06-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the number of people over the age of 64 years in (a) Paisley and Renfrewshire North constituency, (b) Scotland and (c) the UK who were unemployed in each year since 2007.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158721","158721"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2201","2013-06-06","Cabinet Office","2013-06-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the number of people between 55 and 64 years in (a) Paisley and Renfrewshire North constituency, (b) Scotland and (c) the UK who were unemployed in each year since 2007.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158722","158722"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2268","2013-06-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of employment and support allowance claimants with mental illness have been referred to treatments within the NHS or with subcontractors in the last period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158762","158762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2278","2013-06-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what public monies have been allocated to supporting the Government's oil and gas strategy.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158616","158616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2284","2013-06-06","Department for Education","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when he will publish plans for the introduction of a single category of special educational need.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158761","158761"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2330","2013-06-06","Department for Education","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what data assessment his Department has made of the performance of (a) children on free school meals and (b) children not on free school meals in (i) London and (ii) other parts of the country (A) in secondary education before 2005 and (B) in primary education in 2009.","Biography information for Mr Damian Hinds","Damian Hinds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158548","158548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2331","2013-06-06","Department for Education","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of teaching appointments were made through (a) Teach First and (b) other routes in each Government office region in the last year for which information is available.","Biography information for Mr Damian Hinds","Damian Hinds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158549","158549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2332","2013-06-06","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much his Department currently spends on contracts with Capita; and how much was spent in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158457","158457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2333","2013-06-06","Attorney General","2013-06-04","To ask the Attorney General, how much the Law Officers' Departments currently spends on contracts with Capita; and how much was spent in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158458","158458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2334","2013-06-06","Cabinet Office","2013-06-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much his Department currently spends on contracts with Capita; and how much was spent in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158459","158459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2335","2013-06-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much his Department currently spends on contracts with Capita; and how much was spent in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158460","158460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2336","2013-06-06","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how much her Department currently spends on contracts with Capita; and how much was spent in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158461","158461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2337","2013-06-06","Ministry of Defence","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much his Department currently spends on contracts with Capita; and how much was spent in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158462","158462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2338","2013-06-06","Department for Education","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much his Department currently spends on contracts with Capita; and how much was spent in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158463","158463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2339","2013-06-06","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how much his Department currently spends on contracts with Capita; and how much was spent in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158464","158464"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2340","2013-06-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much his Department currently spends on contracts with Capita; and how much was spent in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158465","158465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2341","2013-06-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how much his Department currently spends on contracts with Capita; and how much was spent in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158466","158466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2342","2013-06-06","Department of Health","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much his Department currently spends on contracts with Capita; and how much was spent in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158467","158467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2343","2013-06-06","Home Office","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much her Department currently spends on contracts with Capita; and how much was spent in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158468","158468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2344","2013-06-06","Department for International Development","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much her Department currently spends on contracts with Capita; and how much was spent in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158469","158469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2345","2013-06-06","Ministry of Justice","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much his Department currently spends on contracts with Capita; and how much was spent in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158470","158470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2346","2013-06-06","Northern Ireland Office","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how much her Department currently spends on contracts with Capita; and how much was spent in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158471","158471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2347","2013-06-06","Scotland Office","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how much his Department currently spends on contracts with Capita; and how much was spent in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158472","158472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2348","2013-06-06","Department for Transport","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much his Department currently spends on contracts with Capita; and how much was spent in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158473","158473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2349","2013-06-06","HM Treasury","2013-06-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much his Department currently spends on contracts with Capita; and how much was spent in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158474","158474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2350","2013-06-06","Wales Office","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how much his Department currently spends on contracts with Capita; and how much was spent in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158475","158475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2351","2013-06-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much his Department currently spends on contracts with Capita; and how much was spent in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158476","158476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2352","2013-06-06","Department for Transport","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he plans to review the level of light dues in the remainder of this parliament.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158524","158524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2353","2013-06-06","Ministry of Defence","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many RAF recruits undertook flight training in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158525","158525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2354","2013-06-06","Northern Ireland Office","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, at how many party conferences the Parades Commission has been represented in each year since that body's creation.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158558","158558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2355","2013-06-06","Northern Ireland Office","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how much the Parades Commission has spent on attendance at political party events in Northern Ireland in each year since that body's creation.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158559","158559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2356","2013-06-06","Northern Ireland Office","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how much the Parades Commission has spent on (a) marketing and (b) press advertising in each year since its creation.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158560","158560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2357","2013-06-06","Department of Health","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what comparative assessment he has made of the (a) availability and (b) quality of fertility services in (i) Hartlepool and (ii) the North East Region; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158561","158561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2377","2013-06-06","Home Office","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when her Department will respond to Philip Alliah's letter regarding his mother Diana Adzorker's application for entry clearance.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158694","158694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2378","2013-06-06","Department for International Development","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of funding allocated to young disabled refugees from Syria in (a) Lebanon, (b) Jordan, (c) Iraq and (d) Turkey.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158717","158717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2379","2013-06-06","Department for International Development","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the work conducted by the United Nations Relief and Works Agency in supporting (a) Palestinian refugees who have not been displaced as a result of the conflict in Syria and (b) newly-displaced Palestinian refugees from Syria.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158718","158718"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2380","2013-06-06","Home Office","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when her Department will respond to the letter of Robert Kelly regarding his business partner, Shuai Feng Zhao's business visa application.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158695","158695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2389","2013-06-10","Department of Health","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his Department's policy is on remuneration in the case of the early retirement of (a) clinical staff and (b) all categories of non-clinical staff in the NHS.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158567","158567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2390","2013-06-10","Department of Health","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the policy of the Italian Government towards the classification of medical doctors as executives for the purposes of the European Working Time Directive; and whether this policy could apply to doctors working in the NHS.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158568","158568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2391","2013-06-10","Department for Transport","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, who the members of the High Speed Rail programme board are.","Biography information for Andrea Leadsom","Andrea Leadsom","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158579","158579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2423","2013-06-06","Department of Health","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to address the lack of a specialist neuromuscular care adviser and a specialist neuromuscular consultant in the West Midlands since the agreement of funding for those posts in March 2010.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158606","158606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2424","2013-06-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many enquiries have been made with regards to the Government's Help to Buy scheme in (a) Tameside Metropolitan Borough Council and (b) Stalybridge and Hyde constituency.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158607","158607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2425","2013-06-06","Ministry of Defence","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department has estimated the cost of extending the in-service life of RFA Fort Rosalie and RFA Fort Austin beyond their retirement dates of 2022 and 2021.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158609","158609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2426","2013-06-06","Ministry of Defence","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the cost was of the re-fit of RFA Fort Austin; and whether three replacement solid support ships will be in service in the early 2020s under the contract for the MARS vessels.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158612","158612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2435","2013-06-10","Department for Education","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent representations he has received on the provision of swimming in primary schools.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158569","158569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2437","2013-06-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what progress has been made in assisting the Afghan government to implement fully the law on the elimination of violence against women.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158557","158557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2438","2013-06-10","Department of Health","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what process his Department initiates when it is made aware of a whistleblowing case in the NHS.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158571","158571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2440","2013-06-10","Department of Health","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department has taken to ensure the spread and adoption of the my home life programme since the publication of the Care and Support White Paper; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158589","158589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2441","2013-06-10","Department for Transport","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will publish the report commissioned by HS2 Ltd from the companies Sinclair Knight Merz and Jacobs into the High Speed 2 modelling framework.","Biography information for Andrea Leadsom","Andrea Leadsom","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158580","158580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2459","2013-06-10","Department of Health","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 14 May 2013, Official Report, columns 159-60W, on cancer: drugs, what assessment he has made of the policy statement on selective internal radiation therapy by the Clinical Reference Group chairs and the Specialised Services Portfolio Board; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Pauline Latham","Pauline Latham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158572","158572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2460","2013-06-10","Department of Health","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much was returned to the Government by Primary Care Trusts in Merseyside before their dissolution.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158575","158575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2461","2013-06-10","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what financial and logistical support she intends to offer Liverpool City Council for the centenary anniversary of World War I.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158576","158576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2467","2013-06-10","Department for International Development","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what latest assessment she has made of and what aid the UK is supplying to the humanitarian situation in Syria in response to that situation.","Biography information for Lindsay Roy","Lindsay Roy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158587","158587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2481","2013-06-06","Ministry of Defence","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he expects the Grob 115E tutor trainer aircraft to be back in service; and what the effect of its grounding has been on the RAF's ability to train new pilots.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158526","158526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2491","2013-06-06","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will increase the scope of the pilot TradeUK credit scheme so that it can offer credit to a wider range of small and micro-businesses.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158456","158456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2492","2013-06-10","Home Office","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many asylum seekers have been granted permission to remain in the UK in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Lindsay Roy","Lindsay Roy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158478","158478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2493","2013-06-10","HM Treasury","2013-06-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to tackle inequality in income and wealth in the UK; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lindsay Roy","Lindsay Roy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158479","158479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2494","2013-06-10","Home Office","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many individuals of Syrian nationality have been granted asylum in the UK since March 2011.","Biography information for Lindsay Roy","Lindsay Roy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158480","158480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2496","2013-06-10","Department of Health","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what responsibilities of (a) clinical commissioning groups and (b) local authorities are for the funding of long-term care; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Pauline Latham","Pauline Latham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158482","158482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2540","2013-06-10","Ministry of Defence","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of staffing of the Defence Infrastructure Organisation.","Biography information for Gemma Doyle","Gemma Doyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158488","158488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2594","2013-06-06","Ministry of Defence","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much his Department's work in Libya counted towards the UK's Overseas Development Assistance target.","Biography information for Mr Tobias Ellwood","Mr Tobias Ellwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158447","158447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2595","2013-06-06","Department for Education","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much was spent on and how many people received education maintenance allowance in (a) England and (b) Oxfordshire in the last full year of that scheme's operation.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158450","158450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2597","2013-06-06","Department for Transport","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what funds his Department makes available to upgrade local authority managed seafront piers.","Biography information for Mr Tobias Ellwood","Mr Tobias Ellwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158452","158452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2702","2013-06-06","Ministry of Defence","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the RAF's operational range requirement for the Tornado GR4 replacement is; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Tobias Ellwood","Mr Tobias Ellwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158445","158445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3066","2013-06-06","Ministry of Defence","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many qualified unmanned aerial vehicle pilots are currently employed by the Royal Air Force.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158752","158752"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3067","2013-06-06","Department for International Development","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, which projects her Department funds in Area C of the Occupied Palestinian Territory.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158755","158755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3068","2013-06-06","Department for International Development","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment her Department has made of the relative poverty of Palestinians living in (a) Area C, (b) Areas B and A and (c) East Jerusalem.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158756","158756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3069","2013-06-06","Department for International Development","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what support her Department is giving to Palestinians living in Area C of the Occupied Palestinian Territory.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158757","158757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3070","2013-06-06","Department for International Development","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent assessment her Department has made of the risks and benefits of funding projects in Area C of the Occupied Palestinian Territory.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158758","158758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3071","2013-06-06","Department for International Development","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent discussions her Department has had on funding of development infrastructure in those parts of Area C of the Occupied Palestinian Territory covered by Palestinian master plans with (a) other Government departments, (b) international development ministers of other EU member states and (c) the European Commission.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158759","158759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3072","2013-06-06","Department of Health","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to his Department's announcement of 10 April 2013, when the hospices allocated funding under the capital grants programme will formally receive funds.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158760","158760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3074","2013-06-06","Home Office","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent discussions (a) she and (b) the Minister for Immigration have had with the Minister for Policing and Criminal Justice on human trafficking in the UK.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158724","158724"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3075","2013-06-06","Home Office","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent discussions (a) she and (b) the Minister for Immigration has had with (i) the Cabinet Secretary for Justice and (ii) the Minister for Community Safety and Legal Affairs in the Scottish Government on human trafficking in the UK.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158725","158725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3076","2013-06-06","Home Office","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to improve knowledge of human trafficking amongst social workers in (a) Paisley and Renfrewshire North constituency, (b) Scotland and (c) the UK.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158726","158726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3077","2013-06-06","Home Office","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent discussions she has had with the Minister for Children and Young People in the Scottish Government on improving knowledge of human trafficking amongst social workers in (a) Paisley and Renfrewshire North constituency and (b) Scotland.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158727","158727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3078","2013-06-06","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to improve the transparency of UK companies operating in developing countries.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158734","158734"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3079","2013-06-06","HM Treasury","2013-06-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department is taking to enforce the minimum wage.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158723","158723"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3080","2013-06-10","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what plans she has to meet Facebook to discuss internet trolling.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158800","158800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3266","2013-06-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what support the UK has offered to non-members of the Missile Technology Control Regime to prevent the proliferation of unmanned aerial vehicles.","Biography information for Anas Sarwar","Anas Sarwar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158807","158807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3267","2013-06-10","Department for International Development","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what monitoring her Department is undertaking on the effect of drone strikes on livelihood strategies in the areas affected.","Biography information for Anas Sarwar","Anas Sarwar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158808","158808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3268","2013-06-10","Department for International Development","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what reports she has received of the movement of people in Afghanistan and Pakistan who have been displaced as a result of drone strikes.","Biography information for Anas Sarwar","Anas Sarwar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158809","158809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3269","2013-06-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many (a) people and (b) disabled people in work live in households with incomes below 60 per cent of contemporary median net disposable household income (i) before and (ii) after housing costs.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158805","158805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3270","2013-06-10","Department for International Development","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much and what proportion of the total UK international development budget was spent on abortion services in the last five years, by country.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158806","158806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3271","2013-06-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent correspondence and meetings have taken place between his Department and the UN Special Rapporteur on Counter-Terrorism and Human Rights; and if he will place such correspondence and the minutes of such meetings in the Library.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158781","158781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3272","2013-06-06","Ministry of Defence","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much his Department spent on research and development funding on unmanned air vehicles in (a) 2011, (b) 2012 and (c) 2013.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158782","158782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3273","2013-06-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effect of the introduction of personal independence payment on the number of disabled people living in relative poverty.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158816","158816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3274","2013-06-06","HM Treasury","2013-06-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent consideration he has given to reducing the rate of gross profit tax for bingo to 15 per cent.","Biography information for Sir Tony Cunningham","Sir Tony Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158763","158763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3275","2013-06-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to protect the interests of UK citizens residing and owning property in Goa.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158764","158764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3276","2013-06-06","Home Office","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what target her Department sets for answering letters from hon. Members.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158765","158765"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3277","2013-06-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of employment and support allowance claimants are mentally ill; how many of such claimants have been referred for treatment; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158766","158766"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3278","2013-06-06","Ministry of Defence","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much has been allocated for research and development funding in (a) 2014 and (b) 2015.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158776","158776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3279","2013-06-06","Ministry of Defence","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) Reaper and (b) Hermes 450 vehicles have crashed and subsequently been taken out of service in each year since each model came into operation.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158777","158777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3280","2013-06-06","Ministry of Defence","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what changes his Department plans to make to the data collection process relating to compensation claims for deaths caused by drone strikes in Afghanistan.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158778","158778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3281","2013-06-06","Ministry of Defence","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when and for how long any UK armed forces personnel have been stationed at Shamsi Airbase in Pakistan; and what the purpose of such personnel deployed to that base was.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158779","158779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3282","2013-06-06","Ministry of Defence","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Watchkeeper training flights have taken place; what the location was of such flights; and what the cost to the public purse has been to date.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158780","158780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3283","2013-06-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people are expected to take up post-Work Programme support in each of the next three years.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158817","158817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3284","2013-06-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of people receiving contributory jobseeker's allowance moved on to income-based jobseeker's allowance after reaching the 182-day limit on the contributory element in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158818","158818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3285","2013-06-10","Home Office","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what criteria her Department uses to decide whether an immigration case is deemed complex; and what service standards apply to such cases.","Biography information for Mr David Ward","Mr David Ward","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158819","158819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3286","2013-06-10","Home Office","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average wait for in-country applicants waiting to be sent biometric enrolment invitations from the date their application is acknowledged is.","Biography information for Mr David Ward","Mr David Ward","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158825","158825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3287","2013-06-10","HM Treasury","2013-06-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with his Irish counterpart on the sale of Ulster Bank.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158826","158826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3288","2013-06-10","HM Treasury","2013-06-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will ensure that the Financial Regulation Authority publishes its report into the RBS/Ulsterbank computer system failure.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158827","158827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/3289","2013-06-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans he has to bring forward an aid package for fishermen to cover expenses incurred by them as a result of poor weather conditions and recent gear requirement changes.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158828","158828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5517","2013-06-06","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps he is taking to encourage green officers in private businesses to reduce energy consumption and promote green employment.","Biography information for Iain McKenzie","Iain McKenzie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158547","158547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5555","2013-06-06","Department for International Development","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what discussions she has had with the government of St Helena on the (a) current water supply infrastructure and (b) anticipated demand following the opening of the airport and increased tourism; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158692","158692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5556","2013-06-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the timetable is for the introduction of the bill to ban wild animals in circuses; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158693","158693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5630","2013-06-06","Ministry of Justice","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of the prison population is serving a prison sentence of (a) one year or more and (b) two years or more.","Biography information for Nick Gibb","Mr Nick Gibb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158542","158542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5699","2013-06-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, on what occasions representatives from UK Trade and Investment have met with the Cumbria Local Enterprise Partnership in the last year.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158789","158789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5700","2013-06-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, on which occasions representatives from UK Trade and Investment have met with businesses based in Cumbria in the last year.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158790","158790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5701","2013-06-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many  local authorities have chosen to set their council tax rate for empty properties at above 100 per cent in the 2013-14 financial year.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158791","158791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5702","2013-06-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the spending power per head of (a) Barrow and Furness, (b) South Lakeland, (c) Eden, (d) Allerdale, (e) Copeland and (f) Carlisle district councils was in each of the last five years.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158792","158792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5703","2013-06-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the spending power per head of (a) Cumbria and (b) Lancashire county councils was in each of the last five years.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158793","158793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5756","2013-06-10","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 3 June 2013, Official Report, column 801W, on broadband, whether the UK is on track to meet the EU 2020 broadband targets.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158602","158602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5764","2013-06-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what measures are in place to control the export of cyber security software.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158598","158598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5765","2013-06-10","Cabinet Office","2013-06-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how his Department will implement the proposed changes to the calculation of charges attached to Freedom of Information requests.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158599","158599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5766","2013-06-10","Cabinet Office","2013-06-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment he has made of the role of women in social enterprises.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158600","158600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5767","2013-06-10","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 3 June 2013, Official Report, column 802W, on broadband: rural areas, when the independent review is expected to report; and whether it has made interim findings available to her (a) formally and (b) informally.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158601","158601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5857","2013-06-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, on what evidential basis the badger cull has been planned.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158455","158455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6109","2013-06-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received of the presence of anti-personnel mines in Jonglei State, South Sudan, in breach of the Mine Ban Treaty; and what representations he has made to the government of South Sudan on that matter.","Biography information for Mr William Bain","Mr William Bain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158753","158753"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6110","2013-06-06","Department for International Development","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent assessment she has made of the humanitarian situation in Jonglei State, South Sudan; and what access is being provided by the government of South Sudan to humanitarian and other non-governmental organisations.","Biography information for Mr William Bain","Mr William Bain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158754","158754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6226","2013-06-06","Department for Transport","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will commission new survey data for use in calculating the benefits of High Speed 2 to business travellers.","Biography information for Mr Steve Baker","Steve Baker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158608","158608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6227","2013-06-06","Department for Transport","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when HS2 Ltd will (a) complete and (b) publish an independent audit of passenger demand forecasts and analysis.","Biography information for Mr Steve Baker","Steve Baker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158610","158610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6228","2013-06-06","Department for Transport","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he plans to review his Department's benefit to cost ratio for High Speed 2 to take into account the assumptions on the relationship between passenger numbers and GDP growth that were published in August 2012.","Biography information for Mr Steve Baker","Steve Baker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158611","158611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6422","2013-06-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent steps he has taken to raise the case of Devinderpal Singh Bhullar with his counterparts in the Indian government and to press for his death sentence to be commuted to a life sentence.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158829","158829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6423","2013-06-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his counterparts in the Indian government regarding concerns raised by Amnesty International, Reprieve UK, Human Rights Watch and other organisations regarding the treatment of Devinderpal Singh Bhullar.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158830","158830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6424","2013-06-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has received regarding access for tourists to the West Bank.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158831","158831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6425","2013-06-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will raise with his counterpart in the Israeli government the importance of allowing tourism to Palestinian-controlled areas as a valuable source for economic growth in the area.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158832","158832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6546","2013-06-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with Baroness Amos following her visit to Sudan.","Biography information for Stephen Mosley","Stephen Mosley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158783","158783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6547","2013-06-06","Department for International Development","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the current situation in the Yida and Ajuong refugee camps in South Sudan.","Biography information for Stephen Mosley","Stephen Mosley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158784","158784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6548","2013-06-06","Department for International Development","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what reports she has received on the supply of food in Yida refugee camp in South Sudan.","Biography information for Stephen Mosley","Stephen Mosley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158785","158785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6620","2013-06-10","Home Office","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she intends to reply to the letters from the hon. Member for Harrow West of 3 April 2013 and 20 May 2013 to the UK Border Agency regarding Ms Alpa Odedra of Harrow.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158588","158588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6717","2013-06-10","Cabinet Office","2013-06-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 3 June 2013, Official Report, column 964W, on social action fund, how many organisations benefited from the change in criteria for the Social Action Fund; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158797","158797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6718","2013-06-10","HM Treasury","2013-06-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 3 June 2013, Official Report, column 817W, on banks: loans, when he expects postcode level lending data from the banks to be publically available; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158798","158798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6725","2013-06-10","Cabinet Office","2013-06-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 3 June 2013, Official Report, colums 956-7W, on Big Society Network, what the purpose was of each grant or contract the Big Society Network and its subsidiaries received; what evaluation has been concluded as to whether the objectives behind each contract and grant have been achieved; he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158794","158794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6974","2013-06-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the incidence of transmissible spongiform encephalopathy in the UK sheep flock has been in each of the last 10 years for which data is available.","Biography information for Jesse Norman","Jesse Norman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158834","158834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7185","2013-06-10","Department for International Development","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, when she intends to reply to the letter from the hon. Member for Bury South dated 8 May 2013 regarding her Department's use of private sector contracts.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158820","158820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7373","2013-06-06","Home Office","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the cost to the public purse was of the removal of 1,136,000 DNA profiles from the national DNA database.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158774","158774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7374","2013-06-06","Home Office","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the number of DNA profiles that have been removed from the national DNA database that will be put back on the database in the next three years; and what the total cost to the public purse will be of such a process.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158775","158775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7614","2013-06-06","Department of Health","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when his Department plans to respond to the consultation on the management of HIV-infected healthcare workers.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158453","158453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7664","2013-06-10","Department for International Development","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether her Department provides funds to any aid agencies which provide medical services to female victims of sexual violence and which also receive aid from the US and are constrained by that government's policy towards the provision of abortion services; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Meg Munn","Meg Munn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158477","158477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7665","2013-06-10","Department for International Development","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what her policy is on the rights of women and girls who have been raped in situations of armed conflict and their right to  medical treatment which may include access to a safe abortion.","Biography information for Meg Munn","Meg Munn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158586","158586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7747","2013-06-06","Ministry of Justice","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many requests for registered intermediaries have been made by (a) children and (b) adults in each month since January 2013.","Biography information for Ann Coffey","Ann Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158562","158562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7748","2013-06-06","Ministry of Justice","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many registered intermediaries were appointed in each of the last three years for which data is available; and what the type of case was in each case.","Biography information for Ann Coffey","Ann Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158563","158563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7749","2013-06-06","HM Treasury","2013-06-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many requests for the revaluation of business premises have been made in each region in the last five years for which data is available.","Biography information for Ann Coffey","Ann Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158551","158551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7750","2013-06-06","HM Treasury","2013-06-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many successful appeals have been made against existing house price valuations in each region of the UK in the last five years for which data is available.","Biography information for Ann Coffey","Ann Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158550","158550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7756","2013-06-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his Bangladeshi counterpart in support of the rule of law and the abolition of the death penalty in that country.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158593","158593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7757","2013-06-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the Bangladesh government regarding the establishment of an independent inquiry into the recent violence in that country.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158590","158590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7903","2013-06-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, on what date jobcentres in (a) Wigan, (b) Warrington and (c) Oldham will start to accept applications for universal credit.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158584","158584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7905","2013-06-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people were in receipt of universal credit on 31 May 2013.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158583","158583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7971","2013-06-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, which people aged under 18 years old will be eligible to claim universal credit.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158810","158810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7972","2013-06-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the whole life cost of the universal credit project; whether this estimate has changed since 2010; and if he will make a statement about the differences in those estimates.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158811","158811"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7973","2013-06-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, in what circumstances someone undertaking study or training will be eligible to receive universal credit.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158812","158812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8242","2013-06-10","Department for Transport","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what funding has been allocated from the New Stations Fund; and whether he plans to make further awards from the New Stations Fund.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158799","158799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8516","2013-06-10","Department of Health","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether a formal agreement was signed between the now abolished South Central Strategic Health Authority and Southern Water to add fluoride to the water supply in (a) Southampton and (b) the South West Hampshire area.","Biography information for Mr Mike Thornton","Mr Michael Thornton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158592","158592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8852","2013-06-10","Department of Health","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will publish for each of the last five years (a) mortality rates and (b) risk-adjusted PRAiS data on mortality rates for children's heart surgery units in England, broken down by the number of paediatric surgical procedures on the following basis: (i) less than 150, (ii) 151 to 250, (iii) 251 to 350, (iv) 351 to 450, (v) 451 to 550 and (vi) 551 and over.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158582","158582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8970","2013-06-10","Ministry of Justice","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how contractors will be incentivised under his proposals for the outsouring of probation services.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158487","158487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8975","2013-06-10","Ministry of Justice","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how he plans to ensure public safety underhis proposals for the outsourcing of probation services.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158483","158483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8976","2013-06-10","Ministry of Justice","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how he plans to enable third sector providers to compete for probation services with the private sector underhis proposals for the outsourcing of probation services.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158484","158484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8977","2013-06-10","Ministry of Justice","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how he plans to retain sufficiently qualified and professional staff in the public sector underhis proposals for the outsourcing of probation services.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158485","158485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8978","2013-06-10","Ministry of Justice","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how he plans to assess the success of his proposals for the outsourcing of probation services.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158486","158486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9216","2013-06-10","Department of Health","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his policy is on the provision of advice through the NHS to the public about the importance of diet.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158591","158591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9267","2013-06-10","Department for Education","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Answer to the hon. Member for Gateshead of 1 March 2013, Official Report, colums 753-4W, on schools: transport, if he will take steps to update his Department's statutory guidance to local authorities regarding transport for 16 to18 year olds.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158786","158786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9274","2013-06-10","Ministry of Justice","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether his Department plans to require public sector organisations to take an audit from the Information Commissioner.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158814","158814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9275","2013-06-10","Department of Health","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many GPs in (a) Barnsley Central constituency, (b) South Yorkshire and (c) England use (i) 0844 and (ii) 0845 numbers.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158815","158815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9495","2013-06-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if his Department will bring forward legislative proposals to allow the prosecution of owners of dogs that attack other animals.","Biography information for David Morris","David Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158751","158751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9496","2013-06-10","Ministry of Justice","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will give consideration to implementing a murder offence of terrorism aggravated murder with the punishment of a mandatory whole life sentence without parole.","Biography information for David Morris","David Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158813","158813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9497","2013-06-06","Department for Education","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to improve access to swimming lessons for school children.","Biography information for David Morris","David Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158767","158767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9498","2013-06-06","HM Treasury","2013-06-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department is taking to help people who have been missold loans by high street banks.","Biography information for David Morris","David Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158768","158768"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9499","2013-06-06","HM Treasury","2013-06-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department is taking to ensure banks accurately explain the relationship between variations in the Bank of England base rate of interest and the interest charged on their variable rate loans.","Biography information for David Morris","David Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158769","158769"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9500","2013-06-06","HM Treasury","2013-06-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that vulnerable people are not missold loans they cannot afford to repay.","Biography information for David Morris","David Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158770","158770"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9501","2013-06-06","Department for Transport","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans he has to electrify the Windermere branch line; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for David Morris","David Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158771","158771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/96","2013-06-06","Attorney General","2013-06-04","To ask the Attorney General, what his policy is on prosecuting people for crimes committed while being controlled by traffickers.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158728","158728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/97","2013-06-06","Department for International Development","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to eradicate slavery in business supply chains.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158729","158729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9701","2013-06-10","Department of Health","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the clinical benefits of larger paediatric cardiac surgical units.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158603","158603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9702","2013-06-10","Department of Health","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the latest partial risk adjustment in surgery data confirms the conclusion of the 2011 Safe and Sustainable Review that surgery would be better focused at fewer, larger sites.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158604","158604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9703","2013-06-10","Department of Health","2013-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will commission a detailed analysis of surgical performance, in association with the National Institute for Health Care and Excellence aimed at quantifying other factors that affect surgical success rates such as ethnicity, socioeconomic deprivation, national funding, technical difficulty and unit size.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158605","158605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/99","2013-06-10","Cabinet Office","2013-06-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many immigrants entered the UK from (a) outside and (b) inside the EU in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158585","158585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10007","2013-06-06","HM Treasury","2013-06-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent discussions (a) he and (b) officials in his Department have had with the Scottish Government regarding support to individuals affected by relief at source tax arrangements to ensure they receive the correct amount of tax relief following the introduction of different tax rates under the Scotland Act 2012.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158180","158180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10008","2013-06-05","Cabinet Office","2013-06-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the name is of each individual nominated by the Scottish Government to the Honours Committee since May 2007.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158302","158302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10009","2013-06-05","Ministry of Defence","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate his Department has made of the cost to the public purse of the (a) current and (b) proposed level of support for Syrian opposition forces with regard to military equipment.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158137","158137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10010","2013-06-06","Scotland Office","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what recent discussions he has had with the Chancellor of the Exchequer regarding the effect of different Scottish rates of income tax on individuals who are members of pension schemes who operate the relief at source process for tax relief.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158181","158181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10011","2013-06-06","HM Treasury","2013-06-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent steps he has taken to ensure that taxpayers in Scotland who are members of pension schemes which operate the relief at source process are not adversely affected by differing rates of income tax in Scotland provided for by the Scotland Act 2012.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158189","158189"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10101","2013-06-06","Prime Minister","2013-06-03","To ask the Prime Minister, with reference to his letter to the leaders of the UK's Crown Dependencies and Overseas Territories of 20 May 2013 on tax information exchange and beneficial ownership, whether he has received any replies to that letter; and if he will publish any replies received in full.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158182","158182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10145","2013-06-06","HM Treasury","2013-06-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, on what dates he met representatives of (a) Flybe and (b) EasyJet in each of the last 12 months at which the issue of air passenger duty was discussed.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Mr Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158436","158436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10287","2013-06-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many households will be affected by the introduction of housing costs contributions in (a) Scotland and (b) the UK.","Biography information for Dr Eilidh Whiteford","Dr Eilidh Whiteford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158418","158418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10293","2013-06-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will carry out an impact assessment for the introduction of housing costs contributions under universal credit.","Biography information for Dr Eilidh Whiteford","Dr Eilidh Whiteford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158416","158416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10294","2013-06-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of potential savings to the public purse arising from the introduction of housing costs contributions under universal credit.","Biography information for Dr Eilidh Whiteford","Dr Eilidh Whiteford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158417","158417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10295","2013-06-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the potential effects on levels of youth homelessness of the introduction of housing costs contributions under universal credit.","Biography information for Dr Eilidh Whiteford","Dr Eilidh Whiteford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158419","158419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10338","2013-06-05","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether she is considering extending the public lending right to (a) ebooks whether borrowed remotely or on library premises, (b) audio books borrowed remotely or on library premises and (c) all volunteer libraries; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Peter Bottomley","Sir Peter Bottomley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158109","158109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10381","2013-06-06","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, when she plans to answer Question 156335, tabled by the hon. Member for Reading East on 15 May 2013 for Answer on 20 May 2013.","Biography information for Mr Rob Wilson","Mr Rob Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158396","158396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10392","2013-06-05","Department for Transport","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent work his Department has undertaken to prevent road traffic accidents on major motorways.","Biography information for Mary Macleod","Mary Macleod","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158303","158303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10425","2013-06-06","Ministry of Defence","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what military agreements the UK has with countries in East Asia.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158213","158213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10426","2013-06-06","Ministry of Defence","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many defence attach posts in East Asia have been closed since May 2010.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158214","158214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10427","2013-06-06","Ministry of Defence","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, in which East Asian countries the UK has a defence attach.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158215","158215"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10428","2013-06-06","Ministry of Defence","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what UK capabilities are deployed in East Asia to protect shipping lanes.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158216","158216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10429","2013-06-06","Ministry of Defence","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what military agreements the UK has with (a) China, (b) Japan, (c) Australia, (d) New Zealand, (e) South Korea and (f) Vietnam.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158217","158217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10891","2013-06-05","Ministry of Justice","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many complaints were received about the obligations under the Code of Practice for Victims of Crime by each agency covered by the code in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158122","158122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10896","2013-06-05","Ministry of Defence","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the top 20 highest amounts paid by his Department for external legal advice was in (a) 2010, (b) 2011 and (c) 2012; who received each such payment; and for what reasons the legal advice was sought in each case.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158112","158112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10903","2013-06-05","Ministry of Justice","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which courtrooms he has visited since his appointment.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158147","158147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10904","2013-06-05","Ministry of Defence","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much his Department spent on external legal advice from Queen's Counsel (a) between 7 May 2010 and 4 September 2012 and (b) since 4 September 2012.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158148","158148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10905","2013-06-05","Ministry of Defence","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the highest day rate paid for external legal advice by his Department has been since 7 May 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158149","158149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10906","2013-06-05","Ministry of Justice","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many complaints were received about obligations under the Code of Practice for Victims of Crime in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158150","158150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10907","2013-06-05","Ministry of Justice","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many court cases were delayed because defendants were absent as a result of the failure of GEOAmey to transport prisoners to court in 2012.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158152","158152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10939","2013-06-06","Ministry of Justice","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many cases were dealt with by the commercial courts in England and Wales in (a) 2010, (b) 2011 and (c) 2012.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158177","158177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10966","2013-06-06","Ministry of Justice","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the running costs of the commercial courts in England and Wales were in (a) 2010, (b) 2011 and (c) 2012; and how much income was generated by those courts in each such year.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158178","158178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11395","2013-06-05","Deputy Prime Minister","2013-06-03","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, with reference to the Answer of 16 April 2013, Official Report, column 293W, on lobbying, what period of time was intended to be inferred by the phrase in due course used in the Answer; when he expects to bring forward legislative proposals for a statutory register of lobbyists; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158301","158301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11499","2013-06-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the potential threat from the Soufriere Hills Volcano in Montserrat.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158345","158345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11500","2013-06-05","Department for International Development","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many (a) Ministers and (b) officials in her Department have visited a UK Overseas Territory since May 2010.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158365","158365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11501","2013-06-05","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what plans his Department has to ensure that appropriate signage will be placed correctly at historic county boundaries.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158368","158368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11502","2013-06-05","Department of Health","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make an estimate of the cost of unnecessary accident and emergency attendances in Romford constituency in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158356","158356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11577","2013-06-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received on the formation of a new government in Iceland, and its announcement that it has terminated the accession process of Iceland to the EU; what assessment he has made of the implications of these developments for UK foreign policy; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158350","158350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11578","2013-06-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received on the incident on 9 May 2013 involving a Taiwanese vessel and a Filipino vessel, resulting in the death of Mr Hon Shi-cheng, a Taiwanese fisherman; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158358","158358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11579","2013-06-05","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Code of Recommended Practice on Local Authority Publicity, published in March 2011, what assessment he has made of the extent to which local authorities are continuing to publish their own newspapers.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158359","158359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11580","2013-06-05","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of local authority subsidy to the arts in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158357","158357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11581","2013-06-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the rat infestation on Henderson Island.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158346","158346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11582","2013-06-05","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if his Department will encourage local authorities to follow the example of Cumberland in raising awareness of their county flags and coats of arms.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158347","158347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11583","2013-06-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many (a) Ministers and (b) officials in his Department have visited a UK Overseas Territory since May 2010.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158366","158366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11584","2013-06-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much his Department spent on biodiversity conservation in (a) England and (b) UK Overseas Territories in 2012-13.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158367","158367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11585","2013-06-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his (a) US and (b) Mauritian counterpart on the future of the British Indian Ocean Territory (Chagos Islands).","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158341","158341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11586","2013-06-05","Department for International Development","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what plans her Department has to assist with the development of transport links to encourage tourism in each of the UK Overseas Territories that receive assistance from her Department.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158342","158342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11587","2013-06-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has any plans to increase the number of officials in his Department that are based in the Falkland Islands.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158343","158343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11588","2013-06-05","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how much his Department spent on investment in solar power in UK Overseas Territories in the last two years.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158344","158344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11589","2013-06-05","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what plans his Department has to raise awareness of historic county boundaries amongst (a) children and young people and (b) other people.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158369","158369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11590","2013-06-05","Department for Education","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of changes in the level of government regulation of independent schools during the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158348","158348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11591","2013-06-05","Ministry of Defence","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of tactical military advantages arising from the use of remote piloted air systems; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158349","158349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11592","2013-06-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his counterpart in Argentina on freedom of expression.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158364","158364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11746","2013-06-05","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment his Department has made of whether the decrease in the extent of Arctic sea ice since reliable records began is statistically significant; and what statistical model his Department has used to conduct that assessment.","Biography information for Lord Lilley","Mr Peter Lilley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158206","158206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11824","2013-06-05","Department for Transport","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to protect and enhance the maritime skills base; and when he last discussed this matter with ministerial colleagues in the Department for Business, Innovation and Skills.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158192","158192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11879","2013-06-06","Department for Education","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment has been made of the likely effects of the provisions of the Children and Families Bill to seek child protection outcomes within a 26-week window.","Biography information for Stephen Gilbert","Stephen Gilbert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158179","158179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11888","2013-06-05","Ministry of Justice","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when he expects to bring into force Section 28 of the Youth and Crime Act 1999.","Biography information for Sir Tony Baldry","Sir Tony Baldry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158138","158138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/127","2013-06-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the annual cost to companies in England of workplace absenteeism.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158307","158307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/145","2013-06-06","Home Office","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what consideration the Government has given to implementing a central bank register to facilitate the seizing of proceeds of crime.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158383","158383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/164","2013-06-06","Department for Transport","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect and change in response times that HS2 construction traffic will have on the accident and emergency ambulance routes along the length of the London to Birmingham route of HS2; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158186","158186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/185","2013-06-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what recent discussions he and officials of his Department have had with (a) colleagues in other departments and (b) local authorities on the delivery of enterprise zones.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158444","158444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2041","2013-06-06","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what contribution he expects the Green Investment Bank to make to green growth.","Biography information for Chris White","Chris White","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158096","158096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2042","2013-06-06","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what recent assessment he has made of the level of public support for offshore and onshore wind.","Biography information for Andrea Leadsom","Andrea Leadsom","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158092","158092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2044","2013-06-06","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what contribution he expects the Green Investment Bank to make to green growth.","Biography information for Mr David Ward","Mr David Ward","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158078","158078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2048","2013-06-06","Attorney General","2013-06-03","To ask the Attorney General, at what time and on what date he issued guidance to the media about what could be broadcast about the circumstance of the death in Woolwich of Drummer Lee Rigby; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158327","158327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2057","2013-06-05","Home Office","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when the hon. Member for Warley can expect to receive a reply from her Department to his letter of 18 April regarding the case of Ms. Mangena.","Biography information for John Spellar","Mr John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158107","158107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2058","2013-06-05","Department for Education","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the designated duties of academy brokers are; how many academy brokers are currently employed; what the daily rate of pay for such brokers is; and what the total expenditure of academy brokers was in the last year.","Biography information for John Spellar","Mr John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158108","158108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2105","2013-06-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people have successfully claimed universal credit in the pathfinder to date.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158212","158212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2106","2013-06-05","Attorney General","2013-06-03","To ask the Attorney General, to how many current or former lawyers employed by the Crown Prosecution Service Her Majesty's Inspector of the Crown Prosecution Service has written inviting responses on the interim findings of the inquiry into the collapse of the prosecution of alleged police corruption surrounding the investigation of the murder of Lynette White.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158201","158201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2107","2013-06-05","Attorney General","2013-06-03","To ask the Attorney General, what steps the Crown Prosecution Service takes to monitor the quality of prosecutions of homicide cases where a single counsel is used in the prosecution of multiple defendants.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158204","158204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2108","2013-06-05","Department for Transport","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what his Department's budgeted or estimated expenditure on special adviser salaries is for (a) 2013-14, (b) 2014-15 and (c) 2015-16.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158232","158232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2109","2013-06-05","Department for Transport","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what budget he has allocated to the Driving Standards Agency for (a) 2013-14, (b) 2014-15 and (c) 2015-16.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158234","158234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2110","2013-06-05","Department for Transport","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many members of staff at the Driving Standards Agency are paid over 100,000 per annum.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158237","158237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2111","2013-06-05","Department for Transport","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what budget he has allocated to Passenger Focus for (a) 2013-14, (b) 2014-15 and (c) 2015-16.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158266","158266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2112","2013-06-06","Department for Education","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what guidance his Department issues to primary schools in relation to the spending of ring-fenced funds for physical education and sport.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158306","158306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2113","2013-06-05","Department for Transport","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the Railway Heritage Committee will have any ongoing headquarters or other office costs for (a) 2013-14, (b) 2014-15 and (c) 2015-16.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158275","158275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2114","2013-06-05","Department for Transport","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the name is of each capital project being undertaken by his Department not classed as a major project; and what the (a) budget and (b) traffic light status is of each such project.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158284","158284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2115","2013-06-05","Department for Transport","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many members of staff working on the functions previously carried out by the Railway Heritage Committee are paid over 100,000 per annum.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158278","158278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2116","2013-06-06","Ministry of Defence","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which companies have been awarded sub-contracts for construction of HMS Queen Elizabeth and HMS Prince of Wales; at which sites he expects work under each such contract to be carried out; and what the monetary value is of each such contract.","Biography information for Margaret Curran","Margaret Curran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158311","158311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2117","2013-06-05","Department for Transport","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent estimate he has made of the rental or leasing value of the unused or empty office space or buildings owned or being leased by his Department or its agencies per square foot.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158288","158288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2118","2013-06-05","Department of Health","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 13 May 2013, Official Report, column 49W, on nurses, how many midwives, excluding nurses and health visiting staff, there were (a) in the NHS and (b) in County Durham and Darlington NHS Foundation Trust on (i) 1 May 2010 and (ii) 1 May 2013.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158296","158296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2119","2013-06-05","Home Office","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department has taken to implement the provisions of the Public Services (Social Value) Act 2012.","Biography information for Chris White","Chris White","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158304","158304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2126","2013-06-05","Department of Health","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent steps his Department has taken to promote a social enterprise in delivering services within the NHS.","Biography information for Chris White","Chris White","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158110","158110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2127","2013-06-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent progress has been made on negotiations on the Fissile Material Cut-Off Treaty.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158404","158404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2128","2013-06-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent progress has been made on negotiations on the Strategic Arms Reduction Treaty.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158406","158406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2136","2013-06-06","HM Treasury","2013-06-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what grants and investments have been made under the Business Finance Partnership to date; and of these what funds have been (a) allocated and (b) drawn down to date.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158440","158440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2142","2013-06-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claimants of jobseeker's allowance in Scotland have received a sanction on (a) one, (b) two, (c) three, (d) four, (e) five and (f) more than five occasions in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Margaret Curran","Margaret Curran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158442","158442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2145","2013-06-06","Department of Health","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Answer of 5 March 2013, Official Report, column 938W, on abortion, what progress has been made in (a) cases referred to the Crown Prosecution Service, (b) prosecutions commenced, (c) random inspections of licensed abortion centres and (d) other follow-up steps following the Chief Medical Officer's letter to abortion providers sent in February 2012.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158309","158309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2146","2013-06-05","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what commitments she has received from internet search providers on (a) making safe search the default mechanism, (b) introducing a robust age verification system and (c) putting up warning signs when people are about to enter pornography sites; and whether a timetable has been agreed for the introduction of such measures.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158378","158378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2154","2013-06-05","Department for Education","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what progress his Department is making on ensuring an appropriate separation between awarding organisations and bodies that publish educational textbooks and other educational materials.","Biography information for Baroness Blackwood of North Oxford","Nicola Blackwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158193","158193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2155","2013-06-05","Department for Transport","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the Vehicle and Operator Service Agency budgeted or estimated expenditure for administration is for (a) 2013-14, (b) 2014-15 and (c) 2015-16.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158252","158252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2156","2013-06-05","Department for Transport","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many members of staff at the Vehicle and Operator Service Agency are paid over 100,000 per annum.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158253","158253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2157","2013-06-05","Department for Transport","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what budget he has allocated to the Vehicle Certification Agency for (a) 2013-14, (b) 2014-15 and (c) 2015-16.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158254","158254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2158","2013-06-05","Department for Transport","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the Vehicle Certification Agency budgeted or estimated expenditure for headquarters and other office costs is for (a) 2013-14, (b) 2014-15 and (c) 2015-16.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158255","158255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2159","2013-06-05","Department for Transport","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the Vehicle Certification Agency budgeted or estimated expenditure for administration is for (a) 2013-14, (b) 2014-15 and (c) 2015-16.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158256","158256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2160","2013-06-05","Department for Transport","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many members of staff at the Vehicle Certification Agency are paid over 100,000 per annum.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158257","158257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2161","2013-06-05","Department for Transport","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what budget he has allocated to the British Transport Police Authority for (a) 2013-14, (b) 2014-15 and (c) 2015-16.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158258","158258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2162","2013-06-05","Department for Transport","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the British Transport Police Authority budgeted or estimated expenditure for headquarters and other office costs is for (a) 2013-14, (b) 2014-15 and (c) 2015-16.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158259","158259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2163","2013-06-05","Department for Transport","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the British Transport Police Authority budgeted or estimated expenditure for administration is for (a) 2013-14, (b) 2014-15 and (c) 2015-16.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158260","158260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2164","2013-06-05","Department for Transport","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many members of staff at the British Transport Police Authority are paid over 100,000 per annum.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158261","158261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2165","2013-06-06","Cabinet Office","2013-06-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people in England and Wales described their national identity in their 2011 Census return as (a) Scottish, (b) British and (c) Scottish and British.","Biography information for Margaret Curran","Margaret Curran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158320","158320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2166","2013-06-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the British Ambassador to Burma has attempted to meet (a) Myint Soe and (b) other political prisoners imprisoned in that country.","Biography information for Fiona O'Donnell","Fiona O'Donnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158323","158323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2167","2013-06-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what proportion of grants provided by the British Embassy in Rangoon  were allocated to projects which promote human rights in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Fiona O'Donnell","Fiona O'Donnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158324","158324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2168","2013-06-06","Attorney General","2013-06-03","To ask the Attorney General, what the monetary value is of (a) fines and (b) civil recovery orders imposed on (i) individuals and (ii) companies by the courts as a result of Serious Fraud Office investigations which led to convictions in 2012-13.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158325","158325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2169","2013-06-06","Attorney General","2013-06-03","To ask the Attorney General, what the average prison sentence per conviction was of offenders receiving sentences of imprisonment following a prosecution by the Serious Fraud Office which led to a conviction in (a) 2012-13 and (b) each of the previous five years.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158326","158326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2173","2013-06-05","HM Treasury","2013-06-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the statement on page 6 of his Department's publication, Scotland Analysis: Financial Services and Banking, that Scottish banks have assets totalling around 1254 per cent of an independent Scotland's GDP, if he will provide a full list of assets included to support that figure.","Biography information for Stewart Hosie","Stewart Hosie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158420","158420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2202","2013-06-05","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if he will estimate the proportion of the monetary value of the contract for the Teesside Offshore Wind Farm Project's (a) turbines, (b) rotors, (c) transformers, (d) offshore cables, (e) onshore cables, (f) array cables and (g) subsea capability that is being provided by firms based in (i) Hartlepool constituency, (ii) Teesside, (iii) the North East and (iv) the UK; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158117","158117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2203","2013-06-05","Department for Transport","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether any new franchisee of the East Coast mainline will be required to make a contribution to the costs of the planned infrastructure upgrade to that line scheduled to take place between 2014 and 2019.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158118","158118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2204","2013-06-05","Department for Transport","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether any new franchisee of the East Coast mainline will be required to make a contribution to the costs of the rolling stock upgrade scheduled to be delivered by May 2019.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158119","158119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2205","2013-06-05","Department for Transport","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the cost of refranchising the East Coast mainline to date.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158120","158120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2206","2013-06-05","Department for Transport","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans he has to monitor the performance of the new franchisee of the East Coast mainline.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158121","158121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2207","2013-06-05","Ministry of Defence","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many training sorties have been flown over the Welsh Military Tactical Training area by (a) the Royal Air Force and (b) air force pilots from overseas in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158123","158123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2208","2013-06-05","Ministry of Justice","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what impact assessment he has made of the financial effects of price competitive tendering on legal service provision in Wales.","Biography information for Simon Hart","Simon Hart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158124","158124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2209","2013-06-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will work with homelessness organisations to assess the effectiveness of the toolkit for the identification of homelessness by Jobcentre Plus advisors.","Biography information for Mike Weatherley","Mike Weatherley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158125","158125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2210","2013-06-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will assess the merits of introducing a policy of removing all in-situ asbestos-containing materials within an agreed time-period for the purposes of reducing the continuing risk of exposure.","Biography information for Mike Weatherley","Mike Weatherley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158126","158126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2211","2013-06-05","Department for International Development","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is taking to improve the transparency of UK-based extractive industries operating abroad.","Biography information for Mr Tobias Ellwood","Mr Tobias Ellwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158139","158139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2212","2013-06-05","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the response time for the fire and rescue services to respond to a 999 call in (a) Dorset and (b) London is; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Tobias Ellwood","Mr Tobias Ellwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158140","158140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2213","2013-06-05","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of Facing the Future: findings from the review of efficiency and operations in fire and rescue authorities in England, produced by Sir Ken Knight in May 2013; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Tobias Ellwood","Mr Tobias Ellwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158141","158141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2214","2013-06-05","Ministry of Justice","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many legal offices currently deal with legal aid cases in Carmarthenshire.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158142","158142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2215","2013-06-05","Ministry of Justice","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what consideration he has given to strengthening the penalties available for use against public officials guilty of abusing powers enabled by the Regulation of Investigatory Powers Act 2000.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158143","158143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2216","2013-06-05","Ministry of Defence","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much his Department has spent on funding technical demonstrators to assist the development of wind farms in the last five years.","Biography information for Chris Heaton-Harris","Chris Heaton-Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158144","158144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2217","2013-06-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make a statement on the letter of 29 May 2013 from the Chair of the UK Statistics Authority to the hon. Member for Edinburgh East on the use of official statistics relating to employment and support allowance.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158145","158145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2223","2013-06-05","Ministry of Justice","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to ensure the bi-lingual provision of criminal defence services in Wales.","Biography information for Simon Hart","Simon Hart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158113","158113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2224","2013-06-05","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what discussions he had with the Secretary of State for Defence on  the contract to dismantle HMS Ark Royal; what steps he took to work with (a) UK-based firms and (b) government agencies to ensure that all or some of the work was undertaken by such companies; whether any UK-based facilities bid for the contract; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158114","158114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2225","2013-06-05","Department for Transport","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans he has to consult passengers and other key stakeholders on the tendering of the East Coast mainline rail franchise.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158115","158115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2226","2013-06-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what action his Department is taking to draw attention to householders of the risk arising from the disturbance of asbestos-containing materials within domestic properties.","Biography information for Mike Weatherley","Mike Weatherley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158127","158127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2227","2013-06-05","Department for Education","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the effects on performance in exams, sport and music of the use of mindfulness in secondary schools.","Biography information for Mike Weatherley","Mike Weatherley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158128","158128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2228","2013-06-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether he plans to strengthen the minimum service standards for the Work Programme.","Biography information for Mike Weatherley","Mike Weatherley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158129","158129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2229","2013-06-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he plans to take to improve job outcomes for homeless people in the Work Programme.","Biography information for Mike Weatherley","Mike Weatherley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158130","158130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2230","2013-06-05","Department for Transport","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what criteria his Department uses to determine which contracts for passenger rail franchises are extended and which are brought forward to refranchise.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158131","158131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2239","2013-06-05","Department for Transport","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much Virgin Trains has paid in premiums to the Government in respect of the West Coast Main Line in each year since the company was awarded the franchise.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158132","158132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2241","2013-06-06","Home Office","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what progress has been made on the establishment of a European sexual offenders register.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158219","158219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2242","2013-06-06","Home Office","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many officers are currently working on Operation Nitrate; and whether her Department has provided Operation Nitrate with additional funding.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158220","158220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2243","2013-06-05","Department for Transport","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what budget he has allocated to the Highways Agency for (a) 2013-14, (b) 2014-15 and (c) 2015-16.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158242","158242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2244","2013-06-05","Department for Transport","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the Highways Agency budgeted or estimated expenditure for headquarters and other office costs is for (a) 2013-14, (b) 2014-15 and (c) 2015-16.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158243","158243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2245","2013-06-05","Department for Transport","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the Highways Agency budgeted or estimated expenditure for administration is for (a) 2013-14, (b) 2014-15 and (c) 2015-16.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158244","158244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2246","2013-06-05","Department for Transport","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many members of staff at the Highways Agency are paid over 100,000 per annum.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158245","158245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2247","2013-06-05","Department for Transport","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what budget he has allocated to the Maritime and Coastguard Agency for (a) 2013-14, (b) 2014-15 and (c) 2015-16.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158246","158246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2248","2013-06-05","Department for Transport","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the Maritime and Coastguard Agency budgeted or estimated expenditure for headquarters and other office costs is for (a) 2013-14, (b) 2014-15 and (c) 2015-16.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158247","158247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2249","2013-06-05","Department for Transport","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the Maritime and Coastguard Agency budgeted or estimated expenditure for administration is for (a) 2013-14, (b) 2014-15 and (c) 2015-16.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158248","158248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2250","2013-06-05","Department for Transport","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many members of staff at the Maritime and Coastguard Agency are paid over 100,000 per annum.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158249","158249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2251","2013-06-05","Department for Transport","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what budget he has allocated to the Vehicle and Operator Service Agency for (a) 2013-14, (b) 2014-15 and (c) 2015-16.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158250","158250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2252","2013-06-05","Department for Transport","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the Vehicle and Operator Service Agency budgeted or estimated expenditure for headquarters and other office costs is for (a) 2013-14, (b) 2014-15 and (c) 2015-16.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158251","158251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2253","2013-06-05","Department for Transport","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what budget he has allocated to the Northern Lighthouse Board for (a) 2013-14, (b) 2014-15 and (c) 2015-16.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158262","158262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/2254","2013-06-05","Department for Transport","2013-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the Northern Lighthouse Board budgeted or estimated expenditure for headquarters and other office costs is for (a) 2013-14, (b) 2014-15 and (c) 2015-16.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 158263","158263"
