"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29813","2013-12-18","Department for Education","2013-12-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to question 177099 tabled on 20 November 2013 for answer on 25 November 2013, when he plans to answer that question.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180698","180698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29814","2013-12-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-12-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what his policy is towards Palestinian membership of the International Olive Council.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180687","180687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29815","2013-12-18","Department of Health","2013-12-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what support his Department provides to women to help them maintain a healthy pregnancy.","Biography information for Andrea Leadsom","Andrea Leadsom","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180699","180699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29816","2013-12-17","Department for Education","2013-12-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what consultation his Department carried out before taking its decision to resume funding for full-time 18 year old learners by 17.5 per cent in 2014-15.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180688","180688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29817","2013-12-17","Cabinet Office","2013-12-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the age-standardised incidence rate for breast cancer is; how many diagnoses of breast cancer there were in (a) England, (b) each of the 15 Public Health England regional centres, (c) each primary care trust area and (d) each parliamentary constituency in each year since 2000.","Biography information for Mr John Leech","Mr John Leech","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180689","180689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29818","2013-12-17","Department of Health","2013-12-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what NHS funding was allocated to (a) all breast cancer research, (b) prevention of breast cancer and (c) research into the links between breast cancer and exposure to carcinogenic, hazardous and endocrine-disrupting chemicals in each of the last 10 years; what plans he has for future funding of research on prevention of breast cancer; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr John Leech","Mr John Leech","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180690","180690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29819","2013-12-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-12-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many manufacturers of the chemical Bisphenol A are based in the UK.","Biography information for Mr John Leech","Mr John Leech","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180691","180691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29820","2013-12-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-12-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what volume of the chemical Bisphenol A (BPA) the UK has produced over the last six years; what proportion of global production this constitutes; and what proportion of the total UK production of BPA is used in the food and drinks packaging industry (a) globally and (b) within the UK.","Biography information for Mr John Leech","Mr John Leech","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180692","180692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29546","2013-12-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when his Department next plans to review the rating of plant and machinery for the purposes of business rates.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180425","180425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29547","2013-12-16","Department of Health","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what safeguards are in place to ensure that NHS commissioners comply with guidance on the treatment and care of people with rheumatoid arthritis.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180426","180426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29548","2013-12-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to his Department's Impact Assessment, Child maintenance fees reforms: CSA case closure, introducing CMS fees, supporting family-based arrangements, when he expects the new statutory scheme for child maintenance to attain post-transition steady state.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180427","180427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29549","2013-12-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what funding the Government plans to contribute to the African Elephant Action Plan; whether UK involvement in that plan will be led by Ministers or officials; what outcomes the Government is seeking from that work; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180464","180464"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29550","2013-12-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, for what reasons the UK voted against Palestinian membership of the Olive Council.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180428","180428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29551","2013-12-16","Ministry of Justice","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to section 8.2 of his Department's research paper, The strength and skills of the Judiciary in the Magistrates' Courts, Ministry of Justice Research Series 9/11, dated November 2011, for what reasons a volunteer cost of £10 per magistrate per hour is include within the costs directly associated with magistrates; and which other studies follow this approach.","Biography information for Lord Beith","Sir Alan Beith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180429","180429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29552","2013-12-16","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what capital grants were made by Arts Council England for culture-based projects in each region in (a) 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012 and (d) 2013 to date.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180430","180430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29553","2013-12-16","Ministry of Justice","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse (a) per hour, (b) per case and (c) per year of deploying (i) a district judge and (ii) a bench of three magistrates to reside over cases in magistrates' courts; and what the component elements are of that estimate in each case.","Biography information for Lord Beith","Sir Alan Beith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180431","180431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29554","2013-12-16","Home Office","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she intends to reply to the letter to the Minister of Immigration dated 31 October 2013 from the right hon. Member for Manchester, Gorton with regard to Mr Peter Solaja.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180432","180432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29555","2013-12-16","Home Office","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she intends to reply to the letter to the Minister of Immigration dated 4 November 2013 from the right hon. Member for Manchester, Gorton with regard to Mrs S Parveen.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180433","180433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29556","2013-12-16","Home Office","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, for what reasons her Department's Balance of Compliance study was not published on 11 December 2013; and when she intends to publish this study.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180435","180435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29557","2013-12-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his Israeli counterpart on revoking Military Order 418 and returning planning powers on Area C to the Palestinian Authorities.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180436","180436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29558","2013-12-16","Department for Transport","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with First Trans-Pennine Express on the number of carriages in use on peak commuter trains between Bolton and Manchester.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Mr David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180437","180437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29559","2013-12-16","Home Office","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she intends to reply to the letter to her dated 4 November from the right hon. Member for Manchester, Gorton with regard to Ms Sultanat Khan Ahmad Khan.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180434","180434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29560","2013-12-17","Department for Education","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many two year olds in the London Borough of Southwark currently receive free early education.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180462","180462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29561","2013-12-17","Department for Transport","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 16 October 2013, Official Report, column 734, what his policy is on the proposed five per cent cap on land-based biofuels in the European Union Council negotiations on the EU Commission's proposed reform of EU-biofuel policy.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180463","180463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29562","2013-12-16","Department for Education","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of school leavers in each constituency went to (a) Russell Group Universities and (b) the University of Oxford and the University of Cambridge in the latest year for which data is available.","Biography information for Peter Aldous","Peter Aldous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180448","180448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29563","2013-12-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of annual changes in the size of the universal credit caseload in (a) 2014-15, (b) 2015-16, (c) 2016-17, (d) 2017-18 and (e) 2018-19.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180449","180449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29564","2013-12-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how large the universal credit caseload will be in (a) 2014-15, (b) 2015-16, (c) 2016-17, (d) 2017-18 and (e) 2018-19.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180450","180450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29565","2013-12-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many lorries of live farm animals intended for further fattening or slaughter have been inspected by the Animal Health and Veterinary Laboratories Agency at (a) the point of loading, (b) the Port of Dover and (c) at both loading and at the Port of Dover in each month since 1 May 2013; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Charlie Elphicke","Charlie Elphicke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180438","180438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29566","2013-12-16","Ministry of Justice","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisons in England and Wales were (a) publicly-managed and (b) privately-run or contracted out to be run by the private sector in (i) 2009-10, (ii) 2010-11, (iii) 2011-12 and (iv) 2012-13.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180451","180451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29567","2013-12-17","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 9 December 2013, Official Report, column 13W, on energy: prices, for what reasons he has not held any meeting where he has asked energy companies to lower or not increase their prices.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180473","180473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29568","2013-12-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many statutory notices for breaches of welfare during transport legislation have been issued at the Port of Dover against lorries of live farm animals intended for further fattening or slaughter in each month since 1 May 2013; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Charlie Elphicke","Charlie Elphicke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180440","180440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29569","2013-12-17","Department of Health","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has for reconfiguration of acute hospital trusts providing healthcare to the populations of north Cheshire and south Merseyside.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180474","180474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29570","2013-12-17","Ministry of Justice","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many assaults on (a) prisoners and (b) prison staff there were (i) in HM Prison Lewes and (ii) on average in all adult prisons in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180475","180475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29571","2013-12-16","Department for Education","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to tackle poor performance in school and academy sixth forms.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180465","180465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29572","2013-12-16","Department for Education","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many (a) schools and (b) academy sixth forms have success rates in the education of 16 to 19 year olds lower than the minimum performance levels expected of further education colleges in that area.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180466","180466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29573","2013-12-16","Ministry of Justice","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of prisons in England and Wales were subject to the Freedom of Information Act 2000 in (a) 2009-10, (b) 2010-11, (c) 2011-12 and (d) 2012-13.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180441","180441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29574","2013-12-16","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if she will make an assessment of the value of bringing forward legislative proposals to allow the reintroduction of standing areas for English football club stadia.","Biography information for Caroline Dinenage","Caroline Dinenage","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180467","180467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29575","2013-12-16","Department for Education","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when (a) he, (b) the Minister of State for Schools and (c) the Minister of State for Skills and Enterprise received a copy of Ofsted's Annual Report 2013.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180468","180468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29576","2013-12-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 18 November 2013, Official Report, column 669W, on employment and support allowance, with what medical conditions those people transferred from incapacity benefit to an employment and support allowance work-related activity group without being seen by an assessor have been diagnosed; and how many such people have been diagnosed with each such condition.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180442","180442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29577","2013-12-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to increase the number of people advanced a learner loan in order to undertake an apprenticeship.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180469","180469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29578","2013-12-16","Department for Education","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when he plans to close his Department's 2012-13 financial accounts.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180470","180470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29579","2013-12-16","Department for Education","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether Ofsted released its annual 2013 Annual Report to media organisations before 10.00am on 11 December 2013.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180471","180471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29580","2013-12-16","Leader of the House","2013-12-12","To ask the Leader of the House, what steps he has taken to ensure that the parliamentary Counsel are made aware of the UK's international human rights obligations relating to children including the United Nations Convention on the Rights of the Child.","Biography information for Sarah Teather","Sarah Teather","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180443","180443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29581","2013-12-16","Department of Health","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much the NHS spent in what is now Harlow constituency in (a) 2006-07, (b) 2008-09, (c) 2010-11 and (d) 2012-13.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180444","180444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29582","2013-12-16","Home Office","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will place in the Library records of all the consultations received during the impact assessment for the Immigration Bill in relation to her statutory safeguarding children duties as set out in Section 55 of the Borders, Citizenship and Immigration Act 2009 from (a) the Office of the Children's Champion and (b) other bodies.","Biography information for Sarah Teather","Sarah Teather","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180472","180472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29583","2013-12-16","Ministry of Justice","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate his Department has made of the proportion of prisons in England and Wales that will be subject to the Freedom of Information Act 2000 by May 2015.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180445","180445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29584","2013-12-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many statutory notices for breaches of welfare during transport legislation have been issued at the point of loading for lorries of live farm animals intended for further fattening or slaughter in each month since 1 May 2013; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Charlie Elphicke","Charlie Elphicke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180446","180446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29585","2013-12-17","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what plans she has to review her Department's allocation of capital for culture projects to ensure that areas across the country are treated equitably.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180452","180452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29586","2013-12-16","Ministry of Justice","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the effect of the legal aid reform on family law costs; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Baroness McIntosh of Pickering","Miss Anne McIntosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180447","180447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29587","2013-12-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of incapacity benefit and employment and support allowance claimants waited longer than (a) one week, (b) two weeks, (c) three weeks and (d) one month to have their benefit claim processed in each year since 2006.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180453","180453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29588","2013-12-17","Department for Education","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what guidance he gives further education colleges on action to take if after intervention from the Education Funding Agency they receive insufficient funding from a local authority for a student with high needs.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180454","180454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29589","2013-12-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many lorries of live farm animals intended for further fattening or slaughter have left at the Port of Dover in each month since 1 May 2013; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Charlie Elphicke","Charlie Elphicke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180439","180439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29590","2013-12-17","Department for Education","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to ensure that all local authorities provide sufficient funding to (a) further education, (b) sixth form colleges and (c) specialist colleges that educate 16 to 25 year olds with high needs in 2014-15.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180455","180455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29591","2013-12-17","Department for Education","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many schools have raised concerns with (a) his Department and (b) the Education Funding Agency on the amount of funding they have received from local authorities to educate pupils with high needs aged (a) five to 15 and (b) 16 to 25 years.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180456","180456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29592","2013-12-16","Cabinet Office","2013-12-12","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people aged 22 or over resident in each (a) local authority area and (b) parliamentary constituency were employed in jobs paying less than the national minimum wage in 2013.","Biography information for Mr William Bain","Mr William Bain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180489","180489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29593","2013-12-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when he plans to respond to the letter from the hon. Member for Basildon and Billericay of 23 August 2013 and subsequent letters of 15 October, 8 November and 9 December 2013 on Ms Gillian Willis.","Biography information for Mr John Baron","Mr John Baron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180457","180457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29594","2013-12-17","Department of Health","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the reasons for variations in the uptake of treatments for rheumatoid arthritis.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180458","180458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29595","2013-12-17","Department for Transport","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many times tolls have been suspended on the Lower Thames Crossing since October 2011.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180490","180490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29596","2013-12-17","Home Office","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many asylum seekers are (a) currently seeking asylum in the UK and (b) waiting to be returned to their country of origin.","Biography information for Lindsay Roy","Lindsay Roy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180459","180459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29597","2013-12-17","Ministry of Justice","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the prevalence of gang-related violence in youth offender institutions.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180491","180491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29598","2013-12-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the value to the UK of the British Council; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lindsay Roy","Lindsay Roy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180460","180460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29599","2013-12-17","Ministry of Justice","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to improve the transition of young offenders from custody back into mainstream society.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180492","180492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29600","2013-12-17","Department of Health","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of children in youth offender institutions suffer from mental health disorders.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180493","180493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29601","2013-12-17","Department for Education","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many registered child care places in the London Borough of Southwark there were in (a) 2009, (b) 2010, (c) 2011, (d) 2012 and (e) 2013.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180461","180461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29602","2013-12-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what progress he expects the Sri Lankan government to make on an independent investigation into war crimes and human rights abuses before the UK decides not to pursue a resolution on an international inquiry at the UN Human Rights Council in March 2014.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180494","180494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29603","2013-12-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his international counterparts on (a) the text of a UN Human Rights Council resolution on Sri Lanka for the session in March 2014 calling for an international inquiry, (b) the terms of reference for such an inquiry and (c) the membership of such an inquiry.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180495","180495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29604","2013-12-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with which members of the UN Human Rights Council he has discussed the case for an independent, international inquiry into the Sri Lankan civil war; and what recent assessment he has made of the strength of international support for such an inquiry.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180496","180496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29605","2013-12-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the ability and willingness of the Sri Lankan government to conclude an independent investigation into alleged war crimes before March 2014; and what criteria he has set for such an inquiry to be considered credible.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180497","180497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29606","2013-12-16","HM Treasury","2013-12-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will introduce the rural fuel duty discount for those independent fuel stations having a rateable value below £50,000.","Biography information for Baroness McIntosh of Pickering","Miss Anne McIntosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180476","180476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29607","2013-12-17","Cabinet Office","2013-12-12","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment he has made of the use of digital government services by those on the lowest incomes and unemployed.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180498","180498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29608","2013-12-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department is taking to support small businesses in Hendon constituency in accessing finance.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180477","180477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29609","2013-12-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department is taking to reduce the pressure of regulation on small businesses.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180478","180478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29610","2013-12-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent discussions he has had with the Minister for the Cabinet Office on the red tape challenge.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180479","180479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29611","2013-12-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of how his Department's retail strategy will benefit retailers in Hendon constituency.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180480","180480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29612","2013-12-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 9 December 2013, Official Report, columns 49-50W, on universal credit, for what reason the estimated annual saving of £1.3 billion differs from the figure of £2.2 billion contained in his Department's Impact Assessment of December 2012; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180483","180483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29613","2013-12-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department is taking to support the retail industry.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180481","180481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29614","2013-12-16","Department of Health","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make an assessment of the potential benefits of dispensing Bexsero under general prescription.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180482","180482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29615","2013-12-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average processing times were for incapacity benefit claims in (a) each quarter of (i) 2006 and (ii) 2007 and (b) the first two quarters of 2008; and what the average processing times for employment and support allowance were in (1) the second two quarters of 2008 and (2) each subsequent quarter to date.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180484","180484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29616","2013-12-17","Department of Health","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of the effects of reductions in local authority budgets on bed blocking in NHS hospitals.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180485","180485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29617","2013-12-17","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 9 December 2013, Official Report, column 13W, on energy: prices, how many meetings he had with the big six energy companies in November 2013.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180486","180486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29618","2013-12-17","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 9 December 2013, Official Report, column 13W, on energy: prices, what estimate he has made of the cost of providing the information requested on the dates of meetings.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180487","180487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29619","2013-12-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many companies have (a) been announced as being the recipient of and (b) received money related to the advanced manufacturing supply chain initiative in rounds (i) one, (ii) two, (iii) three and (iv) four to date.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180488","180488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29620","2013-12-17","Department for Transport","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many vehicles have used the Lower Thames Crossing while tolls were suspended since October 2011; and what estimate he has made of the value of the fees foregone.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180506","180506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29621","2013-12-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much funding his Department allocated to the Troubled Families initiative in each of the last three years; and how much funding he expects to allocate to this initiative in each year to 2015.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180499","180499"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29622","2013-12-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how his Department works with the Ministry of Justice, the Home Office and the Department for Education in delivering the Troubled Families initiative.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180500","180500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29623","2013-12-17","Department of Health","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Answer of 13 May 2013, Official Report, column 38W, on cancer, what measures the Clinical Commissioning Group Outcomes Indicator Set 2014/15 will include to drive improvements on five year cancer survival rates.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180507","180507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29624","2013-12-17","Department of Health","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to improve one and five year cancer survival rates for older people.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180508","180508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29625","2013-12-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Statement of 2 December 2013, Official Report, column 629, on energy bills, what discussions he has had with (a) British Gas, (b) RWE Npower, (c) Scottish Power and (d) SSE on the effect of the changes to green levies on household energy bills.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180501","180501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29626","2013-12-17","Department of Health","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to reduce the difference between cancer survival rates in the UK and comparable European countries.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180509","180509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29627","2013-12-16","Department for Transport","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the recent announcement by the Office of Rail Regulation of investment in the North Wales coast mainline, what the timetable is for the signalling improvements to the line.","Biography information for Guto Bebb","Guto Bebb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180502","180502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29628","2013-12-16","Department for Transport","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effects of the review of Local Transport Note 2/95 on policy and practice of devolved government in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180503","180503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29629","2013-12-17","Ministry of Defence","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many military attachés were part of British diplomatic missions in (a) 1990, (b) 2000, (c) 2010 and (d) 2013.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180510","180510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29630","2013-12-16","Department for Transport","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether (a) Local Transport Note 2/95 continues to apply and (b) the Zebra, Pelican and Puffin Pedestrian Crossings Regulations and General Directions 1997 remain in force in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180504","180504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29631","2013-12-17","Ministry of Defence","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, to which British diplomatic missions a military attaché is currently attached.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180511","180511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29632","2013-12-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the median pay was in each sector of Government sponsored apprenticeships in each of the last three years; and what the median pay for each such sector in each such year was for (a) women and (b) men.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180505","180505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29633","2013-12-17","Ministry of Justice","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the relationship between the size of youth offenders institutions and ability to ensure the security and safety of staff and children resident there.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180512","180512"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29634","2013-12-17","Ministry of Defence","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, on what the £1.8 billion underspend from his Department's 2012-13 budget has been spent on; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180513","180513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29635","2013-12-17","Cabinet Office","2013-12-12","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Health regarding assessment of work by Deloitte under its NHS contracts for consultancy services in the first quarter of 2010.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180514","180514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29636","2013-12-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the gender breakdown was of Government-sponsored hairdressing apprenticeships in England and Wales in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180515","180515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29637","2013-12-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the gender breakdown was of Government-sponsored engineering apprenticeships in England and Wales in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180516","180516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29638","2013-12-16","HM Treasury","2013-12-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will extend the Excise Payment Security to independent petrol stations; what assessment he has made of the effect on such petrol stations of failing to apply the scheme to them; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Baroness McIntosh of Pickering","Miss Anne McIntosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180517","180517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29639","2013-12-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what work the Met Office undertakes for foreign governments.","Biography information for Margaret Curran","Margaret Curran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180525","180525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29640","2013-12-16","Department for Transport","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, on how many occasions the M62 between Leeds and Manchester was closed to traffic due to (a) road accidents and (b) inclement weather conditions in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180518","180518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29641","2013-12-16","Department for Transport","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, on how many occasions the A57 Snake Pass between Glossop and the Rivelin Valley was closed to traffic due to (a) road accidents and (b) inclement weather conditions in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180519","180519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29642","2013-12-17","Department of Health","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of fractures by (a) men and (b) women aged 50 or over of the (i) hip, (ii) wrist, (iii) vertebra, (iv) femur, (v) neck and (vi) knee can be attributed to osteoporosis in each of the last 10 years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180526","180526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29643","2013-12-17","Department of Health","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) men and (b) women aged 50 or over have broken a (i) hip, (ii) wrist, (iii) vertebra, (iv) femur, (v) neck and (vi) knee in each of the last 10 years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180527","180527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29644","2013-12-16","Department for Transport","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent estimate his Department has made of the total number of (a) UK, (b) EEA and (c) non-EEA nationals employed as ratings on ships qualified on for the tonnage tax scheme.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180520","180520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29645","2013-12-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what work the Met Office undertakes for the (a) Scottish Government, (b) Welsh Assembly Government and (c) Northern Ireland Executive.","Biography information for Margaret Curran","Margaret Curran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180528","180528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29646","2013-12-16","Department for Transport","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, on how many occasions in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12 and (c) 2012-13 the A628 between Flouch and Mottram was closed to traffic because of (i) road accidents and (ii) weather conditions.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180521","180521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29647","2013-12-16","Department for International Development","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 25 November 2013, Official Report, columns 70-1W, on Afghanistan, how many Afghan nationals were trained in the Bost Airfield and Agricultural Park programme; how many of them were trained outside Afghanistan; and in what other countries they were trained.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180522","180522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29648","2013-12-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the (a) average gross hourly pay and (b) median annual salary was of Government-sponsored hairdressing apprenticeships in England and Wales in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180523","180523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29649","2013-12-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the (a) average gross hourly pay and (b) median annual salary was of Government-sponsored engineering apprenticeships in England and Wales in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180524","180524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29650","2013-12-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the value of receipts in each of the last five financial years from the additional premium applied to automatic fire sprinkler systems as part of plant and machinery valuations for the purposes of business rates is.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180529","180529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29651","2013-12-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department is taking to ensure small businesses can receive assured advice on regulation.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180530","180530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29652","2013-12-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what meetings and discussions took place between (a) Ministers and (b) officials of his Department and (i) the Financial Conduct Authority, (ii) the Prudential Regulation Authority and (iii) the Serious Fraud Office on Mr Lawrence Tomlinson's report on RBS ahead of its publication.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180531","180531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29653","2013-12-17","Home Office","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to make a comprehensive estimate of the number of non-EU international students who leave the UK at the end of their studies.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180558","180558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29654","2013-12-17","Ministry of Justice","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many sex offenders are held at HM Prison Lewes; and how many places on sex offender treatment programmes are available at that prison.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180559","180559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29655","2013-12-16","Ministry of Defence","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 10 December 2013, Official Report, column 198W, on unmanned air vehicles, whether he will place in the Library copies of the factual reports, studies and trials on which the legal review is based.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180532","180532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29656","2013-12-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the progress of the grant-assisted alleviation of shingle migration and flooding at Teal Bay, Morecambe.","Biography information for David Morris","David Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180560","180560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29657","2013-12-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the progress of construction of sea wall defences in the Hest Bank and Teal Bay area of Morecambe.","Biography information for David Morris","David Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180561","180561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29658","2013-12-16","Department for Transport","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 10 December 2013, Official Report, column 198W, on unmanned air vehicles, which RPAS-related departmental polices are informed by the Cross-Government Working Group on Remotely Piloted Aircraft Systems.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180544","180544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29659","2013-12-17","Department for Education","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what role non-executive members of his Department's board play in directing the work of officials in his Department.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180562","180562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29660","2013-12-17","Department for Education","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what office facilities are provided for non-executive members of his Department's board in his Department's buildings.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180563","180563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29661","2013-12-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to his Department's Impact Assessment on Child maintenance reforms: CSA case closure, introducing CMS fees, supporting family-based arrangements, dated 31 March 2013, (a) on what basis and (b) over what period his Department has estimated that the amount of the child maintenance fee income expected to accrue during the transition from the present two statutory schemes to the new 2012 statutory scheme will be £2,220 million.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180533","180533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29662","2013-12-16","Department for Transport","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he expects to publish his Department's green paper on the safety of young drivers.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180534","180534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29663","2013-12-16","Ministry of Defence","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 10 December 2013, Official Report, columns 197-8W, on unmanned air vehicles, if he will disclose details of the funding provided by the United States Visiting Forces (USVF) to meet their day-to-day activities at RAF Croughton and RAF Moleworth identified by reference to each (a) unit present, (b) activity carried out and (c) facility used by USVF.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180546","180546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29664","2013-12-17","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many officials in her Department are working on allowing same-sex couples to convert their civil partnerships to marriages.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180545","180545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29665","2013-12-16","Ministry of Defence","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 10 December 2013, Official Report, column 197W, on unmanned air vehicles, if his Department will implement the recommendations of the UN Special Rapporteur on Counter-Terrorism in paragraph 78 of his September 2013 report.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180547","180547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29666","2013-12-16","Department for Transport","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he plans to publish the outcome of his Department's consultation on Regulations about the new offence of driving with a controlled drug in the body above a specified limit; and when he plans to consult on the proposed such limit for amphetamines.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180535","180535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29667","2013-12-16","HM Treasury","2013-12-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the gender breakdown was of people in receipt of tax credits in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180536","180536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29668","2013-12-17","Department for International Development","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what grants her Department has granted in contravention of UK policy on restrictions, embargoes and sanctions since May 2010.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180541","180541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29669","2013-12-16","Ministry of Defence","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 10 December 2013, Official Report, column 198W, on unmanned air vehicles, what local force protection is currently provided for or planned by Royal Navy and Royal Fleet Auxiliary vessels.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180548","180548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29670","2013-12-17","Department for International Development","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much she personally gave approval to be granted to the TradeMark Southern Africa project.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180540","180540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29671","2013-12-17","Department for International Development","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many (a) meetings, (b) telephone calls, (c) letters and (d) other forms of communication she and her Ministers have had with TradeMark Southern Africa in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180539","180539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29672","2013-12-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the proportion of the total discretionary housing budget that was spent during the first six months of 2013-14.","Biography information for Guto Bebb","Guto Bebb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180542","180542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29673","2013-12-16","Department for Transport","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what material on the current or proposed use of remotely piloted aircraft systems in UK airspace is collated by or on behalf of the Cross-Government Working Group on remotely piloted aircraft systems.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180543","180543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29674","2013-12-16","Ministry of Defence","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer to the hon. Member for Moray, of 15 October 2013, Official Report, column 640W, on unmanned air vehicles, whether his Department has overseen the development of any technologies used in the five new Reaper aircraft to enhance interoperability of those assets between the UK and NATO allied forces.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180549","180549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29675","2013-12-16","Ministry of Defence","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department has taken to promote the interoperability of capabilities and systems at RAF Waddington with the UK's NATO allies in 2013.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180550","180550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29676","2013-12-17","Department for International Development","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much has been clawed back from sums allocated to TradeMark Southern Africa.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180538","180538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29677","2013-12-16","Department of Health","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 22 October 2013, Official Report, column 82W, on radiotherapy, who sat on the panel reviewing stereotactic radiosurgery; and when he expects NHS England to publish the results of that study.","Biography information for Tessa Munt","Tessa Munt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180551","180551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29678","2013-12-17","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, when her Department plans to hold a consultation on broadcast advertising rights for community radio stations.","Biography information for Guto Bebb","Guto Bebb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180537","180537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29679","2013-12-16","Department of Health","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 3 September 2013, Official Report, columns 349-50W, on cancer, how many patients were treated with gamma knife stereotactic radiosurgery at (a) Sheffield Teaching Hospitals NHS Trust, (b) Nova Healthcare in Leeds, (c) the Thornberry Radiosurgery Centre, Sheffield, (d) Bart's Health, London and (e) BUPA-Cromwell, London in each of the last five years; and how many such centres have reached the maximum number of patients allowed under the terms of their contract to provide such surgery in 2013-14.","Biography information for Tessa Munt","Tessa Munt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180552","180552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29680","2013-12-16","Department of Health","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 9 December 2013, Official Report, column 96W, on gender recognition, what the average waiting time from GP referral to an appointment at a gender identity clinic was in (a) the North West and (b) England in each of the last three years for which data are available.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180555","180555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29681","2013-12-16","Department of Health","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 9 December 2013, Official Report, column 96W, on gender recognition, how many people have been referred to gender identity clinics in each of the last three years for which data are available.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180556","180556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29682","2013-12-18","Cabinet Office","2013-12-12","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the number of children being cared for by a single parent in (a) Ribble Valley constituency, (b) Lancashire and (c) the UK.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180564","180564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29683","2013-12-16","Department of Health","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 15 October 2013, Official Report, column 703W, on health services, how many patients have agreed to be transferred from University College London Hospital to (a) BUPA-Cromwell, London and (b) HCA Bart's hospital for gamma knife radiosurgery treatment.","Biography information for Tessa Munt","Tessa Munt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180553","180553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29684","2013-12-16","Ministry of Justice","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many incidences of (a) suicide, (b) attempted suicide and (c) self-harm there were (i) in HM Prison Lewes and (ii) on average in all adult prisons in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180557","180557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29685","2013-12-18","Department of Health","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to promote campaigns to tackle breast cancer.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180565","180565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29686","2013-12-18","Department for Education","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to increase the number of young people who speak a second language.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180566","180566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29687","2013-12-16","Department of Health","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 15 October 2013, Official Report, column 703W, on health services, what the procedure is for patients to exercise their legal right to choose where they are treated after they have waited longer than 18 weeks for treatment.","Biography information for Tessa Munt","Tessa Munt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180554","180554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29688","2013-12-18","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps his Department is taking to promote education about energy and climate change among adults and children in the UK.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180567","180567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29689","2013-12-16","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps she is taking to promote tennis participation to people between the ages of 16 and 25; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180587","180587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29690","2013-12-16","Department of Health","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 9 December 2013, Official Report, columns 107-8W on vaccination: immigrants, which group is responsible for the commissioning of the specific vaccination programmes recommended by the World Health Organisation and National Institute for Health and Care Excellence for newly-arrived migrants from areas with high prevalence of a particular disease; and who is responsible for commissioning hepatitis B vaccinations for newly arrived migrants from areas of high prevalence of this disease.","Biography information for Lord Blunkett","Mr David Blunkett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180568","180568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29691","2013-12-17","Department for Education","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children are in receipt of social services, by local authority in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180600","180600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29692","2013-12-17","Department for Education","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much each local authority spent on child protection services per head of children receiving those services in 2012-13.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180601","180601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29693","2013-12-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the number of small businesses in (a) England, (b) London and (c) Hendon constituency UKTI has helped to start exporting.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180569","180569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29694","2013-12-17","Department of Health","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of people between 10 and 16 years old had received at least one dose of the MMR vaccine as at 31 May 2013.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180602","180602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29695","2013-12-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate his Department has made of the number of new apprenticeship schemes created in (a) England, (b) London and (c) Hendon constituency since 2010.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180570","180570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29696","2013-12-16","Home Office","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what her policy is on the Scottish Government's proposal for joint working between the UK and Scottish security services in the early period after independence, contained in the Scottish Government document, Scotland's Future: Your Guide to an Independent Scotland.","Biography information for Margaret Curran","Margaret Curran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180588","180588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29697","2013-12-17","Department for International Development","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how her Department has implemented the Building Stability Overseas Strategy since 2011; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Martin Horwood","Martin Horwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180603","180603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29698","2013-12-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how his Department has implemented the Building Stability Overseas Strategy since 2011; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Martin Horwood","Martin Horwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180604","180604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29699","2013-12-16","Department of Health","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of provision of kidney transplant services to minority ethnic groups; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180589","180589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29700","2013-12-17","Home Office","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she has made an assessment of the specialist capabilities of the National Crime Agency currently used by Police Scotland.","Biography information for Margaret Curran","Margaret Curran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180605","180605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29701","2013-12-16","HM Treasury","2013-12-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment he has made of the effects of the Commissioners' Directions on passenger information on the UK's general aviation sector.","Biography information for Mr Steve Baker","Steve Baker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180571","180571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29702","2013-12-16","Department of Health","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to reduce the inequalities in the provision of renal disease prevention and management.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180590","180590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29703","2013-12-17","Home Office","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department has given any support to the Scottish Government in (a) tackling cyber crime or (b) combating cyber attacks against the Scottish Government.","Biography information for Margaret Curran","Margaret Curran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180606","180606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29704","2013-12-16","Department for Transport","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will estimate the number of (a) pelican, (b) puffin and (c) countdown crossings in operation.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180572","180572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29705","2013-12-16","Department of Health","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the report by the British Kidney Patient Association entitled Kidney health: delivering excellence.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180591","180591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29706","2013-12-16","Department for Transport","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will estimate the number of new (a) pelican and (b) puffin crossings installed in (i) 2010, (ii) 2011 and (iii) 2012.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180573","180573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29707","2013-12-17","HM Treasury","2013-12-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will suspend fines against official UK motorcycle importers arising from unforeseen consequences of the recent Notification of Vehicle Arrivals (NOVA) legislation, pending development of NOVA procedures for those importers.","Biography information for Mr Steve Baker","Steve Baker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180607","180607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29708","2013-12-16","Home Office","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what activities the National Crime Agency currently conducts in Scotland.","Biography information for Margaret Curran","Margaret Curran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180592","180592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29709","2013-12-16","Department for Transport","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many local highways authorities installed pelican crossings in (a) 2010, (b) 2011 and (c) 2012.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180574","180574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29710","2013-12-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to introduce a new system of electronic certification to facilitate the export of poultry meat and breeding stock.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180608","180608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29711","2013-12-16","Department for Transport","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the latest estimate his Department has made is of the total number of (a) UK, (b) EEA and (c) non-EEA seafarers working on ships qualified for the tonnage tax scheme.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180593","180593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29712","2013-12-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will defend the poultry industry against accusations of dumping made by the International Trade Administration Commission of South Africa.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180609","180609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29713","2013-12-16","HM Treasury","2013-12-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will publish the (a) strategic and (b) commercial links to the UK that (i) owners and (ii) managers of vessels applying for inclusion in the tonnage tax scheme are required to demonstrate in order to qualify for that scheme.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180594","180594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29714","2013-12-16","HM Treasury","2013-12-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will publish the (a) strategic and (b) commercial links to the UK that (i) owners and (ii) managers of vessels that have qualified for the tonnage tax scheme have demonstrated in each year that the scheme has been in operation.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180595","180595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29715","2013-12-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the (a) median and (b) mean (i) annual and (ii) hourly salary is for (A) men and (B) women in Government-sponsored apprenticeship schemes; and what the equivalent figures were in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180596","180596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29716","2013-12-17","Department of Health","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much funding has been allocated to NHS Protect in each year since 2005.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180610","180610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29717","2013-12-16","Department for Transport","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the puffin pedestrian crossing accident study published by TRL in March 2011, for what reasons his Department permits local authorities to install new pelican crossings.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180575","180575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29718","2013-12-17","Department of Health","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will place in the Library copies of correspondence between Peter Coates and Deloitte MCS Limited on 5 February and 10 February 2010.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180611","180611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29719","2013-12-16","Department for Transport","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of whether available research evidence permits firm conclusions about the relative safety performance of pelican and other types of pedestrian crossing; and what guidance his Department issues to local authorities on that matter.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180576","180576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29720","2013-12-17","Department of Health","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many staff are employed by the NHS Trust Development Authority; which external consultants the NHS Trust Development Authority employs; and at what cost such staff are employed.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180612","180612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29721","2013-12-16","Department for Transport","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will issue guidance to local authorities on the dangers of pelican crossings on roads with multi-lane approaches.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180577","180577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29722","2013-12-16","Department for Transport","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 26 March 2012, to the hon. Member for Hertsmere, Official Report, columns 947-8W, on aviation: Hertfordshire, how many meetings Ministers from his Department have had with counterparts in the Department for Communities and Local Government on general planning issues relating to strategic rail freight interchanges since June 2010; and at how many such meetings the Radlett application was mentioned.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180597","180597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29723","2013-12-17","Department of Health","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what procedure will be used to appoint a new chairman of NHS Property Services.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180613","180613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29724","2013-12-17","Home Office","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what her policy is on the Scottish Government's proposal to continue to recognise any currently valid UK passports until their expiry date in the event of Scottish independence, as proposed in the Scottish Government document: Your Guide to an Independent Scotland.","Biography information for Margaret Curran","Margaret Curran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180614","180614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29725","2013-12-16","Department for Transport","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 26 March 2012, to the hon. Member for Hertsmere, Official Report, columns 947-8W, on aviation: Hertfordshire, when the conversation with the hon. Member for Bromley and Chislehurst took place and whether it was minuted.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180598","180598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29726","2013-12-17","Home Office","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which capabilities included in the original e-Borders business case (a) have been taken out of scope and (b) are under consideration for taking out of scope; and what the estimated cost was of each of those capabilities as defined at the time of the original tender.","Biography information for Stephen Barclay","Stephen Barclay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180615","180615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29727","2013-12-16","Home Office","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to her Department's overarching impact assessment of the Immigration Bill, published on 14 October 2013, if she will publish a breakdown of the £4.71 million estimated as the net annual cost to business.","Biography information for Stephen Barclay","Stephen Barclay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180599","180599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29728","2013-12-17","Home Office","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much her Department spent on compliance costs for enforcement of legislation relating to (a) academic institutions and (b) marriages in each of the last five years; how many full-time equivalent staff work on such compliance activity; and what estimate she has made of the amount her Department will spend annually on compliance with new legislation relating to (i) private sector landlords and (ii) NHS staff.","Biography information for Stephen Barclay","Stephen Barclay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180616","180616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29729","2013-12-17","Home Office","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many children were entered onto the UK Border Agency database in each of the last five years; how many alerts requiring investigation were generated from that data, excluding false positives; and what the estimated cost of those investigations was.","Biography information for Stephen Barclay","Stephen Barclay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180617","180617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29730","2013-12-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will review the methodology used by the Government for full base-line badger population analysis to ensure that inaccuracies caused by (a) weather, (b) disease and (c) any other factors are addressed.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180578","180578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29731","2013-12-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will estimate the cost to his Department of aligning the accounting treatment of profits from self-employment for the purpose of universal credit applications with the treatment of self-employment for tax purposes.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180620","180620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29732","2013-12-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will bring forward proposals for more accurate badger population counts.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180579","180579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29733","2013-12-17","Department of Health","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many hospital chaplains were working in the NHS in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180621","180621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29734","2013-12-17","Department for International Development","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what amount has been spent by schemes supported by her Department in Zimbabwe since May 2010.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180622","180622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29735","2013-12-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will support a badger vaccination trial in the South West of England in order to compare the effectiveness and cost-effectiveness of a vaccination programme with (a) the badger cull pilots and (b) gassing as a means of culling.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180580","180580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29736","2013-12-17","Home Office","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the capability to reconcile a passenger arriving on a foreign national passport and leaving on a UK passport as included in the original e-Borders business case, what body or company is responsible for delivering that capability; and by what date that capability is expected to be delivered.","Biography information for Stephen Barclay","Stephen Barclay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180618","180618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29737","2013-12-17","Home Office","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will estimate the likely cost to the public purse of adding fingerprint verification to second generation passports.","Biography information for Stephen Barclay","Stephen Barclay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180619","180619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29738","2013-12-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will publish the full costs of the extended pilot badger culls (a) in total and (b) for each badger culled to (i) the public purse and (ii) landowners.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180581","180581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29739","2013-12-17","Department for Education","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many hours of education or training children receive each week in (a) young offenders institutions and (b) secure training centres.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180623","180623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29740","2013-12-17","Ministry of Defence","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many attacks by unmanned aerial vehicles were carried out by British armed forces in (a) Afghanistan and (b) Pakistan in the last three years.","Biography information for Lindsay Roy","Lindsay Roy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180624","180624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29741","2013-12-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will review the membership of the Independent Expert Panel on the badger cull pilots to introduce additional scientific expertise; and if he will invite suggestions from independent organisations on the composition of that panel.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180582","180582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29742","2013-12-16","Ministry of Defence","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Answer of 9 December 2013, Official Report, column 70W, on unmanned aerial vehicles, what the (a) unit, (b) service and (c) rank is of each of the United States Visiting Forces personnel based at (i) RAF Croughton and (ii) RAF Marham.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180625","180625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29743","2013-12-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will take steps to ensure that the remit of the Independent Expert Group on the badger cull pilot includes specific reference to monitoring humaneness, safety and effectiveness during (a) the original cull period and (b) the extended cull period.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180583","180583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29744","2013-12-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will publish immediately and in full (a) transcripts of all meetings of the Independent Expert Group on the badger cull pilot, (b) evidence presented to that group and (c) that group's report.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180584","180584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29745","2013-12-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will ensure that Parliament has an opportunity to debate the Independent Expert Panel's report on the pilot badger culls before his Department makes any decision to proceed with further culls.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180585","180585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29746","2013-12-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make it his policy that decisions on any further badger culls will only be taken following a debate in the House on a substantive motion relating to such culls.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180586","180586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29123","2013-12-17","Home Office","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many early morning restriction orders have been imposed since their introduction.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180176","180176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29124","2013-12-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate his Department has made of the average annual expenditure on energy for off-grid gas households.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180142","180142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29125","2013-12-17","Home Office","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many late night levies have been imposed since their introduction.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180177","180177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29126","2013-12-17","Department of Health","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when the steering group to reduce the admission of young people with alcohol dependency will next convene.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180178","180178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29127","2013-12-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how much electricity capacity which was connected directly to the distribution network there was in each of the last 16 years.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180143","180143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29128","2013-12-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how much installed electricity capacity connected directly to the transmission capacity there was in each of the last 16 years.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180144","180144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29129","2013-12-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 28 November 2013, Official Report, column 398, on energy security, how many of the new gas plants that have come online since May 2010 (a) received planning consent and (b) began construction before May 2010.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180145","180145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29130","2013-12-17","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what her policy is on the (a) drinking and (b) advertising of alcohol in cinemas.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180179","180179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29131","2013-12-16","Home Office","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, to what extent Europol shares information with Interpol; and what steps Europol takes to ensure that information it relies on has not been obtained by Interpol in breach of human rights.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180062","180062"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29132","2013-12-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 28 November 2013, Official Report, column 397, on green policies, what assessment his Department has made of satisfaction ratings for the Green Deal.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180146","180146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29133","2013-12-16","Department of Health","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress has been made in implementing the National Institute for Health and Care Excellence guidelines on perinatal mental health.","Biography information for Annette Brooke","Annette Brooke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180063","180063"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29134","2013-12-16","Department of Health","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the (a) demand for and (b) capacity of perinatal mental health services in each NHS trust area.","Biography information for Annette Brooke","Annette Brooke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180064","180064"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29135","2013-12-16","Department of Health","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of mother and baby mental health units have been running over capacity in the last five years.","Biography information for Annette Brooke","Annette Brooke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180065","180065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29136","2013-12-16","Home Office","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much Interpol has charged and received for providing major event support teams in (a) the UK and (b) EU member states in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180066","180066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29137","2013-12-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many (a) black-owned and (b) minority ethnic group-owned businesses in the UK have been granted an Enterprise Finance Guarantee loan by the Partnership banks to date.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180067","180067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29138","2013-12-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much was spent on ministerial salaries in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180090","180090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29139","2013-12-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many female-led businesses in the UK have been granted an Enterprise Finance Guarantee loan by the Partnership banks to date.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180068","180068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29140","2013-12-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to his Answer of 11 June 2012, Official Report, column 282W, on universal credit, what recent estimate he has made of IT development and implementation costs related to universal credit in (a) 2013-14 and (b) 2014-15.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180069","180069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29141","2013-12-16","Attorney General","2013-12-11","To ask the Attorney General, how much was spent on ministerial salaries in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180091","180091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29142","2013-12-16","Speaker's Committee for Independent Parliamentary Standards Authority","2013-12-11","To ask the hon. Member for Broxbourne, representing the Speaker's Committee for the Independent Parliamentary Standards Authority, how much in total was spent in salary costs to all hon. Members for performance of their parliamentary duties in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180070","180070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29143","2013-12-16","Cabinet Office","2013-12-11","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much was spent on ministerial salaries in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180092","180092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29144","2013-12-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much was spent on ministerial salaries in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180093","180093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29145","2013-12-16","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how much was spent on ministerial salaries in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180094","180094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29146","2013-12-16","Cabinet Office","2013-12-11","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many unemployed households with children there were in the London Borough of Southwark in (a) 2009, (b) 2010, (c) 2011, (d) 2012 and (e) 2013.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180072","180072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29147","2013-12-16","Ministry of Defence","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much was spent on ministerial salaries in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180095","180095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29148","2013-12-16","Department for Education","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much was spent on ministerial salaries in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180096","180096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29149","2013-12-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how much was spent on ministerial salaries in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180097","180097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29150","2013-12-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much was spent on ministerial salaries in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180098","180098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29151","2013-12-16","Cabinet Office","2013-12-11","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many in-work households with children there were in the London Borough of Southwark in (a) 2009, (b) 2010, (c) 2011, (d) 2012 and (e) 2013.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180073","180073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29152","2013-12-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how much was spent on ministerial salaries in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180099","180099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29153","2013-12-16","Women and Equalities","2013-12-11","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, how much was spent on ministerial salaries in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180100","180100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29154","2013-12-16","Department of Health","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much was spent on ministerial salaries in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180101","180101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29155","2013-12-16","Home Office","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 5 December 2013, Official Report, column 762W, on Interpol, for what reasons it is not possible for figures for Red Notices for UK nationals issued by other countries to be provided.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180071","180071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29156","2013-12-16","Home Office","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much was spent on ministerial salaries in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180102","180102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29157","2013-12-16","Department for International Development","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much was spent on ministerial salaries in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180103","180103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29158","2013-12-16","HM Treasury","2013-12-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many households in the London Borough of Southwark received child tax credits in (a) 2009, (b) 2010, (c) 2011, (d) 2012 and (e) 2013.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180074","180074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29159","2013-12-16","Ministry of Justice","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much was spent on ministerial salaries in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180104","180104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29160","2013-12-16","Leader of the House","2013-12-11","To ask the Leader of the House, how much was spent on ministerial salaries in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180105","180105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29161","2013-12-16","Northern Ireland Office","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how much was spent on ministerial salaries in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180106","180106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29162","2013-12-16","Scotland Office","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how much was spent on ministerial salaries in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180107","180107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29163","2013-12-16","Department for Transport","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much was spent on ministerial salaries in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180108","180108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29164","2013-12-16","HM Treasury","2013-12-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much was spent on ministerial salaries in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180109","180109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29165","2013-12-16","Wales Office","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how much was spent on ministerial salaries in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180110","180110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29166","2013-12-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much was spent on ministerial salaries in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180111","180111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29167","2013-12-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average annual income of non-single parent households in the London Borough of Southwark was in (a) 2009, (b) 2010, (c) 2011, (d) 2012 and (e) 2013.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180075","180075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29168","2013-12-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average annual income of single parent households in the London Borough of Southwark was in (a) 2009, (b) 2010, (c) 2011, (d) 2012 and (e) 2013.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180076","180076"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29169","2013-12-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 28 November 2013, Official Report, column 390, on energy efficiency, how many insulation measures were installed in (a) 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012 and (d) 2013.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180147","180147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29170","2013-12-16","Ministry of Justice","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many staff at HM Prison Oakwood have less than one year's service at this establishment.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180077","180077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29171","2013-12-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Statement of 31 October 2013, Official Report, column 1096, by what criteria he will assess the level of transparency of the fianancial accounts of the energy companies.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180152","180152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29172","2013-12-16","Ministry of Justice","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners have been kept overnight in (a) police cells and (b) court cells in each month since May 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180078","180078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29173","2013-12-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 28 November 2013, Official Report, column 390, on energy efficiency, how many insulation measures were installed through (a) Warm Front, (b) CERT, (c) CESP and (d) ECO.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180148","180148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29174","2013-12-16","Ministry of Justice","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much of the victim surcharge has gone uncollected since the surcharge was introduced.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180079","180079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29175","2013-12-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what his policy is on vertical integration in the electricity industry.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180112","180112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29176","2013-12-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Statement of 31 October 2013, Official Report, column 1095, on Annual Energy Statement, by what criteria he will assess the state of competition in the energy markets.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180153","180153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29177","2013-12-16","Ministry of Justice","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much of the victim surcharge has been (a) collected and (b) uncollected in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180080","180080"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29178","2013-12-16","Department of Health","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his policy is on the use of cannabis in the treatment of multiple sclerosis.","Biography information for Mr Mark Williams","Mr Mark Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180113","180113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29179","2013-12-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how the Work Programme has performed against its targets for those leaving prison in each month since the Programme's inception.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180081","180081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29180","2013-12-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent steps he has taken to reduce the risks to the environment posed by Chinese lanterns.","Biography information for Harriett Baldwin","Harriett Baldwin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180149","180149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29181","2013-12-16","Department of Health","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent studies his Department has commissioned on the medicinal uses of cannabis.","Biography information for Mr Mark Williams","Mr Mark Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180114","180114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29182","2013-12-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many dogs and puppies entered the UK under the Balai Directive in the last 12 months; how old these animals were; and what their country of origin was.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180154","180154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29183","2013-12-16","Department of Health","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress has been made on improving the prevention and detection of perinatal mental health issues.","Biography information for Annette Brooke","Annette Brooke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180115","180115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29184","2013-12-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate his Department has made of the market share of (a) British Gas, (b) E.ON, (c) EDF, (d) RWE npower, (e) SSE and (f) Scottish Power in the domestic (i) electricity and (ii) gas supply market in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180082","180082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29185","2013-12-16","Department for Education","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many schools relinquished School Direct places which had been allocated to them in 2012-13 for training commencing in 2013-14; and to which primary phase or secondary subject each such place related.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180150","180150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29186","2013-12-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate his Department has made of the increase in incidences of zoonotic diseases entering the UK since the relaxation of the regulations under the pet travel scheme in January 2012; and what action his Department plans to take in response to recent rabies cases in the Netherlands and France.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180155","180155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29187","2013-12-16","Department of Health","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much funding each NHS Trust and Foundation Trust has (a) allocated and (b) been spent on perinatal mental health services in the last five years.","Biography information for Annette Brooke","Annette Brooke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180116","180116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29188","2013-12-16","Home Office","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent discussions she has had with the National Crime Agency on its work in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180122","180122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29189","2013-12-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Statement of 2 December 2013, Official Report, column 630, on energy bills, if he will place in the Library a copy of his Department's assessment of the energy freeze proposal.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180083","180083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29190","2013-12-16","Cabinet Office","2013-12-11","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether the support of a majority of employees is required for the spinning out of an organisation as an employee-owned or employee-led public service mutual.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180156","180156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29191","2013-12-16","Department for Education","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the proportion of pupils that will sit the EBacc at GCSE in (a) 2014 and (b) 2015.","Biography information for Peter Aldous","Peter Aldous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180117","180117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29192","2013-12-16","Department for Education","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many school days were lost in England this year due to strike action in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Peter Aldous","Peter Aldous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180118","180118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29193","2013-12-16","Cabinet Office","2013-12-11","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment he has made of the effect of the National Citizen Service on Peterborough constituency; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stewart Jackson","Mr Stewart Jackson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180157","180157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29194","2013-12-16","Department for Education","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, in which local education authority in England average per pupil funding is the (a) highest and (b) lowest.","Biography information for Peter Aldous","Peter Aldous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180119","180119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29195","2013-12-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Statement of 31 October 2013, Official Report, column 1095, if he will publish the terms of reference of the annual review of the state of competition in the energy markets.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180084","180084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29196","2013-12-16","Department of Health","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the proportion of people in the latest survey with suspected cancer is who have seen a cancer specialist within the two weeks target in (a) Donacaster and (b) South Yorkshire.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180158","180158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29197","2013-12-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to encourage local communities to fund social enterprises through crowdfunding.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180120","180120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29198","2013-12-16","Home Office","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to improve the tourist visa application process.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180085","180085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29199","2013-12-16","Home Office","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to refine the working visa application process.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180086","180086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29200","2013-12-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate his Department has made of how many people are eligible for the Warm Home discount core group rebate in (a) 2013-14 and (b) 2014-15.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180159","180159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29201","2013-12-16","Cabinet Office","2013-12-11","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the amount donated to UK charitable organisations through UK crowdfunding platforms in the last year","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180121","180121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29202","2013-12-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if he will require all electricity suppliers to pay the Warm Home discount in (a) 2014 and (b) 2015.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180160","180160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29203","2013-12-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he was first informed that some claimants would not transfer to universal credit by the end of 2017-18.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180087","180087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29204","2013-12-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate his Department has made of the number of customers eligible for the Warm Home discount who are not customers of suppliers who participate in the scheme.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180161","180161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29205","2013-12-16","HM Treasury","2013-12-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether maternity and paternity pay will be included in the cap on welfare spending announced in the Autumn Statement 2013.","Biography information for Fiona O'Donnell","Fiona O'Donnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180088","180088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29206","2013-12-16","HM Treasury","2013-12-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many Her Majesty's Revenue and Customs staff based in Nottingham are employed on work relating to the introduction of universal credit.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180089","180089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29207","2013-12-16","Department for Education","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether a Teach First trainee who is recruited to focus on mathematics can switch subject specialism after two years.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180151","180151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29208","2013-12-16","Department for International Development","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent discussions her Department has had with (a) the Organisation for Economic Co-operation and Development, (b) the World Bank and (c) other international bodies on improving the tax collecting capabilities of developing countries","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180132","180132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29209","2013-12-16","Department for International Development","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is taking to help developing countries develop their own capital markets.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180133","180133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29210","2013-12-16","Home Office","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment she has made of the operation of the National Crime Agency in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180123","180123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29211","2013-12-16","Home Office","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people aged over 65 have been murdered in each year since 2010; and how many people have been (a) charged with and (b) convicted of such murders to date.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180124","180124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29212","2013-12-16","Ministry of Justice","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 9 October 2013, Official Report, column 308W, on prison sentences, if he will provide a gender breakdown of the figures contained in Table 3.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180134","180134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29213","2013-12-16","Home Office","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people from which country of origin were granted asylum on grounds of religious persecution in each year since 2007.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180125","180125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29214","2013-12-16","Home Office","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the speed and methods by which missing people are traced.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180126","180126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29215","2013-12-16","Home Office","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people of each age group and gender are currently registered as missing.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180127","180127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29216","2013-12-16","Ministry of Defence","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 12 June 2013, Official Report, column 327W, on unmanned aerial vehicles, what recent discussions he has had with his international counterparts on the legality of the armed drones programme.","Biography information for Annette Brooke","Annette Brooke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180135","180135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29217","2013-12-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to his Answer of 28 November 2013, Official Report, column 386, on decarbonisation, what the evidential basis is for the statement that £31 billion has been invested in renewable electricity since 2010.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180193","180193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29218","2013-12-16","HM Treasury","2013-12-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people in (a) Stafford and (b) the UK were claiming each of the major in-work benefits in each of the last 10 years; and what the cost of such benefits was to the Exchequer.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180128","180128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29219","2013-12-16","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate she has made of the amount invested in UK creative industries through UK crowdfunding platforms in the last year.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180129","180129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29220","2013-12-16","Department for Transport","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the commitment on page 10 of the National Infrastructure Plan to invest £5 million during 2014-15 in a large-scale electric vehicle readiness programme for public sector fleets,  what that programme will include; how many public sector contracts will be awarded under this investment; and when the procurement procedure for this process will start.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180136","180136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29221","2013-12-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 28 November 2013, Official Report, column 385, on decarbonisation, what estimate his Department has made of the difference in cost to consumers of setting a decarbonisation target in (a) 2014 and (b) 2016.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180194","180194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29222","2013-12-16","Department for International Development","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent assessment her Department has made of the work of the Commonwealth Development Corporation.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180130","180130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29223","2013-12-16","Ministry of Defence","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether military, civil servants and privately contracted staff within the Defence Equipment and Support plus will receive different terms and conditions of employment for similarly qualified and graded positions.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180137","180137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29224","2013-12-16","Department for International Development","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to tackle drug-resistant strains of tuberculosis in developing countries.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180131","180131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29225","2013-12-16","Department for International Development","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many women have been involved in senior negotiations and decisions on the UKs withdrawal from Afghanistan; and what proportion of the total number of senior negotiators and decision makers this figure represents.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180138","180138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29226","2013-12-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment she has made of progress in the human rights situation in Sri Lanka as a result of the UK presence at CHOGM.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180139","180139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29227","2013-12-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the possible effects of Scottish independence on the UK diplomatic network.","Biography information for Ann McKechin","Ann McKechin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180162","180162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29228","2013-12-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if he will make it his policy to introduce a ring-fence between generation and supply businesses in vertically integrated energy companies.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180140","180140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29229","2013-12-16","Ministry of Defence","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what representations his Department has received from the Scottish Government in the last 12 months on the proposed transfer of armed forces personnel in the event of Scottish independence, as outlined in Scotland's Future: Your Guide to An Independent Scotland.","Biography information for Ann McKechin","Ann McKechin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180163","180163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29230","2013-12-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate his Department has made of the number of pre-payment energy customers who are in fuel poverty.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 18014","18014"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29231","2013-12-16","Cabinet Office","2013-12-11","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what representations his Department has received from the Scottish Government in the last 12 months on continuity of employment of UK Government civil servants working in Scotland in the event of Scottish independence, as outlined in Scotland's Future: Your Guide to An Independent Scotland.","Biography information for Ann McKechin","Ann McKechin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180164","180164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29232","2013-12-16","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what representations her Department has received from the Scottish Government in the last 12 months on the proposed establishment of a joint venture between the BBC and a Scottish Broadcasting Service in the event of Scottish independence, as outlined in Scotland's Future: Your Guide to An Independent Scotland.","Biography information for Ann McKechin","Ann McKechin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180165","180165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29233","2013-12-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 28 November 2013, Official Report, column 398, on energy security, if he will make a statement on the proposals for 12 new nuclear reactors.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180180","180180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29234","2013-12-16","Home Office","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what representations her Department has received from the Scottish Government in the last 12 months on the proposed continued membership of the Common Travel Area for residents of an independent Scotland, as outlined in Scotland's Future: Your Guide to An Independent Scotland.","Biography information for Ann McKechin","Ann McKechin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180166","180166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29235","2013-12-16","Department of Health","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of patients were provided with a GP appointment within 48 hours in (a) Doncaster and (b) South Yorkshire for the last quarter for which figures are available.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180167","180167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29236","2013-12-16","HM Treasury","2013-12-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he plans to answer question 177828 from the hon. Member for Middlesbrough South and East Cleveland tabled on 26 November 2013.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180171","180171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29237","2013-12-16","Department for Education","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether it is possible for a school to bid for and be allocated to a School Direct place for a physics trainee teacher without having a trained physics teacher as a member of staff.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180168","180168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29238","2013-12-16","Cabinet Office","2013-12-11","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what change there has been in median gross weekly pay for (a) men and (b) women in Middlesbrough South and East Cleveland constituency since 2010.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180172","180172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29239","2013-12-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 28 November 2013, Official Report, column 392, on energy efficiency, what the evidential basis is for the statement that over 100,000 Green Deal measures are to be installed in people's homes.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180195","180195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29240","2013-12-16","Attorney General","2013-12-11","To ask the Attorney General, how many local Crown Prosecution Service offices were located in the same building as the police force for that area in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180169","180169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29241","2013-12-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, which local authorities are currently in breach of the Code of Recommended Practice on Local Authority Publicity.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180173","180173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29242","2013-12-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to Oral Answer of 28 November 2013, Official Report, column 390, on energy efficiency, what the evidential basis is for the statement that 4.8 million insulation measures have been installed through Government schemes.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180196","180196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29243","2013-12-16","Attorney General","2013-12-11","To ask the Attorney General, if he will list (a) the Crown Prosecution Service offices in England and Wales that have closed since 2010, (b) the function of each such office and (c) the number of (i) voluntary and (ii) compulsory redundancies at each such office.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180170","180170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29244","2013-12-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to his Answer of 28 November 2013, Official Report, column 394, on energy costs, what the evidential basis for the statement is that there has been a huge increase in wholesale gas prices.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180181","180181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29245","2013-12-16","Ministry of Defence","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the application of project trust funds to defence contracts.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180182","180182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29246","2013-12-16","Home Office","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much Interpol major event support teams cost for the London 2012 Summer Olympics.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180174","180174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29247","2013-12-16","Ministry of Defence","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the staffing of the new DE&S+ security will be; whether it will use existing Civil Service grades; and what accountability arrangements there will be.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180183","180183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29248","2013-12-16","Department for International Development","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will attend the Sanitation and Water for All high level meeting in Washington DC on 11 April 2014.","Biography information for Naomi Long","Naomi Long","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180206","180206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29249","2013-12-16","Department for Education","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many School Direct numbers were requested by school clusters by (a) primary phase and (b) secondary subject (i) nationally and (ii) by English region; and how many places were allocated by the National College of Teaching and Leadership to those school clusters in the 2014-15 allocations.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180175","180175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29250","2013-12-16","Ministry of Defence","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when the new DE&S+ entity will be established; when he expects it to take over the running of procurement for his Department; and when he expects the service pillars to transfer to the new entity.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180184","180184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29251","2013-12-16","HM Treasury","2013-12-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make it his policy to adopt the gross output measure of the economy developed by the US Bureau of Economic Analysis in order to reveal the total sales volume at all stages of production in the UK.","Biography information for Mr Steve Baker","Steve Baker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180207","180207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29252","2013-12-16","Department for Transport","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will ensure that the Crown Dependencies are consulted on the recommendations of the Airports Commission before a decision on this matter is made.","Biography information for Mr Steve Baker","Steve Baker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180208","180208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29253","2013-12-16","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, which Minister is accountable to Parliament for (a) oversight of broadband roll-out in Wales and (b) the funding of Sianel Pedwar Cymru.","Biography information for Guto Bebb","Guto Bebb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180185","180185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29254","2013-12-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the government of Sudan on the protection of civilians in armed conflict.","Biography information for Mr William Bain","Mr William Bain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180209","180209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29255","2013-12-16","Department for Education","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many teacher education places have been allocated by the National College of Teaching and Leadership for (a) each secondary subject and (b) primary phase (i) nationally and (ii) by English region to (A) HE providers, (B) SCITTs, (C) School Direct and (D) salaried School Direct.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180190","180190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29256","2013-12-16","Department for International Development","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the number of fatalities from yellow fever in Sudan's West and Southern Kordofan states in the last year.","Biography information for Mr William Bain","Mr William Bain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180210","180210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29257","2013-12-16","Ministry of Defence","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to his Statement of 10 December 2013, Official Report, columns 146-8, on defence procurement, whether he will publish an impact assessment of the changes announced.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180186","180186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29258","2013-12-16","Department for Education","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, on what basis his Department agreed the allocations of teacher education places in 2014-15 by the National College of Teaching and Leadership to meet the future need for primary and secondary subject teachers.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180191","180191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29259","2013-12-16","Ministry of Defence","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he expects the chief executive of the arm's length company that will run DE&S will also act as Chief of Defence Materiel.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180187","180187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29260","2013-12-16","Ministry of Defence","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will details the breakdown of the costs incurred to date by his Department in establishing a GoCo and running the tendering process.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180188","180188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29261","2013-12-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to his Statement of 2 December 2013, Official Report, column 628, on energy bills, what the evidential basis is for the statement that changes to the  energy company obligation will result in a reduction in bills of between £30 and £35.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180203","180203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29262","2013-12-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to his Statement of 2 December 2013, Official Report, column 627, on energy bills, what the evidential basis is for the statement that (a) rising wholesale energy costs and (b) investment in energy infrastructure are the main driver of energy price rises.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180197","180197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29263","2013-12-16","Home Office","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many sexual offences reported to the police in the last five years occurred (a) more than 20 years ago, (b) between one and 20 years ago and (c) in the last year.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180189","180189"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29264","2013-12-16","Department for International Development","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what representations she has made to the United Nations on the polio vaccination campaign that had been due to take place in Sudan's Southern Kodorfan and Blue Nile states.","Biography information for Mr William Bain","Mr William Bain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180211","180211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29265","2013-12-16","Department for International Development","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the effect of the recent polio vaccination campaign in Sudan's Southern Kordofan and Blue Nile states.","Biography information for Mr William Bain","Mr William Bain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180212","180212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29266","2013-12-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to his Statement of 2 December 2013, Official Report, column 631, on energy bills, when his Department will publish the (a) consultation paper and (b) impact assessment on the proposed changes to the energy company obligation.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180204","180204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29267","2013-12-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to his statement of 2 December 2013, Official Report, column 631, on energy bills, what assessment his Department has made of the distributional effects of paying for social and environmental obligations on (a) energy bills and (b) taxes.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180205","180205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29268","2013-12-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he has taken to ensure that adequate support is being offered to people in financial hardship following the abolition of crisis loans and community care grants.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180213","180213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29269","2013-12-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to his Statement of 2 December 2013, Official Report, column 627, on energy bills, what the evidential basis is for the statement that the Government is increasing competition in the energy market.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180198","180198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29270","2013-12-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to his Statement of 2 December 2013, Official Report, column 627, on energy bills, what measures he has taken to force the energy companies to (a) open up their books and (b) justify price rises to customers.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180199","180199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29271","2013-12-16","Department for Education","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what funding his Department provides to advertise marriage and relationship support courses; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Selous","Andrew Selous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180192","180192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29272","2013-12-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to his Statement of 2 December 2013, Official Report, column 627, on energy bills, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of Ofgem's retail market review on consumer engagement in the energy market.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180200","180200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29273","2013-12-16","Department for Transport","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, for what reasons undamaged stretches of steel central reservation barriers are being replaced with concrete ones; what the cost of new concrete barrier installation is; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180214","180214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29274","2013-12-16","Ministry of Justice","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much of the Government's funding for rape support centres has been spent in each region in each year since 2011.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180215","180215"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29275","2013-12-16","Ministry of Justice","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which domestic violence helplines received how much funding in each year since 2011.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180216","180216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29276","2013-12-16","Ministry of Justice","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which rape support centres have received what funding in each year since 2011.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180217","180217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29277","2013-12-16","HM Treasury","2013-12-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, which benefits (a) will and (b) will not be included in the welfare cap.","Biography information for Dr Alasdair McDonnell","Dr Alasdair McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180218","180218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29278","2013-12-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many women in each region have received an exemption from conditions applied to claimants of jobseeker's allowance because they have been victims of domestic violence since April 2012.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180219","180219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29279","2013-12-16","Ministry of Defence","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many apprenticeships are offered in the Army in each year.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180234","180234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29280","2013-12-16","Department for Transport","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the practicality of fitting sensors to heavy goods vehicles for the protection of cyclists.","Biography information for Sir Graham Brady","Mr Graham Brady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180220","180220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29281","2013-12-16","Ministry of Defence","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many apprenticeships the Army offers each year; and what steps he is taking to ensure that figure is reached in 2013 and 2014.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180235","180235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29282","2013-12-16","Department for Education","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if his Department will make an assessment of how the position of England in the recent PISA results tables, published on 3 December 2013 by the Organisation for Economic Co-operation and Development, would have differed if the rest of England performed at the same level as the Trafford local education authority area.","Biography information for Sir Graham Brady","Mr Graham Brady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180221","180221"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29283","2013-12-16","Ministry of Defence","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to ensure that regular Army numbers are maintained until the numbers of those serving in the Territorial Army is increased to prevent a manpower shortfall arising from his restructuring plans.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180236","180236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29284","2013-12-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to his Statement of 2 December 2013, Official Report, column 627, on energy bills, what the evidential basis is for the statement that Ofgem's reforms for competition in the retail market are making it easier for consumers to (a) understand their bills, (b) work out where they can get the best deal and (c) switch providers.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180201","180201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29285","2013-12-16","HM Treasury","2013-12-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if his Department will make an assessment of the potential effect on financial markets of a move to staggering the release of economically sensitive headline data and supporting tables by the Office for National Statistics.","Biography information for Sir Graham Brady","Mr Graham Brady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180222","180222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29286","2013-12-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assistance his Department offers to construction companies in the Middle East and North Africa to prevent disruption of their work.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180237","180237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29287","2013-12-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to his Statement of 2 December 2013, Official Report, column 628, on energy bills, (a) when and (b) how the £12 rebate to domestic electricity customers will be paid.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180202","180202"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29288","2013-12-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to his Statement of 2 December 2013, Official Report, column 635, on energy bills, what estimate his Department has made of the likely reductions in solid wall insulations as a result of the proposed change to the energy company obligation.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180223","180223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29289","2013-12-16","Ministry of Justice","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people were received into custody for contempt of court in each month since January 2012.","Biography information for John Hemming","John Hemming","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180224","180224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29290","2013-12-16","Ministry of Defence","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to work better with the Department for International Development.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180238","180238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29291","2013-12-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, with reference to section 3 of his Department's response to the Energy and Climate Change Select Committee's Report on Energy prices, profits and poverty, published on 10 October 2013, HC 717, if he will make it his policy to require energy companies to disclose their trading profits in their segmental statements.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180239","180239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29292","2013-12-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, with reference to section 3 of his Department's response to the Energy and Climate Change Select Committee's Report on Energy prices, profits and poverty, published on 10 October 2013, HC 717, what assessment his Department has made of the effectiveness of segmental statements provided by the vertically integrated energy companies.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180240","180240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29293","2013-12-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 10 December 2013, Official Report, column 157W, on the Curzon Institute, whether the contract agreed with the Curzon Institute (a) was advertised beforehand and (b) open to other organisations invited to bid for it.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180225","180225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29294","2013-12-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate his Department has made of the (a) number and (b) proportion of off-grid gas households who are in fuel poverty.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180241","180241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29295","2013-12-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 10 December 2013, Official Report, column 157W, on the Curzon Institute, how much his Department is paying the Curzon Institute under this contract.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180226","180226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29296","2013-12-16","HM Treasury","2013-12-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many publicans have been in receipt of tax credits in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Tessa Munt","Tessa Munt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180242","180242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29297","2013-12-16","Ministry of Justice","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will make it his policy to offer parents legal aid for placement proceedings involving their children.","Biography information for John Hemming","John Hemming","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180243","180243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29298","2013-12-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 10 December 2013, Official Report, column 157W, on the Curzon Institute, whether Afzal Amin was involved in negotiating this contract.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180227","180227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29299","2013-12-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 10 December 2013, Official Report, column 157W, on the Curzon Institute, if he will publish the minutes of meetings between his Department and the Curzon Institute at which this contract was discussed.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180228","180228"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29300","2013-12-16","Department of Health","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many nurses are engaged in full-time daily care of patients in (a) England and (b) Greater London.","Biography information for Simon Hughes","Simon Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180254","180254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29301","2013-12-16","HM Treasury","2013-12-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what proportion of income tax paid by those in Scotland is paid by (a) basic rate, (b) higher rate and (c) additional rate taxpayers.","Biography information for Margaret Curran","Margaret Curran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180229","180229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29302","2013-12-16","Department of Health","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the rate of pay is of each grade of nurse working in (a) administration, (b) education and (c) clinical care in (i) England and (ii) Greater London; and how many nurses were working in each such grade at the latest date for which figures are available.","Biography information for Simon Hughes","Simon Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180255","180255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29303","2013-12-16","HM Treasury","2013-12-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many (a) basic rate, (b) higher rate and (c) additional rate taxpayers there were in total and in each constituent part of the UK in 2012-13.","Biography information for Margaret Curran","Margaret Curran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180230","180230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29304","2013-12-16","Department for Education","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the number of (a) primary and (b) secondary school places needed by 2020 in (i) England, (ii) Greater London and (iii) the London Borough of Southwark.","Biography information for Simon Hughes","Simon Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180256","180256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29305","2013-12-16","Ministry of Defence","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the financial savings that would be achieved over a 10 year period from (a) the Defence Equipment and Support plus model and (b) a government-owned, contractor-operated entity.","Biography information for Sir Peter Luff","Peter Luff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180231","180231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29306","2013-12-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how much his Department has budgeted to spend on research into (a) carbon capture and storage and (b) carbon capture and use in the next five years.","Biography information for Laura Sandys","Laura Sandys","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180232","180232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29307","2013-12-16","Department for International Development","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is taking to ensure that the commitment to distribute 4.5 million mosquito nets in Ghana by 2015 is reached.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180233","180233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29308","2013-12-16","Department of Health","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will issue guidance to employers and employees on identifying signs of early dementia; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180264","180264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29309","2013-12-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what forecast his Department has made of the capacity of Eggborough Power Station in (a) 2014-15, (b) 2015-16, (c) 2016-17, (d) 2017-18 and (e) 2018-19.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180257","180257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29310","2013-12-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many solid wall installations he expects to be completed in financial years (a) 2013-14, (b) 2014-15, (c) 2015-16 and (d) 2016-17.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180244","180244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29311","2013-12-16","Attorney General","2013-12-11","To ask the Attorney General, how much the Crown Prosecution Service has spent on administering witness care units in each of the last seven years.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180258","180258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29312","2013-12-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the total spend on fuel poverty measures will be for 2013 compared to each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180245","180245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29313","2013-12-16","Attorney General","2013-12-11","To ask the Attorney General, how many Crown Prosecution Service staff were employed in front-line witness care in each of the last seven years.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180259","180259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29314","2013-12-16","Department of Health","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make an assessment of the potential effect on local services of NHS England's proposed changes to the funding formula for NHS Wakefield Clinical Commissioning Group.","Biography information for Sir Kevin Barron","Mr Kevin Barron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180310","180310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29315","2013-12-16","Department of Health","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make an assessment of the potential effect on local services of NHS England's proposed changes to the funding formula for NHS North Kirklees Clinical Commissioning Group.","Biography information for Sir Kevin Barron","Mr Kevin Barron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180311","180311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29316","2013-12-16","Home Office","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of appeals for witnesses in criminal investigations.","Biography information for Simon Hughes","Simon Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180260","180260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29317","2013-12-16","Department of Health","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make an assessment of the potential effect on local services of NHS England's proposed changes to the funding formula for NHS Leeds South and East Clinical Commissioning Group.","Biography information for Sir Kevin Barron","Mr Kevin Barron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180312","180312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29318","2013-12-16","Cabinet Office","2013-12-11","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what plans his Department has to (a) support and (b) increase the number of youth workers in Greater London.","Biography information for Simon Hughes","Simon Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180261","180261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29319","2013-12-16","Department of Health","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make an assessment of the potential effect on local services of NHS England's proposed changes to the funding formula for NHS Leeds West Clinical Commissioning Group.","Biography information for Sir Kevin Barron","Mr Kevin Barron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180313","180313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29320","2013-12-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, with reference to table 1.2 of his Department's statutory security of supply report, published October 2013, if he will list each plant scheduled to close in (a) 2013-14, (b) 2014-15, (c) 2018-19, (d) 2019-20 and (e) 2023-24.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180246","180246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29321","2013-12-16","Department of Health","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make an assessment of the potential effect on local services of NHS England's proposed changes to the funding formula for NHS Greater Huddersfield Clinical Commissioning Group.","Biography information for Sir Kevin Barron","Mr Kevin Barron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180314","180314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29322","2013-12-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what new resources he has made available for new nuclear research through (a) the National Nuclear Laboratory, (b) University of Manchester, (c) the Nuclear Decommissioning Authority, (d) Nuclear Advanced Manufacturing Research Centre and (e) the Technology Strategy Board; what projects at what value have been given support; and what the source of funding has been in each case.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180265","180265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29323","2013-12-16","Department of Health","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make an assessment of the potential effect on local services of NHS England's proposed changes to the funding formula for NHS Bradford City Clinical Commissioning Group.","Biography information for Sir Kevin Barron","Mr Kevin Barron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180315","180315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29324","2013-12-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many people under 21 (a) started and (b) completed an apprenticeship in each of the 33 London local authorities in (i) 2010, (ii) 2011, (iii) 2012 and (iv) 2013 to date.","Biography information for Simon Hughes","Simon Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180262","180262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29325","2013-12-16","Department of Health","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make an assessment of the potential effect on local services of NHS England's proposed changes to the funding formula for NHS Leeds North Clinical Commissioning Group.","Biography information for Sir Kevin Barron","Mr Kevin Barron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180316","180316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29326","2013-12-16","Department of Health","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make an assessment of the potential effect on local services of NHS England's proposed changes to the funding formula for NHS Bradford Districts Clinical Commissioning Group.","Biography information for Sir Kevin Barron","Mr Kevin Barron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180317","180317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29327","2013-12-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, with reference to paragraph 1.16 of his Department's Statutory security of supply report, published October 2013, what estimate he has made of the time required to make each mothballed plant operational.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180247","180247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29328","2013-12-16","Home Office","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the procedures used on animals at Imperial College London; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180263","180263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29329","2013-12-16","Department of Health","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make an assessment of the potential effect on local services of NHS England's proposed changes to the funding formula for NHS Calderdale Clinical Commissioning Group.","Biography information for Sir Kevin Barron","Mr Kevin Barron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180318","180318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29330","2013-12-16","Department of Health","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make an assessment of the potential effect on local services of NHS England's proposed changes to the funding formula for NHS Airedale, Wharfdale and Craven Clinical Commissioning Group.","Biography information for Sir Kevin Barron","Mr Kevin Barron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180319","180319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29331","2013-12-16","Department of Health","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make an assessment of the potential effect on local services of NHS England's proposed changes to the funding formula for NHS Sheffield Clinical Commissioning Group.","Biography information for Sir Kevin Barron","Mr Kevin Barron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180320","180320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29332","2013-12-16","Department of Health","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make an assessment of the potential effect on local services of NHS England's proposed changes to the funding formula for NHS Rotherham Clinical Commissioning Group.","Biography information for Sir Kevin Barron","Mr Kevin Barron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180321","180321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29333","2013-12-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, with reference to paragraph 1.261 of the Autumn Statement, what new incentives will be in the schemes to support the take-up of energy efficiency measures.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180248","180248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29334","2013-12-16","Department of Health","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make an assessment of the potential effect on local services of NHS England's proposed changes to the funding formula for NHS Doncaster Clinical Commissioning Group.","Biography information for Sir Kevin Barron","Mr Kevin Barron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180322","180322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29335","2013-12-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if his Department will commission an assessment of the effects on employers and the additional support they may require owing to the potential increase in the number of people of employment age who have dementia as a result of the extension in retirement age; and what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Health on the needs of older workers.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180266","180266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29336","2013-12-16","Department of Health","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make an assessment of the potential effect on local services of NHS England's proposed changes to the funding formula for NHS Bassetlaw Clinical Commissioning Group.","Biography information for Sir Kevin Barron","Mr Kevin Barron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180323","180323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29337","2013-12-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment he has made of the effect of the changes to the Energy Companies Obligation announced in the Autumn Statement on meeting the UK's climate obligations for the period up to 2020.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180249","180249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29338","2013-12-16","Department of Health","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make an assessment of the potential effect on local services of NHS England's proposed changes to the funding formula for NHS Barnsley Clinical Commissioning Group.","Biography information for Sir Kevin Barron","Mr Kevin Barron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180324","180324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29339","2013-12-16","Ministry of Justice","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have received the (a) maximum fine and (b) maximum prison sentence for (i) possession and (ii) trafficking of (A) Class A drugs (B) Class B drugs and (C) Class C drugs in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180267","180267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29340","2013-12-16","Department of Health","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make an assessment of the potential effect on local services of NHS England's proposed changes to the funding formula for NHS Vale of York Clinical Commissioning Group.","Biography information for Sir Kevin Barron","Mr Kevin Barron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180325","180325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29341","2013-12-16","Department for Education","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the effects of the time taken to allocate subject knowledge enhancement places on the capacity of universities to recruit to those programmes in the 2013-14 academic year.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180298","180298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29342","2013-12-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate he has made of the average saving on energy bills for (a) those on direct debit schemes, (b) those who pay the bill upon receipt and (c) those who use prepayment meters following the changes announced in the Autumn Statement.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180250","180250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29343","2013-12-16","Department of Health","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make an assessment of the potential effect on local services of NHS England's proposed changes to the funding formula for NHS Scarborough and Ryedale Clinical Commissioning Group.","Biography information for Sir Kevin Barron","Mr Kevin Barron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180326","180326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29344","2013-12-16","Ministry of Justice","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of jails are free of illegal drug use.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180268","180268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29345","2013-12-16","Department for Education","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, for what reasons the allocation of subject knowledge enhancement places to universities in academic year 2013-14 was not made until 8 November 2013.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180299","180299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29346","2013-12-16","Department of Health","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make an assessment of the potential effect on local services of NHS England's proposed changes to the funding formula for NHS North Lincolnshire Clinical Commissioning Group.","Biography information for Sir Kevin Barron","Mr Kevin Barron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180327","180327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29347","2013-12-16","Department of Health","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make an assessment of the potential effect on local services of NHS England's proposed changes to the funding formula for NHS North East Lincolnshire Clinical Commissioning Group.","Biography information for Sir Kevin Barron","Mr Kevin Barron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180328","180328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29348","2013-12-16","Department of Health","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make an assessment of the potential effect on local services of NHS England's proposed changes to the funding formula for NHS Hull Clinical Commissioning Group.","Biography information for Sir Kevin Barron","Mr Kevin Barron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180329","180329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29349","2013-12-16","Department for Education","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what measures are in place to ensure clarity of responsibility between his Department and the Ministry of Defence over safeguarding concerns in Combined Cadet Forces.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180300","180300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29350","2013-12-16","Home Office","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the trend has been of the number of people using mephedrone since it was made a controlled drug in 2010.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180269","180269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29351","2013-12-16","Department of Health","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make an assessment of the potential effect on local services of NHS England's proposed changes to the funding formula for NHS Harrogate Rural District and Clinical Commissioning Group.","Biography information for Sir Kevin Barron","Mr Kevin Barron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180330","180330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29352","2013-12-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what discussions he has had with the insulation industry about potential job losses as a result of the changes to the Energy Companies Obligation announced in the Autumn Statement.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180251","180251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29353","2013-12-16","Department for Education","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the results of the Military ethos in schools programme.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180301","180301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29354","2013-12-16","Department of Health","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make an assessment of the potential effect on local services of NHS England's proposed changes to the funding formula for NHS Hambleton, Richmondshire and Whitby Clinical Commissioning Group.","Biography information for Sir Kevin Barron","Mr Kevin Barron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180331","180331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29355","2013-12-16","Department for Transport","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of First Great Western's recent performance and their capacity to manage passenger demand to Plymouth and the South West over the Christmas and New Year period.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180270","180270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29356","2013-12-16","Department for Education","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans he has to expand the Military ethos in schools programme.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180302","180302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29357","2013-12-16","Department of Health","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make an assessment of the potential effect on local services of NHS England's proposed changes to the funding formula for NHS East Riding of Yorkshire Clinical Commissioning Group.","Biography information for Sir Kevin Barron","Mr Kevin Barron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180332","180332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29358","2013-12-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Statement of 31 October 2013, Official Report, column 1096, on Annual Energy Statement, what the terms of reference of the report on the transparency of the financial accounts of the energy companies are; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180276","180276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29359","2013-12-16","Department for Education","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the evidential basis is for the benefits of a Military ethos in schools.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180303","180303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29360","2013-12-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate he has made of the amount by which energy companies' spending on people in fuel poverty will change over the course of the current Parliament as a result of the changes to the Energy Companies Obligation announced in the Autumn Statement.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180252","180252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29361","2013-12-16","Department for Education","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what consideration was given to sources other than the Military in the design of a programme to foster the values of self-discipline and teamwork.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180304","180304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29362","2013-12-16","Department of Health","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many beds are available to juveniles who have been sectioned under the Mental Health Act with violent behaviour as one of the indicators; and where each such bed is situated.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180271","180271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29363","2013-12-16","Department for Education","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what activities military ethos programmes in alternative provision consist of; and whether pupils can choose not to participate.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180305","180305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29364","2013-12-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the average household fuel poverty gap was for the most recent period for which figures are available; and whether he expects this to increase following the changes to the Energy Companies Obligation announced in the Autumn Statement.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180253","180253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29365","2013-12-16","Department for Education","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what alternatives to physical activities are available for those unable to take part in military ethos programmes as a result of a disability or for other reasons.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180306","180306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29366","2013-12-16","Ministry of Defence","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he expects a legal agreement between his Department and Taylor Wimpey plc to be signed in respect of the discharge of rain water from the new housing estate on former Ministry of Defence (MoD) land off Berechurch Hall Road, Colchester, into Friday Wood Brook watercourse through MoD land; what the reasons are for the time taken to conclude such an agreement; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180277","180277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29367","2013-12-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions his Department has had with Aung San Suu Kyi on visiting places in Burma where anti-Muslim violence has taken place.","Biography information for Mr David Ward","Mr David Ward","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180286","180286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29368","2013-12-16","Department for Education","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of pupils in mentoring schemes provided by Skillforce progressed into (a) further education, (b) a civil apprenticeship, (c) the armed forces and (d) other employment for each year the scheme has been available.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180307","180307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29369","2013-12-16","Ministry of Justice","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the risks posed to the Transforming Rehabilitation Probation programme by (a) insufficient and (b) delayed guidance from his Department.","Biography information for Mr Elfyn Llwyd","Mr Elfyn Llwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180272","180272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29370","2013-12-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how much funding his Department has provided to the European Marine Energy Centre in each year since 2003.","Biography information for Tom Greatrex","Tom Greatrex","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180287","180287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29371","2013-12-16","Ministry of Justice","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the cost per annum to the Probation Service in England and Wales is of supervising a person on licence for (a) 12 months, (b) 24 months and (c) 36 months.","Biography information for Mr Elfyn Llwyd","Mr Elfyn Llwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180273","180273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29372","2013-12-16","Department for Education","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what support exists for children and adoptive parents post adoption.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180341","180341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29373","2013-12-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the use of sustainable urban drainage systems to support water management in urban areas.","Biography information for Simon Hughes","Simon Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180351","180351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29374","2013-12-16","Ministry of Justice","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment the Government has made of trends in the take-up of mediation following recent legal aid changes applicable to matrimonial law.","Biography information for John Pugh","John Pugh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180342","180342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29375","2013-12-16","Ministry of Justice","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average wait for a benefit appeal tribunal hearing for benefit claimants from the Kettering constituency is; what steps he is taking to reduce these waiting times to at least the national average; and what the reasons are for the length of wait faced by claimants in Kettering constituency.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180278","180278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29376","2013-12-16","Ministry of Justice","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the risk posed to the Transforming Rehabilitation Probation programme of a failure of the programme to be delivered either in scope or within the timescale set by Ministers.","Biography information for Mr Elfyn Llwyd","Mr Elfyn Llwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180274","180274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29377","2013-12-16","Ministry of Defence","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 14 October 2013, Official Report, column 483W, how many full-time equivalent staff are assigned to work supporting the Historical Enquiries Team and the National Archives in identifying files for release.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180288","180288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29378","2013-12-16","Ministry of Justice","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the risks posed to the Transforming Rehabilitation Probation programme of insufficient Ministry of Justice capacity to manage the process due to its scale and a lack of coordination between different Ministry of Justice work streams.","Biography information for Mr Elfyn Llwyd","Mr Elfyn Llwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180275","180275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29379","2013-12-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, with reference to paragraph 38 of update 3: contract award process, final investment decision enabling for renewables, for what reason he has introduced technology-based rules to the selection process when allocating investment contracts.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180343","180343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29380","2013-12-16","Department of Health","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he has taken to implement the recommendations in the report, Tackling FGM in the UK; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180279","180279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29381","2013-12-16","Ministry of Justice","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what provision is made for video conferencing for Child Support Agency Tribunal cases when one party is unable to attend in person.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180352","180352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29382","2013-12-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, with reference to paragraph 38 of update 3: contract award process, final investment decision enabling for renewables, published by his Department on 4 December 2013, what representations he has received on the introduction of technology based rules to the selection process when allocating investment contracts.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180344","180344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29383","2013-12-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what guidance he has issued to the Child Support Agency on the implications of the Armed Forces Covenant in respect of child custody and visiting rights.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180353","180353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29384","2013-12-16","Department for Transport","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer from the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, of 26 November 2013, Official Report, column 188W, on Driver and Vehicle Agency: Coleraine, when a decision on the future of the Driver and Vehicle Agency at Coleraine will be made and announced.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180289","180289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29385","2013-12-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the level of religious freedoms for Christians in Pakistan.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180354","180354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29386","2013-12-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, with reference to update 3: contract award process, final investment decision enabling for renewables, published by his Department on 4 December 2013, how many of the applications for final investment decision enabling contracts for renewables phase 2 have engineering and construction contracts in place.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180345","180345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29387","2013-12-16","Department for International Development","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what discussions she has had with (a) her international counterparts, (b) non-governmental organisations and (c) the Philippine government about increasing investment in disaster risk reduction within the Philippines.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180280","180280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29388","2013-12-16","Department of Health","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of agency social workers employed by local authorities in 2013-14.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180361","180361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29389","2013-12-16","Department for Education","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many instances of bullying, abuse or neglect were reported by cadets in school Combined Cadet Forces in each academic year between 2010 and 2013.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180308","180308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29390","2013-12-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, with reference to update 3: contract award process, final investment decision enabling for renewables, published by his Department on 4 December 2013, how many of the applications for final investment decision enabling contracts for renewables phase 2 are expected to come online in (a) 2015, (b) 2016, (c) 2017, (d) 2018, (e) 2019 and (f) 2020 or later.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180346","180346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29391","2013-12-16","Department for International Development","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what discussions she has had with the Secretaries of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs and for Defence about the situation in the Central African Republic.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180281","180281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29392","2013-12-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he envisages all Child Support Agency arrears cases with no ongoing maintenance liabilities to be moved off the 1993 and 2003 computer systems; how many cases it is anticipated will be moved off the two computer systems at this stage; and whether all relevant cases will be transferred on to the new 2012 scheme computer system.","Biography information for Dame Anne Begg","Dame Anne Begg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180355","180355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29393","2013-12-16","Department for International Development","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is taking to increase human resources available for health services in developing countries.","Biography information for Sir Tony Cunningham","Sir Tony Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180362","180362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29394","2013-12-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what help his Department is providing to local authorities affected by the recent flooding.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180309","180309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29395","2013-12-16","Department for International Development","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what discussions she has had with the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs about European Union aid to Belarus.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180282","180282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29396","2013-12-16","Ministry of Justice","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many defendants were sentenced to between six and 12 months custody by a Crown Court for one either way offence in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180347","180347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29397","2013-12-16","Department for Education","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the effect of changes in public sector spending on services for children with special educational needs.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180363","180363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29398","2013-12-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will use a non-geographic number for the Personal Independence Payment helpline.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180348","180348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29399","2013-12-16","Department for Education","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will publish the records of monitoring visits to all Free Schools opened since May 2010.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180283","180283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29400","2013-12-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many UK-based patents have been granted for use of graphene in each year since that material's discovery.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180333","180333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29401","2013-12-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Education and his Welsh counterpart on the inclusion of educational material supporting the use of nuclear power in the national curriculum; what the cost is of the preparation of this work; and from which departmental budget it is funded.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180356","180356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29402","2013-12-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what his Department's budget is for research into (a) carbon capture and storage and (b) carbon capture and use.","Biography information for Laura Sandys","Laura Sandys","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180284","180284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29403","2013-12-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the implications of public policy on the number of UK-based patents for graphene; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180334","180334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29404","2013-12-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the evidential basis is for his Department's statement that scientific evidence shows that extreme weather events are most certainly intensifying.","Biography information for Lord Lilley","Mr Peter Lilley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180349","180349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29405","2013-12-16","Department of Health","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect of migrant health workers from developing countries working in the National Health Service.","Biography information for Sir Tony Cunningham","Sir Tony Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180357","180357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29406","2013-12-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many cases he expects to fall within each of the five segments scheduled for closure, listed in the Government's full response to the Supporting separated families; securing children's futures consultation Cm 8742.","Biography information for Dame Anne Begg","Dame Anne Begg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180364","180364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29407","2013-12-16","Department for International Development","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to address the shortage of health workers in developing countries; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Tony Cunningham","Sir Tony Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180358","180358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29408","2013-12-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many households in each (a) parliamentary constituency and (b) local authority area have been flooded in the last three years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180335","180335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29409","2013-12-16","Department for Transport","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, why policy option two, institutional reform without legislation, set out in the roads reform impact assessment was not considered in the consultation on transforming the Highways Agency.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180350","180350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29410","2013-12-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his Department has commissioned an investigation into reports by Human Rights Watch that ethnic cleansing and crimes against humanity have been committed against the ethnic Rohingya in Burma.","Biography information for Mr David Ward","Mr David Ward","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180285","180285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29411","2013-12-16","Department for Transport","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to tackle delays by the Driver and Vehicle Licensing Agency to process type approval testing for HGV trailers.","Biography information for Natascha Engel","Natascha Engel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180359","180359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29412","2013-12-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many household fires were caused by electric heaters in each of the last 10 years; and how many such fires resulted in (a) injuries and (b) fatalities.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180336","180336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/29413","2013-12-16","Department for Education","2013-12-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much children's social work departments spent on agency workers in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12 and (c) 2012-13.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 180360","180360"
