"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707671","2017-03-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with the Government of South Sudan on the deployment of UN peacekeepers in that country; and whether he plans for those peacekeepers to include UK service personnel.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66432","66432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707672","2017-03-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the stability of the official Government in Libya; and what recent progress he has made on developing Government relations with Government leaders in Libya.","Biography information for Tom Elliott","Tom Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66446","66446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707673","2017-03-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent communications he has had with the Israeli Government on the topic of Khan al-Ahmar.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66478","66478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707674","2017-03-08","Department of Health","2017-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to page 24 of the document, Children and Young People's Eating Disorder Access and Waits Commissioning Guide, published by NHS England in July 2015, when he expects NHS England to publish the tolerance level for referral to treatment for 2017-18.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66479","66479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707675","2017-03-08","Department of Health","2017-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how clinical commissioning groups have issued guidance to GPs on reducing the number of prescriptions for medicines which could be obtained over the counter.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66481","66481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707676","2017-03-08","Department of Health","2017-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of national gross domestic product was spent on social care in each year since 2010; and where the UK ranked among other countries in the EU in this regard in each such year.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66474","66474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707677","2017-03-08","Department of Health","2017-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the recovery rate has been for patients referred to the Improving Access to Psychological Therapies programme for patients receiving (a) only high intensity treatment, (b) only low intensity treatment and (c) both high and low intensity therapy in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66461","66461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707678","2017-03-07","Department for Education","2017-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of the cost of the Immigration Skills Charge to NHS and social care sponsors of Tier 2 visas in 2016-17; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66472","66472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707679","2017-03-07","Department for Education","2017-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether the revenue raised by the Immigration Skills Charge applied to NHS and social care sponsors of Tier 2 visas will be hypothecated for investment in apprenticeships in health and social care; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66471","66471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707680","2017-03-07","Department of Health","2017-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much the Government plans to spend on health and social care apprenticeships in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66470","66470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707681","2017-03-08","Department of Health","2017-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much and what percentage of Public Health England's budget was spent on mental health in each year since 2013.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66475","66475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707682","2017-03-08","Department of Health","2017-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the press release of 11 January 2016, Prime Minister pledges a revolution in mental health treatment, how much of the £290 million pledged to provide specialist care to mothers before and after having their babies has been spent to date; and on which services has such funding been spent.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66473","66473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707683","2017-03-07","Department of Health","2017-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that children and young people accessing inpatient mental health services and their families are aware of their rights and that those rights are always upheld.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66448","66448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707684","2017-03-08","Department of Health","2017-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people were treated for personality disorders in each clinical commissioning group area in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66449","66449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707685","2017-03-07","Department of Health","2017-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect of the abstinence based approach for the treatment of drug addiction on levels of deaths from drug misuse.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66453","66453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707686","2017-03-08","Department of Health","2017-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many and what proportion of care homes in Ilford North constituency were rated (a) outstanding, (b) good, (c) requires improvement and (d) inadequate in the most recent ratings exercise.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66437","66437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707687","2017-03-08","Department of Health","2017-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of GPs in Ilford North constituency were rated (a) outstanding, (b) good, (c) requires improvement and (d) inadequate in each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66438","66438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707688","2017-03-08","Department of Health","2017-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of regulation for online doctor services.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66526","66526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707689","2017-03-07","Home Office","2017-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications for asylum in the UK were made by visiting members of the Palestine Youth Orchestra during its tour of the UK during (a) July and (b) August 2016.","Biography information for Mrs Flick Drummond","Mrs Flick Drummond","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66507","66507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707690","2017-03-07","Home Office","2017-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications for asylum in the UK were made by people from the Occupied Palestinian Territories during (a) July and (b) August 2016.","Biography information for Mrs Flick Drummond","Mrs Flick Drummond","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66508","66508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707692","2017-03-07","House of Commons Commission","2017-03-03","To ask the right hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington, representing the House of Commons Commission, what proportion of schools visiting Parliament through Parliament's Education Service were fee-paying schools in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66503","66503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707693","2017-03-07","Department for International Development","2017-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment her Department has made of the risk of famine in (a) Nigeria, (b) Yemen and (c) Somalia.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66506","66506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707694","2017-03-07","Department for International Development","2017-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how her Department is working with other international donors to ensure that sufficient funding is made available for a rapid and effective response to the famine in South Sudan.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66427","66427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707695","2017-03-07","Department for International Development","2017-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how her Department plans to provide more high-impact nutrition interventions as a means of preventing famine.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66428","66428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707696","2017-03-07","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps she plans to take to ensure the independence of the Prison Officers' Pay Review Body from (a) prison service management and (b) Government.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66425","66425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707697","2017-03-07","Home Office","2017-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, (a) how many and (b) what proportion of prisoners recommended for deportation have been (i) deported and (ii) released and not deported in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66491","66491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707698","2017-03-07","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been prosecuted for offences under the Modern Slavery Act 2015 since that legislation came into force.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66482","66482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707699","2017-03-07","Home Office","2017-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether Diamond Babamuboni was deported from the UK after serving a prison sentence for manslaughter.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66492","66492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707700","2017-03-07","Northern Ireland Office","2017-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what assessment he has made of the Northern Ireland Executive's ability to meet the requirements set out in the Fresh Start document to release the £5 million Government funding in 2016-17 to tackle paramilitary activity.","Biography information for Tom Elliott","Tom Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66442","66442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707701","2017-03-07","Department for Transport","2017-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 22 February 2017 to Question 63666, on driving: licensing, what the ethnic profile is of British citizens that hold a (a) UK or (b) provisional UK driving licence.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66424","66424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707702","2017-03-07","Department for Transport","2017-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the punctuality of services on the Wrexham-Bidston train line; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66500","66500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707703","2017-03-07","Department for Transport","2017-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 3 March 2017 to Question 65245, on Gatwick Airport night flying, when he plans to establish the Commission on Civil Aviation Noise; which groups he plans to consult on that Commission's remit; and what opportunities he plans to provide for public engagement.","Biography information for Tom Tugendhat","Tom Tugendhat","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66489","66489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707704","2017-03-08","Department for Transport","2017-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the potential road safety implications of aircraft flying low over and alongside the M4 motorway in the event that a third runway is built at Heathrow Airport.","Biography information for Dr Tania Mathias","Dr Tania Mathias","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66458","66458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707705","2017-03-07","Department for Transport","2017-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to ensure train passengers are aware of their rights under the Consumer Rights Act 2015.","Biography information for Tom Tugendhat","Tom Tugendhat","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66466","66466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707706","2017-03-07","Department for Transport","2017-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to ensure companies are compliant with consumer law with particular regard to the Consumer Rights Act 2015.","Biography information for Tom Tugendhat","Tom Tugendhat","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66467","66467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707707","2017-03-07","Department for Transport","2017-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to address local authority cross-border hiring in relation to taxi and private hire vehicles.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66502","66502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707708","2017-03-07","Department for Transport","2017-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will introduce minimum national standards for taxi and private hire vehicle licenses.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66501","66501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707709","2017-03-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in (a) Wakefield constituency and (b) Wakefield Metropolitan District Council area were in receipt of the widowed parent's allowance in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66518","66518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707710","2017-03-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in (a) Wakefield constituency and (b) Wakefield Metropolitan District Council area were in receipt of the bereavement payment in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66519","66519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707711","2017-03-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in (a) Wakefield constituency and (b) Wakefield Metropolitan District Council area were in receipt of the bereavement allowance in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66517","66517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707712","2017-03-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what his most recent estimate is of the number of women in (a) Camberwell and Peckham constituency, (b) the London Borough of Southwark and (c) Greater London affected by the increase to the State Pension Age for women born after 6 April 1951.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66435","66435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707713","2017-03-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of employment and support allowance claimants who will fall below the poverty line as a result of recent changes in support to the work-related activity group.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66433","66433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707714","2017-03-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effect of the proposed supported housing funding model on the (a) level of funding to and (b) viability of women's refuges.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66447","66447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707715","2017-03-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 8 February 2017 to Question 63711, what measures the Government has put in place to prohibit energy suppliers from charging households upfront for the costs of smart meters and their installation.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66454","66454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707716","2017-03-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when he plans to publish proposals on the revision of landlord energy efficiency regulations.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66455","66455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707717","2017-03-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what his most recent estimate is of UK gas reserves; and what independent sources his Department uses to validate those estimates.","Biography information for Tom Elliott","Tom Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66443","66443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707718","2017-03-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether he plans to establish a contingency bond to cover the costs of environmental clean up in the event of a shale oil or gas company going into administration.","Biography information for Tom Elliott","Tom Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66444","66444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707719","2017-03-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what revisions he has made to his Department's forthcoming emissions reduction plan.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66490","66490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707720","2017-03-08","Department for International Trade","2017-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, pursuant to the Answer of 27 February 2017 to Question 65736, when he plans to lay the EU-Canada Comprehensive Economic and Trade Agreement before Parliament for scrutiny purposes.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66464","66464"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707721","2017-03-08","Department for International Trade","2017-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what plans he has for the House to (a) debate and (b) vote on the Comprehensive Economic and Trade Agreement as part of the process of ratification.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66457","66457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707722","2017-03-08","Department for International Trade","2017-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether he has had discussions with the Leader of the House to ensure that the 21-day ratification period for the Comprehensive Economic and Trade Agreement takes place during a time in the parliamentary calendar which contains at least one Opposition Day.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66429","66429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707723","2017-03-07","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what recent discussions his Department has had with representatives of the agricultural sector on the implications on agriculture of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66505","66505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707724","2017-03-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how much EU funding the Falkland Islands has received in each of the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66512","66512"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707725","2017-03-07","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what steps his Department has taken to engage with UK universities in relation to the negotiations on the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66504","66504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707726","2017-03-07","HM Treasury","2017-03-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he plans to include provisions relating to (a) transparency and (b) changes in foreign currency transactions in the Payment Services Regulations 2017.","Biography information for Tom Tugendhat","Tom Tugendhat","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66469","66469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707727","2017-03-07","HM Treasury","2017-03-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what progress has been made on the Government's plans to increase transparency in foreign currency transactions.","Biography information for Tom Tugendhat","Tom Tugendhat","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66468","66468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707205","2017-03-06","Cabinet Office","2017-03-02","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps his Department is taking to encourage people aged 16 or 17 to register to vote.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66274","66274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707206","2017-03-06","Cabinet Office","2017-03-02","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps the Government is taking to make registration and voting more accessible to people with disabilities.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66275","66275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707207","2017-03-06","Cabinet Office","2017-03-02","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the announcement of 27 December 2016, Press release: Eliminating electoral fraud in polling stations, when the Government plans to publish further guidance on the trial of identification in polling stations at the local government elections in May 2018; and whether the Government plans that that guidance will clarify (a) how the Government will communicate those changes to electors and (b) what training will be given to polling station staff.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66287","66287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707208","2017-03-07","Cabinet Office","2017-03-02","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much has been spent on central government procurement in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66291","66291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707209","2017-03-07","Cabinet Office","2017-03-02","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many companies owned by tax exiles have been awarded public contracts in each of the last five years for which data is available; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66293","66293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707210","2017-03-06","Cabinet Office","2017-03-02","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the HM Revenue and Customs Digital press release of 13 February 2017, Green light for Government Gateway Transformation, which future transactions will be processed through the (a) new verification service and (b) Government Digital Service platform Verify.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66306","66306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707211","2017-03-06","Cabinet Office","2017-03-02","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the Written Statement of 9 January 2015, HCWS 180, on maximising voter registration, which local authorities and organisations have received funding; how much funding each local authority or organisation received; who has responsibility for monitoring activity locally; and what evaluation processes are in place to assess the effect of that activity on under-registered groups.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66307","66307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707212","2017-03-06","Cabinet Office","2017-03-02","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to his Department's press release of 27 December 2016, Eliminating Electoral Fraud in Polling Stations, if he will carry out an equality and human rights impact assessment on the voter identification pilots; and whether he plans to make an assessment of the effect of those pilots on the demographic composition of voters in future elections.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66325","66325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707213","2017-03-07","HM Treasury","2017-03-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of reducing the tax on aviation gasoline.","Biography information for Sir Roger Gale","Sir Roger Gale","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66370","66370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707214","2017-03-06","HM Treasury","2017-03-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much (a) income tax and (b) VAT was accrued to the public purse from activities related to flight training schools in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Tom Elliott","Tom Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66376","66376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707215","2017-03-07","HM Treasury","2017-03-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 29 November 2016 to Question 55287, on Housing Infrastructure Fund, when further details will be sent out regarding that fund including when local authorities will be able to apply for funding; and when funding will be received by those authorities that apply to that fund successfully.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66396","66396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707216","2017-03-06","HM Treasury","2017-03-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what process his Department has for allocating funds for the payment for copyright licenses by the Government; and what funds were allocated for such payments in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Dowd","Jim Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66284","66284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707217","2017-03-06","HM Treasury","2017-03-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make it his policy to increase road tax for diesel vehicles.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66277","66277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707218","2017-03-06","HM Treasury","2017-03-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he plans to increase taxes on diesel fuel.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66278","66278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707219","2017-03-07","HM Treasury","2017-03-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what progress the Government has made on bringing greater transparency to foreign currency transactions.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66412","66412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707220","2017-03-07","HM Treasury","2017-03-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if the Government will take steps to make currency conversion fully transparent in forthcoming payment services regulations.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66413","66413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707221","2017-03-07","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 28 February 2017 to Question 64623, on rented housing, how much funding for help to rent projects the Government has provided to Birmingham City Council in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66411","66411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707222","2017-03-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to monitor (a) letting agent fees, (b) lease terms and (c) safety standards in rented properties.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66288","66288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707223","2017-03-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will take steps to consult on Chapters 3 and 4 of his Department's White Paper, entitled Fixing our broken housing market, Cm 9352, published in February 2017.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66309","66309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707224","2017-03-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how he plans to increase economic opportunities for women in the Northern Powerhouse.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66303","66303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707225","2017-03-07","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the oral contribution of 27 February 2017, Official Report, column 6, whether the Government plans to maintain the level of Community Infrastructure Levy returned to a community at 25 per cent once a Neighbourhood Plan is in place.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66397","66397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707226","2017-03-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the effect of business rate revaluations on the financial sustainability of private nursery providers.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66388","66388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707227","2017-03-07","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many businesses in (a) Camberwell and Peckham constituency and (b) the London Borough of Southwark will be affected by the 2017 change in rateable values.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66392","66392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707228","2017-03-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what plans the Government has to support home-buyers with small deposits.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66377","66377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707229","2017-03-06","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, when she plans to launch the consultation on making company directors and those in similar positions accountable for breaches of the Privacy and Electronic Communications Regulations 2003 in relation to direct marketing; and what the period of that consultation will be.","Biography information for Patricia Gibson","Patricia Gibson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66379","66379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707230","2017-03-06","Department for Education","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of how many National College for Digital Skills students in the (a) current and (b) next cohort are resident outside London.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66375","66375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707231","2017-03-07","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to page 41 of the Government's industrial strategy green paper, published in January 2017, whether it remains her Department's policy that free basic digital skills training will be available for all adults.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66371","66371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707232","2017-03-07","Department for Education","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to page 5, Part 2 of the Government's Digital Strategy, published on 1 March 2017, with whom she plans to consult to ensure that adults who lack core digital skills can access specified basic digital skills training; and what qualifications she envisages those adults attaining on completion of that training.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66385","66385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707233","2017-03-07","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of the UK's potential relationship with Creative Europe after (a) the UK leaves the EU and (b) Creative Europe's current budget period ends in 2020.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66355","66355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707234","2017-03-07","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of the potential benefits to the audiovisual, creative and cultural sectors of continued participation in Creative Europe and its successors after the UK leaves the EU; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66356","66356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707235","2017-03-06","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what progress her Department has made on its independent review of full-time volunteering by young people.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66308","66308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707236","2017-03-07","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to Part 2 of the Government's UK Digital Strategy, published on 1 March 2017, whether additional funding will be provided to libraries to help make them the go-to provider of digital access, training and support for local communities.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66418","66418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707237","2017-03-07","Department for Education","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to page 5, Part 2 of the Government's Digital Strategy, published on 1 March 2017, whether additional funding will be provided to ensure that adults who lack core digital skills can access specified basic digital skills training free of charge.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66416","66416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707238","2017-03-07","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many members of the Royal Navy Police are working as part of the Iraq Historic Allegations Team; and what duties those members have.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66422","66422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707239","2017-03-07","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the Order of Battle of the Royal Navy Police is.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66423","66423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707240","2017-03-07","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many military working dogs are in service in the (a) Royal Navy Police, (b) Royal Military Police and (c) Royal Air Force Police; and what duties those dogs perform in each such service.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66398","66398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707241","2017-03-07","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the Order of Battle is of the Royal Air Force Police.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66399","66399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707242","2017-03-06","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how his Department is promoting the Defence Discount Service in each region and constituent part of the UK.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66383","66383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707243","2017-03-06","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the uptake level has been of the Defence Discount Service in each region and constituent part of the UK since its introduction.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66384","66384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707244","2017-03-06","Department for Education","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to paragraph 1.89 of the Budget 2016, what progress has been made on Professor Sir Adrian Smith's review of mathematics teaching for 16 to 18 year olds; and when her Department plans to publish the terms of reference of that review.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66378","66378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707245","2017-03-07","Department for Education","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if the Institute for Apprenticeships will produce guidance for employers on peer reviewing apprenticeship standards.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66367","66367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707246","2017-03-07","Department for Education","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether the Government's response to the consultation on the the Institute for Apprenticeships strategic guidance will be published before the Institute assumes its functions in April 2017.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66368","66368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707247","2017-03-07","Department for Education","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether the Government's response to the consultation on the Institute for Apprenticeships, operational guidance will be published before the Institute assumes its functions in April 2017.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66369","66369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707248","2017-03-06","Department for Education","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of the average cost of educating a pupil in schools with (a) up to 100, (b) 101 to 500, (c) 501 to 1,000 and (d) more than 1,000 pupils.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66326","66326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707249","2017-03-06","Department for Education","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps the Government is taking to improve young people's political literacy in secondary and post-16 education.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66276","66276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707250","2017-03-06","Department for Education","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which local authorities (a) offer or (b) have offered an education maintenance allowance since 2010.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66273","66273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707251","2017-03-07","Department for Education","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many schools undertook reception baseline assessment in the academic year 2016-17 with her Department's approved provider (a) Centre for Evaluation and Monitoring, Durham University, (b) Early Excellence, (c) GL Assessment and (d) National Foundation for Education Research.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66312","66312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707252","2017-03-06","Department for Education","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what role her Department plans to play in developing and implementing the Government's carers strategy in respect of support provided to young carers.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66283","66283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707253","2017-03-06","Department for Education","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many people have qualified as an early years educator in each of the last six years; and what the distribution of those people was in each region in that period.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66285","66285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707254","2017-03-06","Department for Education","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the effect of requiring applicants for the early years educator qualification to have English and mathematics GCSEs at grade C or above on the number of early years educators entering the profession.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66286","66286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707255","2017-03-07","Department for Education","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment her Department has made of the breadth of the range of modern foreign languages taught in schools; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66295","66295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707256","2017-03-07","Department for Education","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate her Department has made of the proportion of places at outstanding secondary schools filled by children from low-income families.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66296","66296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707257","2017-03-07","Department for Education","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 23 February 2017 to Question 64690, how many physical education teachers have been trained in the UK in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66401","66401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707258","2017-03-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether her Department will make staged funding available for the England Coastal Path as it opens.","Biography information for Sir Hugo Swire","Sir Hugo Swire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66405","66405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707259","2017-03-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much funding her Department plans to make available for the maintenance and improvement of the English National Trails in (a) 2018-19, (b) 2019-20 and (c) 2020-21.","Biography information for Sir Hugo Swire","Sir Hugo Swire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66403","66403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707260","2017-03-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether she plans to reinstate the three year funding cycle for the English National Trails as set out by Natural England in 2013.","Biography information for Sir Hugo Swire","Sir Hugo Swire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66404","66404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707261","2017-03-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what meetings Ministers of her Department have had with the Department (a) for Transport and (b)  of Health on meeting the air pollution targets set out in the EU's 2008 Ambient Air Quality Directive.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66280","66280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707262","2017-03-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate she has made of the total (a) expenditure and (b) number of full-time equivalent officials working for her Department on the prevention of the spread of avian flu in each month of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66299","66299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707263","2017-03-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, which local authorities have breached the World Health Organisation's air quality limits in each of the last seven years.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66318","66318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707264","2017-03-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to ensure local authorities meet statutory air quality targets.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66319","66319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707265","2017-03-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 23 January 2017 to Question 60586, what recent assessment he has made of the likelihood of the UK failing to meet its 15 per cent renewable target by 2020; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66314","66314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707266","2017-03-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, which local authorities have breached legal air quality limits in each of the last seven years.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66316","66316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707267","2017-03-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to her Department's press release of 4 January 2017, Avian flu prevention zone extended, what plans she has to offer assistance or insurance protection to free range egg producers affected by the imposition of the avian influenza prevention zones.","Biography information for Anne-Marie Trevelyan","Mrs Anne-Marie Trevelyan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66386","66386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707268","2017-03-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether the Government plans to retain the air quality targets contained in the 2008 Ambient Air Quality Directive after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66372","66372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707269","2017-03-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much the licensing scheme for wild animals in circuses has cost since its introduction; and what proportion of those costs are incurred by licensed operators.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66382","66382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707270","2017-03-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to encourage the adoption of low emission zones in urban areas.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66333","66333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707271","2017-03-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with the Commonwealth Secretariat on the issue of readmitting the Maldives into the Commonwealth.","Biography information for Sir Hugo Swire","Sir Hugo Swire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66321","66321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707272","2017-03-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with the UN on the political situation in the Maldives.","Biography information for Sir Hugo Swire","Sir Hugo Swire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66322","66322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707273","2017-03-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with the Government of the Maldives on the political situation in that country.","Biography information for Sir Hugo Swire","Sir Hugo Swire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66323","66323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707274","2017-03-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many Scottish people are detained in the United Arab Emirates.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66272","66272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707275","2017-03-07","Department of Health","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 18 July 2016 to Question 42687, on chronic illnesses, what progress his Department has made in delivering the Implementation Plan, published in March 2016, to support the Prime Minister's Challenge on Dementia 2020.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66315","66315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707276","2017-03-06","Department of Health","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many officials of his Department were asked to give evidence to the 2009 Independent Public Inquiry into the contaminated blood scandal by Lord Archer of Sandwell QC; and how many of those requests were (a) accepted and (b) refused.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66302","66302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707277","2017-03-06","Department of Health","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what representations he has received as a result of the decision of 13 January 2017 of the Nursing and Midwifery Council on the adequacy of indemnity insurance provided to independent midwives; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66282","66282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707278","2017-03-06","Department of Health","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what meetings Ministers of his Department have had with the Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs on that Department's forthcoming air quality strategy.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66317","66317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707279","2017-03-06","Department of Health","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to reduce the screening age for bowel cancer to 50 years old.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66351","66351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707280","2017-03-06","Department of Health","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many letters NHS Shared Business Services were contracted to deliver to GP surgeries between 2011 and 2015; and of those letters how many were (a) delivered and (b) not delivered.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66335","66335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707281","2017-03-06","Department of Health","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when NHS Choices plans to add Williams syndrome to its list of recognised conditions.","Biography information for Andrew Bridgen","Andrew Bridgen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66352","66352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707282","2017-03-06","Department of Health","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to prevent the loss of confidential NHS correspondence since the loss of such correspondence by NHS Shared Business Services.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66336","66336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707283","2017-03-06","Department of Health","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patient letters were not delivered by NHS Shared Business Services to GP surgeries in (a) each English region and (b) parliamentary constituency.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66337","66337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707284","2017-03-06","Department of Health","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much NHS Shared Business Services received for delivering letters from hospitals to GP surgeries; and whether that company was paid for the letters which were not delivered.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66341","66341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707285","2017-03-06","Department of Health","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how often he has received updates on the work of NHS Shared Business Services as required under the contract signed by Sopra Steria; and if he will publish any reports relating to data loss which have been received by NHS Shared Business Services or his Department since 2011.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66338","66338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707286","2017-03-06","Department of Health","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, in which English regions NHS Shared Business Services were contracted to deliver GP mail redirection services.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66343","66343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707287","2017-03-06","Department of Health","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much compensation has been paid to GP practices for investigating the letters undelivered by NHS Shared Business Services; and how such compensation has been calculated.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66339","66339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707288","2017-03-06","Department of Health","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he expects the Information Commissioner to publish his report into the loss of confidential NHS correspondence by NHS Shared Business Services.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66344","66344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707289","2017-03-06","Department of Health","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the (a) staff time and (b) cost of that staff time of the hospital staff who prepared and sent letters to GPs which were not delivered by NHS Shared Business Services between 2011 and 2016.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66340","66340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707290","2017-03-06","Department of Health","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many incidents of patient harm have been identified as a result of the loss of confidential NHS correspondence by NHS Shared Business Services; and whether any compensation will be paid to patients who have been found to have been harmed as a result of that lost correspondence.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66345","66345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707291","2017-03-06","Department of Health","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether any person working or NHS Shared Business Services was (a) disciplined or (b) dismissed as a result of the loss of confidential NHS correspondence.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66346","66346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707292","2017-03-06","Department of Health","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what inquiry or inquiries into the loss of confidential NHS correspondence (a) his Department, (b) NHS England and (c) NHS Shared Business Services has undertaken; what the terms of reference were of that inquiry; and what the outcome was of that inquiry.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66347","66347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707293","2017-03-06","Department of Health","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will publish the emails and letters sent between (a) NHS Shared Business Services and his Department and (b) NHS Shared Business Services and NHS England on the loss of confidential NHS correspondence.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66348","66348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707294","2017-03-06","Department of Health","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the potential benefits of reducing the screening age for bowel cancer to 50 years old.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66349","66349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707295","2017-03-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that the Government meets the air pollution targets in the 2008 Ambient Air Quality Directive.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66373","66373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707296","2017-03-06","Department of Health","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, (a) how, (b) when and (c) by whom the loss of confidential NHS correspondence was discovered; who at NHS Shared Business Services discussed the loss with who at (i) his Department and (ii) NHS England; and on what dates any such discussions took place.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66350","66350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707297","2017-03-06","Cabinet Office","2017-03-02","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the oral contributions of the hon. Member for Brighton Pavilion and the hon. Member for Totnes of 28 February 2017, Official Report, Column 80, on trends of deaths registered in England and Wales, what assessment he has made of the cause of the rise in deaths (a) between 2014 and 2015 and (b) in January 2015 (i) in total and (ii) for people aged over 75.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66374","66374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707298","2017-03-06","Department of Health","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make it his policy that future grants awarded for work previously conducted by Action on Smoking and Health will be awarded on a competitive basis.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66381","66381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707299","2017-03-07","Department of Health","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 2 March 2017 to Question 64999, on Department of Health: procurement, how many full-time equivalent members of staff are employed in the central contract management team; and how many members of staff that team manages across his Department.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66400","66400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707300","2017-03-07","Home Office","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 27 February 2017 to Question 64102, on immigration and EU nationals, how many of the documents certifying permanent residence and permanent residence cards refused in Quarter 3 2016 were (a) issued to European Economic Area nationals and (b) accompanied with refusal letters including the instruction to recipients to make preparations to leave the UK.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66415","66415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707301","2017-03-07","Home Office","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 22 February 2017 to Question 64038, when her Department plans to respond to the letter from the hon. Member for  Wolverhampton South West of 21 December 2016 on the use of hotels to accommodate asylum seekers.","Biography information for Rob Marris","Rob Marris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66406","66406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707302","2017-03-07","Home Office","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many Disclosure and Barring Service applications from (a) Camberwell and Peckham constituency and (b) London took more than 60 days to process in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66393","66393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707303","2017-03-07","Home Office","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average time for a Disclosure and Barring Service application to be processed from (a) Camberwell and Peckham constituency and (b) London was in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66394","66394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707304","2017-03-06","Home Office","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will change the text of EEA Permanent Residence refusal letters to remove the instruction to recipients to make preparations to leave the UK.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66324","66324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707305","2017-03-07","Cabinet Office","2017-03-02","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people from each other EU country are resident in the UK; and how many of those people have the right to remain from each of those countries.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Turner","Mr Andrew Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66292","66292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707306","2017-03-07","Home Office","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make an assessment of the feasibility of extracting figures on the number of international students from overall migration numbers.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66313","66313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707307","2017-03-07","Home Office","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment she has made of the adequacy of provision of services for (a) BAME and (b) LGBT victims of domestic abuse.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66300","66300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707308","2017-03-06","Home Office","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions she or officials of her Department have had regarding placing limitations on UK universities' ability to recruit international students to the UK.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66301","66301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707309","2017-03-06","Home Office","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 5 December 2016 to Question 54640, on passports, what the ethnic profile is of UK passport holders.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66279","66279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707310","2017-03-07","Department for International Development","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 22 February 2017 to Question 65001, what proportion of live contracts held by her Department are the 450 live contracts above the EU threshold; what estimate she has made of the amount of staff time spent overseeing those contracts; how many Senior Responsible Owners there are for those contracts; and how many staff those Senior Responsible Owners  manage in relation to monitoring those contracts.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66402","66402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707311","2017-03-07","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what her plans are for the (a) building of new prisons and (b) closure of prisons constructed in the Victorian period; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Peter Bone","Mr Peter Bone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66414","66414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707312","2017-03-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many telecommunication restriction orders have been (a) applied for and (b) granted in each month since those orders were introduced.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66331","66331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707313","2017-03-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when she plans to reply to the letter from the hon. Member for Sheffield, Heeley of 15 February 2017 on section 67 of the Serious Crime Act 2015.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66332","66332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707314","2017-03-06","HM Treasury","2017-03-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when the Government plans to complete its review of a proposed breathing space scheme for families in debt.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66342","66342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707315","2017-03-07","Prime Minister","2017-03-02","To ask the Prime Minister, what plans she has to visit Yorkshire.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66297","66297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707316","2017-03-07","Prime Minister","2017-03-02","To ask the Prime Minister, on what occasions she has visited Yorkshire since she assumed office.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66298","66298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707317","2017-03-07","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the dividend from investment recorded as proceeding from others in the table below paragraph 16.26 of his Department's Annual Report and Accounts, 2010-11, HC 992, represents a dividend from IMS Ltd; whether the National Audit Office audited that sum and the funds invested for which that sum was a dividend; and what use was made of the funds arising from that dividend.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66363","66363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707318","2017-03-08","Scotland Office","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, whether paragraph 55 of the Smith Commission Agreement applies to payments made under part 3 of the Scotland Act 2016 related to the calculations of the benefit cap.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66365","66365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707319","2017-03-07","Scotland Office","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, pursuant to his oral contribution of 1 March 2017, Official Report, column 280, what further powers he expects to be exercised by the Scottish Parliament once the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66407","66407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707320","2017-03-07","Scotland Office","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, pursuant to his oral contribution of 1 March 2017, Official Report, column 280, whether he intends to bring forward primary legislation to devolve further powers to the Scottish Parliament.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66408","66408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707321","2017-03-07","Scotland Office","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, pursuant to his oral contribution of 1 March 2017, Official Report, column 280, whether he plans for the Scottish Parliament to be able to assume legislative competence over areas which are currently exercised by the EU and are not listed in schedule 5 of the Scotland Act 1998 after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66409","66409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707322","2017-03-07","Scotland Office","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, pursuant to his oral contribution of 1 March 2017, Official Report, column 280, whether he intends to bring forward orders under the terms of section 30 of the Scotland Act 1998 to devolve further powers to the Scottish Paliament.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66410","66410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707323","2017-03-06","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2017-03-02","To ask the hon. Member for Houghton and Sunderland South, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, with reference to the Electoral Commission's Electoral Administration Bulletin Issue 173, published in December 2016, what assessment the Commission has made of the potential merits of encouraging the voluntary adoption by (a) local electoral registration officers and (b) the Association of Electoral Administrators, of a standardised uniform format for the supply of information to make it easier for materials to be prepared and web services to be built by political parties and others to encourage electoral participation.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66391","66391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707324","2017-03-06","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2017-03-02","To ask the hon. Member for Houghton and Sunderland South, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, with reference to the Electoral Commission's Electoral Administration Bulletin Issue 173, published in December 2016, whether the Commission plans to advise the Secretary of State to issue a direction under section 52 of the Representation of the People Act 1983 to require local electoral registration officers to make such information available in an easy-to-reuse format which includes as much geographic information as possible to make it easier for materials to be prepared and web services to be built to encourage electoral participation.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66390","66390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707325","2017-03-06","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2017-03-02","To ask the hon. Member for Houghton and Sunderland South, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, with reference to the Electoral Commission's Electoral Administration Bulletin Issue 173, published in December 2016, what further steps the Commission has taken to encourage (a) local electoral registration officers and (b) the Association of Electoral Administrators, to make information available in a format which includes as much geographic information as possible, to make it easier for materials to be prepared and web services to be built to encourage electoral participation.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66389","66389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707326","2017-03-06","Department for Transport","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when the Government plans to publish its response to the Law Commission's 2014 recommendations on the reform of taxi and private hire vehicles legislation.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66387","66387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707327","2017-03-06","Department for Transport","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with the (a) Mayor of London and (b) Greater Manchester Combined Authority on additional toxicity charges for diesel vehicles.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66320","66320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707328","2017-03-06","Department for Transport","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will take steps to postpone the proposed deadline for the installation of 8.33 KHz-compatible radio equipment in aircraft until the outcome of the negotiations on the UK leaving the EU is known.","Biography information for Sir Roger Gale","Sir Roger Gale","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66327","66327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707329","2017-03-07","Department for Transport","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many staff are on a secondment to HS2 Ltd; form which companies such staff have been seconded; and how many staff are a based in HS2 Ltd offices.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66354","66354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707330","2017-03-06","Department for Transport","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many reapplications to the DVLA for driving licences following medical conditions have taken more than 8 weeks to assess in each of the last two years.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66334","66334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707331","2017-03-07","Department for Transport","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when the wall outside Liverpool Lime Street Station which collapsed on 1 March 2017 was last surveyed by Network Rail; and how often Network Rail surveys the (a) rail bridges, (b) cuttings and (c) tunnels leading to Liverpool Lime Street Station.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66421","66421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707332","2017-03-07","Department for Transport","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with Network Rail on the collapse of the wall outside Liverpool Lime Street Station on 1 March 2017.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66419","66419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707333","2017-03-07","Department for Transport","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with Network Rail on the safety of the (a) rail bridges, (b) cuttings and (c) tunnels in (i) Liverpool and (ii) Liverpool, Wavertree constituency.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66420","66420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707334","2017-03-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what progress his Department has made since May 2015 in reducing the disability employment gap.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66294","66294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707335","2017-03-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will take steps to provide financial aid to employees requiring support to up-skill and retrain in the event of the closure of the Walkers crisps factory in Peterlee.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66311","66311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707336","2017-03-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the National minimum wage: Low Pay Commission autumn 2016 report, published in November 2016, what measures are being taken to address the findings of the Apprentice Pay Survey that some apprentices are being paid less than the £3.40 minimum set by the Government.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66329","66329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707337","2017-03-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the latest annual percentage change was in the claimant court in areas operating universal credit (a) full service and (b) live service; and what reasons he ascribes to the difference in the change in the claimant count between full service and live service areas.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66330","66330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707338","2017-03-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether an increase in the rate of Child Benefit in Scotland under section 24 of the Scotland Act 2016 will be included in the calculations of the benefit cap.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66366","66366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707339","2017-03-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 1 March 2017 to Question 65481, how many and what proportion of the 2016 Queen's Award for Enterprise awards were presented to women in the (a) International Trade, (b) Innovation and (c) Sustainable Development category.","Biography information for Gareth Johnson","Gareth Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66380","66380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707340","2017-03-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the Chatham House research paper, Woody Biomass for Power and Heat: Impacts on the Global Climate, published in February 2017, if he will (a) reassess subsidies to biomass for electricity and (b) review biomass policy to ensure it delivers carbon emissions reduction.","Biography information for Tommy Sheppard","Tommy Sheppard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66358","66358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707341","2017-03-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether his Department plans to transfer subsidies for coal to established technologies subsidies.","Biography information for Tommy Sheppard","Tommy Sheppard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66357","66357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707342","2017-03-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the Chatham House research paper, Woody Biomass for Power and Heat: Impacts on the Global Climate, published in February 2017, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to prevent coal power stations continuing to burn coal indefinitely if they co-fire with biomass.","Biography information for Tommy Sheppard","Tommy Sheppard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66360","66360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707343","2017-03-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies on energy and energy subsidies of the Chatham House research paper, Woody Biomass for Power and Heat: Impacts on the Global Climate, published in February 2017.","Biography information for Tommy Sheppard","Tommy Sheppard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66359","66359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707344","2017-03-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he plans to take to improve manufacturing competitiveness in (a) Peterlee and (b) East Durham.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66310","66310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707345","2017-03-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to ensure the Government meets the air pollution targets set out in the EU's 2008 Ambient Air Quality Directive.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66281","66281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707346","2017-03-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he has taken to increase manufacturing job opportunities in East Durham.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66289","66289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707347","2017-03-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to increase levels of employment in areas of high deprivation.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66290","66290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707348","2017-03-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate he has made of the percentage of UK energy that will come from renewable sources in each year to 2020; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66417","66417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707349","2017-03-06","Department for International Trade","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, if he will make it his policy to seek to agree trade deals with the world's poorest countries once the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66304","66304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707350","2017-03-06","HM Treasury","2017-03-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to HM Revenue and Customs digital press release of 13 February 2017, Green light for Government Gateway Transformation, which other Government Departments are planning to use the new verification service.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66305","66305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707351","2017-03-07","Department for International Trade","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether he approved the inclusion in the cultural fit criteria used to evaluate suppliers bidding for the Market Access Discovery Team contract, published on 13 February 2017, that potential bidders must be contracted to the best possible outcome after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66361","66361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707352","2017-03-06","Department for International Trade","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, if UK Export Finance officials conducting its review into support for Rolls-Royce will examine support beyond that referred to in the statement of facts agreed in the deferred prosecution agreement between Rolls Royce and the Serious Fraud Office (SFO) on 17 January 2017 and published by the SFO.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66353","66353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707353","2017-03-07","Department for International Trade","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what the (a) planning, (b) setting up and (c) running costs of the Civil Nuclear Showcase Event held in the Millennium Gloucester Hotel, London from 28 February to 1 March 2017 were; which companies attended that event; and what cost was charged to each company for its attendance at that event.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66395","66395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707354","2017-03-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the oral contribution of Lord Lamont of Lerwick of 2 February 2017, House of Lords, Official Report, column 1280, what assessment his Department has made of the potential implications for any future trade deal with Iran of that country's continued detention of Nazanin Zaghari-Ratcliffe.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66364","66364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707355","2017-03-07","Department for International Trade","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether it is his policy to require all companies bidding for contracts with his Department to demonstrate a commitment to the best possible outcomes for the UK after the UK leaves the EU as part of the cultural fit criteria.","Biography information for Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66362","66362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/707356","2017-03-07","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-03-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to his oral contribution of 24 January 2017, Official Report, columns 180-81, when he plans to confirm the cost of the Supreme Court appeal of the Brexit court case decision.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66328","66328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706638","2017-03-06","Cabinet Office","2017-03-01","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what contracts are undertaken for the Government by Capita; and what the total value is of those contracts.","Biography information for Christian Matheson","Christian Matheson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66054","66054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706639","2017-03-06","Cabinet Office","2017-03-01","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many and what proportion of people employed by the Civil Service by Department are non-UK EU nationals.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66058","66058"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706640","2017-03-08","Cabinet Office","2017-03-01","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps he is taking to ensure that internships are accessible to people from all backgrounds.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66181","66181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706641","2017-03-06","Cabinet Office","2017-03-01","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 23 February 2017 to Question 63957, on Electoral register: Northern Ireland, if the Cabinet Office will conduct an impact assessment into the effectiveness of electoral identity cards for use at elections in England, Wales and Scotland.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66258","66258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706642","2017-03-06","HM Treasury","2017-03-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much funding his Department has provided to the Landfill Communities Fund in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66226","66226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706643","2017-03-06","HM Treasury","2017-03-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of excise duty rates on beer exports.","Biography information for Graham Evans","Graham Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66175","66175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706644","2017-03-06","HM Treasury","2017-03-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 23 February 2017 to Question 63665, what discussions he has had with the Minister for the Cabinet Office on whether he has taken into consideration the estimated number of adults without a bank account in developing his Department's voter identification trial.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66236","66236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706645","2017-03-06","HM Treasury","2017-03-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of freezing rates of child benefit and child tax credit on families in Blaydon constituency.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66164","66164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706646","2017-03-06","HM Treasury","2017-03-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of freezing rates of child benefit and child tax credit on families in Poplar and Limehouse constituency.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66165","66165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706647","2017-03-06","HM Treasury","2017-03-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect on jobs and investment in pubs and breweries of the (a) reduction in beer duty in 2014, (b) reduction in beer duty in 2015 and (c) freeze in beer duty in 2016.","Biography information for Graham Evans","Graham Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66176","66176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706648","2017-03-06","HM Treasury","2017-03-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the number of children living in poverty in Airdrie and Shotts constituency if child benefit is (a) frozen and (b) increased in line with inflation in the next three years.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66179","66179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706649","2017-03-06","HM Treasury","2017-03-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will assess the potential merits of exempting hot sandwiches that are made to takeaway from VAT.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66187","66187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706650","2017-03-06","HM Treasury","2017-03-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what comparative estimate he has made of the number of children living in poverty in (a) the UK, (b) Scotland and (c) Inverclyde constituency if child benefit is (i) frozen and (ii) increased in line with inflation in the next three years.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66159","66159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706651","2017-03-06","HM Treasury","2017-03-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will assess the potential merits of exempting all new zero-emissions taxis from VAT from 2018 to 2025.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66083","66083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706652","2017-03-06","HM Treasury","2017-03-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when the Government plans to implement provisions in the Finance Act 2016 to require (a) multinational enterprises and (b) UK subgroups of multinational enterprises to provide annual country-by-country tax reports to HM Revenue and Customs.","Biography information for Dr Alasdair McDonnell","Dr Alasdair McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66080","66080"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706653","2017-03-06","HM Treasury","2017-03-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent estimate he has made of the number of golf clubs which are run as (a) members' and (b) proprietors' clubs for the purpose of VAT assessment; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66090","66090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706654","2017-03-06","Department for Education","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps the Government takes to reclaim student loans from graduates from non-UK EU countries who fail to repay those loans.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66121","66121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706655","2017-03-06","HM Treasury","2017-03-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans his Department has to make available additional funds to the NHS in order to mitigate the potential effect of changes to the personal injury formula.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66117","66117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706656","2017-03-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to deliver nature-friendly housing developments.","Biography information for Kelly Tolhurst","Kelly Tolhurst","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66073","66073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706657","2017-03-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what plans he has to exempt publicly-owned special protection and conservation areas from any future public land disposal.","Biography information for Kelly Tolhurst","Kelly Tolhurst","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66074","66074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706658","2017-03-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what representations his Department has received on the levels of fines issued by local authorities to residents for litter-related offences.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66061","66061"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706659","2017-03-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much funding his Department has allocated to local authorities to fund children's social care in each year between 2011 and 2016.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66052","66052"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706660","2017-03-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what advice his Department provides to local authorities on how to fund social care for children and young people.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66050","66050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706661","2017-03-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what plans he has to audit local authorities to assess what proportion of funding raised specifically through the social care precept is spent on frontline social care.","Biography information for James Cartlidge","James Cartlidge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66127","66127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706662","2017-03-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what meetings he has had with Dorset hon. Members since 1 January 2017 at which possible reorganisation of local government structures in Dorset has been discussed; what the dates of those meetings were; and which hon. Members were present at each meeting.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66172","66172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706663","2017-03-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to his Answer of 1 March 2017 to Question 65508, what assumption about the notional amount of council tax for 2019-20 was included in the submission of 9 February 2017; and what criteria he will use to evaluate the financial case without making any such assumption himself.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66173","66173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706664","2017-03-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to his Answer of 1 March 2017 to Question 65075, what evidence he will have before him on the opinions and counter-proposals of the three councils which do not support the proposal.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66169","66169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706665","2017-03-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to his Answer of 1 March 2017 to Question 65075, what options he will consider in determining how to proceed.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66170","66170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706666","2017-03-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to his Answer of 1 March 2017 to Question 65075, how long councils and others interested will have to make representations.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66171","66171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706667","2017-03-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to paragraph 4.53 of the White Paper, Fixing our broken housing market, published in February 2017, what his Department's definition is of social lettings agencies.","Biography information for David Mackintosh","David Mackintosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66196","66196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706668","2017-03-06","Department for Education","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will make an assessment of the implications for her policies of the report by the Children's Commissioner for England on young carers, published in December 2016; and if she will provide additional support to councils in England to help them to (a) identify and (b) improve support for young carers.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66249","66249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706669","2017-03-06","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to page 3, Part 2 of the Digital Strategy 2017, what budget has been provided to the Council for Digital Inclusion to increase collaboration and deliver initiatives to help more citizens to confidently go online and take advantage of the internet.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66259","66259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706670","2017-03-06","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 23 February 2017 to Question 64455, on public libraries: voluntary organisations, what support the Government is providing for library services and other public sector organisations to consider alternative funding and delivery models; and how that support can be accessed.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66203","66203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706671","2017-03-06","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how much of the £2.5 billion commercial investment in broadband planned by BT has been delivered to date.","Biography information for Tom Elliott","Tom Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66195","66195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706672","2017-03-06","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate she has made of the change in the number of librarians trained in digital skills from 2010 to date.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66227","66227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706673","2017-03-06","Department for Education","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the UK Digital Strategy published on 1 March 2017, by what date the Government expects to deliver coding in the National Curriculum from Key Stage 1 onwards.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66228","66228"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706674","2017-03-06","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to the UK Digital Strategy published on 1 March 2017, how many people are expected to take part in pilots of new ways to include digital skills and careers in the National Citizen Service; and when she expects such content to become a core part of the National Citizen Service programme.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66229","66229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706675","2017-03-06","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to page 2, Part 1 of her Department's Digital Strategy, published on 1 March 2017, whether the independent research cited indicates the speed to which broadband would need to be increased to add £17 billion to UK output by 2024.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66180","66180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706676","2017-03-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to Part 4 of the Digital Strategy released on 1 March 2017, what estimate his Department has made of the number of businesses the Productivity Council will connect, in person, to share what good looks like.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66128","66128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706677","2017-03-06","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to page 6, Part 1 of her Department's Digital Strategy published on 1 March 2017, what estimate she has made of the 4G coverage on UK motorways provided by each of the four major operators.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66156","66156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706678","2017-03-06","Department for Transport","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to page 5, Part 1 of the Digital Strategy published on 1 March 2017, what broadband speed train operators will be required to deliver to provide high-speed connectivity to ensure fast and reliable WiFi.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66157","66157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706679","2017-03-06","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of the effect of permitting children to gamble in family entertainment centres on future gambling habits.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66153","66153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706680","2017-03-06","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of the effect of locating ATMs in gambling premises on the level of gambling.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66154","66154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706681","2017-03-06","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of the effect of displaying gaming machines in shop windows on the level of gambling in those shops.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66155","66155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706682","2017-03-06","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to the Government's digital strategy, what support will be provided to Great Grimsby from the digital skills programme; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66059","66059"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706683","2017-03-06","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to the Government's digital strategy, which companies have committed to work in Great Grimsby as part of the Digital Skills Partnership.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66060","66060"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706684","2017-03-09","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate she has made of the (a) number and (b) cost to the public purse, of the loss of library books in the last five years; and what steps she is taking to help local authorities prevent such losses.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66125","66125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706686","2017-03-06","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 12 January 2017 to Question 59241, what the planned date is for the main investment decision and contractual signing for the procurement of the Type 26 frigates.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66079","66079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706687","2017-03-06","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of changes in the exchange rate on the Equipment Plan 2016 to 2026.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66092","66092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706688","2017-03-06","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what proportion of the Government's reporting to NATO on defence expenditure in 2016 was categorised as (a) war pensions, (b) contributions to UN peacekeeping missions, (c) the Single Intelligence Account and (d) pensions for retired civilian personnel.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66096","66096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706689","2017-03-06","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the total value was of contracts awarded by his Department to single-source suppliers in each of the last seven years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66097","66097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706690","2017-03-06","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many penalty notices his Department has issued to suppliers for failing to disclose information on costs and pricing in each of the last seven years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66098","66098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706691","2017-03-06","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that maintenance and repairs to service family accommodation and single living accommodation are carried out quickly and effectively.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66134","66134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706692","2017-03-06","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, for what reasons the Defence Fire and Rescue Project is not listed in the Ministry of Defence Government Major Projects Portfolio data.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66104","66104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706693","2017-03-06","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the value is of the Defence Fire and Rescue Project.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66105","66105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706694","2017-03-06","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 24 February 2017 to Question 64606, how many additional Defence Equipment and Support staff are needed to reduce the manning risk to Initial Capability of the F-35 Lightning II programme.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66270","66270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706695","2017-03-06","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 24 February 2017 to Question 64606, which (a) Royal Navy and (b) Royal Air Force roles required to support the F-35 Lightning II programme are undermanned; and what estimate he has made of the number of personnel required to adequately support that programme.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66271","66271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706696","2017-03-06","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 24 February 2017 to Question 64606, how many Defence Equipment and Support staff are working in direct support of the F-35 Lightning II programme.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66268","66268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706697","2017-03-06","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 24 February 2017 to Question 64606, what further steps he is taking as part of the review to address the lack of manpower needed to support Initial Capability of the F-35 Lightning II programme.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66265","66265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706698","2017-03-06","Ministry of Defence","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 24 February 2017 to Question 64606, how many specialist personnel from the (a) Royal Navy and (b) Royal Air Force were part of the increase in specialist personnel needed to support the Lightning II programme since his Department's Major Projects Portfolio data was published.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66266","66266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706699","2017-03-06","Department for Education","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 28 February 2017 to Question 64974, on what date the Schools Funding Formula will be published.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66261","66261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706700","2017-03-06","Department for Education","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to her Written Ministerial Statement HCWS509 of 1 March 2017 on sex and relationships education, whether the duty will apply to (a) academy schools, (b) faith schools, (c) independent schools and (d) free schools.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66230","66230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706701","2017-03-06","Department for Education","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, for what reasons she has not answered named day Question 65038 tabled on 22 February 2017 and Questions 64794, 64793, 64792 and 64791 tabled on 21 February 2017.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66232","66232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706702","2017-03-06","Department for Education","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Written Ministerial Statement of 1 March 2017, HCWS509, on sex and relationships education (SRE), whether she plans that new regulations and statutory guidance on the teaching of SRE will include teaching on (a) transsexuality, (b) same-sex relationships, (c) staying safe online, (d) cyber bullying, (e) sexting, (f) violence against women and girls, (g) consent and (h) child abuse.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66197","66197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706703","2017-03-06","Department for Education","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 28 February 2017 to Question 64973, whether the Schools Funding Formula reflects the higher labour market costs of attracting labour to hard to access areas.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66260","66260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706704","2017-03-06","Department for Education","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many pupils were displaced from school buildings as a result of fire in each of the last 10 years; and for how long on average those pupils were placed in temporary classrooms.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66218","66218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706705","2017-03-06","Department for Education","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what progress has been made on simplifying, clarifying and rationalising the quality awards system for careers education, information and guidance in England's schools.","Biography information for Rishi Sunak","Rishi Sunak","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66133","66133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706706","2017-03-06","Department for Education","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how the performance of careers services provided in secondary schools is assessed.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66162","66162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706707","2017-03-06","Department for Education","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment her Department has made of the effect of the housing market on teacher (a) recruitment and (b) retention rates in (i) Tottenham constituency, (ii) the Borough of Haringey and (iii) Greater London.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66093","66093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706708","2017-03-06","Department for Education","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment her Department has made of the effect of changes to school funding on (a) teacher numbers, (b) school standards, (c) pupil outcomes and (d) levels of youth crime in (i) Tottenham constituency and (ii) the Borough of Haringey.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66094","66094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706709","2017-03-06","Department for Education","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when decisions from the Education Funding Agency on applications to the Condition Improvement Fund for 2017-18 will be announced.","Biography information for Mr David Winnick","Mr David Winnick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66082","66082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706710","2017-03-06","Department for Education","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to page 15 of Sandymoor Free School's annual report and financial statement for the year ending 31 August 2016, for what reasons that school received  advanced funding from the Education Funding Agency; and what the amount of that advanced funding was.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66084","66084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706711","2017-03-06","Department for Education","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 27 February 2017 to Question 65091, why page 30 of Sandymoor Free School's annual report and financial statement for the year ending 31 August 2016 includes reference to a deficit of £522,760.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66085","66085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706712","2017-03-06","Department for Education","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment her Department has made of the number of additional (a) school places and (b) teachers and teaching assistants that will be required in (i) Tottenham constituency, (ii) the Borough of Haringey and (iii) Greater London between 2017 and 2020.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66075","66075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706713","2017-03-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to reduce companies' use of non-recyclable black plastic packaging.","Biography information for Richard Graham","Richard Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66099","66099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706714","2017-03-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment she has made of the adequacy of funding provided to Natural England for carrying out mapping.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66089","66089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706715","2017-03-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to (a) improve the recyclability of black plastic and (b) reduce the amount of waste going to landfill.","Biography information for Richard Graham","Richard Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66095","66095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706716","2017-03-06","Department of Health","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he plans to review the Infant Formula and Follow-on Formula Regulations 2007; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66055","66055"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706717","2017-03-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the answer of 27 February 2017 to Question 65236 on microplastics, what estimate she has made of the reduction in harm to the marine environment as a consequence of the proposed ban on the use of microbeads in cosmetics and personal care products.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66167","66167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706718","2017-03-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 25 January 2017 to Question 60340, whether the last payment window for the equivalent CAP Pillar 1 funding to which the Government has committed will open in 2019 or in 2020.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66182","66182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706719","2017-03-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 25 January 2017 to Question 60340, whether the Government plans to provide existing levels of CAP Pillar 1 funding for applications that are scheduled to begin to be paid on 1 December 2020.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66183","66183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706720","2017-03-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 28 February 2017 to Question 64958, when she expects the Drinking Water Inspectorate to report its findings into the crytosporidium incident in Lancashire which took place in August 2015.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66161","66161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706721","2017-03-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to reduce the use of microbeads in products that are not included within the scope of her Department's proposed ban on microbeads.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66186","66186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706722","2017-03-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps the Government plans to take to learn lessons from the ban on microbeads in the US; and if she will make an assessment of the merits and effect of the US measures.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66188","66188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706723","2017-03-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what requirements are placed on farmers who use knapsack sprayers to undertake training on the use of those sprayers; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66101","66101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706724","2017-03-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the additional cost to farmers of purchasing rodent control products as a result of the recent change to the licensing of such products.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66102","66102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706725","2017-03-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of the Food Standards Agency in monitoring meat processing in abattoirs to ensure that meat is produced in accordance with regulatory requirements.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66140","66140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706726","2017-03-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 17 January 2017 to Question 60831, what the country of origin was of each trophy for which an import application was received; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66129","66129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706727","2017-03-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to encourage people in affected areas to continue badger control beyond the four years of the initial badger culling trials.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66219","66219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706728","2017-03-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of extending the current six week period for carrying out trial badger culls in affected areas.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66220","66220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706729","2017-03-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans she has to tackle bovine tuberculosis in high risk areas which have not undergone trial badger culling.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66235","66235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706730","2017-03-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what information she holds on the total value of Basic Payment Scheme payments (a) not paid on time and (b) paid on time since January 2016; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66174","66174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706731","2017-03-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 28 February 2017 to Question 65352, what plans she has to meet the United States Environment Protection Agency to discuss the use of microbeads.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66256","66256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706732","2017-03-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many legal green lanes have been closed using Traffic Regulation Orders in (a) Brecon Beacons National Park Authority, (b) Broads Authority, (c) Cairngorms National Park Authority, (d) Dartmoor National Park Authority, (e) Exmoor National Park Authority, (f) Lake District National Park Authority, (g) Loch Lomond and The Trossachs National Park Authority, (h) New Forest National Park Authority, (i) Northumberland National Park Authority, (j) North York Moors National Park Authority, (k) Peak District National Park Authority, (l) Pembrokeshire Coast National Park Authority, (m) Snowdonia National Park Authority, (n) South Downs National Park Authority and (o) Yorkshire Dales National Park Authority in each of the last five years.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66200","66200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706733","2017-03-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment his Department has made of Sri Lanka's progress in implementing UN Human Rights Council Resolution 30/1; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66241","66241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706734","2017-03-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the progress of negotiations on the potential accession of Azerbaijan to the World Trade Organisation.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66212","66212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706735","2017-03-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his counterpart in Azerbaijan on the implementation of constitutional reforms in that country.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66213","66213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706736","2017-03-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the progress of negotiations on a revised Association Agreement between the EU and Armenia; and when he expects such an agreement to be finalised.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66209","66209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706737","2017-03-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the progress of the Government of Armenia in implementing the recommendations made by the OSCE Office for Democratic Institution and Human Rights since its monitoring mission to that country in 2013.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66208","66208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706738","2017-03-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the progress of negotiations on a comprehensive agreement between the EU and Azerbaijan; and what the Government's policy is on the potential scope of such an agreement.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66211","66211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706739","2017-03-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the level of politically-motivated violence in Armenia.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66210","66210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706740","2017-03-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the security situation in Nagorno-Karabakh.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66214","66214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706741","2017-03-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the conduct of the referendum held in Nagorno-Karabakh on 20 February 2017.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66215","66215"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706742","2017-03-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effect of increased revenue from oil production in Libya on the effectiveness of economic sanctions imposed on that country.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66184","66184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706743","2017-03-06","Department of Health","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will publish details of the process leading to the review by NHS England's Clinical Priorities Advisory Group of commissioning of medicines for rare diseases in 2017-18.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66189","66189"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706744","2017-03-06","Department of Health","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average time taken has been between marketing authorisation being granted and NHS England publishing a funding decision for rare disease medicines in (a) 2015-16 and (b) 2016-17 to date.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66190","66190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706745","2017-03-06","Department of Health","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many Individual Funding Requests (IFRs) have been considered by (a) the IFR Screening Group and (b) the IFR Panel in each of the last five years; how many of those IFRs have been approved; and what the total cost of those procedures was.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66178","66178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706746","2017-03-06","Department of Health","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of treatment provision for people diagnosed with early onset dementia.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66177","66177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706747","2017-03-07","Department of Health","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the current status is of the application he has received from Anglia Ruskin University on establishing a new medical school; and what the timetable is for a decision on that application.","Biography information for Sir Simon Burns","Sir Simon Burns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66139","66139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706748","2017-03-06","Department of Health","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the relative availability of second stem cell transplants for patients whose disease relapses in England and the (a) devolved nations of the UK, (b) EU and (c) US.","Biography information for Mark Tami","Mark Tami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66130","66130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706749","2017-03-06","Department of Health","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when the Government plans to publish the new carers strategy.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66131","66131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706750","2017-03-06","Department of Health","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the cost of prescriptions dispensed in the community was for people aged (a) over 60 and (b) between 60 and 66 in the last year for which information is available.","Biography information for James Cartlidge","James Cartlidge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66126","66126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706751","2017-03-06","Department of Health","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of additional physician associates required to support the delivery of seven-day working in the NHS.","Biography information for Anne Marie Morris","Anne Marie Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66107","66107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706752","2017-03-06","Department of Health","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to support the education and professional development of physician associates.","Biography information for Anne Marie Morris","Anne Marie Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66108","66108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706753","2017-03-06","Department of Health","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department has taken to work with the Department for Education to ensure that children with complex disabilities and their families can access short breaks for respite which meet their health needs.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66051","66051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706754","2017-03-06","Department of Health","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will implement the recommendation in the Palliative Care Funding Review that short breaks which provide respite for the carers and families of children requiring palliative care should be funded by local authorities and the NHS under their respective legal short breaks duties.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66049","66049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706755","2017-03-06","Department of Health","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 30 January 2017 to Question 61544, what estimate has been made of the average five year (a) health and (b) social care costs of atrial fibrillation-related stroke after onset for patients aged (i) 50 to 59, (ii) 60 to 69, (iii) 70 to 79, (iv) 80 to 89 and (v) over 90.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66086","66086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706756","2017-03-06","Department of Health","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 30 January 2017 to Question 61544, what estimate has been made of the average (a) health and (b) social care costs of atrial fibrillation-related stroke to the NHS in each of the first five years after onset.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66087","66087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706757","2017-03-06","Department of Health","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on the NHS of changes to the personal injury formula.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66118","66118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706758","2017-03-06","Department of Health","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Justice on changes to the personal injury formula.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66115","66115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706759","2017-03-06","Department of Health","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he was consulted prior to the announced changes to the personal injury formula.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66116","66116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706760","2017-03-06","Department of Health","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when the consultation on the role of physician associates announced in his keynote speech to the NHS Providers conference on 30 November 2016 will be launched.","Biography information for Anne Marie Morris","Anne Marie Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66109","66109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706761","2017-03-06","Department of Health","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 28 February 2017 to Question 65346, on health professions: training, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions on the roll out of that training.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66110","66110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706762","2017-03-06","Department of Health","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much of the NHS budget was spent on commissioning private providers in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66091","66091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706763","2017-03-06","Department of Health","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he has taken to reduce waiting times for orthopaedic operations in the last 12 months; and whether waiting times for such operations have reduced in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66233","66233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706765","2017-03-06","Department of Health","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 8 February 2017 to Question 63015, on eating disorders: children and young people, whether the referral to treatment performance data will be published for each clinical commissioning group.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66234","66234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706766","2017-03-06","Department of Health","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which specialised medicines, procedures and medical technologies are undergoing evaluation by NHS England Specialised Services for potential commissioning in 2017-18 and 2018-19.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66192","66192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706767","2017-03-06","Department of Health","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will publish details of the process by which NICE plans to create commissioning support documents on rare disease medicines for NHS England in 2017.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66191","66191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706768","2017-03-06","Department of Health","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the Accessible Information Standard.","Biography information for Tom Elliott","Tom Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66194","66194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706769","2017-03-06","Department of Health","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients have waited longer than (a) two weeks, (b) five weeks, (c) 10 weeks and (d) 15 weeks between an assessment for knee replacement surgery and for that surgery taking place.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66263","66263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706770","2017-03-06","Department of Health","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients have had to wait longer than (a) two weeks, (b) five weeks, (c) 10 weeks and (d) 15 weeks between being assessed for hip replacement surgery and that surgery taking place.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66264","66264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706771","2017-03-06","Department of Health","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the reasons for the increase in drug-related deaths in 2015.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66248","66248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706772","2017-03-06","Department of Health","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many NHS apprenticeships have been provided in the West Midlands in each (a) local authority and (b) NHS Trust area in (i) the last year for which figures are available, (ii) 2015 and (iii) 2010; and how many nursing associates have been appointed in the West Midlands in the same areas and in the same years.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66221","66221"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706773","2017-03-06","Department of Health","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of nationals of other EU countries working in the NHS as psychotherapists; and what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the UK leaving the EU on (a) the number of such nationals and (b) NHS productivity.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66262","66262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706774","2017-03-06","Department of Health","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to increase the recruitment of GPs in the London Borough of Newham.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66222","66222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706775","2017-03-06","Home Office","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 26 January 2017 to Question 61929, what steps her Department has taken to raise awareness of the service launched in October 2016 to enable single EEA applicants to apply for permanent residence online.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66202","66202"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706776","2017-03-06","Home Office","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much funding her Department allocated to the Metropolitan Police for diplomatic protection in (a) 2015-16, (b) 2014-15, (c) 2013-14, (d) 2012-13 and (e) 2011-12.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66239","66239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706777","2017-03-06","Home Office","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the cost to the Metropolitan Police was of diplomatic protection in (a) 2015-16, (b) 2014-15, (c) 2013-14, (d) 2012-13 and (e) 2011-12.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66240","66240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706778","2017-03-06","Home Office","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 26 January 2017 to Question 61929, whether her Department plans to launch services for non-single EEA applicants to apply for permanent residence online; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66201","66201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706779","2017-03-06","Home Office","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many school fires have been reported in each of the last 10 years; how many of those fires were caused by arson; and what the total cost was of replacing school buildings affected by (a) those fires and (b) those fires caused by arson.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66216","66216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706780","2017-03-06","Home Office","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she plans to introduce a fully online application process for permanent residency in the UK.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66113","66113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706781","2017-03-06","Home Office","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, for what reasons the entitlement to free NHS care is not considered as fulfilling the comprehensive sickness insurance requirement for EU nationals applying for permanent residency.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66114","66114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706783","2017-03-06","Home Office","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions she has had with her Cabinet colleagues on whether the Government can change the rights of citizens from other EU countries resident in the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66122","66122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706784","2017-03-06","Home Office","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she has made an assessment of the effectiveness of the introduction of Independent Child Trafficking Advocates in three early adopter sites; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66056","66056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706785","2017-03-06","Home Office","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many refugees have been resettled in the UK in each of the last five years; what countries those refugees arrived from; what those refugees' countries of origin were; how many of those refugees were assessed as being under the age of 19; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66137","66137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706786","2017-03-06","Home Office","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to resettle child refugees in (a) the UK and (b) Scotland.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66136","66136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706787","2017-03-06","Home Office","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the potential merits of offering equivalent visitor visa arrangements to Indians as those that are provided to Chinese visitors.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66142","66142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706788","2017-03-06","Home Office","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the projected spending power for each fire authority is for 2019-20.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66160","66160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706789","2017-03-06","Home Office","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the spending power for each fire authority will be in 2017-18.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66163","66163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706790","2017-03-06","Department for International Development","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what the total cost of the Government's projects in Iraq was in each year between 2010 and 2017.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66168","66168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706791","2017-03-06","Department for International Development","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will take steps to (a) reduce the effects of the US Administration's Mexico City Policy disallowing promotion of abortion as a method of family planning by organisations receiving US assistance and (b) ensure that comprehensive sexual and reproductive health rights are supported worldwide.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66198","66198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706792","2017-03-06","Department for International Development","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much aid in real terms the UK has provided to refugee camps in and around Syria in each of the last five years; what comparative assessment she has made of how much the UK has provided relative to that of each of the five largest donors; and if she will make statement.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66231","66231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706793","2017-03-06","Department for International Development","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether her Department plans to contribute to the global fund to help women access abortion services, announced by Sweden, Denmark, Belgium, Luxembourg, Finland, Canada and Cape Verde in response to reinstatement of the US Administration's Mexico City Policy.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66199","66199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706794","2017-03-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners HM Prison Berwyn plans to receive over the next 12 months; and what the estimated operating cost is for the first 12 months of that prison being open to prisoners.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66204","66204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706795","2017-03-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the total cost of designing and building HM Prison Berwyn was.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66205","66205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706796","2017-03-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many staff have been recruited to work in HM Prison Berwyn to date.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66206","66206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706797","2017-03-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many staff worked in HM Prison Berwyn prior to it opening to prisoners; and what the total cost of that staffing was for that time period.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66207","66207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706798","2017-03-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Oral contribution of the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Justice of 1 March 2017, Official Report, column 103WH, what proportion of the 7,000 prison officer posts which have been lost since 2010 were employed by the 18 prisons that have been closed over that period.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66251","66251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706799","2017-03-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the oral contribution of the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Justice of 1 March 2017, Official Report, column 101WH, what proportion of prison staff will take part in the national learning day for prison staff on suicide and self-harm on 14 March 2017; what activities the day will involve; and who is responsible for organising the day.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66267","66267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706800","2017-03-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the oral contribution of the Parliamentary Under-Secretary for Justice of 1 March 2017, Official Report, column 101WH, when the new self-harm diagnostic tool for use by prison governors and staff will be in place.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66269","66269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706801","2017-03-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if she will introduce a system for financial checks on means forms filled out by offenders in criminal courts which are used to determine the level of fines and the contribution that should be made to the costs of the case.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66057","66057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706802","2017-03-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will commission a public inquiry into UK involvement in the 1984 Amritsar massacre.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66238","66238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706803","2017-03-06","Department for Transport","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 21 July 2016 to Question 43142, what progress he has made on providing a further round of accessibility funding for (a) lifts and (b) other accessibility devices at mainline railway stations; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for James Cartlidge","James Cartlidge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66254","66254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706804","2017-03-06","Department for Transport","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 22 February 2017 to Question 63666, what discussions he has had with the Cabinet Office on the matter of adults who do not hold either a (a) UK or (b) provisional UK driving licence in respect of the trial pilot scheme on voter identification due to take place in May 2018.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66252","66252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706805","2017-03-06","Department for Transport","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make it his policy to bring forward legislative proposals to give the Government power to ring-fence landing slots at Heathrow Airport to protect connections to regional airports as was proposed in the Airports (Amendment) Bill [HL] 2010-12.","Biography information for Tom Elliott","Tom Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66193","66193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706806","2017-03-06","Department for Transport","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when the Government plans to bring forward proposals on cross-border hiring and sub-contracting clause in the Deregulation Act 2015.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66088","66088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706807","2017-03-06","Department for Transport","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many cyclists have been injured in accidents with trucks in the last 12 months for which figures are available.","Biography information for John Redwood","John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66069","66069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706808","2017-03-06","Department for Transport","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many pedestrians have been injured in accidents with cyclists in the last 12 months for which figures are available.","Biography information for John Redwood","John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66070","66070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706809","2017-03-06","Department for Transport","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what proportion of road fatalities occur at road junctions.","Biography information for John Redwood","John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66071","66071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706810","2017-03-06","Department for Transport","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what proportion of road accidents involving serious injury occur at road junctions.","Biography information for John Redwood","John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66072","66072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706811","2017-03-06","Department for Transport","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which rolling stock on Northern Rail is (a) compliant with rail vehicle accessibility regulations and (b) has been given exemptions from rail vehicle accessibility regulations.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66124","66124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706812","2017-03-06","Department for Transport","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which rail vehicle accessibility regulations apply to (a) existing rolling stock on Northern Rail and (b) new rolling stock to be delivered for Northern Rail.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66123","66123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706813","2017-03-06","Department for Transport","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps the Government is taking to tackle non-compliance of train companies related to the provision to passengers of information relating to their rights required under the Consumer Rights Act 2015.","Biography information for Will Quince","Will Quince","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66100","66100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706814","2017-03-06","Department for Transport","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many pedestrians have been killed in accidents with buses in the last 12 months for which figures are available.","Biography information for John Redwood","John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66062","66062"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706815","2017-03-06","Department for Transport","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many pedestrians have been seriously injured in accidents with buses in the last 12 months for which figures are available.","Biography information for John Redwood","John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66063","66063"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706816","2017-03-06","Department for Transport","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many cyclists have been killed in accidents with buses in the last 12 months for which figures are available.","Biography information for John Redwood","John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66064","66064"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706817","2017-03-06","Department for Transport","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many cyclists have been seriously injured in accidents with buses in the last 12 months for which figures are available.","Biography information for John Redwood","John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66065","66065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706818","2017-03-06","Department for Transport","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many pedestrians have been killed in accidents with trucks in the last 12 months for which figures are available.","Biography information for John Redwood","John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66066","66066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706819","2017-03-06","Department for Transport","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many pedestrians have been seriously injured in accidents with trucks in the last 12 months for which figures are available.","Biography information for John Redwood","John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66067","66067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706820","2017-03-06","Department for Transport","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many cyclists have been killed in accidents with trucks in the last 12 months for which figures are available.","Biography information for John Redwood","John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66068","66068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706821","2017-03-06","Department for Transport","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much and for what reasons compensation has been paid by Govia Thameslink to passengers under the Consumer Rights Act 2015.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66146","66146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706822","2017-03-06","Department for Transport","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much and for what reasons compensation has been paid by Southern Rail to passengers under the Consumer Rights Act 2015.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66147","66147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706823","2017-03-06","Department for Transport","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much and for what reasons compensation has been paid by South Eastern to passengers under the Consumer Rights Act 2015.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66148","66148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706824","2017-03-06","Department for Transport","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps the Government is taking to provide passengers with information on their rights under the Consumer Rights Act 2015 related to train companies' compliance with consumer law.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66135","66135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706825","2017-03-06","Department for Transport","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what progress the rail industry has made on making new data available to third party retailers in the rail ticketing market.","Biography information for Will Quince","Will Quince","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66138","66138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706826","2017-03-06","Department for Transport","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what progress has been made on opening up the retail ticketing market to third party retailers and new market entrants.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66132","66132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706827","2017-03-06","Department for Transport","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much compensation has been paid to passengers under the Consumer Rights Act 2015 by Abellio Greater Anglia in each year for which compensation has been paid.","Biography information for Will Quince","Will Quince","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66103","66103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706828","2017-03-06","Women and Equalities","2017-03-01","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what steps she is taking to encourage the provision of easy read versions of content published by (a) government departments and agencies, (b) utility companies, (c) banks and (d) other private sector service providers.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66217","66217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706829","2017-03-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to his Answer of 14 November 2016 to Question 51999, how many referrals of those defaulting on their child maintenance liabilities have been made to credit reference agencies since March 2015.","Biography information for Ms Karen Buck","Ms Karen Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66223","66223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706830","2017-03-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, for what reasons he plans to deny additional points in the assessment for personal independence payments to people who are unable to plan the route of a journey, or follow the route of a familiar or unfamiliar journey without help, if the reason is psychological distress.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66250","66250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706831","2017-03-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of providing compensation for losses women who have already reached their state pension age have incurred through changes to the state pension law made by the 1995 and 2011 Pension Acts.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66237","66237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706832","2017-03-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he expects to publish regulations on the treatment of 18-21 year old housing benefit claimants.","Biography information for Ms Karen Buck","Ms Karen Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66225","66225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706833","2017-03-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claims for Employment Support Allowance (ESA) were made in each of the last three years from claimants who had received ESA (a) at any time and (b) in the year prior to the claim.","Biography information for Ms Karen Buck","Ms Karen Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66224","66224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706834","2017-03-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans he has to reform bereavement benefits.","Biography information for Tom Elliott","Tom Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66253","66253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706835","2017-03-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make an assessment of the implications for his policies of research by Oxford University, published by The Trussell Trust in October 2017, on the effect of benefit sanctions on food insecurity and food bank usage.","Biography information for Jo Churchill","Jo Churchill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66242","66242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706836","2017-03-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much his Department is making available for the Targeted Affordability Funding concession to the freeze on local housing allowance rates in (a) 2016-17, (b) 2017-18, (c) 2018-19 and (d) 2019-20.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66076","66076"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706837","2017-03-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of housing benefit applicants that have benefitted from the three per cent increase in local housing allowance rates in areas where it has been increased through the Targeted Affordability Funding concession.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66077","66077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706838","2017-03-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, for what reasons there is no planned increase in the local housing allowance rate for any property size in the Outer North East London Broad Rental Market Area under the Targeted Affordability Funding concession in 2017-18.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66078","66078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706839","2017-03-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make an assessment of the effect on tenants in the private rented sector of the changes in local housing allowance rates of housing benefit to the 30th percentile of local market rents and the freeze of those rates since April 2016.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66120","66120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706840","2017-03-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether EU nationals who have made national insurance contributions for 20 years or more will be entitled to a state pension after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66111","66111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706841","2017-03-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he plans to publish his Department's response to the 2016 consultation on child maintenance deduction orders against joint accounts; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66119","66119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706842","2017-03-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the daily living activity 3 of the personal independence payment assessment, how many people with multiple sclerosis have scored points on descriptors c, d, e or f for (a) new claims and (b) disability living allowance reassessments in (i) each year before and (ii) the period since November 2016.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66081","66081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706843","2017-03-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the mobility activity 1 of the personal independence payment (PIP) assessment, how many people with multiple sclerosis have scored points on descriptors d or f on a PIP assessment for (a) new claims and (b) disability living allowance reassessments in (i) each year before and (ii) in the period since November 2016.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66053","66053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706844","2017-03-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when the Nuclear Industry Council last met; what was discussed at that meeting and what decisions were made; and what changes have been made to the composition of the council since its previous meeting.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66112","66112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706845","2017-03-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the Government's campaign launched on 27 February 2017 to increase low paid workers' knowledge of national minimum and national living wage rights, what involvement trade unions will have in raising awareness of that campaign.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66151","66151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706846","2017-03-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the Government's campaign launched on 27 February 2017 to increase low paid workers' knowledge of national minimum and national living wage rights, how workers who identify a problem should seek to reclaim any arrears if they are unable to take their employer to an employment tribunal.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66152","66152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706847","2017-03-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the Government campaign launched on 27 February 2017 to increase low paid workers' knowledge of national minimum and national living wage rights, in which languages the advertising for that campaign will be written.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66149","66149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706848","2017-03-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the Government's campaign launched on 27 February 2017 to increase low paid workers' knowledge of national minimum and national living wage rights, how the advertising of that campaign will be targeted.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66150","66150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706849","2017-03-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the Government's campaign launched on 27 February 2017 to increase low paid workers' knowledge of national minimum and national living wage rights, what advice and support is available to employees to challenge their employers on their rights regarding pay.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66158","66158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706850","2017-03-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the effect of the exclusion of Northern Ireland from the Warm Home Discount Scheme on (a) the environment, (b) fuel poverty and (c) pensioner health and well-being.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66257","66257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706851","2017-03-06","Department for International Trade","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many bidders for the Trade Remedies Discovery Team contract, published on 13 February 2017, failed to meet the cultural fit criteria.","Biography information for Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66243","66243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706852","2017-03-06","Department for International Trade","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many bidders for the Market Access Discovery Team contract, published on 13 February 2017, failed to meet the cultural fit criteria.","Biography information for Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66244","66244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706853","2017-03-06","Department for International Trade","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether he approved the inclusion of the criteria of being committed to the best possible outcome for the UK following its departure from the EU in the cultural fit criteria used to evaluate suppliers bidding for the Trade Remedies Discovery Team contract, published on 13 February 2017.","Biography information for Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66245","66245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706854","2017-03-06","Department for International Trade","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what evaluation weighting applied to each of the cultural fit critera included in the advertisement for the Trade Remedies Discovery Team contract, published on 13 February 2017.","Biography information for Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66246","66246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706855","2017-03-06","Department for International Trade","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what evaluation weighting applied to each of the four cultural fit critera included in the advertisement for the Market Access Discovery Team contract, published on 13 February 2017.","Biography information for Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66247","66247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706856","2017-03-06","Department for International Trade","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, when he plans to fill the role of trade envoy to South Africa.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66166","66166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706857","2017-03-06","Department for International Trade","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what representations he has received from other Commonwealth countries on future trade agreements after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66141","66141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706858","2017-03-06","Department for International Trade","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether his Department has had discussions with the Home Office on the potential merits of including visa liberalisation within future trade agreements.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66144","66144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706859","2017-03-06","Department for International Trade","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps he is taking to encourage investment from other Commonwealth countries.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66145","66145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706860","2017-03-06","Department for International Trade","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, which other Commonwealth countries he plans to prioritise for trade agreements after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66143","66143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706861","2017-03-06","Department for International Trade","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether he plans to replicate existing EU non-reciprocal preferential trade agreements with developing countries after the UK leaves the EU; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66106","66106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706862","2017-03-06","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether the Government is gathering and monitoring the views of UK citizens who live in non-UK EU countries on the process of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66185","66185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706863","2017-03-06","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-03-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, pursuant to the Answer of 23 February 2017 to Question 64535, if he will make it his Department's policy to publish all correspondence between his Department and EU representatives prior to the UK's exit of the EU.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 66255","66255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706081","2017-03-02","Attorney General","2017-02-28","To ask the Attorney General, whether he has made an assessment of the written legal opinion by Sir David Edward, Sir Francis Jacobs and Sir Jeremy Lever on the constitutional role of Parliament in future decision making on withdrawal from the European Union and whether an Article 50 notification may be unilaterally withdrawn.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65913","65913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706082","2017-03-02","Cabinet Office","2017-02-28","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps he is taking to create a single copyright licensing arrangement across Government.","Biography information for Jim Dowd","Jim Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65907","65907"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706083","2017-03-02","Cabinet Office","2017-02-28","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what progress he is making in renegotiating the agreement with the Copyright Licensing Agency to facilitate the scanning and photocopying of documents by Government Departments where secondary royalties may be payable.","Biography information for Jim Dowd","Jim Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65908","65908"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706084","2017-03-02","HM Treasury","2017-02-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what funding his Department provides for the renewal of Government copyright licences.","Biography information for Jim Dowd","Jim Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65910","65910"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706086","2017-03-02","HM Treasury","2017-02-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what role his Department has in ensuring compliance with copyright licensing conditions across Government.","Biography information for Jim Dowd","Jim Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65911","65911"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706087","2017-03-02","HM Treasury","2017-02-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what representations he has received from the Welsh Government on the proposed Swansea Bay City Region deal.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65904","65904"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706088","2017-03-02","HM Treasury","2017-02-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will bring forward proposals to protect families recovering from debt from internet enforcement action and other charges related to such debt.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65883","65883"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706089","2017-03-02","HM Treasury","2017-02-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of section 24 of the Finance (No. 2) Act 2015 on (a) rental costs and (b) the supply of rental housing.","Biography information for Kwasi  Kwarteng","Kwasi Kwarteng","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65891","65891"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706091","2017-03-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to his letter of 16 July 2015 to Joanne Demetrius of Veolia ES (UK) Ltd, reference APP/M1900/V/13/2192045, if he will place in the Library a copy of the correspondence between his Department and Mr Kosky referred to in paragraph 250 of that letter.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65875","65875"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706092","2017-03-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether his Department has made an assessment of the potential effect of a combination of more restrictive immigration controls and lower population growth on (a) housing and planning (i) mechanisms and (ii) policy and (b) the amount of building taking place on land in the green belt.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65905","65905"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706093","2017-03-02","Ministry of Defence","2017-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, to whom US military bases sited in the UK are accountable.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65855","65855"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706094","2017-03-06","Department for Education","2017-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment her Department has made of the effect of recent changes in local government funding on the workloads of staff in schools.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65914","65914"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706095","2017-03-02","Department for Education","2017-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to ensure that schools in the North East are adequately funded.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65887","65887"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706097","2017-03-02","Department for Education","2017-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the effects of the introduction of the National Funding Formula on funding for schools in the North East.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65888","65888"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706098","2017-03-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 7 February 2017 to Question 62238, on Pets: Imports, for what reasons the number of dogs reported as entering the UK non-commercially under the Pet Travel Scheme increased between 2015 and 2016.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65885","65885"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706100","2017-03-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether her Department remains committed to developing a National Policy Statement for water supply for infrastructure; what recent assessment she has made of the need for such a statement; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65876","65876"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706101","2017-03-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to reduce or eliminate microbeads in products that are not currently included within the scope of the proposed ban; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65879","65879"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706102","2017-03-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the level of media freedom in Belarus; and what representations he has made to his Belarusian counterpart on the accreditation of journalists in that country.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65867","65867"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706103","2017-03-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent estimate he has made of the number of political prisoners in Belarus; and what representations he has made to his Belarusian counterpart on the reinstatement of the civil and political rights of former political prisoners in that country.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65868","65868"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706104","2017-03-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the fairness of the conduct of parliamentary elections in Belarus held in September 2016.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65869","65869"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706105","2017-03-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his Sudanese counterpart on the imprisonment of Reverend Hassan Abduraheem, Petr Jašek and Abdulmonem Abdumawla.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65874","65874"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706106","2017-03-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Belarusian counterpart on the imposition by Russian authorities of border controls between Belarus and Russia.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65866","65866"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706107","2017-03-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his Belarusian counterpart on the use of the death penalty in that country.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65862","65862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706108","2017-03-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the progress of negotiations on the potential accession of Belarus to the World Trade Organisation.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65863","65863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706109","2017-03-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the progress of implementation of the EU's Mobility Partnership with Belarus.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65864","65864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706110","2017-03-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the work of the EU-Belarus Human Rights Dialogue.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65865","65865"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706111","2017-03-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the Government's policy is on the maintenance of (a) the current EU arms embargo on Belarus and (b) EU-imposed travel bans and asset freezes in place in relation to certain specified Belarusian nationals.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65871","65871"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706113","2017-03-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the progress made by the Government of Belarus in implementing the recommendations of the final report of the OSCE Office for Democratic Institutions and Human Rights on the conduct of that country's presidential elections in October 2015.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65880","65880"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706114","2017-03-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Belarusian counterpart on the effects of Eurasian Economic Union membership on the economic performance of that country.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65890","65890"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706115","2017-03-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to ensure implementation of UN resolution 2334 (2016).","Biography information for Tommy Sheppard","Tommy Sheppard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65902","65902"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706116","2017-03-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, which of the recommendations set out by the Intelligence Services Commissioner in the Supplementary Report to the Annual Report of 2015, HC 458, the Government has implemented.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65920","65920"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706118","2017-03-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the Government plans to revise its guidance entitled, Consolidated Guidance to Intelligence Officers and Service Personnel on the Detention and Interviewing of Detainees Overseas, and on the Passing and Receipt of Intelligence Relating to Detainees, published in July 2010.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65921","65921"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706119","2017-03-06","HM Treasury","2017-02-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will consider mitigating the effects of the soft drinks industry levy on those manufacturers currently paying additional tax to use organic rather than conventional sugar.","Biography information for Sir Hugo Swire","Sir Hugo Swire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65915","65915"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706120","2017-03-06","Department of Health","2017-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effects of high-cost and low-volume sugary drinks on levels of obesity.","Biography information for Sir Hugo Swire","Sir Hugo Swire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65916","65916"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706121","2017-03-06","Department of Health","2017-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much of the recently announced additional funding for mental health and dementia services will be allocated to Hertfordshire; and what criteria will determine where and how that funding is spent.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65917","65917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706122","2017-03-06","Department of Health","2017-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he has received an application from Anglia Ruskin University in Chelmsford to establish a new medical school.","Biography information for Sir Simon Burns","Sir Simon Burns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65918","65918"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706123","2017-03-02","Department of Health","2017-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average waiting time is for (a) new patients presenting with symptoms of mental ill health to access talking therapies and (b) referrals to psychiatrists to receive an appointment.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65912","65912"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706124","2017-03-06","Department of Health","2017-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of healthcare research funding was allocated to each region in the most recent year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65898","65898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706125","2017-03-06","Department of Health","2017-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will publish a list of the savings targets for HIV treatment NHS England has asked each regional team to make in (a) 2017-18 and (b) 2018-19; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65896","65896"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706126","2017-03-02","Department of Health","2017-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will assess the potential effects of the one per cent cap on pay rises on the recruitment and retention of nurses.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65884","65884"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706129","2017-03-02","Department of Health","2017-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 3 February 2017 to Question 61825, what estimate his Department has made of the number of deaths that may arise from a lack of availability of bisphosphonates between now and that guidance being published in July 2018.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65858","65858"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706130","2017-03-08","Department of Health","2017-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many complaints were made about discharge packages for (a) nursing and residential homes and (b) patients' homes provided by (a) Lancashire Teaching Hospitals NHS Foundation Trust, (b) Blackpool Teaching Hospitals NHS Foundation Trust, (c) University Hospitals of Morecambe Bay NHS Foundation Trust and (d) East Lancashire Hospitals NHS Trust in each month in 2016.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65878","65878"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706131","2017-03-07","Home Office","2017-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many deportation charter flights there have been from Scotland to other countries in the last 12 months; and on what dates those flights took place.","Biography information for Tommy Sheppard","Tommy Sheppard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65877","65877"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706132","2017-03-02","Home Office","2017-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what guidelines her Department provides on the process for the removal of people from the UK who have exhausted an asylum application and appeal process.","Biography information for James Duddridge","James Duddridge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65886","65886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706133","2017-03-02","Home Office","2017-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many asylum applications to the UK by Eritrean nationals were (a) made and (b) granted in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65906","65906"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706134","2017-03-06","Department for International Development","2017-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what proportion of her Department's humanitarian aid budget in 2016 was allocated for a period of two or more years.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65899","65899"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706135","2017-03-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what plans the Government has to reform requirements for eligibility for legal aid for victims of domestic violence.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65872","65872"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706137","2017-03-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if she will take steps to ensure that domestic violence victims are not required to pay a fee to their GP to provide evidence of eligibility to legal aid.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65873","65873"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706138","2017-03-02","Department for Transport","2017-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many full-time equivalent civil servants of his Department and the Civil Aviation Authority are working on negotiating international aviation agreements.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65860","65860"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706139","2017-03-02","Department for Transport","2017-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many days of strike action have taken place on the railways in each of the last 10 years; and how many journeys have been affected by that action in each of those years.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65861","65861"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706140","2017-03-02","Department for Transport","2017-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what research his Department has recently commissioned on likely trends in the international aviation market.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65856","65856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706141","2017-03-06","Department for Transport","2017-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will bring forward proposals to address the use to local authority-specific licences for private hire vehicles in areas not covered by that licence.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65919","65919"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706142","2017-03-06","Department for Transport","2017-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much per capita funding was spent on roads maintenance in each region in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65897","65897"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706143","2017-03-06","Department for Transport","2017-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many times in the last year CrossCountry trains travelling from Birmingham to Bristol were late arriving at Cheltenham but on time arriving at Bristol Temple Meads.","Biography information for Richard Graham","Richard Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65922","65922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706144","2017-03-06","Department for Transport","2017-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many CrossCountry trains from (a) Birmingham to Bristol and (b) Bristol to Birmingham via Gloucester were on time in (i) each of the last five years and (ii) each year from 1998 to 2003.","Biography information for Richard Graham","Richard Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65923","65923"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706146","2017-03-02","Wales Office","2017-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what representations he has received from the Welsh Government on the proposed Swansea Bay City Region deal.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65903","65903"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706147","2017-03-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the proportion of people who will be affected by proposed changes to support for bereaved parents.","Biography information for Michelle Thomson","Michelle  Thomson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65889","65889"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706148","2017-03-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department takes to ensure the safe use of equipment used by companies to whom his Department's services are contracted.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65881","65881"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706150","2017-03-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department takes to ensure face-fit testing by the Fit2Fit Scheme providers is undertaken for all workers using tight-fitting respiratory face pieces.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65882","65882"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706151","2017-03-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to work with local authorities to (a) promote good health at work and (b) ensure that workers are protected from work-related illness.","Biography information for Stephen Pound","Stephen Pound","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65893","65893"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706152","2017-03-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how long the training programme is for a personal independence payment assessor.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65857","65857"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706153","2017-03-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department has taken to improve the personal independence payment assessment process to reduce the number of successful appeals against assessments.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65859","65859"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706156","2017-03-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps the Government is taking to provide advice and mentoring support to those who will receive the new lower rate of employment and support allowance; who will provide such advice and mentoring support; and when those measures will be in place.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65870","65870"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706159","2017-03-02","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will make an assessment of the effect of recent change in the value of sterling on exports from the UK's manufacturing sector.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65854","65854"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706161","2017-03-02","Department for International Trade","2017-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether any officials of his Department had their travel to or from the US affected by the US administration's recent changes to US entry regulations.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65894","65894"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706163","2017-03-02","Department for International Trade","2017-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many times Mr Adam Werritty has been received on his Department's premises at his behest since he took office.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65895","65895"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706164","2017-03-06","Department for International Trade","2017-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what plans he has to ensure that future UK trade deals take account of the Government's policy on increasing equity and support for farmers and other workers in developing countries.","Biography information for Tommy Sheppard","Tommy Sheppard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65900","65900"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706165","2017-03-02","Department for International Trade","2017-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many of his Department's staff by (a) sector focus and (b) country focus are (i) UK-based and (ii) based overseas.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65892","65892"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706167","2017-03-02","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what discussions his Department has had with representatives from the tourism sector on the implications of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65909","65909"
