"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42350","2014-03-11","HM Treasury","2014-03-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will discuss with the charitable and third sectors extending to those sectors the tax advantages offered by the Seed Enterprise Investment Scheme.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 902945","902945"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42351","2014-03-11","HM Treasury","2014-03-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of further borrowing on the UK economy.","Biography information for Stephen Phillips","Stephen Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 902948","902948"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42352","2014-03-11","HM Treasury","2014-03-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent fiscal steps he has taken to support small businesses.","Biography information for George Freeman","George Freeman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 902952","902952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42353","2014-03-11","HM Treasury","2014-03-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment he has made of the level of bank lending to businesses since May 2010.","Biography information for Mark Tami","Mark Tami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 902946","902946"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42354","2014-03-11","HM Treasury","2014-03-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what his policy is on the level of taxation on high-value property.","Biography information for Mike Freer","Mike Freer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 902947","902947"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42355","2014-03-11","HM Treasury","2014-03-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment he has made of the rate of economic growth.","Biography information for Mr Tim Yeo","Mr Tim Yeo","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 902951","902951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41146","2014-03-10","Attorney General","2014-03-04","To ask the Attorney General, what steps he is taking to ensure that more cases of female genital mutilation are prosecuted.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190517","190517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41148","2014-03-06","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether his Department provides funding to strengthen supply chains in the UK so that British producers and farmers can sell more of their food to public sector institutions.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190412","190412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41149","2014-03-06","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what his policy is on the Fairtrade Foundation's Make Bananas Fair campaign.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190535","190535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41150","2014-03-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what recent guidance he has issued to local authorities on their funding of trades union posts and facilities; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stewart Jackson","Mr Stewart Jackson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190538","190538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41151","2014-03-06","Cabinet Office","2014-03-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether the Cabinet Office has provided advice to ensure that all local resilience forums have effective and linked websites providing public information before, during and after an emergency.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190463","190463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41152","2014-03-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of children in each income decile and of each ethnicity live in lone parent households.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190547","190547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41153","2014-03-10","Cabinet Office","2014-03-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will publish on his Department's website the minutes of the Fraud Error and Debt Taskforce from June 2013.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190570","190570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41155","2014-03-06","Cabinet Office","2014-03-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment he has made of the amount of surplus public land sold to support housebuilding and development to date.","Biography information for Martin Vickers","Martin Vickers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190435","190435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41156","2014-03-06","HM Treasury","2014-03-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, for what reason he decided not to charge VAT on the sale of cryptocurrencies.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190434","190434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41157","2014-03-10","HM Treasury","2014-03-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what his policy is on merging income tax and national insurance.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190446","190446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41158","2014-03-06","HM Treasury","2014-03-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people changing from a single working tax credit claim to a joint claim have had to submit a fresh application in each of the last five years; what the average back-dated payment was to such an applicant in each such year; and what average time was taken for the joint claim to be paid in each such year.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190400","190400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41159","2014-03-06","HM Treasury","2014-03-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people have had working tax credits stopped in each of the last 10 years in each constituency.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190403","190403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41160","2014-03-18","HM Treasury","2014-03-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what funding his Department provided for staff to carry out trade union activities in each of the last three years; and how many days staff spent on those activities in those years.","Biography information for Alun Cairns","Alun Cairns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190486","190486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41161","2014-03-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will take steps to increase investment in house building; and if he will consider the introduction of rent controls.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190549","190549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41162","2014-03-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 3 March 2014, Official Report, column 694W, on polling stations, what assessment he has made of the effect of foreign language translation by local authorities on integration of non-English speakers into their communities.","Biography information for Robert Neill","Robert Neill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190554","190554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41163","2014-03-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many draft local plans have been referred back to local authorities for revision since the adoption of the National Planning Policy Framework.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190571","190571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41164","2014-03-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the average cost to a local authority of making an Article 4 direction.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190567","190567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41165","2014-03-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will publish his Department's evidence to the All Party Commission on Physical Activity.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190582","190582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41166","2014-03-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to ensure that car boot sales are properly regulated and do not contribute to traffic congestion in the surrounding area.","Biography information for Gavin Williamson","Gavin Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190563","190563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41167","2014-03-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to remove permitted development rights for car boot sales.","Biography information for Gavin Williamson","Gavin Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190565","190565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41168","2014-03-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many refusals of planning permission involving flood risk were appealed to the Planning Inspectorate in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12 and (c) 2012-13; and how many of these were (i) dismissed, (ii) allowed with conditions to fully implement the advice of the Environment Agency, (iii) allowed with conditions to partially implement the advice of the Environment Agency and (iv) allowed against the advice of the Environment Agency.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190566","190566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41169","2014-03-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many people subject to the under-occupancy penalty were evicted in each local authority in the North East in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190498","190498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41170","2014-03-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much brownfield land has been designated for house building within Greater London.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190540","190540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41171","2014-03-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many rough sleepers there were in each local authority in the North East in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190504","190504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41172","2014-03-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, in how many cases draft local plans have been referred back to authorities because of points raised about the duty to co-operate set out in the National Planning Policy Framework since the adoption of that framework.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190572","190572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41173","2014-03-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what he has made of the total number of people who will pay (a) increased council tax and (b) council tax for the first time from April 2014 as a result of the withdrawal of the council tax support transitional funding that was offered in the 2013-14 financial year.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190573","190573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41174","2014-03-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much land is available for house building within Greater London.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190477","190477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41175","2014-03-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the average density of homes per hectare is for new build developments within Greater London in the latest period for which data are available.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190508","190508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41176","2014-03-10","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, when the hon. Member for Walsall North will receive a reply to his letter of 23 January 2014, case reference CMS 244813.","Biography information for Mr David Winnick","Mr David Winnick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190523","190523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41177","2014-03-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much of the £20 million funding allocation for the Rural Community Broadband Fund will be spent by March 2015; and how much of the Fund he estimates will be returned to the European Union fund from which it was granted.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190506","190506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41178","2014-03-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many projects have been granted funding under the Rural Community Broadband Fund; how many projects under this Fund are under consideration for funding; how many such projects have been declined; and how many homes have been connected under this scheme to date.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190505","190505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41179","2014-03-10","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if she will publish the dates, agendas and minutes of meetings Ministers and officials in her Department have had on children, child obesity and food advertising with representatives of the (a) Advertising Association, (b) Direct Marketing Association and (c) Internet Advertising Bureau between January 2012 and March 2014.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190442","190442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41180","2014-03-10","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if she will publish her Department's evidence to the All Party Commission on Physical Activity.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190583","190583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41181","2014-03-06","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what progress his Department has made on translating and accrediting skills, experience and qualifications gained in the armed forces to the civilian world.","Biography information for Caroline Dinenage","Caroline Dinenage","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190537","190537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41182","2014-03-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what progress has been made since the NATO Bucharest summit in April 2008 in inviting Ukraine to join NATO; and whether this issue is on the agenda for the NATO summit in Newport in 2014.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190407","190407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41183","2014-03-10","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many allegations of (a) rape and (b) sexual assault were made within the chain of command against members of the armed forces in (i) 2010, (ii) 2011, (iii) 2012 and (iv) 2013; and, of such cases, how many resulted in a prosecution by the Service Prosecution Authority.","Biography information for Gemma Doyle","Gemma Doyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190438","190438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41184","2014-03-10","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many prosecutions of (a) rape and (b) sexual assault of members of the armed forces resulted in a conviction by the Military Courts Service in (i) 2010, (ii) 2011, (iii) 2012 and (iv) 2013.","Biography information for Gemma Doyle","Gemma Doyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190437","190437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41185","2014-03-27","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the objectives are of Britain's Defence and Security Strategy.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190480","190480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41186","2014-03-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much was paid to returning officers in England for running (a) council by-elections and (b) parish council by-elections in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190520","190520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41187","2014-03-06","Department for Education","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will introduce universal qualifications for functional skills to better allow employers to understand an individual's competencies.","Biography information for Mr Marcus Jones","Mr Marcus Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190405","190405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41188","2014-03-10","Department for Education","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many draft regulations were raised by his Department in each of the last five years; and how many such regulations (a) were and (b) were not consulted upon.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Turner","Mr Andrew Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190510","190510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41189","2014-03-12","Department for Education","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 24 February 2014, Official Report, column 223W, on schools: construction, how many bids his Department has received for financing to date.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190448","190448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41190","2014-03-10","Department for Education","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to ensure that teachers receive adequate training in recognising children at risk of female genital mutilation; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190521","190521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41191","2014-03-10","Department for Education","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Health on Harperbury Free School.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190513","190513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41192","2014-03-06","Department for Education","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to his Answer of 13 February 2014, Official Report, column 825W, on students: finance, for what reason his Department has not compared the number of 18-year-olds affected by changes in funding for full-time education with the 16 to 18 cohort in full-time education.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190472","190472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41193","2014-03-12","Department for Education","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 24 February 2014, Official Report, column 223W, on schools: construction, which schools (a) are expected to open in February 2014 and (b) are not planned to open before 2015.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190449","190449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41194","2014-03-06","Department for Education","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 24 February 2014, Official Report, column 211W, on Children's Social Services, how many local authorities have stopped using the Integrated Children's System since 2006.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190471","190471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41195","2014-03-18","Department for Education","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what funding his Department provided for staff to carry out trade union activities in each of the last three years; and how many days staff spent on those activities in those years.","Biography information for Alun Cairns","Alun Cairns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190482","190482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41196","2014-03-10","Department for Education","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to ensure that schools have policies in place to (a) help to identify girls who have undergone female genital mutilation and (b) refer them to appropriate support.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190516","190516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41197","2014-03-06","Department for Education","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will make employability and employment outcomes key measures of accountability for schools.","Biography information for Mr Marcus Jones","Mr Marcus Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190431","190431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41198","2014-03-10","Department for Education","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will publish his Department's evidence to the All Party Commission on Physical Activity.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190581","190581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41199","2014-03-06","Department for Education","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what services and support his Department plans to provide to families who will be ineligible for the Government's new childcare scheme.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190551","190551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41200","2014-03-06","Department for Education","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to support low-income families to access affordable and quality childcare and to ensure that no children miss out on the early stages of education.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190552","190552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41201","2014-03-10","Department for Education","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which local authorities offer Family Group Conferences to families undergoing care proceedings.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190545","190545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41202","2014-03-10","Department for Education","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which children's centres offer (a) antenatal appointments, (b) birth registration and (c) parenting classes.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190544","190544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41203","2014-03-10","Department for Education","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, in which (a) primary and (b) secondary schools in each local authority area more than (i) 10, (ii) 20, (iii) 30 and (iv) 40 per cent of pupils were classified as persistent absentees in the latest year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190543","190543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41204","2014-03-06","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps his Department took to mark Cold Homes Week.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190532","190532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41205","2014-03-06","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what his policy is on compensatory forestry planting to mitigage deforestation undertaken as a result of wind turbine construction.","Biography information for Sandra Osborne","Sandra Osborne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190502","190502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41206","2014-03-18","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what funding his Department provided for staff to carry out trade union activities in each of the last three years; and how many days staff spent on those activities in those years.","Biography information for Alun Cairns","Alun Cairns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190483","190483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41207","2014-03-10","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate he has made of likely changes in wholesale electricity prices in the period 2014 to 2018; and whether the influence of the Carbon Price Floor has been incorporated into those estimates. [R]","Biography information for Nigel Adams","Nigel Adams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190561","190561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41208","2014-03-10","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what comparative estimate his Department has made of (a) clean spark spreads as applicable to gas generation and (b) clean dark spreads as applicable to coal generation, including the effect of the Carbon Price Floor, for winter 2015 and winter 2014; and whether they are consistent with recognised market data such as ICIS Heren. [R]","Biography information for Nigel Adams","Nigel Adams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190579","190579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41209","2014-03-06","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what progress his Department has made on plans for an interconnector to Iceland.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190470","190470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41210","2014-03-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether the Government has established a programme to support and encourage individuals and communities to be better prepared and more self-reliant during emergencies.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190420","190420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41211","2014-03-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what work his Department and infrastructure operators have done to build a level of resilience into critical infrastructure assets that ensures continuity during a worst-case flood event.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190418","190418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41212","2014-03-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether category 1 and 2 responders currently assess the effectiveness of their emergency response facilities, including flexible accommodation, IT and communications systems.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190423","190423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41213","2014-03-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether, in all cases relating to the recent flooding, upper tier local authorities have become the lead responders to multi-agency planning for severe weather emergencies at the local level and for triggering multi-agency arrangements in response to severe weather warnings and local impact assessments.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190421","190421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41214","2014-03-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether his Department has begun its systematic programme to reduce the disruption of essential services resulting from natural hazards by publishing a national framework and policy statement, setting out the process, timescales and expectations.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190416","190416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41215","2014-03-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of whether local authorities have co-ordinated a systematic programme of community engagement in their area during recovery phases.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190414","190414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41216","2014-03-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when national flooding exercises have taken place in order to test arrangements which Government departments have put into place to deal with flooding and infrastructure emergencies in the last five years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190415","190415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41217","2014-03-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what work Government departments and the Environment Agency have undertaken with infrastructure operators to identify the vulnerability and risk of assets to flooding; and if he will publish a summary of the analysis found in sector resilience plans.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190417","190417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41218","2014-03-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to his Department's announcement of 6 February 2014 on new flood defence schemes, what proportion of that funding will be allocated to (a) the York area and (b) York Outer constituency.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190413","190413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41219","2014-03-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether the Government has established a National Resilience Forum to facilitate national level multi-agency planning for flooding and other emergencies.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190456","190456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41220","2014-03-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether the Government has established a Cabinet Committee with a remit to improve the country's ability to deal with flooding and implement the recommendations of the Review following the 2007 floods.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190455","190455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41221","2014-03-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether all upper tier local authorities have established Oversight and Scrutiny Committees to review work by public sector bodies and essential service providers in order to manage flood risk and implement the suggestions of the Review following the 2007 floods; and whether any such reports have been made public and reviewed by Government Offices and the Environment Agency.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190457","190457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41222","2014-03-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with regard to the environmental land management scheme announced on 26 February 2014, if he will provide further details on (a) how the scheme will be targeted, (b) whether specific local areas have been identified for the scheme, (c) what the (i) minimum and (ii) maximum grants available to farmers are, (d) when the scheme will be open for applications to farmers and (e) what assessment his Department has made of the potential environmental benefits of this scheme.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190487","190487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41223","2014-03-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether and when local resilience forums have evaluated and shared lessons from both the response and recovery phases to inform planning for future emergencies.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190458","190458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41224","2014-03-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much of the Rural Development Pillar within the Common Agricultural Policy envelope has been allocated in (a) cash and (b) percentage terms to date.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190488","190488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41225","2014-03-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether flood risk has been made part of the mandatory search requirements for property purchase; and whether flood risk has formed part of home information packs.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190460","190460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41226","2014-03-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether the Risk and Regulation Advisory Council has explored how the public can improve their understanding of community risks, including those associated with flooding; and whether his Department has implemented such findings as appropriate.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190459","190459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41227","2014-03-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will rewrite the counter-invasive species strategy to reduce the cost of management of non-native invasive species.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190491","190491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41228","2014-03-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of whether local authority contact centres have taken the lead in dealing with general enquiries from the public during and after major flooding and redirecting calls to other organisations when appropriate.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190461","190461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41229","2014-03-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether the Environment Agency now works with local responders to raise awareness in flood risk areas and identifies a range of mechanisms to warn the public in response to flooding.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190462","190462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41230","2014-03-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether the insurance industry has developed and implemented industry guidance for flooding events, covering reasonable expectations of the performance of insurers and reasonable actions by customers.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190426","190426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41231","2014-03-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether local recovery coordination groups have made early recommendations to elected local authority members about longer-term regeneration and economic development opportunities.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190452","190452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41232","2014-03-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of whether insurance notices now include information on flood risk and the simple steps that can be taken to mitigate the effects in flood risk areas.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190427","190427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41233","2014-03-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether all Government guidance has been updated to reflect the new arrangements for recovery; and whether local resilience forums have planned, trained and exercised on this basis.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190453","190453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41234","2014-03-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether the Environment Agency has yet provided a specialised site-specific flood warning service for infrastructure operators in order to offer longer lead times and greater levels of detail about the velocity and depth of flooding.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190428","190428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41235","2014-03-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether the Government has issued clear guidance on expected levels of Category 2 responders' engagement in planning, exercising and response; and what assessment the Government has made of the case for strengthening enforcement arrangements.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190432","190432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41236","2014-03-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether the Government has extended the duty to undertake business continuity planning to infrastructure operating Category 2 responders to a standard equivalent to BS25999, which is ensured through an annual benchmarking exercise within each sector.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190419","190419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41237","2014-03-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether the Government has published an action plan to implement the recommendations of the Review released after the 2007 floods, with a director in his Department overseeing the programme of delivery and issuing regular updates.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190454","190454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41238","2014-03-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, under what parameters the UK is eligible for funding from the EU's Solidarity Fund; and whether he plans to make an application for funding under the Fund following recent cases of severe weather.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190507","190507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41239","2014-03-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what work the Environment Agency has done with its partners to progressively develop and bring into use flood visualisation tools that are designed to meet the needs of flood-risk managers, emergency planners and responders.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190429","190429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41240","2014-03-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what progress the Government has made towards creating a fully-funded national capability for flood rescue, with fire and rescue authorities playing a leading role.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190430","190430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41241","2014-03-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department and the insurance industry have taken to deliver a public education programme setting out the benefits of insurance in the context of flooding.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190425","190425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41242","2014-03-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the degree to which, for emergencies spanning more than a single local authority area, Government Offices have ensured coherence and coordination between recovery operations.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190451","190451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41243","2014-03-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to protect ancient woods in (a) the UK and (b) South Staffordshire.","Biography information for Gavin Williamson","Gavin Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190564","190564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41244","2014-03-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what funding his Department provided for staff to carry out trade union activities in each of the last three years; and how many days staff spent on those activities in those years.","Biography information for Alun Cairns","Alun Cairns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190484","190484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41245","2014-03-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans he has to increase commercial coniferous forest planting; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sandra Osborne","Sandra Osborne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190500","190500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41246","2014-03-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate he has made of the proportion of UK forests that are under sustainable management.","Biography information for Sandra Osborne","Sandra Osborne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190501","190501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41247","2014-03-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received of recent weapons transfers to Hezbollah from Syria.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190528","190528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41248","2014-03-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many executions there were in Iran of (a) adults and (b) minors in 2013. [R]","Biography information for Mr Mark Hoban","Mr Mark Hoban","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190539","190539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41249","2014-03-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to encourage Syrian opposition groups to work together.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190533","190533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41250","2014-03-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of Iran's relationship with Hezbollah.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190527","190527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41251","2014-03-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many requests for consular assistance relating to crime have been made by UK citizens at the UK embassy in Kiev since November 2013.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Mr David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190474","190474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41252","2014-03-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to ensure the safety of British citizens in Ukraine.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Mr David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190475","190475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41253","2014-03-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what funding his Department provided for staff to carry out trade union activities in each of the last three years; and how many days staff spent on those activities in those years.","Biography information for Alun Cairns","Alun Cairns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190485","190485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41254","2014-03-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what guidance he has issued to Government Departments and Agencies on when it is appropriate to refer to the Falkland Islands as Falkland Islands (Malvinas) or Malvinas when answering parliamentary questions.","Biography information for Thomas Docherty","Thomas Docherty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190557","190557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41255","2014-03-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to the Egyptian government about trafficking of East African refugees in the Sinai Peninsula; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190553","190553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41256","2014-03-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with the government of Myanmar about the Fortify Rights report, Policies of Persecution and discrimination and violence against Rohingya Muslims in Myanmar.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190555","190555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41257","2014-03-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the publication by Christian Solidarity Worldwide, Indonesia: Pluralism in peril, what assessment he has made of the conclusions of that report; what representations he has made to the Indonesian government about tolerance for religious communities including Christians; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr James Clappison","Mr James Clappison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190568","190568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41258","2014-03-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what guidance his Department has issued to Paralympians attending the Sochi Paralympics.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190518","190518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41259","2014-03-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of Hezbollah's military presence in Syria.","Biography information for Nick de Bois","Nick de Bois","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190515","190515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41260","2014-03-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received of involvement by Hezbollah's political wing in terrorist activities.","Biography information for Nick de Bois","Nick de Bois","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190514","190514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41261","2014-03-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his Russian counterpart on the Russian government's perceptions of events in Ukraine; and if he will place in the Library a copy of any written communication he has had on this matter with Mr Lavrov.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190444","190444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41262","2014-03-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent reports he has received of arms sales from Iran to Iraq.","Biography information for Guto Bebb","Guto Bebb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190445","190445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41263","2014-03-10","Department of Health","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of loneliness on (a) life expectancy, (b) cardiovascular disease, (c) dementia and (d) recovery from illness.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190440","190440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41264","2014-03-10","Department of Health","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of (a) the number of people in the UK suffering from (i) loneliness and (ii) chronic loneliness and (b) the cost to the NHS of such conditions.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190439","190439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41265","2014-03-10","Department of Health","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if his Department plans to introduce guidance for non-statutory pregnancy counselling services.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190441","190441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41266","2014-03-10","Department of Health","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if his Department will publish its assessment of the UK Council for Psychotherapy's February 2014 report on Conversion therapy.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190443","190443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41267","2014-03-10","Department of Health","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that health workers identify girls at risk of female genital mutilation and refer them to social services for a safeguarding plan to be put in place.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190519","190519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41268","2014-03-10","Department of Health","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, for what reasons the Chairman of NHS Property Services has not yet been appointed.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190512","190512"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41269","2014-03-06","Department of Health","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much his Department paid in fees and allowances to pharmacies in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Ben Gummer","Ben Gummer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190473","190473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41270","2014-03-06","Department of Health","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will review the effectiveness of the test used to diagnose those with pernicious anaemia; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190481","190481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41271","2014-03-06","Department of Health","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make it his policy that future grants from his Department to the Nursing and Midwifery Council should be subject to agreement of a cap on registration fees for newly-qualified nurses.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190450","190450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41272","2014-03-10","Department of Health","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will publish his Department's evidence to the All Party Commission on Physical Activity.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190584","190584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41273","2014-03-10","Department of Health","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which organisation is responsible for responding to requests under the Freedom of Information Act 2000 about issues which formerly fell under the remit of strategic health authorities.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190569","190569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41274","2014-03-10","Department of Health","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many prescriptions for (a) methlphenidate, (b) benzodiazepines, (c) morphine sulphate and (d) oxycodone were issued in (i) the UK, (ii) England, (iii) Scotland, (iv) Wales, (v) Northern Ireland, (vi) each English local authority and (vii) each Welsh local authority area in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190546","190546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41275","2014-03-06","Department of Health","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he was informed that NHS England would not complete the Congenital Heart Disease Review by June 2014.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190536","190536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41276","2014-03-06","Home Office","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the number of EU migrants who have arrived in the UK for work since 1 January 2014.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190497","190497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41277","2014-03-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what work his Department has commissioned on the use by migrants of UK welfare systems.","Biography information for Baroness Jowell","Dame Tessa Jowell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190447","190447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41278","2014-03-10","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-03-04","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what requirements there are for a political party operating in another country which has a branch in the UK to register with the Electoral Commission.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190541","190541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41279","2014-03-10","Home Office","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she became aware of the administrative scheme giving on-the-run republican terrorist suspects reassurances that they were no longer being sought for prosecution within the UK: and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190562","190562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41280","2014-03-06","Home Office","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether, in all cases of recent flooding, where a Gold Command has been established for severe weather events, the police, unless agreed otherwise locally have convened and led the multi-agency response.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190422","190422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41281","2014-03-06","Home Office","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what measures her Department has in place to (a) safeguard biosecurity and (b) protect against animal welfare violations regarding the importing of dogs from Eastern Europe to the UK.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190489","190489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41282","2014-03-06","Home Office","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent discussions her Department has had with ferry companies operating out of the UK on the illegal transportation of dogs into the UK from Continental Europe; and what recent assessment she has made of the adequacy of such measures.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190490","190490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41284","2014-03-06","Department for International Development","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to promote World Water Day; and if she will prioritise financial support for water sanitation and waste water treatment up to 2015.","Biography information for Naomi Long","Naomi Long","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190402","190402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41285","2014-03-10","Department for International Development","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what discussions (a) she and (b) Ministers in her Department have had with representatives of the Rwandan government since December 2013.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190465","190465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41286","2014-03-10","Department for International Development","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many full-time officials in her Department have responsibility for its role and activities in Afghanistan.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190466","190466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41287","2014-03-10","Department for International Development","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many full-time officials in her Department have responsibility for issues related to women and girls.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190467","190467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41288","2014-03-10","Department for International Development","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department has taken to assess the human rights records of states in receipt of direct development aid from the UK.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190468","190468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41289","2014-03-10","Department for International Development","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department has taken to evaluate the UK's role in the relief effort in the Philippines following Typhoon Haiyan.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190469","190469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41290","2014-03-06","Department for International Development","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what procedures are in place to ensure foreign aid reaches its target and is not embezzled by corrupt or dictatorial regimes.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190534","190534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41291","2014-03-10","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much his Department spent on first-class rail travel by (a) Ministers and (b) officials in (i) 2010, (ii) 2011, (iii) 2012 and (iv) 2013.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190548","190548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41292","2014-03-10","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps the Government is taking to encourage people to make wills.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190577","190577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41293","2014-03-10","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many special advisors are employed in his Department; what the budget is for the employment of special advisors; and what the cost of employing special advisors in his Department was in each year from 2010.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190578","190578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41294","2014-03-10","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what guidelines are applied when making a Public Defence Service appointment; and what provision is made for advertising Public Defence Service appointments in Welsh.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190464","190464"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41295","2014-03-10","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many cases of (a) chemical castration of prisoners and (b) assaults by prisoners on other prisoners resulting in castration there have been in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190522","190522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41296","2014-03-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when he plans to bring forward legislative proposals to ban the use of wild animals in circuses.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190499","190499"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41297","2014-03-06","Northern Ireland Office","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, pursuant to her Written Statement of 25 February 2014, Official Report, columns 16-18WS, on High Court judgment, what the current status is of the 187 administrative letters sent to on-the-runs; whether the letters have been rescinded; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190556","190556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41298","2014-03-10","Northern Ireland Office","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, with reference to the judgment in the case of John Downey, whether she plans to correct the Answer of 10 January 2011 given by the right hon. Member for North Shropshire to the hon. Member for North Down, Official Report, column 46W, on on-the-runs; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190585","190585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41299","2014-03-10","Northern Ireland Office","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, whether the IRA members suspected of the murder of Chief Superintendant Breen and Superintendent Buchanan in March 1989 are amongst the 187 on-the-runs who received so-called comfort or administrative letters; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190586","190586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41300","2014-03-06","HM Treasury","2014-03-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether recently announced additional funding for anti-flooding measures has a consequential funding implication for Wales.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190493","190493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41301","2014-03-10","Scotland Office","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what assessment he has made of the effect of the Government's welfare reforms on sick and disabled people in Scotland.","Biography information for Iain McKenzie","Iain McKenzie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190559","190559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41302","2014-03-10","Scotland Office","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what plans he has to meet representatives of the Trussell Trust in Scotland; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Iain McKenzie","Iain McKenzie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190542","190542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41303","2014-03-06","Speaker's Committee on the Electorial Commission","2014-03-04","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what percentage of postal votes were cast in the 100 constituencies with the largest amount of postal votes in the most recent general election.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190399","190399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41304","2014-03-06","Speaker's Committee on the Electorial Commission","2014-03-04","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, how many (a) items of correspondence and (b) meetings with Ministers in the Electoral Commission has had on (i) postal ballot restrictions and (ii) use of photo ID for voting, in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190401","190401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41305","2014-03-06","Department for Transport","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the Highways Agency has recently considered (a) the vulnerability of motorways and trunk roads to flooding, (b) the potential for better warnings and strategic road clearance to avoid people becoming stranded and (c) plans to support people who become stranded.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190424","190424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41306","2014-03-06","Department for Transport","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the average number of rail passengers travelling in first class on weekdays from London to (a) Darlington and (b) Eaglescliffe.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190503","190503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41307","2014-03-10","Department for Transport","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent proposals he has considered for provision by open access train operating companies on the East Coast Mainline; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stewart Jackson","Mr Stewart Jackson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190560","190560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41308","2014-03-10","Department for Transport","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will publish his Department's evidence to the All Party Commission on Physical Activity.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190580","190580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41309","2014-03-10","Department for Transport","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the level of funding per head of the population for transport in (a) Barnsley Central constituency, (b) Yorkshire and the Humber, (c) London and (d) England.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190576","190576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41310","2014-03-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what additional help his Department offers to young unemployed people in regions of high unemployment.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190574","190574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41311","2014-03-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 3 March 2014, Official Report, column 685W, on pensions regulator, on what grounds the regulator did not take action in three cases; and who the 26 employers were.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190575","190575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41312","2014-03-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the changes in the level of absolute child poverty since May 2010; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Iain McKenzie","Iain McKenzie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190558","190558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41313","2014-03-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to encourage under-19 school leavers to start apprenticeships.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190550","190550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41314","2014-03-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will publish the results of the reclassification of arrears trial run by the Child Maintenance Group which began in June 2012 and ended in October 2013.","Biography information for Stephen Lloyd","Stephen Lloyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190496","190496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41315","2014-03-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will bring forward proposals to ensure that British nationals taking part in the International Citizen's Service are exempt from undergoing the habitual residency test.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190531","190531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41316","2014-03-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether his Department plans to carry out a public consultation on the statistics being developed to give information on the new 2012 statutory child maintenance scheme.","Biography information for Stephen Lloyd","Stephen Lloyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190495","190495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41317","2014-03-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he will publish statistics on the performance of the Child Maintenance Service in collecting statutory maintenance liabilities under the 2012 scheme; and whether such statistics will include information on the amount and proportion of liabilities not collected each month.","Biography information for Stephen Lloyd","Stephen Lloyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190494","190494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41318","2014-03-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people have started their own business with support from the work programme.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190526","190526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41319","2014-03-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the cost of introducing a jobseeker classification instrument.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190525","190525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41320","2014-03-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people received a first lower tier sanction which was subsequently overturned in the most recent year for which data are available.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190530","190530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41321","2014-03-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of people who have begun an apprenticeship through support provided on the work programme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190529","190529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41322","2014-03-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the growth of credit union membership since the award of the Credit Union Expansion Project contract to the Association of British Credit Unions in April 2013.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190433","190433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41323","2014-03-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the extent to which the commitment to 90 per cent of expected pension entitlement for those involved in the Financial Assistance Scheme has been reached.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190492","190492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41324","2014-03-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the progress of the Work Programme best practice group; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190524","190524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41325","2014-03-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will establish a hotline open to hon. Members seeking to contact his Department on the Capita-run health assessment for personal independence payments.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190511","190511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41326","2014-03-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people have had their benefits reduced to the maximum under the benefit cap (a) nationally and (b) in Scotland to date.","Biography information for Iain McKenzie","Iain McKenzie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190509","190509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41327","2014-03-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of all claims for (a) jobseeker's allowance, (b) incapacity benefit or severe disablement allowance or employment and support allowance and (c) income support in the last 10 years have lasted for (i) less than three months, (ii) between three and six months, (iii) between six and 12 months, (iv) between one and two years and (v) over two years.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190436","190436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41328","2014-03-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will take steps to encourage local authorities to make longer term awards of discretionary housing payments for those people with disabilities.","Biography information for John Hemming","John Hemming","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190410","190410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41329","2014-03-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much in discretionary housing payments has been allocated in (a) England and (b) Birmingham for those affected by the under-occupancy penalty in (i) 2013-14, (ii) 2014-15 and (iii) 2015-16.","Biography information for John Hemming","John Hemming","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190411","190411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41330","2014-03-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the use of discretionary housing payment to deal with people affected by the under-occupancy penalty over the next two financial years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for John Hemming","John Hemming","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190409","190409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41331","2014-03-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the total cost of processing and managing claims for disability living allowance was in (a) 2008-09, (b) 2009-10, (c) 2010-11, (d) 2011-12 and (e) 2012-13.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190404","190404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41332","2014-03-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how people who begin claiming universal credit in a pilot area will be treated if they (a) move to live in an area where universal credit is not being piloted, (b) form a new relationship such that they are classified as part of a couple and (c) have a child.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190479","190479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41333","2014-03-06","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many tribunals have been stayed pending decisions in other courts relating to decisions on benefits for over six months; how many claimants this involves; and what the total value of benefits involved is.","Biography information for John Hemming","John Hemming","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190406","190406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41334","2014-03-06","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many tribunals considering appeals on benefits decisions are currently held pending decisions in other courts; how many claimants this affects; what the value of such benefit claims is; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for John Hemming","John Hemming","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190408","190408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41335","2014-03-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when the the universal credit programme will start accepting claims from people currently eligible for or claiming employment support allowance.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190478","190478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41336","2014-03-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people who have begun claiming universal credit in a pilot area have (a) moved to live in an area where universal credit is not being piloted, (b) formed a new relationship such that they are classified as part of a couple and (c) have had a child.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190476","190476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42047","2014-03-10","Home Office","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to reduce crime and disorder caused by alcohol.","Biography information for Jesse Norman","Jesse Norman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 902917","902917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42048","2014-03-10","Home Office","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the reliability of crime statistics.","Biography information for Nick Smith","Nick Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 902922","902922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42049","2014-03-10","Home Office","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to involve the private sector in crime reduction and prevention.","Biography information for Margot James","Margot James","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 902918","902918"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42050","2014-03-10","Home Office","2014-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to prevent violent crime.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 902926","902926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40878","2014-03-06","Attorney General","2014-03-03","To ask the Attorney General, how much (a) wrongly-claimed VAT and (b) interest on such VAT the Serious Fraud Office has been required to pay to HM Revenue and Customs in 2014 to date.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190272","190272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40879","2014-03-06","Attorney General","2014-03-03","To ask the Attorney General, how much the Serious Fraud Office has been fined in respect of VAT claims in 2014 to date.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190273","190273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40880","2014-03-05","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to ensure that unrepresented defendants in very high cost cases are adequately supported in court.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190253","190253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40881","2014-03-05","Attorney General","2014-03-03","To ask the Attorney General, what conclusions the Crown Prosecution Service has drawn from its September 2013 consultation on the functioning of the victims' right to review.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190256","190256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40882","2014-03-05","Attorney General","2014-03-03","To ask the Attorney General, if he will investigate the extent and appropriateness of the Serious Fraud Office's co-operation with the Iranian authorities in recent years.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190257","190257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40883","2014-03-05","Attorney General","2014-03-03","To ask the Attorney General, what recent discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Justice on defendants who represent themselves in very high cost cases.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190255","190255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40884","2014-03-05","Attorney General","2014-03-03","To ask the Attorney General, what estimate has been made of the number of upcoming very high cost prosecutions by the (a) Crown Prosecution Service and (b) Serious Fraud Office that will involve defendants who will be representing themselves.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190259","190259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40885","2014-03-05","Attorney General","2014-03-03","To ask the Attorney General, what proportion of the sentences that he successfully referred to the Court of Appeal as unduly lenient in 2013 were the result of guilty pleas.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190262","190262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40886","2014-03-05","Attorney General","2014-03-03","To ask the Attorney General, pursuant to the Answer of 14 January 2014, Official Report, columns 466-8W, on taxation: fraud, what the annual sum total was of the confiscation orders listed in that Answer.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190292","190292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40887","2014-03-05","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to encourage Government departments to use the Post Office to provide additional services to replace ones being moved solely online or abolished.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190265","190265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40888","2014-03-06","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many meetings his Department (a) has had and (b) plans to have with publicans tied to the large pub companies to discuss plans for a statutory code and adjudicator.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190229","190229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40889","2014-03-05","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to repeal paragraph 6 of Schedule 1 of the Copyright, Designs and Patents Act 1988.","Biography information for Mr Gerry Sutcliffe","Mr Gerry Sutcliffe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190269","190269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40890","2014-03-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what funding his Department provided for staff to carry out trade union activities in each of the last three years; and how many days staff spent on those activities in each of those years.","Biography information for Alun Cairns","Alun Cairns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190234","190234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40891","2014-03-06","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of his Department's proposed changes to the Land Registry on jobs in Plymouth.","Biography information for Oliver Colvile","Oliver Colvile","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190323","190323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40892","2014-03-05","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 10 February 2014, Official Report, column 499W, on further education: older people, if he will publish an analysis of the age groups accessing advanced learning loans; and if he will promote the scheme to enable younger workers to gain skills from older colleagues.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190250","190250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40893","2014-03-05","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether consideration was given to including schemes to protect leaseholders within the Consumer Rights Bill.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190239","190239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40894","2014-03-05","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what his policy is on amendments to the EU proposal to update the accounting directives to include non-financial reporting for large companies that would require companies to report with regard to the UN Guiding Principles on Business and Human Rights.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190240","190240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40895","2014-03-05","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assistance is available to businesses affected by flooding.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190157","190157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40896","2014-03-06","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answers of 24 February 2014, Official Report, column 166W, on students: loans, when he expects to start reviewing the RAB charge model.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190199","190199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40897","2014-03-05","Cabinet Office","2014-03-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people have reported phishing emails purporting to be from a Government department in each year of the last five years; how many such people have been so defrauded; and how many times action has successfully been taken against the sender of such emails.","Biography information for Richard Graham","Richard Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190162","190162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40898","2014-03-05","Cabinet Office","2014-03-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what discussions his Department has had with internet service providers on removing fake or misleading websites for government services.","Biography information for Richard Graham","Richard Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190164","190164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40899","2014-03-05","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-03-03","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, how much the 10 most highly-paid returning officers in the UK are paid.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190165","190165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40900","2014-03-17","Cabinet Office","2014-03-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what funding his Department provided for staff to carry out trade union activities in each of the last three years; and how many days staff spent on those activities in each of those years.","Biography information for Alun Cairns","Alun Cairns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190235","190235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40901","2014-03-06","Cabinet Office","2014-03-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the total amount of remuneration paid to non-executive directors of Government departments was for the financial year (a) 2010-11 and (b) 2012-13.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190309","190309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40902","2014-03-05","Cabinet Office","2014-03-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps his Department is taking to identify and remove misleading or fake websites for government services.","Biography information for Richard Graham","Richard Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190298","190298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40903","2014-03-06","Cabinet Office","2014-03-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people were employed in Number 10 Downing Street in 2012; and how many people are so employed currently.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190310","190310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40904","2014-03-05","Cabinet Office","2014-03-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what action his Department is taking against companies or individuals who set up and profit from fake and or misleading websites for government services.","Biography information for Richard Graham","Richard Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190299","190299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40905","2014-03-06","HM Treasury","2014-03-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many awards of tax credits there have been where the national insurance number of one or more claimants was identifiable as one issued to a person who was not a UK national at the time of issue of the number in the latest period for which figures are available; and what the total amount was of those awards.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190311","190311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40906","2014-03-05","HM Treasury","2014-03-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will press for amendments allowing national governments discretion to exempt low risk industries from the provisions of the Fourth EU Anti-Money Laundering Directive; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Gerry Sutcliffe","Mr Gerry Sutcliffe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190268","190268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40907","2014-03-06","HM Treasury","2014-03-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 25 February 2014, Official Report, column 284W, on equality, what the (a) total departmental expenditure, (b) number and (c) cost of people employed for the purpose of promoting equality and diversity was in 2013-14 to date.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190201","190201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40908","2014-03-05","HM Treasury","2014-03-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with the Financial Conduct Authority regarding fees charged by payday lenders.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190251","190251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40909","2014-03-05","HM Treasury","2014-03-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what fiscal steps he has taken to reduce the amount of tax paid by families.","Biography information for Guy Opperman","Guy Opperman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190183","190183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40910","2014-03-06","HM Treasury","2014-03-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the number of units of alcohol sold in the UK in the most recent year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190274","190274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40911","2014-03-05","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will bring forward legislative proposals aimed at ensuring that all new properties are fitted with flood resistent bricks.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190152","190152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40912","2014-03-05","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what powers he has to investigate the financial management of local authorities.","Biography information for Mr Ben Wallace","Mr Ben Wallace","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190293","190293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40913","2014-03-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many individuals registered as homeless in Barrow and Furness constituency were aged (a) under 16 and (b) 16 to 18 in each of the last three years.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190315","190315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40914","2014-03-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what funding his Department provided for staff to carry out trade union activities in each of the last three years; and how many days staff spent on those activities in each of those years.","Biography information for Alun Cairns","Alun Cairns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190236","190236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40915","2014-03-05","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what formula his Department uses to value Best and Most Versatile (BMV) land for the purposes of assessing planning applications to local planning authorities; if he will make it his policy to include in that formula the economic value of food production from BMV agricultural land over a sixty-year period, in a similar way as for infrastructure applications; and what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs on planning applications for BMV agricultural land and their potential effects on local food security and biodiversity.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190335","190335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40916","2014-03-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many bowling greens have been listed as assets of community value.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190316","190316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40917","2014-03-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what support his Department offers to the Coalfields Regeneration Trust.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190330","190330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40918","2014-03-17","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what funding her Department provided for staff to carry out trade union activities in each of the last three years; and how many days staff spent on those activities in each of those years.","Biography information for Alun Cairns","Alun Cairns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190237","190237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40919","2014-03-05","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate her Department has made of the number of betting shops per head of population in each local authority area in the UK.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190176","190176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40920","2014-03-05","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate her Department has made of the number of fixed odds betting machines in each of the (a) 100 poorest and (b) 100 richest council wards in the UK.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190180","190180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40921","2014-03-05","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate her Department has made of how much was bet per head of population in each local authority area of the UK.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190174","190174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40922","2014-03-05","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what data is available to her Department to monitor levels of betting across the UK.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190175","190175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40923","2014-03-05","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the effects of power cuts on those areas without mobile phone coverage which are reliant on analogue services.","Biography information for Susan Elan Jones","Susan Elan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190241","190241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40924","2014-03-05","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate her Department has made of the number of fixed odds betting machines per head of population in each local authority area of the UK.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190177","190177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40925","2014-03-05","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate her Department has made of the amount bet each week on fixed odds betting machines per head of population in each local authority area in the UK.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190178","190178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40926","2014-03-05","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the cost of military support provided during the recent winter floods; and from which budget Operation Pitchpole will be funded.","Biography information for Baroness McIntosh of Pickering","Miss Anne McIntosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190169","190169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40927","2014-03-06","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many cases of (a) rape, (b) attempted rape, (c) sexual assault by penetration and (d) sexual assault were referred to the Services Prosecuting Authority from the Royal Military Police in each of the last three years; and how many such cases were prosecuted (i) successfully and (ii) unsuccessfully.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190278","190278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40928","2014-03-06","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 24 February 2014, Official Report, column 68W, on equality, what the (a) number of staff and (b) total salary cost of the Head Office team members in equality and diversity roles was in each year from 2008-09 to 2013-14.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190204","190204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40929","2014-03-06","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many naval ships are at sea on duty; on what tasks; and where.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190197","190197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40930","2014-03-05","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the final performance cost and time envelope for the Military Afloat Reach and Sustainability tankers has been agreed with the Ministry of Defence Approving Authority.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190159","190159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40931","2014-03-05","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the re-baselining of the QE Class aircraft carrier has been completed and whether the programme has been re-approved.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190161","190161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40932","2014-03-05","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he expects the End Crypto Graphic Unit programme to be completed.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190141","190141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40933","2014-03-17","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what funding his Department provided for staff to carry out trade union activities in each of the last three years; and how many days staff spent on those activities in each of those years.","Biography information for Alun Cairns","Alun Cairns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190238","190238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40934","2014-03-12","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans he has to spend the funds for plug in vehicle charge points announced by the Office for Low Emission Vehicles in January 2014 allocated to (a) his Department centrally and (b) the Defence Science and Technology Laboratory.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190328","190328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40935","2014-03-12","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 24 February 2014, Official Report, column 67W, on conflict resolution: females, with which bodies (a) he, (b) Ministers and (c) officials in his Department have had discussions on the implementation of UN Security Council Resolution 1325.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190331","190331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40936","2014-03-05","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-03-03","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what steps he is taking to increase awareness of and interest in politics among young people aged 16 to 24 years old.","Biography information for John Robertson","John Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190282","190282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40937","2014-03-05","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-03-03","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what estimate he has made of the number of people aged 18 to 24 years who vote in (a) Glasgow North West constituency, (b) Glasgow, (c) Scotland and (d) the UK.","Biography information for John Robertson","John Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190283","190283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40938","2014-03-05","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-03-03","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, how the performance of returning officers is monitored.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190154","190154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40939","2014-03-05","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-03-03","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, how much was paid to returning officers in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190155","190155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40940","2014-03-05","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-03-03","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, (a) how and (b) by whom pay levels for returning officers are set.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190156","190156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40941","2014-03-06","Department for Education","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the contribution by the Parliamentary Under Secretary of State for Children and Families of 21 January 2014, Official Report, column 275, on the Staying Put Agenda, what work is being carried out by the National Children's Bureau; and when he expects it to be completed.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190206","190206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40942","2014-03-06","Department for Education","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 29 January 2014, Official Report, column 535W, on schools: finance, when he plans to publish the consultation on a fair funding formula; and what the timetable for the consultation will be.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190200","190200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40943","2014-03-05","Department for Education","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what guidance his Department issues to local authority social services departments on preventing violence and other abusive behaviour against social workers in the course of their work.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190167","190167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40944","2014-03-05","Department for Education","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when he expects the Ofsted Data Dashboard to be updated with the 2013 results.","Biography information for Dr Thérèse  Coffey","Dr Thérèse Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190135","190135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40945","2014-03-05","Department for Education","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 13 February 2014, Official Report, column 817W, on equality, what his Department's total expenditure on equality and diversity was in (a) 2008-09 and (b) 2013-14; and what the cost of the full-time equivalent officials who advised on quality and diversity was in each year since 2008-09.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190149","190149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40946","2014-03-06","Department for Education","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many pupils of each ethnicity who (a) were and (b) were not eligible for free school meals attended faith (i) primary and (ii) secondary schools in each year for which records are available.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190275","190275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40947","2014-03-05","Department for Education","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what guidance his Department gives to local authorities and adoption agencies on the prominence given to disabilities in determining whether an applicant is fit to foster a child.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190306","190306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40948","2014-03-05","Department for Education","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many applications to foster or adopt have been made by individuals with a registered disability in each of the last five years; and how many of those applications were successful.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190305","190305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40949","2014-03-06","Department for Education","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will make it his policy that free schools and academies be granted discretion to give preference to children who attend their nursery classes during the admissions process for a reception place. [R]","Biography information for Nick de Bois","Nick de Bois","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190313","190313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40950","2014-03-06","Department for Education","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which primary schools offer nursery provision on or off site; and which of those schools have been rated outstanding by Ofsted.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190231","190231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40951","2014-03-06","Department for Education","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of pupils of each ethnicity who were (a) eligible and (b) not eligible for free school meals and who did not have statements of Special Education Needs did not achieve an A* to C GCSE grade in (i) English, (ii) mathematics and (iii) either English or mathematics in the most recent year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190232","190232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40952","2014-03-05","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate he has made of the effect of (a) onshore and (b) offshore wind turbines on the average domestic energy bill.","Biography information for Mr Stephen O'Brien","Mr Stephen O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190267","190267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40953","2014-03-05","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many UK households currently have smart meters installed.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190248","190248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40954","2014-03-05","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate his Department has made of the number of smart meters installed in UK households that will be replaced during mass roll-out to meet agreed interoperability standards.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190247","190247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40955","2014-03-06","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment has been made of the potential effect of the recommendations of the interim report of the UK Continental Shelf Maximising Recovery Review on his Department's (a) regulatory role in the offshore oil and gas industry and (b) work implementing the recommendations of the Maitland Review.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190280","190280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40956","2014-03-05","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many UK households currently have insufficient communications coverage to enable smart meters to work to their full capability.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190242","190242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40957","2014-03-06","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the current status is of the memorandum of understanding agreed in 2012 between his Department and the Health and Safety Executive on the co-ordination of their respective regulatory roles in the offshore oil and gas industry.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190216","190216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40958","2014-03-05","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment he has made of the incidence of fuel poverty in rural off-gas grid areas; and what steps he is taking to tackle such fuel poverty.","Biography information for Baroness McIntosh of Pickering","Miss Anne McIntosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190134","190134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40959","2014-03-06","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, which recommendations of the Maitland Review into Offshore Oil and Gas in the UK have not been implemented due to the publication of the EU Offshore Safety Directive.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190202","190202"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40960","2014-03-06","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what his policy is on implementation of the competent authority model of regulating the offshore oil and gas industry required by the EU Offshore Safety Directive.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190198","190198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40961","2014-03-06","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment his Department has made of the incidence and impact of load management measures on manufacturing industry.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190194","190194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40962","2014-03-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when he plans to bring forward legislative proposals to ban the use of wild animals in circuses.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190195","190195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40963","2014-03-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans he has to adopt sustainable drainage systems for the building of new developments and the renovation of existing landscapes.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190136","190136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40964","2014-03-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of sustainable drainage systems in reducing the risk of, and damage caused by, flooding.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190137","190137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40965","2014-03-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when the new national standards for sustainable drainage systems will be published.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190233","190233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40966","2014-03-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much (a) resource and (b) capital funding was received by his Department, excluding non-departmental public bodies, to achieve its core responsibility of improving the environment in (i) 2012-13 and (ii) 2013-14.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190221","190221"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40967","2014-03-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much (a) resource and (b) capital funding was received by his Department, excluding non-departmental public bodies, to achieve its core responsibility of safeguarding plant health in (i) 2012-13 and (ii) 2013-14.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190222","190222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40968","2014-03-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much (a) resource and (b) capital funding was received by his Department, excluding non-departmental public bodies, to achieve its core responsibility of growing the rural economy in (i) 2012-13 and (ii) 2013-14.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190223","190223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40969","2014-03-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much (a) resource and (b) capital funding was received by his Department, excluding non-departmental public bodies, to achieve its core responsibility of safeguarding animal health in (i) 2012-13 and (ii) 2013-14.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190224","190224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40970","2014-03-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he plans to take to implement the findings of Household food security in the UK: a review of food aid.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190225","190225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40971","2014-03-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what information his Department holds on whether in her capacity as High Representative of the European Union for Foreign Affairs and Security Policy the right hon. Baroness Ashton of Upholland scheduled to visit Iran for nuclear talks.","Biography information for Guto Bebb","Guto Bebb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190314","190314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40972","2014-03-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether it is intended that a permanent nuclear agreement between Iran and the P5+1 will include a comprehensive monitoring framework of Iran's future nuclear activities.","Biography information for Guto Bebb","Guto Bebb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190322","190322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40974","2014-03-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the political situation in the Ukraine; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Baroness McIntosh of Pickering","Miss Anne McIntosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190166","190166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40975","2014-03-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, to which African countries he (a) has appointed and (b) intends to appoint prosperity officers.","Biography information for Crispin Blunt","Mr Crispin Blunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190210","190210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40976","2014-03-06","Department of Health","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many health trusts are currently under consideration for the trust special administration regime.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190207","190207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40977","2014-03-05","Department of Health","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 21 January 2014, Official Report, column 143W, on muscular dystrophy, what clinical definition of (a) muscular dystrophy and (b) mitochondrial myopathy he used to prepare his answer; and what the evidential basis is for consideration of mitochondrial myopathy to be a form of muscular dystrophy.","Biography information for Dr Liam Fox","Dr Liam Fox","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190143","190143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40978","2014-03-05","Department of Health","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 21 January 2014, Official Report, column 143W, on muscular dystrophy, regarding those cases of muscular dystrophy that he stated are new techniques, which of the genes or genetic loci associated with muscular dystrophy in the Mendelian Inheritance in Man database map to the mitochondrial genome.","Biography information for Dr Liam Fox","Dr Liam Fox","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190144","190144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40979","2014-03-05","Department of Health","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 21 January 2014, Official Report, column 143W, on muscular dystrophy, what proportion of cases of muscular dystrophy are caused by mitochondrial DNA abnormalities every year; and what estimate he has made of the proportion of cases of serious muscular dystrophy caused by mitochondrial DNA abnormalities that will be prevented each year by new techniques which aim to prevent mitochondrial disorders.","Biography information for Dr Liam Fox","Dr Liam Fox","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190145","190145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40980","2014-03-05","Department of Health","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 25 February 2014, Official Report, column 279W, on Specialised Services Patient and Public Engagement Steering Group, if he will publish a list of all the members of the Steering Group and the organisations they represent.","Biography information for Tessa Munt","Tessa Munt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190254","190254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40981","2014-03-05","Department of Health","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what representations he has received from the National Screening Committee on evidence for increased routine HIV testing in high prevalence areas.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190246","190246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40982","2014-03-05","Department of Health","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 25 February 2014, Official Report, column 279W, on Specialised Services Patient and Public Engagement Steering Group, how many times NHS England's Patient and Public Engagement Steering Group has met since 1 April 2013; and for what reason the minutes of those meetings have not yet been agreed to be published.","Biography information for Tessa Munt","Tessa Munt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190252","190252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40983","2014-03-06","Department of Health","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many previous years' spending was used in calculations for the baseline funding allocation for specialised commissioning in 2013-14.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190277","190277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40984","2014-03-05","Department of Health","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what organisations outside NHS England provide administrative or research support to NHS England.","Biography information for Tessa Munt","Tessa Munt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190182","190182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40985","2014-03-06","Department of Health","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to improve the mental health of LGBT people.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190192","190192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40986","2014-03-06","Department of Health","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make it his policy to put a trace on medical records to indicate past military service to enable armed forces veterans to be identified after their death for the purpose of arranging their funeral.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190271","190271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40987","2014-03-06","Department of Health","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with the Chief Coroner's Office on collecting sexual orientation data on people who have committed suicide.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190190","190190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40988","2014-03-06","Department of Health","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, who is responsible for commissioning Tier 3 obesity treatments.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190191","190191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40989","2014-03-06","Department of Health","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will publish the (a) dates, (b) agendas and (c) minutes of any meetings (i) Ministers and (ii) officials in his Department have had with representatives of the Advertising Association between January 2012 and February 2014.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190321","190321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40990","2014-03-05","Department of Health","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will introduce a patient experience survey for people receiving NHS treatment for HIV.","Biography information for Mr Stephen O'Brien","Mr Stephen O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190290","190290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40991","2014-03-05","Department of Health","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, in what proportion of HSA1 did (a) one or (b) both certifying doctors not indicate whether or not they had seen and examined the pregnant woman to whom the certificate related in (i) 2011 and (ii) 2012.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190301","190301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40992","2014-03-05","Department of Health","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what scrutiny measures are in place to identify illegal abortion referrals; whether the competence for such scrutiny rests with the Chief Medical Office alone; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190304","190304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40993","2014-03-05","Department of Health","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what consideration his Department has given to the withdrawal of support for independent abortion providers in situations where their guidance does not comply with legislation.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190302","190302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40994","2014-03-05","Department of Health","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make it his policy that pharmacies deliver a common ailments service.","Biography information for Oliver Colvile","Oliver Colvile","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190295","190295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40995","2014-03-05","Department of Health","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he plans to remove strict liability on single dispensing errors from pharmacists.","Biography information for Oliver Colvile","Oliver Colvile","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190296","190296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40996","2014-03-06","Department of Health","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how his Department will ensure that communication professionals engaged to work with deaf people meet the standards for enhanced criminal records checks as maintained by the Disclosure and Barring Service.","Biography information for Lord Blunkett","Mr David Blunkett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190227","190227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40997","2014-03-05","Department of Health","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will publish the total expenditure from the Cancer Drugs Fund in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Tessa Munt","Tessa Munt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190264","190264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40998","2014-03-06","Home Office","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when the Ellison Review will be published.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190228","190228"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40999","2014-03-06","Department of Health","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how his Department will ensure that communication professionals working with deaf people are eligible for an enhanced Disclosure and Barring Service declaration.","Biography information for Lord Blunkett","Mr David Blunkett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190226","190226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41000","2014-03-05","Home Office","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many seizures of (a) tobacco and cigars, (b) alcohol and (c) drugs were made at (i) Manchester, (ii) London Heathrow, (iii) London Gatwick, (iv) London Stansted, (v) Liverpool, (vi) Newcastle, (vii) Belfast International, (viii) Belfast George Best, (ix) Glasgow, (x) Edinburgh, (xi) Birmingham International, (xii) East Midlands and (xiii) Cardiff airports in each year since 2010; and what the estimated value was of each such seizure.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190300","190300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41001","2014-03-06","Home Office","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the total value was of illegal drugs seized by police in Barrow and Furness constituency in each of the last five years.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190317","190317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41002","2014-03-05","Home Office","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 27 February 2014, Official Report, column 431W, on equality, what the (a) total departmental expenditure, (b) number and (c) cost of people employed for the purpose of promoting equality and diversity was in 2013-14.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190307","190307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41003","2014-03-12","Home Office","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have been arrrested under the Computer Misuse Act 1990 in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190332","190332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41004","2014-03-06","Home Office","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Assistance for the Voluntary Return and Reintegration of Returnees project, what the countries of origin of the 1,470 irregular migrants were; what assistance will be provided to the 30 victims of human trafficking from EU countries; how it will provide reintegration assistance to the 75 returning vulnerable migrants; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190276","190276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41005","2014-03-05","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of changes in the level of legal aid under the Legal Aid, Sentencing and Punishment of Offenders Act 2012 on (a) migrant children and (b) unaccompanied children who have made Article 8 right to private life and family claims.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190138","190138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41006","2014-03-05","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of changes in the level of legal aid under the Legal Aid, Sentencing and Punishment of Offenders Act 2012 on trafficked children who are seeking leave to remain.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190139","190139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41010","2014-03-06","Department for International Development","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is taking to provide better healthcare and more trained midwives to reduce the deaths of new born babies in the poorest countries; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190279","190279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41011","2014-03-05","Department for International Development","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what arrangements her Department has in place to assess the value-for-money of its funding for (a) Programme Partnership Arrangements Marie Stopes International, (b) the International Planned Parenthood Federation and (c) the United Nations Population Fund; whether those arrangements include the collection of data on the number of abortions provided by these organisations; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mark Durkan","Mark Durkan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190303","190303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41012","2014-03-05","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, for how long approved enforcement agents hold distress warrants before they are returned to his Department as uncollected.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190297","190297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41013","2014-03-05","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners in each category of prisoner who have absconded from prisons since May 2010 remain at large.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190263","190263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41014","2014-03-05","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many students were taken to court by universities for recovery of their student fees after dropping out of university courses in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Graham Stuart","Mr Graham Stuart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190291","190291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41015","2014-03-18","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate his Department has made of the full costs of the National Compliance and Enforcement Service and the value of its business; and when this estimate was made.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190327","190327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41016","2014-03-05","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people convicted of manslaughter in (a) 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012 and (d) 2013 received (i) no custodial sentence, (ii) a custodial sentence of up to one year, (iii) a custodial sentence of one to two years, (iv) a custodial sentence of two to five years, (v) a custodial sentence of five to 10 years and (vi) a custodial sentence of more than 10 years.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190333","190333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41017","2014-03-06","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the purpose is of his Department's new Building Better Relationships Programme; how that purpose differs from the purpose of the (a) Integrated Domestic Abuse Programme and (b) Community Domestic Violence Programme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190342","190342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41018","2014-03-05","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many employees of his Department and its agencies had a salary in excess of (a) £100,00 and (b) £142,000 per annum on 1 February (i) 2011, (ii) 2012, (iii) 2013 and (iv) 2014.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190286","190286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41019","2014-03-05","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many escapes by prisoners there have been while being transported, by category of prisoner, in each month since May 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190287","190287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41020","2014-03-05","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many absconds from prison there have been, by month and category of prisoner, since May 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190288","190288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41021","2014-03-05","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of appeals against unduly lenient sentences in (a) 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012 and (d) 2013 were successful; and what the outcomes of the appeals were.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190308","190308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41022","2014-03-12","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what funds are dedicated to the rehabilitation and management of offenders convicted under the Computer Misuse Act 1990.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190329","190329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41023","2014-03-05","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, for what reason his Department's shared services will no longer be a stand-alone centre.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190181","190181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41024","2014-03-05","Attorney General","2014-03-03","To ask the Attorney General, how many appeals there have been against unduly lenient sentences of those sentenced in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190258","190258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41025","2014-03-05","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what financial targets he plans to set for the successful bidder for the National Compliance and Enforcement Service contract in that contract.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190243","190243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41026","2014-03-05","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate his Department has made of the costs of running the National Compliance and Enforcement Service contract.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190244","190244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41027","2014-03-05","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which of the short-listed bidders for the National Compliance and Enforcement Service contract were involved in his Department's aged debt pilot.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190245","190245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41028","2014-03-05","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much his Department paid to Steria UK for its work on the Oracle Enterprise Resource Planning system for shared services.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190170","190170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41029","2014-03-06","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when the decision to hire new Public Defender System advocates was made.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190188","190188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41030","2014-03-06","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the average salary of a Public Defender Service advocate after the current recruitment drive is complete.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190189","190189"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41031","2014-03-05","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many cases referred by the police or the Crown Prosecution Service to a Crown or magistrates' court in England and Wales were adjourned (a) once, (b) twice, (c) three times and (d) four or more times in each of the last two years.","Biography information for Mary Macleod","Mary Macleod","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190168","190168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41032","2014-03-06","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much has been spent on televising courts to date.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190213","190213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41033","2014-03-06","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which broadcasters have expressed an interest in televising courts; how much he expects to spend on televising courts in each of the next five years; and what proportion of the total cost will be paid by the broadcasters.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190214","190214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41034","2014-03-06","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, for how many advocate positions in the Public Defender System his Department plans to recruit.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190193","190193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41035","2014-03-05","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many of each category of prisoner released from prison in error since May 2010 are still at large.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190140","190140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41036","2014-03-05","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of distress warrants sent to approved enforcement agents are returned uncollected.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190142","190142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41037","2014-03-05","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much has been spent on recruitment of temporary staff by his Department and its agencies in each month since May 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190150","190150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41038","2014-03-05","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which prisons have reported staff shortages that required staff to be called in from another prison in each month since September 2013.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190151","190151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41039","2014-03-05","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many staff in the Prison Service have been on detached duty in each month since September 2013.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190153","190153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41040","2014-03-06","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will introduce a mandatory 10 year minimum prison sentence for anyone who kills someone with a single punch while under the influence of alcohol; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Nick de Bois","Nick de Bois","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190186","190186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41041","2014-03-06","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many applications for each vacancy for the Public Defender System his Department received.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190208","190208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41042","2014-03-06","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which prisons closed since May 2010 were previously housing young adults.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190211","190211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41043","2014-03-06","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what plans he has to bring forward legislative proposals on killing by one punch; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Nick de Bois","Nick de Bois","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190185","190185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41044","2014-03-06","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which prisons in England and Wales have changed their prison population to accommodate young adults for the first time since May 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190205","190205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41045","2014-03-06","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what representations he has received on legislation on killing by one punch; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Nick de Bois","Nick de Bois","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190184","190184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41046","2014-03-05","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many civil claims involving litigants in person were referred to mediation in (a) July to September 2013 and (b) July to September 2012.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190158","190158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41047","2014-03-05","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much was spent on (a) travel, (b) accommodation and (c) subsistence costs for detached duty cover for staff in the Prison Service in each month since September 2013.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190148","190148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41048","2014-03-05","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many complaints have been received against named judges in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190160","190160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41049","2014-03-06","Northern Ireland Office","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, pursuant to the Answer of 25 February 2014, Official Report, column 296W, on equality, what the cost to her Department was of section 75 equality training in each year between 2008-09 and 2012-13.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190203","190203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41050","2014-03-05","Speaker's Committee for Independent Parliamentary Standards Authority","2014-03-03","To ask the hon. Member for Broxbourne, representing the Speaker's Committee for the Independent Parliamentary Standards Authority, how many hon. Members have been provided with additional funds by IPSA to cover increased staffing costs as a consequence of dealing with higher demand for assistance from constituents in 2013-14 to date.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190339","190339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41051","2014-03-05","Speaker's Committee for Independent Parliamentary Standards Authority","2014-03-03","To ask the hon. Member for Broxbourne, representing the Speaker's Committee for the Independent Parliamentary Standards Authority, what estimate IPSA has made of the amount in staffing budgets for hon. Members which will not be claimed by the end of the current financial year.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190340","190340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41052","2014-03-05","Speaker's Committee on the Electorial Commission","2014-03-03","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, if the Electoral Commission will publish its correspondence with the hon. Member for Vale of Clwyd on the increase in the estimated number of unregistered voters.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190172","190172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41053","2014-03-05","Speaker's Committee on the Electorial Commission","2014-03-03","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, how much the Electoral Commission spent on estimating the number of unregistered voters in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190171","190171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41054","2014-03-06","Department for Transport","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will ensure that the full independent summary of the consultation into the proposed High Speed 2 route from Birmingham to the North of England is published by IPSOS Mori.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190270","190270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41055","2014-03-05","Department for Transport","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of changes in train passenger numbers over the next 10 years.","Biography information for Mr Stephen O'Brien","Mr Stephen O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190260","190260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41056","2014-03-05","Department for Transport","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much has been paid to each communication firm for advice on High Speed 2 to date.","Biography information for Mr Stephen O'Brien","Mr Stephen O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190261","190261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41057","2014-03-10","Department for Transport","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, for what reason he did not require the work currently being carried out on the M1 motorway between junctions 28 and 32 to be phased in smaller sections so as to reduce congestion and delays; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190324","190324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41058","2014-03-05","Department for Transport","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the average number is of passengers travelling in first class on weekdays from London to (a) Manchester, (b) Leeds and (c) Birmingham.","Biography information for Mr Stephen O'Brien","Mr Stephen O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190281","190281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41059","2014-03-10","Department for Transport","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will consider introducing variable temporary speed limits on stretches of motorway where roadworks are taking place so that such temporary speed limits are not artificially low during times of light traffic use.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190325","190325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41060","2014-03-05","Department for Transport","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many times the Maritime Rescue Co-ordination Centre, Belfast, was staffed at below risk-assessed levels in January 2014.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190146","190146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41061","2014-03-05","Department for Transport","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many times the Maritime Rescue Co-ordination Centre, Stornoway, was staffed at below risk-assessed levels in January 2014.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190147","190147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41062","2014-03-06","Department for Transport","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will publish the most recent report on High Speed 2 by the Major Projects Authority.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190209","190209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41063","2014-03-06","Department for Transport","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he expects to publish his Department's review of the Traffic Signs Regulations and General Directions.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190196","190196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41064","2014-03-05","Department for Transport","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many times the Maritime Rescue Co-ordination Centre, Liverpool, was staffed at below risk-assessed levels in January 2014.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190163","190163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41065","2014-03-05","Department for Transport","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to encourage train companies to inform customers of their rights to compensation and to provide information on this matter to the public.","Biography information for John Robertson","John Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190289","190289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41066","2014-03-06","Department for Transport","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many seats are available on the diesel train fleet allocated to Transpennine Express; and how many are expected to be available in December 2015.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190318","190318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41067","2014-03-05","Department for Transport","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 26 February 2014, Official Report, columns 387-8W, on High Speed 2 railway line, which of the Yorkshire local authorities with which he has had meetings and which have responded to the consultation have set out a position (a) supportive of and (b) opposed to High Speed 2; and if he will place in the Library copies of those authorities' consultation responses.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190334","190334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41068","2014-03-05","Department for Transport","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the strands of the South East Flexible Ticketing project are; what the budget and relevant train operating company is for each such strand; when he expects the competition for the flexible ticketing trial for part-time workers to commence; when the outcome of that competition will be announced; when he expects that trial to begin; and how long the trial will last.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190284","190284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41069","2014-03-05","Department for Transport","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the criteria for success will be of the flexible ticketing trial for part-time workers and how success will be measured; and if he will include a requirement for flexible ticketing for part-time workers in all future franchise agreements in the event that the trial is successful.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190285","190285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41070","2014-03-10","Department for Transport","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he expects junctions 28 to 32 of the M1 motorway in both directions to be devoid of all roadworks and lane closures; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190326","190326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41071","2014-03-06","Department for Transport","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he expects to publish his Department's cycling delivery plan.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190230","190230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41072","2014-03-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, which back-to-work schemes being delivered by local authorities he has visited since May 2010.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190312","190312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41073","2014-03-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will extend the support given to former Remploy workers beyond May 2014.","Biography information for Teresa Pearce","Teresa Pearce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190266","190266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41074","2014-03-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of employment and support allowance claimants who allege they did not receive letters informing them of their next work capability assessment.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190319","190319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41075","2014-03-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent representations he has received on errors in processing claims for jobseeker's allowance.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190320","190320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41076","2014-03-05","HM Treasury","2014-03-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the number of people who use credit unions in (a) Glasgow North West constituency, (b) Glasgow, (c) Scotland and (d) the UK.","Biography information for John Robertson","John Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190336","190336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41077","2014-03-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people who have indicated they are living with HIV (a) applied for personal independence payment and (b) received a decision about their claim between April and December 2013.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190249","190249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41078","2014-03-06","Cabinet Office","2014-03-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the average duration of unemployment or inactivity is of those who become unemployed or inactive having previously been in employment for (a) less than six months, (b) between six months and a year, (c) between one and two years, (d) between two and three years, (e) between three and four years, (f) between four and five years, (g) between five and 10 years and (h) 10 or more years.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190220","190220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41079","2014-03-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of those making a new claim for employment and support allowance immediately before their claim was made were (a) in employment, (b) in receipt of jobseeker's allowance or income support or (c) neither in employment nor claiming another out of work benefit.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190219","190219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41080","2014-03-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many individuals made a claim for any of jobseeker's allowance, incapacity benefit or severe disablement allowance, employment support allowance or income support (a) once, (b) twice and (c) three or more times in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190218","190218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41081","2014-03-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of those making a new claim for jobseeker's allowance immediately before their claim was made were (a) in employment, (b) in receipt of employment support allowance, incapacity benefit, severe disablement allowance or income support and (c) neither in employment nor claiming another out of work benefit.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190217","190217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41082","2014-03-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of people who have stopped claiming jobseeker's allowance in each of the last six months have done so following the application of sanctions.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190215","190215"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41083","2014-03-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what account is taken of medical assessments by (a) GPs and (b) consultants of their patients' ability to work by Atos when examining the (i) physical and (ii) mental capabilities of those undertaking a fit for work test.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190173","190173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41084","2014-03-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many individuals have been in receipt of (a) job seeker's allowance, (b) incapacity benefit, severe disablement allowance and employment support allowance and (c) income support for (i) up to one year, (ii) between one and two years, (iii) between two and five years and (iv) over five years over the last 10 years.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190212","190212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41085","2014-03-05","HM Treasury","2014-03-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the value of child benefit for the first child was in real terms in each of the last 30 years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190179","190179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41086","2014-03-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 24 February 2014, Official Report, column 6W, on equality, what the figures are for 2013-14.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190187","190187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41087","2014-03-05","Attorney General","2014-03-03","To ask the Attorney General, what services the Law Officers' Departments provide that are (a) available online only and (b) planned to move to online only.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190358","190358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41088","2014-03-05","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what services his Department provides that are (a) available online only and (b) planned to move to online only.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190357","190357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41089","2014-03-05","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the value was of UK (a) exports to and (b) imports from Ukraine in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190380","190380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41090","2014-03-05","Cabinet Office","2014-03-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people with an eating disorder died in the UK in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190382","190382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41091","2014-03-05","Cabinet Office","2014-03-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what services his Department provides that are (a) available online only and (b) planned to move to online only.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190359","190359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41092","2014-03-05","HM Treasury","2014-03-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what services his Department provides that are (a) available online only and (b) planned to move to online only.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190372","190372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41093","2014-03-05","HM Treasury","2014-03-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the Department for Business, Innovation and Skills Analysis Paper No. 3, Insights from international benchmarking of the UK science and innovation system, published in January 2014, paragraph 6, whether he is considering proposing targets for increasing public and private research and development spending to meet the 2.9 per cent average of the UK's competitors.","Biography information for Oliver Colvile","Oliver Colvile","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190356","190356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41094","2014-03-05","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what services his Department provides that are (a) available online only and (b) planned to move to online only.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190360","190360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41095","2014-03-05","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what services her Department provides that are (a) available online only and (b) planned to move to online only.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190361","190361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41096","2014-03-05","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many people visited the National Railway Museum's Mallard 75 events; how many other major exhibitions were staged outside London by national museums in 2013-14 and how many people attended each of those exhibitions; what plans national museums have to attract more visitors to exhibitions outside London; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190350","190350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41097","2014-03-06","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps she has taken to ensure that her Department's contracts with BT for the roll-out of rural superfast broadband include a reasonable market rate for (a) equipment costs and (b) other non-management costs.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190397","190397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41098","2014-03-05","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what financial support the Government has provided for shooting sports in the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190379","190379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41099","2014-03-06","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the Defence Planning Assumptions set out in the Strategic Defence and Security Review in October 2010 remain in place.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190391","190391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41100","2014-03-05","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what services his Department provides that are (a) available online only and (b) planned to move to online only.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190362","190362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41101","2014-03-05","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what criteria were applied when evaluating the suitability of the automatic wing sweep for installation on the Tornado F3.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190343","190343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41102","2014-03-05","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when his Department received copies of Martin-Baker's Special Information Leaflets, SIL 704 and SIL 704A; and what steps it has taken to incorporate the revised checks into the appropriate maintenance publications.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190344","190344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41103","2014-03-05","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will place in the Library a list of Martin-Baker's Special Information Leaflets, with contents summary, issued between 1990 and 1996.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190345","190345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41104","2014-03-05","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what UK assets are currently assigned to NATO's Immediate Response Force.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190346","190346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41105","2014-03-05","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, on how many occasions the submarine asset assigned to NATO's Immediate Response Force has not been available for tasking in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190347","190347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41106","2014-03-05","Department for Education","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what services his Department provides that are (a) available online only and (b) planned to move to online only.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190363","190363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41107","2014-03-06","Department for Education","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the average daily number of children absent from school is; and what assessment his Department has made of the reasons for their non-attendance.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190354","190354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41108","2014-03-05","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what services his Department provides that are (a) available online only and (b) planned to move to online only.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190364","190364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41109","2014-03-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what services his Department provides that are (a) available online only and (b) planned to move to online only.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190365","190365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41110","2014-03-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what progress he has made in preparing a Bill to outlaw the use of wild animals in circuses.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190388","190388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41111","2014-03-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions he has had with his counterpart in the Republic of Ireland on the effectiveness of that country's programme of humanely destroying badgers in reducing the incidence of bovine TB.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190375","190375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41112","2014-03-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate he has made of how many dogs in the UK have distemper; and what steps his Department is taking to reduce the incidence of that condition.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190378","190378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41113","2014-03-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he plans to bring forward legislative proposals to prohibit the possession and use of wild animals by circuses by the end of the present Parliament.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190384","190384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41114","2014-03-05","Department of Health","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to make 3G implants for children with a heart condition available to NHS patients.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190383","190383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41115","2014-03-06","Department of Health","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 13 February 2014, Official Report, column 832W, on abortion, under what conditions and in relation to what other factors gender may be considered a relevant criterion for an abortion under the Abortion Act 1967, as amended; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Selous","Andrew Selous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190396","190396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41116","2014-03-05","Department of Health","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 21 January 2014, Official Report, column 145W, on muscular dystrophy, and in relation to the mitochondrial abnormalities that are alleged to cause muscular dystrophy, how muscular dystrophy is defined clinically; how mitochondrial myopathy is defined clinically; and on what basis mitochondrial myopathy is considered to be a form of muscular dystrophy.","Biography information for Mark Durkan","Mark Durkan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190393","190393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41117","2014-03-05","Department of Health","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to introduce SensiumVitals patches in NHS hospitals.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190376","190376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41118","2014-03-05","Department of Health","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, in how many cases of acute appendicitis (a) the patient's appendix has burst and (b) the patient has died as a result in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190377","190377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41119","2014-03-05","Department of Health","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 21 January 2014, Official Report, column 145W, on muscular dystrophy, and in relation to those cases of muscular dystrophy that are alleged to be caused by mitochondrial DNA abnormalities that could be prevented by new in-vitro fertilisation techniques, what proportion of cases of muscular dystrophy are caused by mitochondrial DNA abnormalities per year; and what proportion of cases of serious muscular dystrophy caused by mitochondrial DNA abnormalities are expected to be prevented each year by new techniques which aim to prevent mitochondrial disorders.","Biography information for Mark Durkan","Mark Durkan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190394","190394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41120","2014-03-05","Department of Health","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people in the UK were diagnosed with an eating disorder in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190381","190381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41121","2014-03-05","Department of Health","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 21 January 2014, Official Report, column 145W, on muscular dystrophy, and in relation to those cases of muscular dystrophy that are alleged to be caused by mitochondrial DNA abnormalities that could be prevented by new in-vitro fertilisation techniques, which of the genes or genetic loci associated with muscular dystrophy in the Mendelian Inheritance in Man database map to the mitochondrial genome.","Biography information for Mark Durkan","Mark Durkan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190395","190395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41122","2014-03-06","Department of Health","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will investigate abortion providers whose advice on the legality of gender abortions contradicts that of his Department.","Biography information for Andrew Selous","Andrew Selous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190389","190389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41123","2014-03-06","Department of Health","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department considers cleft palate to be a serious disability for the purposes of establishing the legality of abortions.","Biography information for Andrew Selous","Andrew Selous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190390","190390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41124","2014-03-06","Department of Health","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what evidence his Department holds or has assessed on whether giving birth to a baby of a specific gender constitutes a greater risk to the mother's physical or mental health than termination of the pregnancy.","Biography information for Andrew Selous","Andrew Selous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190392","190392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41125","2014-03-06","Department of Health","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 13 February 2014, Official Report, column 828W, on abortion, whether gender may be considered a contributing factor to grounds for abortion when compounded by other considerations.","Biography information for Andrew Selous","Andrew Selous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190387","190387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41126","2014-03-05","Department of Health","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what mechanisms his Department has put in place to assess whether health commissioners are paying learning disability services a fee that reflects the cost of the service that they provide.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame M. Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190341","190341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41127","2014-03-05","Home Office","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what services her Department provides that are (a) available online only and (b) planned to move to online only.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190366","190366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41128","2014-03-06","Home Office","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the nature and purpose is of the Government-funded Assistance for the Voluntary Return and Reintegration of Returnees project being implemented by the International Organisation for Migration in co-operation with the Greek government; how that project will assist irregular migrants to return to their countries of origin; and how the project will help identified victims of human trafficking from EU countries.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190398","190398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41129","2014-03-05","Department for International Development","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, with reference to her Department's policy document entitled, Safe and Unsafe Abortion, how much her Department spent on (a) legal and policy reform campaigns to liberalise abortion law and policy in other countries and (b) raising awareness among policy-makers, legislators, national health authorities and health personnel in other countries of the circumstances under which abortion may be allowed by (i) country, (ii) region and (iii) nature of recipient in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mark Durkan","Mark Durkan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190385","190385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41130","2014-03-05","Department for International Development","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what services her Department provides that are (a) available online only and (b) planned to move to online only.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190367","190367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41131","2014-03-05","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what services his Department provides that are (a) available online only and (b) planned to move to online only.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190368","190368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41132","2014-03-06","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether the National Offender Management Service review of Assessment, Care in Custody and Teamwork includes secure colleges in its scope.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190353","190353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41133","2014-03-05","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people received a life sentence in each of the last three decades; what length of sentence each served; how many such prisoners are still in prison; and how many such prisoners died while serving their sentence.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190386","190386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41134","2014-03-05","Northern Ireland Office","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what services her Department provides that are (a) available online only and (b) planned to move to online only.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190369","190369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41135","2014-03-05","Scotland Office","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what services his Department provides that are (a) available online only and (b) planned to move to online only.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190370","190370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41136","2014-03-05","Speaker's Committee for Independent Parliamentary Standards Authority","2014-03-03","To ask the hon. Member for Broxbourne, representing the Speaker's Committee for the Independent Parliamentary Standards Authority, what the membership is of the IPSA Contingency Panel.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190337","190337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41137","2014-03-05","Speaker's Committee for Independent Parliamentary Standards Authority","2014-03-03","To ask the hon. Member for Broxbourne, representing the Speaker's Committee for the Independent Parliamentary Standards Authority, what total amount was paid in overtime payments to IPSA staff in the first nine months of 2013-14.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190338","190338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41138","2014-03-05","Department for Transport","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what services his Department provides that are (a) available online only and (b) planned to move to online only.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190371","190371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41139","2014-03-05","Wales Office","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what services his Department provides that are (a) available online only and (b) planned to move to online only.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190373","190373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41140","2014-03-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what services his Department provides that are (a) available online only and (b) planned to move to online only.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190374","190374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41141","2014-03-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many complaints he received about the Work Programme in (a) 2011, (b) 2012 and (c) 2013.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190352","190352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41142","2014-03-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of people who have been refused benefit over the last 12 months; and what steps his Department has taken to ascertain whether those claimants are in receipt of any income.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190355","190355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41143","2014-03-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many times claimants for jobseeker's allowance were sanctioned inappropriately due to processing errors in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190348","190348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41144","2014-03-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will investigate the effect of sanctions on jobseeker's allowance claimants.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190349","190349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41145","2014-03-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, which sectors of the economy are excluded from the requirement for inspection by the Health and Safety Executive.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190351","190351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41147","2014-03-06","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what progress he has made on rebalancing the economy across regions and sectors.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 902880","902880"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41154","2014-03-06","Cabinet Office","2014-03-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what recent assessment he has made of the level of underemployment.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 902867","902867"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41396","2014-03-06","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of removing the cap on student numbers at higher education institutions.","Biography information for Duncan Hames","Duncan Hames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 902868","902868"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40766","2014-03-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what progress his Department has made on drafting the regulations needed to implement changes to copyright exceptions; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mike Weatherley","Mike Weatherley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190065","190065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40767","2014-03-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what discussions his Department had with UK Export Finance about a licence to the Indonesian military for the purchase of surveillance equipment for its Strategic Intelligence Agency from Gamma TSE; what assessment his Department made of the impact of providing this equipment on human rights in (a) West Papua and (b) Indonesia; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190066","190066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40768","2014-03-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how the £1.3 billion Government investment into the Post Office network will be spent over what time period.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190067","190067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40769","2014-03-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment his Department has made of the effect on the Post Office network of withdrawing car tax discs administration and similar services.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190068","190068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40770","2014-03-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the effects of the Government's investment into the Post Office network.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190069","190069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40771","2014-03-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to extend the scope of the Public Interest Disclosure Act 1998 to cover student nurses who raise concerns about patient care.","Biography information for Mr Aidan Burley","Mr Aidan Burley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190082","190082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40772","2014-03-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department has taken to increase the level of access to credit for businesses in (a) Cannock Chase constituency and (b) Staffordshire in the last year.","Biography information for Mr Aidan Burley","Mr Aidan Burley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190084","190084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40773","2014-03-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department is taking to support small and medium-sized businesses in Cannock Chase constituency.","Biography information for Mr Aidan Burley","Mr Aidan Burley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190086","190086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40774","2014-03-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the effect of the time taken to implement section 74 of the Enterprise and Regulatory Reform Act 2013 on design businesses and consumers.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190092","190092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40775","2014-03-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, when the statutory instrument implementing section 74 of the Enterprise and Regulatory Reform Act 2013 will be laid; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190093","190093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40776","2014-03-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent representations he has received from universities facing financial challenges.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190121","190121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40777","2014-03-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment his Department has made of the financial viability of UK non-Russell Group universities beyond the next 15 years.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190122","190122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40778","2014-03-04","Ministry of Justice","2014-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to ensure that users of public services can access and control personal data held on them by the Government, its agencies and other public bodies.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190106","190106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40779","2014-03-04","Cabinet Office","2014-02-28","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what progress his Department has made in enabling small and medium-sized enterprises to tender for Government procurement contracts.","Biography information for Mr Aidan Burley","Mr Aidan Burley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190087","190087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40780","2014-03-04","Cabinet Office","2014-02-28","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many firms in (a) Cannock Chase constituency and (b) Staffordshire have been awarded Government procurement contracts in the last four years.","Biography information for Mr Aidan Burley","Mr Aidan Burley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190085","190085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40781","2014-03-05","HM Treasury","2014-02-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what his policy is on how national debt might be apportioned in the event of Scotland's withdrawal from the UK.","Biography information for Mike Weatherley","Mike Weatherley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190102","190102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40782","2014-03-05","HM Treasury","2014-02-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of annual revenue foregone as a result of granting VAT relief to mountain, cave and lowland volunteer rescue teams.","Biography information for Stephen Barclay","Stephen Barclay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190120","190120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40783","2014-03-05","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, on what basis the figures that the Get Britain Building Scheme would create 16,000 and 3,000 jobs were calculated.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190129","190129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40784","2014-03-05","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much was spent on the Get Britain Building Scheme in (a) 2011, (b) 2012 and (c) 2013.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190130","190130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40785","2014-03-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate his Department has made of how many people buying leasehold properties in (a) 2012 and (b) 2013 were charged over £500 by management companies for the information they needed to complete the purchase.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190123","190123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40786","2014-03-05","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many (a) successful and (b) unsuccessful applications were received for Get Britain Building funding in (i) round one in January 2012 and (ii) round two in July 2012.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190131","190131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40787","2014-03-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate his Department has made of how long it took people buying leasehold properties in (a) 2012 and (b) 2013 to obtain from management companies the necessary information they needed to complete the purchase.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190124","190124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40788","2014-03-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will extend the Redress scheme to include management agencies for leasehold properties.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190125","190125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40790","2014-03-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he plans to lay the draft Durham, Northumberland and Tyne and Wear Combined Authority Order 2014.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190089","190089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40791","2014-03-04","Ministry of Defence","2014-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the (a) names of contractors, (b) dates, (c) value, (d) contracted services to be provided and (e) location in Afghanistan are of any contracts to UK-based private military security companies for work in Afghanistan.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190064","190064"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40792","2014-03-04","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-02-28","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what assessment he has made of the (a) fairness, (b) accuracy and (c) completeness of using the (i) census and midterm census and (ii) electoral register to determine the size of constituencies when drawing boundaries.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190096","190096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40793","2014-03-04","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-02-28","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what assessment he has made of the potential benefits of bringing forward legislative proposals to make voting compulsory as a means of increasing voter turnout and engagement.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190095","190095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40794","2014-03-04","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how much each of the Big Six energy companies should have spent on energy conservation schemes to fulfil their statutory obligations in the last three years; and how much those energy companies spent on such schemes.","Biography information for Lord Watts","Mr Dave Watts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190088","190088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40795","2014-03-05","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many officials in his Department are working on the implementation of the recommendations of the Maitland Review of the regulatory regime in the offshore oil and gas industry; how many such officials have worked on implementing those recommendations to date; and for how long each such official was so employed.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190080","190080"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40796","2014-03-05","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many officials from his Department were appointed to the Steering Group which considered the recommendations of the Maitland Review of the regulatory regime in the offshore oil and gas industry; how many such officials have worked on that Steering Group to date; and for how long in each case.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190081","190081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40797","2014-03-05","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment he has made of the effect on energy-generating capacity in the UK in the event of Scotland's withdrawal from the UK.","Biography information for Mike Weatherley","Mike Weatherley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190103","190103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40798","2014-03-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many staff at nuclear facilities in the UK have tested positive for radiation poisoning in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190117","190117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40799","2014-03-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with the Association of British Insurers on the replacement of old air bricks in flooded properties with new water-proof air bricks.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190115","190115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40800","2014-03-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will publish figures on the number of badgers culled in total in the Gloucestershire and Somerset pilots.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190116","190116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/40801","2014-03-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effect of the expansion of Heathrow on the ability of local authorities in Berkshire, Surrey and the surrounding areas to manage high levels of rainfall.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190107","190107"
