"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662859","2017-01-09","Department for Education","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether her Department has a policy on tackling sexual harassment in universities.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58632","58632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662860","2017-01-09","Department for Education","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many EU nationals work in each local authority area (a) as teachers and (b) in other positions in schools.","Biography information for Mr Pat McFadden","Mr Pat McFadden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58468","58468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662861","2017-01-09","Department for Education","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment her Department has made of the potential effect of the schools funding formula on the funding of schools in Richmond Park and North Kingston constituency in real terms in each of the next three years.","Biography information for Sarah Olney","Sarah Olney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58506","58506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662862","2017-01-09","Department for Education","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 8 December 2016 to Question 55853, how many academies have been closed by the Secretary of State since (a) 2010 and (b) 2015 in (i) Birmingham and (ii) the West Midlands.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58494","58494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662863","2017-01-09","Department for Education","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 8 December 2016 to Question 55853, what the cost was of the complete closure of the 14 academies since 2010.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58495","58495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662864","2017-01-09","Department for Education","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 8 December 2016 to Question 55853, what assessment her Department has made of the reasons why the West Midlands has a high level of school closures and openings in comparison with other regions.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58496","58496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662865","2017-01-09","Department for Education","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 8 December 2016 to Question 55853, for what reasons her Department does not record centrally the costs of school closures.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58497","58497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662866","2017-01-10","Department for Education","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will make an assessment of the merits of launching an inquiry into the levels of staff-to-student sexual harassment in universities.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58641","58641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662867","2017-01-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 8 December 2016 to Question 56069, what plans the Government has to remove the exemption from licensing requirements of people repeatedly selling kittens bred from their non-pedigree pet cat, currently in place under the provisions of the Pet Animals Act 1951, within new regulations governing the sale of pet animals made under the Animal Welfare Act 2006.","Biography information for Rob Marris","Rob Marris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58493","58493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662868","2017-01-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions she has had with the Secretary of State for Health on the effect of the linear programming model used to develop the Eatwell Guide on the dairy and milk industry.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58434","58434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662869","2017-01-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what representations she has received on the Eatwell Guide since March 2016.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58435","58435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662870","2017-01-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions she has had with the Secretary of State for Transport on the effect of the proposed third runway at Heathrow Airport on air quality; and what steps her Department is taking to incorporate its assessment of the air quality effect of a third runway in its revised air quality plan.","Biography information for Dr Tania Mathias","Dr Tania Mathias","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58485","58485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662871","2017-01-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much her Department and its arms-length departmental bodies have spent on (a) staffing, (b) other revenue costs and (c) capital expenditure in the current fiscal year in Yorkshire and the Humber.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58503","58503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662872","2017-01-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what advice she has received from the Chief Scientific Adviser to her Department on the cost and associated benefits of introducing separate food waste collections in England.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58609","58609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662873","2017-01-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what metrics for success her Department has set for the framework for consistency in household waste collections, launched by WRAP in September 2016.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58610","58610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662874","2017-01-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to remove barriers to a more resource-efficient economy; and if she will encourage the Environment Agency to reopen its online definition of waste tool to new submissions.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58351","58351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662875","2017-01-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether her Department permits its employees to join a credit union through payroll deductions; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58450","58450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662876","2017-01-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the effect of the Eatwell Guide, published in March 2016, on the milk and dairy industry.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58416","58416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662877","2017-01-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether human rights issues were raised during the recent (a) UK-China Economic and Trade Dialogue and (b) UK-China People to People Dialogue.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58398","58398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662878","2017-01-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his Department permits its employees to join a credit union through payroll deductions; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58452","58452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662879","2017-01-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the President of The Gambia on (a) the outcome of the election and (b) protection of democratic rights in that country; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58438","58438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662880","2017-01-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 16 November 2016 to Question 52554, who his Department's regional partners are in the facilitation of humanitarian access for aid agencies in South Sudan.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58348","58348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662881","2017-01-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the government of Egypt on recent UN reports of human rights abuses in that country.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58350","58350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662882","2017-01-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the level of political cooperation between the UK and Tanzania.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58360","58360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662883","2017-01-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the level of political cooperation between the UK and Zambia.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58361","58361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662884","2017-01-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to secure visits to Tibet by UK diplomatic personnel.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58397","58397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662885","2017-01-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has raised with the Chinese authorities the detention of the family of Tashi Rabten.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58394","58394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662886","2017-01-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the case of Tashi Wangchuk was raised in the recent UK-China Human Rights Dialogue; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58395","58395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662887","2017-01-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will seek to arrange a ministerial visit to Tibet.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58396","58396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662888","2017-01-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Argentinian counterpart on UK oil drilling in the Falkland Islands since the beginning of 2016.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58367","58367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662889","2017-01-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with officials (a) of the European Commission, (b) the EU member states and (c) of the European Parliament on the regulation of social media operators.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58388","58388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662890","2017-01-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what preparations (a) his Department and (b) the British Embassy in Belgrade undertook in advance of his State Visit to Serbia in November 2016.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58382","58382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662891","2017-01-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his Department has formally requested the release of Mr Andargachew Tsege; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58611","58611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662892","2017-01-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 24 November 2016 to Question 53303, what representations the Government has made to the Iranian government on the release of Kamal Foroughi and Nazanin Zaghari-Ratcliffe.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58595","58595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662893","2017-01-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to the governments of India and Pakistan on the situation in Kashmir; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58613","58613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662894","2017-01-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his (a) Russian and (b) Turkish counterpart on the shooting of the Russian Ambassador to Turkey, Andrei Karlov, in Ankara on 19 December 2016.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58631","58631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662895","2017-01-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to the governments of Burma and Bangladesh on the Rohingya people in those countries; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58612","58612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662896","2017-01-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, (a) how many contracts the Government has placed with UK-based public relations companies that include work in or on Somalia and (b) with which companies those contracts have been placed.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58596","58596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662897","2017-01-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, on what dates the first multilateral discussions with other signatories of the Joint Declaration for the Export and Subsequent Use of Armed or Strike-Enabled Unmanned Aerial Vehicles are planned.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58534","58534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662898","2017-01-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to promote good governance by the Palestinian Authority.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58551","58551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662899","2017-01-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the Palestinian Authority's ability to ensure equal respect for the human rights of its citizens.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58552","58552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662900","2017-01-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Israeli counterpart on the security situation in Israeli cities in range of Hamas terrorist attacks.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58553","58553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662901","2017-01-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the effectiveness of efforts by the Palestinian Authority to deter terrorism.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58554","58554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662902","2017-01-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent steps he has taken to support projects that foster co-operation and co-existence between Israelis and Palestinians.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58555","58555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662903","2017-01-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the security situation in Berlin since the terrorist attacks in that city on 19 December 2016.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58576","58576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662904","2017-01-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to work with the Palestinian Authority on promoting gender equality in the Palestinian Territories.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58561","58561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662905","2017-01-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that free and fair elections take place in both the West Bank and Gaza.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58562","58562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662906","2017-01-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the effect that projects fostering co-operation and co-existence have on the potential development of long-term peaceful relations between the Israel and Palestinian people.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58563","58563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662907","2017-01-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what amendments the Government proposed to drafts of the Joint Declaration for the Export and Subsequent Use of Armed or Strike-Enabled Unmanned Aerial Vehicles.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58533","58533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662908","2017-01-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to support the creation of an International Fund for Israeli-Palestinian Peace.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58564","58564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662909","2017-01-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government is taking (a) in Mauritania and (b) internationally to tackle slavery.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58507","58507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662910","2017-01-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many times in 2016 he met the Russian ambassador to discuss the humanitarian situation in Aleppo.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58505","58505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662911","2017-01-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what his policy is on whether the use of cluster munitions is always a contravention of international humanitarian law.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58517","58517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662912","2017-01-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what his policy is on whether designating whole cities with civilian populations as military targets is a contravention of international humanitarian law.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58516","58516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662913","2017-01-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what estimate his Department has made of the number of Saudi Arabian civilians killed as a result of Houthi attacks in Saudi Arabia since the recent suspension of the ceasefire in Yemen.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58518","58518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662914","2017-01-09","Ministry of Defence","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the cost to the public purse has been of training provided to the Burmese army.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58521","58521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662915","2017-01-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what (a) reports he has received and (b) representations he has made to his Bahrainian counterpart on the reported denial of adequate medical treatment to Husain Abdulwahab at Jau prison in Bahrain.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58522","58522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662916","2017-01-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when his Department last met the main opposition parties in Mauritania; and whether slavery and reprisals against anti-slavery human rights defenders in that country were discussed at that meeting.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58536","58536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662917","2017-01-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the Government's policy is on each of the findings of the Saudi-led Coalition's Joint Incident Assessment Team's investigations of eight airstrikes, published on 4 August 2016.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58527","58527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662918","2017-01-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what issues he raised to whom which related to human rights at the Manama Dialogue 2016.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58528","58528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662919","2017-01-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations the Government has made to the Bahrainian government on the release of Nabeel Rajab.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58529","58529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662920","2017-01-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received on the reported arbitrary detention of Mauritanian anti-slavery human rights defenders between 30 June and 3 July 2016; and what representations his Department has made to the Mauritanian government on (a) that reported detention and (b) the treatment of human rights defenders in that country.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58530","58530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662921","2017-01-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his international counterparts on the evacuation of civilians from eastern Aleppo since 14 December 2016.","Biography information for Naz Shah","Naz Shah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58626","58626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662922","2017-01-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the rates of conviction and sentencing in Somalia for the unlawful killing of journalists in that country; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58647","58647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662923","2017-01-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the ability of independent news media based in Somalia to report freely on the forthcoming presidential elections in that country.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58648","58648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662924","2017-01-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, on what dates (a) he, (b) ministers from his Department and (c) predecessors met the Eritrean Ambassador to the UK in each year since 2010; and when (i) he or (ii) Ministers from his Department plan to meet that Ambassador.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58657","58657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662925","2017-01-09","Department of Health","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions his Department has had with representatives from (a) NHS England, (b) Biogen pharmaceutical company and (c) patient groups on the Expanded Access programme for nusinersen for the treatment of infants with spinal muscular atrophy type 1.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58640","58640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662926","2017-01-09","Department of Health","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 5 December 2016 to Question 55033, what the number of private patients treated by the NHS was in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58618","58618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662927","2017-01-09","Department of Health","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the time available for due diligence related to (a) finance, (b) IT, (c) estates, (d) clinical quality and (e) employees prior to the transition to the new contract for community services to Bridgewater NHS Trust in March 2017; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58638","58638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662928","2017-01-09","Department of Health","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that the UK maintains medical, treatment and pharmaceutical cooperation with other EU countries after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Julian Knight","Julian Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58586","58586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662929","2017-01-09","Department of Health","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the value is of the contract won by Bridgewater NHS Trust for community health services in Liverpool; and if he will make an assessment of the likelihood of redundancies within those services in the first two years of that contract.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58635","58635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662930","2017-01-09","Department of Health","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment has been made of the potential savings to the public purse of the re-use of (a) casts, (b) walking boots, (c) crutches and (d) other aids within the NHS.","Biography information for Julian Knight","Julian Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58587","58587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662931","2017-01-09","Department of Health","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what timetable has been set by his Department for eliminating hepatitis C based on current testing and treatment rates.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58500","58500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662932","2017-01-09","Department of Health","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether Public Health England identified any disadvantages to using a linear programming model to generate the food group segment sizes in the revised Eatwell Guide.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58477","58477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662933","2017-01-09","Department of Health","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much the NHS has spent in Yorkshire and the Humber in the current financial year.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58509","58509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662934","2017-01-09","Department of Health","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many EU nationals work in each NHS Trust (a) as doctors, (b) as nurses and (c) in other positions.","Biography information for Mr Pat McFadden","Mr Pat McFadden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58469","58469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662935","2017-01-09","Department of Health","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which organisations and bodies are involved in decisions on whether Sustainability and Transformation Plans are implemented; which of these organisations makes that final decision; and what the Government's policy is on requiring the implementation of such plans in the event that agreement on implementation cannot be reached.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58545","58545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662936","2017-01-09","Department of Health","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment has been made of the potential effect of a £100,000 quality-adjusted life years threshold for evaluating highly specialised technologies on access to and uptake of new medicines for patients with very rare and complex diseases.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58569","58569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662937","2017-01-09","Department of Health","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions has he had with Skills for Care on increasing training requirements for homecare workers from tier 1 to tier 2 in the care certificate.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58535","58535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662938","2017-01-09","Department of Health","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the annual (a) budget is for and (b) spending is on dementia training for NHS workers.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58531","58531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662939","2017-01-09","Department of Health","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what comparative assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of dementia training provided to (a) homecare workers and (b) NHS practitioners who deliver care to people with dementia.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58532","58532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662940","2017-01-09","Department of Health","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much funding in addition to the core contract value for community services in Liverpool has been agreed between Bridgewater NHS Trust and Liverpool Clinical Commissioning Group to support transaction costs related to the transition between contracts; and in which years of that contract such funding will be available.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58637","58637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662941","2017-01-09","Department of Health","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when the change in financial value of the tendered contract for community services in Liverpool to £77 million was communicated to the bidders for that contract; and whether the bid for that contract from Bridgewater NHS trust was changed following that change in value.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58636","58636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662942","2017-01-09","Department of Health","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the proposed (a) governance and (b) financial risk-sharing arrangements are between Bridgewater NHS Trust, Liverpool City Council and the GP provider organisation relating to the new contract for community health services in Liverpool; and what contingency arrangements there are in the event of the failure of that contract.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58639","58639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662943","2017-01-09","Department of Health","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to introduce a UK-wide national patient register and database for familial hypercholesterolemia.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58568","58568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662944","2017-01-09","Department of Health","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps are being taken to ensure that patients with very rare diseases are not adversely affected by the introduction of a £100,000 quality adjusted life years threshold for evaluating highly specialised technologies.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58570","58570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662945","2017-01-09","Department of Health","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the availability of specialist psychology care for patients attending the neuromuscular service at the Newcastle Hospitals NHS Foundation Trust.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58387","58387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662946","2017-01-09","Department of Health","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidance his Department issues to clinical commissioning groups on the provision of NHS walk-in centres.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58385","58385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662947","2017-01-09","Department of Health","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the Expert Working Group for looked-after children's mental health plans to publish recommendations on mental health assessments for both looked-after children and care leavers.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58379","58379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662948","2017-01-09","Department of Health","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to introduce a UK-wide national patient register and database for familial hypercholesterolemia.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58375","58375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662949","2017-01-09","Department of Health","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients in England are currently  being treated with PCSK9 inhibitors for high cholesterol.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58391","58391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662950","2017-01-09","Department of Health","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that care leavers receive specialist mental health assessments.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58377","58377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662951","2017-01-09","Department of Health","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to improve patient access to PCSK9 inhibitors and other NICE-recommended cardiovascular disease medicines.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58392","58392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662952","2017-01-09","Department of Health","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of the extent of unmet mental health needs among care leavers.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58378","58378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662953","2017-01-09","Department of Health","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make it the Government's policy to report annually on the progress made in increasing the diagnosed familial hypercholesterolemia population across England.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58393","58393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662954","2017-01-09","Department of Health","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to improve the diagnosis and treatment of kidney failure in the UK.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58365","58365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662955","2017-01-09","Department of Health","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the role of the findings of Public Health England's report, From Plate to Guide: What, Why and How for the eatwell model, published in November 2016, in the process of determining changes to recommended dairy consumption levels.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58433","58433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662956","2017-01-09","Department of Health","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department permits its employees to join a credit union through payroll deductions; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58454","58454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662957","2017-01-09","Department of Health","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the announcement by NHS England of 4 December 2016 on a large-scale clinical trial of pre-exposure prophylaxis (PrEP) for HIV  prevention, how his Department plans to review progress during that trial; whether his Department plans to publish interim results of that trial; and whether his Department plans to fully commission PrEP before the end of the trial in the event that preliminary evidence shows it to be (a) effective at reducing HIV transmission, (b) cost effective and (c) affordable.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58399","58399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662958","2017-01-09","Department of Health","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the announcement by NHS England of 4 December 2016 on a large-scale clinical trial of pre-exposure prophylaxis for HIV  prevention, whether the reference to 10,000 people over three years means 10,000 people for up to three years each.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58400","58400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662959","2017-01-09","Department of Health","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many personal health budgets were available in each local authority area over the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58417","58417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662960","2017-01-09","Department of Health","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to support personal budgets which integrate health and social care funding.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58418","58418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662961","2017-01-09","Department of Health","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to develop a long-term sustainable funding system for social care.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58419","58419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662962","2017-01-09","Home Office","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many deaths have occurred in immigration detention centres in each year since 2007.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58426","58426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662963","2017-01-09","Home Office","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people are on suicide watch in immigration detention centres.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58427","58427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662964","2017-01-09","Home Office","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many claims for asylum were refused in (a) Scotland, (b) England, (c) Wales and (d) Northern Ireland in each month since January 2016.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58422","58422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662965","2017-01-09","Home Office","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many claims for asylum were granted in (a) Scotland, (b) England, (c) Wales and (d) Northern Ireland in each month since January 2016.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58423","58423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662966","2017-01-09","Home Office","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many claims for asylum were lodged and are still outstanding in (a) Scotland, (b) England, (c) Wales and (d) Northern Ireland in each month since January 2016.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58424","58424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662967","2017-01-09","Home Office","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department permits its employees to join a credit union through payroll deductions; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58455","58455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662968","2017-01-09","Home Office","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many enforced removals of failed asylum seekers were conducted in (a) Scotland, (b) England, (c) Wales and (d) Northern Ireland in each month since January 2016.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58425","58425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662969","2017-01-09","Home Office","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what consultations took place with the National Asylum Seekers stakeholder forum and other interested parties on changes to the sharing criteria of asylum accommodation contracts to allow children up to the age of 16 to share with their parents; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58481","58481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662970","2017-01-09","Home Office","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) EU and (b) non-EU nationals are employed by (i) her Department, (ii) the UK Border Force and (iii) her Department's other agencies.","Biography information for Mr Pat McFadden","Mr Pat McFadden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58467","58467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662971","2017-01-09","Home Office","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what consultations took place with the National Asylum Seekers stakeholder forum and other interested parties on changes to the sharing criteria in asylum accommodation contracts to allow willing mothers to use shared non-mother and baby unit accommodation; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58482","58482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662972","2017-01-09","Home Office","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent steps the Government has taken to speed up family reunification for unaccompanied refugee children in Europe.","Biography information for Sammy Wilson","Sammy Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58466","58466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662973","2017-01-09","Home Office","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what consultations took place with the National Asylum Seekers stakeholder forum and other interested parties on changing the sharing criteria in asylum accommodation contracts to allow siblings of the same sex to room-share to the age of 20; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58478","58478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662974","2017-01-09","Home Office","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what consultations took place with the National Asylum Seekers stakeholder forum and other interested parties on extending the contracts on asylum accommodation.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58479","58479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662975","2017-01-09","Home Office","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when the additional £10 million funding for English language teaching announced in September 2016 for refugees from the Syrian Vulnerable Person's Resettlement Scheme and the Vulnerable Children's Resettlement Scheme will be made available to those groups.","Biography information for Caroline Ansell","Caroline Ansell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58368","58368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662976","2017-01-09","Home Office","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what reports her Department has received on (a) staffing shortages and (b) waiting times at passport control at UK airports in the last three months; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58372","58372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662977","2017-01-09","Home Office","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer to the hon. Member for the Cotswolds of 1 December 2017 to Question 54884, for what reasons the Government does not collect or publish data on firearm and shotgun certificate applications.","Biography information for Mr Ian Liddell-Grainger","Mr Ian Liddell-Grainger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58381","58381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662978","2017-01-09","Home Office","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she plans to respond to the letter from the hon. Member for Wolverhampton South West of 3 November 2016 on representation of the Special Constabulary, reference ZA5692.","Biography information for Rob Marris","Rob Marris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58386","58386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662979","2017-01-09","Ministry of Justice","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment the Government has made of the potential merits of bringing forward legislative proposals on extra-territorial effects for offences related to honour-based violence","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58579","58579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662980","2017-01-09","Home Office","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many work permit applications have been approved for (a) doctors and (b) nurses and auxiliary nurses from (i) Nigeria, (ii) Ghana and (iii) other African countries in each year since 2007.","Biography information for Lord Lilley","Mr Peter Lilley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58592","58592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662981","2017-01-09","Ministry of Justice","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the Government's plans are for investigating allegations of honour-based violence which are transnational.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58580","58580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662982","2017-01-09","Cabinet Office","2016-12-20","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many EU nationals are estimated to be (a) living and (b) working in the UK.","Biography information for Mr Pat McFadden","Mr Pat McFadden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58594","58594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662983","2017-01-09","Home Office","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the letter from the Minister for Immigration to the Home Affairs Select Committee of 18 November 2016, what review of detention needs is taking place; and what the timescale is for that review.","Biography information for Gavin Newlands","Gavin Newlands","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58597","58597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662984","2017-01-09","Ministry of Justice","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many compensation awards of what amount were made to victims related to each of the 30 convictions for human trafficking recorded in 2015.","Biography information for Lord Garnier","Sir Edward Garnier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58541","58541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662985","2017-01-09","Home Office","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans she has to collect data on outcomes of victims of human trafficking referred to in the national referral mechanism after they have co-operated with police and provided evidence to assist with prosecutions.","Biography information for Lord Garnier","Sir Edward Garnier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58540","58540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662986","2017-01-09","Home Office","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many students have been granted short-term study visas to study English in the UK in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Paul Scully","Paul Scully","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58543","58543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662987","2017-01-09","Home Office","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department intends to review security procedures in relation to terrorist attacks using vehicles following the attacks in Berlin on 19 December 2016.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58577","58577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662988","2017-01-09","Home Office","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department reviewed security procedures in relation to terrorist attacks using vehicles following the attacks in Nice in July 2016.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58578","58578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662989","2017-01-09","Home Office","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what consultations took place with the National Asylum Seekers stakeholder forum and other interested parties on changing the sharing criteria in asylum accommodation contracts to allow siblings of opposite sex to room-share to the age of 16; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58480","58480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662990","2017-01-09","Home Office","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much her Department and its arms-length departmental bodies have spent on (a) staffing, (b) other revenue costs and (c) capital expenditure in the current fiscal year in Yorkshire and the Humber.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58504","58504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662991","2017-01-09","Home Office","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the Government has received an application from Ravil Mingazov for asylum since she has been granted release from Guantanamo Bay.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58526","58526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662992","2017-01-09","Home Office","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have been investigated by police forces for impersonating a candidate and taking their written or practical driving test for them by police force area in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Karl McCartney","Karl McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58620","58620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662993","2017-01-09","Home Office","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what information her Department holds on the total amount of compensation payments it has made at the request of the Parliamentary and Health Service Ombudsman in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Naz Shah","Naz Shah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58589","58589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662994","2017-01-09","Home Office","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what checks are made to ensure that people convicted of using an impersonator to take a written or practical driving test do not continue to drive using a fraudulently obtained driving licence.","Biography information for Karl McCartney","Karl McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58619","58619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662995","2017-01-09","Home Office","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what her policy is on continuing direct grant funding from her Department to support independent domestic violence advisers and multi-agency risk assessment conference coordinators after March 2017.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58622","58622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662996","2017-01-09","Home Office","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what information her Department holds on how much compensation has been paid as a result of the mis-administration of applications for indefinite leave to remain in 2015.","Biography information for Naz Shah","Naz Shah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58590","58590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662997","2017-01-09","Home Office","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have been investigated by police forces for using an impersonator to take a written or practical driving test for them by police force area in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Karl McCartney","Karl McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58621","58621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662998","2017-01-09","Department of Health","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many women have been held in isolation in Yarl's Wood Immigration Removal Centre in the last month as a result of the recent outbreak of tuberculosis in that centre.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58656","58656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/662999","2017-01-09","Home Office","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many emergency services network masts will be built in Orkney and Shetland constituency; and what steps she is taking to ensure that mobile phone services are provided from all four mobile network operators at all such sites.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58650","58650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/663000","2017-01-09","Home Office","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions she has had with local authorities, other commissioners and the voluntary and community sector on planned changes to funding arrangements for independent domestic violence advisers and multi-agency risk assessment conference coordinators from March 2017.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58623","58623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/663001","2017-01-09","Department for Transport","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answers of 18 November 2016 to Question 50859 and 19 December 2016 to Question 55636, and with reference to the article entitled DVLA works with police and HM Revenue and Customs to crack down on illegal foreign registered vehicles, published on the gov.uk website on 30 January 2015, what assessment has been made of (a) the number of illegal foreign registered vehicles on the roads in the UK and (b) the effectiveness of the DVLA working with the police and HM Revenue and Customs to tackle the presence of such vehicles.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58608","58608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/663002","2017-01-09","Department for International Development","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what her policy is on the Government's long-term commitment to spending 0.7 per cent of gross national income on overseas development assistance.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58508","58508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/663003","2017-01-09","Department for International Development","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether older people will be included within the indicators used to measure government performance against the Sustainable Development Goals.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58523","58523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/663004","2017-01-09","Department for International Development","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, for what reasons the Government reduced the bilateral aid budget to (a) South Sudan and (b) Yemen in 2016-17.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58524","58524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/663005","2017-01-09","Department for International Development","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to ensure changes to the bilateral aid budgets for (a) Rwanda, (b) Kenya and (c) Ghana do not affect poverty reduction in those countries.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58525","58525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/663006","2017-01-09","Department for International Development","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps the Government is taking to ensure the Sustainable Development Goals are implemented in the UK.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58519","58519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/663007","2017-01-09","Department for International Development","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment her Department has made of the effect of the implementation of the Sustainable Development Goals on older women.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58520","58520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/663008","2017-01-09","Department for International Development","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what mechanisms her Department has in place to ensure that spending of public funds by the Commonwealth Development Corporation is focused on the reduction of poverty.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58567","58567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/663009","2017-01-09","Department for International Development","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to improve relationship management with bilateral government partners through transition by risk management and more coordinated communications.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58565","58565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/663010","2017-01-09","Department for International Development","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that its policies focus on means to achieve the Sustainable Development Goals.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58566","58566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/663011","2017-01-09","Department for International Development","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking regularly to report on its funding for non-governmental organisations.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58556","58556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/663012","2017-01-09","Department for International Development","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to support the creation of an international fund for Israeli-Palestinian peace.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58557","58557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/663013","2017-01-09","Department for International Development","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what mechanisms are in place within government to ensure that development considerations are taken account of in wider government bilateral relationships.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58558","58558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/663014","2017-01-09","Department for International Development","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to improve transparency and accountability on its commitments to end aid or change aid relationships.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58559","58559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/663015","2017-01-09","Department for International Development","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that it maintains accountability and oversight of the use of public funds by the Commonwealth Development Corporation.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58560","58560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/663016","2017-01-09","Department for International Development","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment her Department has made of the effect of UK aid expenditure on decentralised renewable energy on rural communities; and if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of increasing such aid expenditure.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58401","58401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/663017","2017-01-09","Department for International Development","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether the Government plans to include future arrangements for the allocation of development funds previously distributed by EU institutions in its negotiation plan on leaving the EU.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58442","58442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/663018","2017-01-09","Department for International Development","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether her Department permits its employees to join a credit union through payroll deductions; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58456","58456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/663019","2017-01-09","Department for International Development","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many people globally she estimates (a) are without reliable access to electricity and (b) will be without reliable access to electricity in 2030.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58409","58409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/663020","2017-01-09","Department for Transport","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the average length of sentence was for people convicted of impersonating a candidate and taking the (a) written and (b) practical parts of the driving test for them in each of the last five years and by geographical area.","Biography information for Karl McCartney","Karl McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58405","58405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/663021","2017-01-09","Ministry of Justice","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether her Department permits its employees to join a credit union through payroll deductions; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58458","58458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/663022","2017-01-09","Department for Transport","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the average length of sentence was for people convicted of using an impersonator to take the (a) written and (b) practical parts of the driving test for them in each of the last five years and by geographical area.","Biography information for Karl McCartney","Karl McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58402","58402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/663023","2017-01-09","Ministry of Justice","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if she will extend the duration of her Department's consultation on Reforming the Soft Tissue Injury (Whiplash) Claims Process to take account of the Christmas period.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58491","58491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/663024","2017-01-09","Ministry of Justice","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to section 14 of the Marriage (Same Sex) Couples Act 2013, what recent assessment her Department has made of the potential merits of legalising humanist marriages; and whether the Government has plans to bring forward legislative proposals to legalise such marriages.","Biography information for Naz Shah","Naz Shah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58588","58588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/663025","2017-01-09","Northern Ireland Office","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, whether his Department permits its employees to join a credit union through payroll deductions; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58459","58459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/663026","2017-01-09","Prime Minister","2016-12-20","To ask the Prime Minister, when information on her external meetings from July to September 2016 will be published.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58547","58547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/663027","2017-01-09","Scotland Office","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, whether his Department permits its employees to join a credit union through payroll deductions; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58460","58460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/663028","2017-01-09","Scotland Office","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what plans he has to visit a food bank in January 2017.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58430","58430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/663029","2017-01-09","Scotland Office","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, whether he has visited a food bank in December 2016.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58429","58429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/663030","2017-01-09","Department for Transport","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will meet the All-Party Parliamentary Cycling Group to discuss issues facing cyclists in London and elsewhere.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58357","58357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/663031","2017-01-09","Department for Transport","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he, his driver or any official reported to the police the incident on 12 October 2016 in which a cyclist came off his bike.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58358","58358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/663032","2017-01-09","Department for Transport","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of section 42 of the Road Traffic Act 1988 in protecting cyclists.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58352","58352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/663033","2017-01-09","Department for Transport","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate his Department has made of the number of people who currently hold a driving licence fraudulently obtained by using an impersonator to take the (a) written and (b) practical parts of the driving test for them.","Biography information for Karl McCartney","Karl McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58408","58408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/663034","2017-01-09","Department for Transport","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department permits its employees to join a credit union through payroll deductions; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58461","58461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/663035","2017-01-09","Department for Transport","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the charges for Departmental Pool Car Service Charges to the Attorney General's Office between 2012 and 2015, published by his Department on 17 December 2016, what the (a) purpose, (b) distance travelled and (c) cost was of each journey booked by his office.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58492","58492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/663036","2017-01-09","Department for Transport","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the timetable is for the publication of draft flight paths to and from an expanded Heathrow Airport.","Biography information for Dr Tania Mathias","Dr Tania Mathias","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58498","58498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/663037","2017-01-09","Department for Transport","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he plans to publish the draft National Policy Statement on the expansion of Heathrow Airport.","Biography information for Dr Tania Mathias","Dr Tania Mathias","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58488","58488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/663038","2017-01-09","Department for Transport","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he plans to announce which elements of surface access to the proposed third runway at Heathrow Airport will be funded from the public purse.","Biography information for Dr Tania Mathias","Dr Tania Mathias","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58487","58487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/663039","2017-01-09","Department for Transport","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the (a) resilience of power supply arrangements to railway signalling centres and (b) provision of back-up power supplies in the event of National Grid failures.","Biography information for Mrs Flick Drummond","Mrs Flick Drummond","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58431","58431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/663040","2017-01-09","Department for Transport","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment he has made of the potential (a) economic benefits and (b) level of new jobs resulting from the third runway at Heathrow Airport by region of the UK.","Biography information for Dr Tania Mathias","Dr Tania Mathias","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58484","58484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/663041","2017-01-09","Department for Transport","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what guidance his Department issues on standards of consultations prior to bus route changes; and whether there is a requirement in that guidance that passenger number surveys are conducted on multiple days of the week at multiple times of the day.","Biography information for Julian Knight","Julian Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58593","58593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/663042","2017-01-09","Department for Transport","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what lessons his Department learned from the Sheffield to Rotherham tram-train pilot; and what steps he is taking to apply those lessons in the proposed tram-train to Glasgow Airport project.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58628","58628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/663043","2017-01-09","Wales Office","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, whether his Department permits its employees to join a credit union through payroll deductions; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58462","58462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/663044","2017-01-09","Women and Equalities","2016-12-20","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, whether the Government Equalities Office permits its employees to join a credit union through payroll deductions; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58453","58453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/663045","2017-01-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether his Department permits its employees to join a credit union through payroll deductions; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58463","58463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/663046","2017-01-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, on which date a Minister of his Department last visited Bridgeton Jobcentre Plus in Glasgow.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58428","58428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/663047","2017-01-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many representations he has received on the effect of the Pension Protection Fund Levy on retail co-operatives; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58436","58436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/663048","2017-01-09","Cabinet Office","2016-12-20","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 10 November 2016 to Question 51658, when he expects the UK Statistics Authority to place its additional analysis in the Library.","Biography information for Margaret Greenwood","Margaret Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58421","58421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/663049","2017-01-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment his Department has made of trends in employment in the construction sector over the next five years.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58366","58366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/663050","2017-01-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what information his Department holds on the use of three-day emergency food parcels.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58354","58354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/663051","2017-01-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will review his Department's plans to cap housing benefit for those in supported housing in line with local housing allowance.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58369","58369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/663052","2017-01-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 15 December 2016 to Question 56948, if his Department will meet the PCS union in January 2017 to discuss social security benefits for children.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58591","58591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/663053","2017-01-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the proposed jobcentre closures in Glasgow on levels of deprivation in (a) Glasgow South constituency and (b) the city of Glasgow.","Biography information for Stewart Malcolm McDonald","Stewart Malcolm McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58473","58473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/663054","2017-01-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent discussions he has had with third sector organisations on the proposed jobcentre closures in Glasgow.","Biography information for Stewart Malcolm McDonald","Stewart Malcolm McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58472","58472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/663055","2017-01-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many national insurance numbers have been issued by jobcentres in (a) Castlemilk and (b) Langside in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Stewart Malcolm McDonald","Stewart Malcolm McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58474","58474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/663056","2017-01-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to provide an equality impact assessment in relation to the proposed jobcentre closures in Glasgow.","Biography information for Stewart Malcolm McDonald","Stewart Malcolm McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58475","58475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/663057","2017-01-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans he has to meet with representatives of the eight jobcentres in Glasgow earmarked for closure before his Department's public consultation ends on 31 January 2017.","Biography information for Stewart Malcolm McDonald","Stewart Malcolm McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58476","58476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/663058","2017-01-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of claimants affected by the lower benefit caps in Hounslow are in receipt of (a) jobseeker's allowance, (b) employment and support allowance, (c) income support, (d) another benefit and (e) housing benefit alone.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58512","58512"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/663059","2017-01-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much his Department and any of its arms-length departmental bodies have spent on (a) staffing, (b) other revenue costs and (c) capital expenditure in the current fiscal year in Yorkshire and the Humber.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58502","58502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/663060","2017-01-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what instructions are given to staff working on the universal credit enquiry lines on protocols concerning the disclosure of personal data to third parties who have implicit consent from the claimant.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58511","58511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/663061","2017-01-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether the Government has conducted an Equality Impact Assessment to evaluate the effect that the closure of Jobcentre Plus offices will have in Glasgow.","Biography information for Natalie McGarry","Natalie McGarry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58624","58624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/663062","2017-01-09","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what support the Government provides to people who received Green Deal finance from a company that has since gone into liquidation.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58549","58549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/663063","2017-01-09","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what representations his Department has received from consumers on the sale of Green Deal services by Home Energy and Lifestyle Management Ltd.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58548","58548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/663064","2017-01-09","HM Treasury","2016-12-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps have been taken to aid those firms affected by the mis-selling of synthetic fixed-rate loans between 2001 and 2009.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58617","58617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/663065","2017-01-09","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 25 October 2016 to Question 47955, what steps his Department has taken to ensure that the targeted reduction of CO2 emissions to 57 per cent of 1990 levels by 2030 is met.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58581","58581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/663066","2017-01-09","HM Treasury","2016-12-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps the Government has taken to assist people affected by the mis-selling of synthetic fixed-rate loans between 2001 and 2009.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58582","58582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/663067","2017-01-09","Department for Education","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what information her Department holds on the number of people employed in English language colleges in each region and constituent part of the UK.","Biography information for Paul Scully","Paul Scully","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58544","58544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/663068","2017-01-09","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will make it his policy to ensure that any proceeds from the sale of the Green Investment Bank are greater than or equivalent to the 10 per cent portfolio return forecast by that Bank in its latest Annual Report.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58384","58384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/663069","2017-01-09","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether his Department permits its employees to join a credit union through payroll deductions; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58443","58443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/663070","2017-01-09","Department for International Trade","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps his Department is taking to offer support to new exporters with meeting areas and networking facilities at overseas exhibitions.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58410","58410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/663071","2017-01-09","Department for International Trade","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what assessment his Department has made of the effect on international trade policy of the Prime Minister's announcement of the creation of the GREAT club bespoke visa and immigration service.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58411","58411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/663072","2017-01-09","Department for International Trade","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what assessment he has made of the potential access of British coatings companies to European markets after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58412","58412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/663073","2017-01-09","Department for International Trade","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what assessment he has made of the relative commercial success of UKTI sponsored multi-industry market visits and industry-specific events since his Department was created.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58413","58413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/663074","2017-01-09","Department for International Trade","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what representations his Department has received from chemical companies based in the UK on their access to EU markets after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58414","58414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/663075","2017-01-09","Department for International Trade","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps he plans to take to ensure that British industries dependent on the REACH regulation to import raw materials for coatings and inks will be able to import the materials they need after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58415","58415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/663076","2017-01-09","Department for International Trade","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what plans his Department has to make use of the proposed expansion of Heathrow Airport and potential new long-haul air links arising from that expansion in negotiating future trade agreements.","Biography information for Sammy Wilson","Sammy Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58465","58465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/663077","2017-01-09","Department for International Trade","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether his Department permits its employees to join a credit union through payroll deductions; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58457","58457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/663078","2017-01-09","Department for International Trade","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps the Government is taking to promote trade between the UK and Tanzania.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58362","58362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/663079","2017-01-09","Department for International Trade","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps the Government is taking to promote trade between the UK and Zambia.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58363","58363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/663080","2017-01-09","Department for International Trade","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps the Government is taking to promote trade between the UK and (a) Jamaica, (b) St Lucia and (c) Montserrat and Anguilla.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58364","58364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/663081","2017-01-09","Department for International Trade","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps he is taking to ensure that human rights considerations are included in the negotiation of future international trade and investment agreements.","Biography information for Sammy Wilson","Sammy Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58572","58572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/663082","2017-01-09","Department for International Trade","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether he plans to include the issue of corporate responsibility to respect human rights in international investment agreements after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Sammy Wilson","Sammy Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58571","58571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/663083","2017-01-09","Department for International Trade","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many licence applications have been refused under Criterion 2c of the Consolidated EU and National Arms Export Licensing Criteria in each year since 2008; and what the destination country was of each of those applications so refused.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58546","58546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/663084","2017-01-09","Department for International Trade","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what his policy is on whether the UK's schedules of concessions and commitments will be submitted to the WTO as modifications or as rectifications after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58537","58537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/663085","2017-01-09","Department for International Trade","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what the annual budget is for the GREAT campaign.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58539","58539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/663086","2017-01-09","Department for International Trade","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, with reference to his Written Ministerial Statement of 5 December 2016, HCWS316, how the planned UK-specific WTO schedules he announced in his 5 December statement will differ from the UK's existing obligations.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58538","58538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/663087","2017-01-09","Department for International Trade","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many (a) EU and (b) non-EU nationals are employed by his Department.","Biography information for Mr Pat McFadden","Mr Pat McFadden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58471","58471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/663088","2017-01-09","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many (a) EU nationals and (b) non-EU nationals are employed by his Department.","Biography information for Mr Pat McFadden","Mr Pat McFadden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58470","58470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/663089","2017-01-16","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the UK leaving the EU on further and higher education institutions' revenue from the hosting of EU conferences by such institutions.","Biography information for John McNally","John Mc Nally","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58627","58627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/663090","2017-01-09","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether his Department permits its employees to join a credit union through payroll deductions; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58451","58451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669680","2017-01-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent estimate his Department has made of the number of people saving into a pension scheme as a result of auto-enrolment.","Biography information for Nigel Mills","Nigel Mills","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 908074","908074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669681","2017-01-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent estimate his Department has made of the number of people saving into a pension scheme as a result of auto-enrolment.","Biography information for Matt Warman","Matt Warman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 908072","908072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669682","2017-01-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of his Department's policy to remove housing benefit from 18 to 21 year olds on their living standards.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 908073","908073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669683","2017-01-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the recent trends in the number of women in employment.","Biography information for Ben Howlett","Ben Howlett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 908071","908071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669684","2017-01-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of his Department's policy to remove housing benefit from 18 to 21 year olds on their living standards.","Biography information for Callum McCaig","Callum McCaig","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 908070","908070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/669685","2017-01-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent discussions he has had with the Chancellor of the Exchequer on improving pension transition arrangements for women born in the 1950s.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 908079","908079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/670420","2017-01-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the strength of diplomatic relations between Poland and the UK.","Biography information for David Morris","David Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 908050","908050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/670421","2017-01-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what progress has been made on tackling Daesh in Libya.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 908047","908047"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/670422","2017-01-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions the Government has had with the incoming US administration on climate change.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 908045","908045"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/670423","2017-01-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what his future plans are for the Marshall Scholarship scheme.","Biography information for Alan Mak","Mr Alan Mak","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 908054","908054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/670424","2017-01-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent reports he has received on the persecution of Christian and other religious minorities by Daesh.","Biography information for Michelle Donelan","Michelle Donelan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 908046","908046"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/670425","2017-01-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of (a) trends in the level and (b) the causes of recent violence in Israel and the West Bank.","Biography information for Craig Tracey","Craig Tracey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 908051","908051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/670426","2017-01-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to promote press freedom abroad.","Biography information for Stewart Malcolm McDonald","Stewart Malcolm McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 908048","908048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/671383","2017-01-11","Department for International Development","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent steps she has taken to support the implementation of the Sustainable Development Goals.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 908011","908011"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/671384","2017-01-11","Department for International Development","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what plans her Department has to introduce greater financial accountability to the international aid system.","Biography information for David Morris","David Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 908009","908009"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/671385","2017-01-11","Department for International Development","2016-12-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much her Department has spent on private consultancies in the last 12 months.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 908003","908003"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661592","2017-01-09","Cabinet Office","2016-12-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 19 April 2016 to Question 33684, on what page in the Cabinet Office annual report and accounts 2015-16 the specific costs incurred by the Government's Anti-Corruption Champion are set out.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58106","58106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661593","2017-01-09","Cabinet Office","2016-12-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether he plans to publish the Government Transformation Strategy before 1 January 2017.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58341","58341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661594","2017-01-09","Cabinet Office","2016-12-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the number of people in (a) Scotland and (b) the UK (i) between the ages of 16 and 21 earing less than £8.45 per hour, (ii) aged under 18 earning £4 per hour, (iii) aged 21 and over earning £6.95 per hour, (iv) aged 18 to 20 earning £5.55 per hour and (v) who are apprentices and earing £3.40 per hour.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58343","58343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661595","2017-01-09","HM Treasury","2016-12-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether his Department has awarded any commercial contracts to iNHouse Communications Ltd in the last five years.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58306","58306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661596","2017-01-09","HM Treasury","2016-12-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether his Department is in communication with iNHouse Communications Ltd in relation to any ongoing commercial tender process.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58307","58307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661597","2017-01-09","HM Treasury","2016-12-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, who the diversity champion is on his departmental board.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58244","58244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661598","2017-01-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to ensure that proposed increases in business rates do not have a negative effect on the financial services sector.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58221","58221"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661599","2017-01-09","HM Treasury","2016-12-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he plans to publish an estimate of the potential effect on the public finances of the UK's decision to leave the EU; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58259","58259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661600","2017-01-09","HM Treasury","2016-12-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the potential for further increases in the employment rate in the UK economy over the next (a) two, (b) four and (c) six years.","Biography information for John Penrose","John Penrose","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58255","58255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661601","2017-01-09","HM Treasury","2016-12-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the revenue to be raised from the Apprenticeship Levy in (a) 2017-18, (b) 2018-19 and (c) 2019-20.","Biography information for Callum McCaig","Callum McCaig","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58108","58108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661602","2017-01-09","HM Treasury","2016-12-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 2 November 2016 to Question 13949, if he will publish the Government's analysis on determining any loss of VED revenues following VW Group's use of defeat devices; and whether any of the models among the 1.2 million vehicles affected were subsequently re-banded.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58110","58110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661603","2017-01-09","HM Treasury","2016-12-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment the Government has made of the effect of Financial Conduct Authority requirements for mortgage affordability assessments on the ability of home owners to re-mortgage or switch mortgage provider.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58150","58150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661604","2017-01-09","HM Treasury","2016-12-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps the Government is taking to assist home owners who seek to re-mortgage but who, following the Mortgage Market Review, no longer meet Financial Conduct Authority requirements on mortgage affordability assessments.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58151","58151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661605","2017-01-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, who the diversity champion is on his departmental board.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58230","58230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661607","2017-01-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate his Department has made of the potential effect on the budget of each local authority in Greater Manchester of the (a) reduction in the New Homes Bonus scheme and (b) additional funding through the adult social care support grant in each of the next three years.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58291","58291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661608","2017-01-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the cost to the public purse has been of compulsory purchase orders in each London borough in each year since 1990.","Biography information for Dr Andrew Murrison","Dr Andrew Murrison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58195","58195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661609","2017-01-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many compulsory purchase orders have been made, by London borough, (a) in total, (b) for heritage purposes and (c) to provide housing in each year since 1990.","Biography information for Dr Andrew Murrison","Dr Andrew Murrison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58193","58193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661611","2017-01-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, which local authorities have made compulsory purchase orders in each year since 1990.","Biography information for Dr Andrew Murrison","Dr Andrew Murrison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58194","58194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661612","2017-01-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the effect on the amount of office floor space in London of the relaxation of permitted development rights.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58273","58273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661613","2017-01-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to his oral contribution of 15 December 2016, Official Report, columns 976 to 979, on the local government finance settlement, whether the decision by a local authority to raise revenue through the adult social care precept was a criterion used by his Department in assessing the allocation of adult social care support grant awards.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58326","58326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661614","2017-01-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the amount that each local authority could raise if they employed use of the three per cent social care precept on council tax in the 2016-17 financial year.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58325","58325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661615","2017-01-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the value of (a) staffing expenditure, (b) other revenue costs and (c) capital expenditure by his Department and its arms-length bodies in whole or in part in Yorkshire and the Humber in 2016-17.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58317","58317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661616","2017-01-09","Department of Health","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much has been spent by each local authority on Deprivation of Liberty Safeguards cases in (a) 2014-15, (b) 2015-16 and (c) 2016-17 to date; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58330","58330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661617","2017-01-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much additional revenue he estimates Salford City Council could receive as a result of increasing council tax rates by three per cent in the 2017-18 financial year.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58334","58334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661618","2017-01-09","Department of Health","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much of the additional £25 million provided by his Department in 2015-16 to support local authorities in their deprivation of liberty safeguards work each local authority received.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58347","58347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661619","2017-01-09","Department of Health","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent estimate his Department has made of the financial cost to a local authority of a Deprivation of Liberty Safeguards assessment; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58331","58331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661620","2017-01-09","Department of Health","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many Deprivation of Liberty Safeguards assessments each local authority in England made in (a) 2014-15, (b) 2015-16 and (c) 2016-17 to date; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58332","58332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661621","2017-01-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much additional revenue he estimates Salford City Council could receive by increasing council tax rates by three per cent in the 2016-17 financial year.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58333","58333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661622","2017-01-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to his oral contribution of 15 December 2016, Official Report, columns 976-9, on the local government finance settlement, what methodology his Department plans to use to determine relative need when awarding the adult social care support grant in 2017-18.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58335","58335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661623","2017-01-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to the provisional local government finance settlement 2017 to 2018, by how much Salford City Council's new homes bonus payments will be reduced; how much Salford City Council will receive from the adult social care support grant; and what the net effect is of those funding changes.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58336","58336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661624","2017-01-09","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what legal powers TV Licensing have to compel an occupier who does not have television receiving equipment to notify TV Licensing that no television licence is required.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58337","58337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661625","2017-01-09","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether she has received any representations about the tone of letters sent by TV Licensing to occupiers who do not have television receiving equipment but who choose not to notify TV Licensing of that fact.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58338","58338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661626","2017-01-09","Home Office","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many mobile telephone masts are planned to be built in Salisbury constituency under the Emergency Services Network Mobile Services contract.","Biography information for John Glen","John Glen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58328","58328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661627","2017-01-09","Home Office","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether data held by her Department on the geographic location of mobile telephone masts constructed under the Emergency Services Network Mobile Services contract will be released.","Biography information for John Glen","John Glen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58327","58327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661628","2017-01-09","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether her Department is in communication with iNHouse Communications Ltd in relation to any ongoing commercial tender process.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58312","58312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661629","2017-01-09","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether her Department has awarded any commercial contracts to iNHouse Communications Ltd in the last five years.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58313","58313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661630","2017-01-09","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if her Department will undertake an impact assessment of macro not-spot roaming in order to improve mobile coverage.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58264","58264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661631","2017-01-09","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to the report of the National Infrastructure Commission, entitled Connected Future, published on 14 December 2016, what her Department's plans are for preparing the UK's mobile telephone infrastructure for universal geographical coverage of 5G.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58265","58265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661632","2017-01-09","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, who the diversity champion is on her departmental board.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58231","58231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661633","2017-01-09","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of portable television licences for people living in multiple accommodation.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58171","58171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661634","2017-01-09","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of providing social tariffs to improve access to broadband among low-income households.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58093","58093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661635","2017-01-09","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if she will undertake a further review of the adequacy of a 10 Mbit/s broadband speed before deciding on the level at which such a speed should be set in a Universal Service Obligation.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58204","58204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661636","2017-01-09","Ministry of Defence","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, who the diversity champion is on his departmental board.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58232","58232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661637","2017-01-09","Ministry of Defence","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to his comments on the Andrew Marr BBC TV programme on 11 December 2016, on Yemen, what the evidential basis is for his statement that Houthis in Yemen are supported by al-Qaeda.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58289","58289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661638","2017-01-09","Ministry of Defence","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what ammunition his Department plans to use for the Semi-Armour-Piercing High-Explosive Incendiary-Tracer round for the F35B Lightning II gun.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58279","58279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661639","2017-01-09","Ministry of Defence","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 16 December 2016 to Question 57051, what the final test point score was for the F-35B Lightning II; and what the planned such test point score was in flight sciences testing through to 30 September 2016.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58280","58280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661640","2017-01-09","Ministry of Defence","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 15 December 2016 to Question 56630, what the cost was to the public purse of (a) travel and (b) accommodation for the 25 members of the Armed Forces and 10 MoD civilian staff who attended the naming ceremony for RFA Tiderace.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58282","58282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661642","2017-01-09","Ministry of Defence","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 19 December 2016 to Question 57254, what the cost was to the public purse of accommodation in South Korea for the Lady Sponsor for the naming ceremony for RFA Tiderace.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58281","58281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661643","2017-01-09","Ministry of Defence","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the cost to the public purse was of (a) recruitment and (b) redundancy as a result of the rebasing programme at Imphal Barracks.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58298","58298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661644","2017-01-09","Ministry of Defence","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the total cost to the public purse was of locating Army units from Imphal Barracks in York to Catterick Barracks in 2014; and what proportion of that cost was spent on upgrading accommodation in Catterick.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58299","58299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661645","2017-01-09","Ministry of Defence","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the cost to the public purse was of refurbishing Imphal Barracks in York in order to accommodate 1st Division Headquarters.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58300","58300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661646","2017-01-09","Department of Health","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what support his Department provides to veterans who have lost one or more limb during their service.","Biography information for Gavin Robinson","Gavin Robinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58227","58227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661647","2017-01-09","Ministry of Defence","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he was first made aware of the results of the internal investigation that found recent use of UK cluster munitions in Yemen.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58304","58304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661648","2017-01-09","Ministry of Defence","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what environmental impact assessment his Department plans to undertake for the runway resurfacing project on Ascension Island; and whether that assessment will be open to stakeholder consultation.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58274","58274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661649","2017-01-09","Ministry of Defence","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what involvement UK armed forces personnel have had in training Saudi armed forces in (a) cluster bomb use, (b) air warfare skills and (c) artillery techniques.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58305","58305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661650","2017-01-09","Ministry of Defence","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he discussed with his Saudi counterpart its recent use of cluster munitions in Yemen in the last six months; and what the outcome of each of those discussions was.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58303","58303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661651","2017-01-09","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to help facilitate collaboration between universities and the private sector.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58322","58322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661652","2017-01-09","Department for Education","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of the value of (a) staffing expenditure, (b) other revenue costs and (c) capital expenditure by her Department and its arms-length bodies in whole or in part in Yorkshire and the Humber in 2016-17.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58318","58318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661653","2017-01-09","Department for Education","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of falling international student numbers on the financial sustainability of the UK university sector.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58320","58320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661654","2017-01-09","Department for Education","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much funding will be available through the digital apprenticeship service in (a) 2017-18, (b) 2018-19 and (c) 2019-20.","Biography information for Hannah Bardell","Hannah Bardell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58224","58224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661655","2017-01-09","Department for Education","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much is planned to be spent on apprenticeships in (a) 2017-18, (b) 2018-19 and (c) 2019-20.","Biography information for Hannah Bardell","Hannah Bardell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58225","58225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661656","2017-01-09","Department for Education","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of recent trends in the number of grandparents providing free childcare for working parents; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58189","58189"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661657","2017-01-09","Department for Education","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to encourage teachers to remain in the UK after they have completed their studies.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58190","58190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661658","2017-01-09","Department for Education","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to ensure special needs places are available for all children who have a statement of need; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58188","58188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661659","2017-01-09","Department for Education","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent discussions she has had with Ofsted on inspections of children's centres.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58292","58292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661660","2017-01-09","Department for Education","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, who the diversity champion is on her departmental board.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58233","58233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661661","2017-01-09","Department for Education","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 19 December 2016 to Question 57119, what stakeholders she has met since 18 August 2016 to discuss mechanisms to ensure that academies and free schools meet the School Food Standards.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58161","58161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661662","2017-01-09","Department for Education","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 16 December 2016 to Question 57119, what progress she has made in ensuring that academies and free schools meet the School Food Standards since the publication of Childhood Obesity: a plan for action.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58160","58160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661663","2017-01-09","Department for Education","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when the Government plans to publish its consultation on the future of children's centres.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58217","58217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661664","2017-01-09","Department for Education","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of early years' practitioners are male.","Biography information for Karl McCartney","Karl McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58218","58218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661665","2017-01-09","Department for Education","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to early-years foundation stage profile results, what number and proportion of children in receipt of the early-years pupil premium achieved (a) a good level of development and (b) at least the expected level across all early-learning goals.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58105","58105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661666","2017-01-09","Department for Education","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answers of 8 December 2016 to Questions 55854 and 55853, on academy closures, for what reasons there is a difference between the number of academies that have been completely closed in those Answers.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58100","58100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661667","2017-01-09","Department for Education","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will bring forward legislative proposals to make provision for age-appropriate personal, social, health and economic education, including sex and relationships education, to be a statutory requirement for all schools; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58120","58120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661668","2017-01-09","Department for Education","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Children and Education's letter to HM Chief Inspector of Education of 25 September 2015, on Ofsted Inspection of Sure Start Children's Centres, what steps she is taking to reinstate the inspection framework for Sure Start children's centres.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58112","58112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661669","2017-01-09","Department for Education","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 8 December 2016 to Question 55973, on school closures, whether the guidance her Department gives to academies on school closure consultations includes advice on pausing such consultations.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58097","58097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661670","2017-01-09","Department for Education","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 8 December 2016 to Question 55973, on school closures, on how many occasions a school closure consultation has been paused and that school subsequently closed down completely since 2015.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58098","58098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661671","2017-01-09","Department for Education","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 8 December 2016 to Question 55973, on school closures, for what reasons she would deem it necessary to pause a school closure consultation.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58099","58099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661672","2017-01-09","Department for Education","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what evaluation her Department has made of the Mental Health Services and Schools Link pilots; and what plans her Department has for those pilots to be extended.","Biography information for Nicky Morgan","Nicky Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58087","58087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661673","2017-01-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the potential effect of the UK leaving the EU on the application in the UK of standards under the REACH  regulation on the sale of chemicals.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58077","58077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661674","2017-01-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what progress her Department has made on the roll-out of Greening Government Commitments for 2016-2020; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58109","58109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661675","2017-01-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of the National Wildlife Crime Unit in tackling wildlife crime and protecting endangered species.","Biography information for David Mackintosh","David Mackintosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58209","58209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661676","2017-01-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when the Government plans to publish a Flood Resilience Review addressing the risks of flooding from surface water.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58126","58126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661677","2017-01-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment she has made of the effect of rising food prices on average household budgets.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58127","58127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661678","2017-01-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to help prevent the hunting to extinction of endangered species.","Biography information for David Mackintosh","David Mackintosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58128","58128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661679","2017-01-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to prohibit the importation of trophies secured from the killing of (a) lions, (b) elephants and (c) other mammals in African countries.","Biography information for David Mackintosh","David Mackintosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58129","58129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661680","2017-01-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to prevent further reductions in the world populations of elephants, rhinos and other species.","Biography information for David Mackintosh","David Mackintosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58130","58130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661681","2017-01-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions she has had with the government of India on the conservation of Asian elephants and the potential merits of banning the use of elephants in tourist attractions.","Biography information for David Mackintosh","David Mackintosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58131","58131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661682","2017-01-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to support the Indian government in protecting Asian elephants.","Biography information for David Mackintosh","David Mackintosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58133","58133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661683","2017-01-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions she has had with her EU counterparts on ensuring elephants are given the highest level of international protection.","Biography information for David Mackintosh","David Mackintosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58134","58134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661684","2017-01-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to promote a ban on trade of captive lion parts.","Biography information for David Mackintosh","David Mackintosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58135","58135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661685","2017-01-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to promote the up-listing of African lions to Appendix 1 of the Convention on International Trade in Endangered Species.","Biography information for David Mackintosh","David Mackintosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58137","58137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661686","2017-01-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to support the Chinese government in protecting tigers.","Biography information for David Mackintosh","David Mackintosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58139","58139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661687","2017-01-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, who the diversity champion is on her departmental board.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58234","58234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661688","2017-01-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, on what the additional £13 million to tackle the illegal wildlife trade announced in her Department's press release, UK leading global fight against illegal wildlife trade, published on 17 November 2016, will be spent.","Biography information for David Mackintosh","David Mackintosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58249","58249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661689","2017-01-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 12 September 2016 to Question 56277, what the evidential basis is for the target figures for 2018 and 2019; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58201","58201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661690","2017-01-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will assess the merits of introducing a deposit return system for plastic bottles.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58340","58340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661691","2017-01-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to paragraph 2.151 and table 1.10 of the Autumn Statement 2015, Cm 9162, how much in planned efficiency savings will fund the capital funding for flood protection in each year from 2016-17 to 2020-21.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58346","58346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661692","2017-01-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the co-sponsored resolution on Sri Lanka at the 30th Session of the UN Human Rights Council held in October 2015, if he will make representations to the government of Sri Lanka to respect its commitments and allow international prosecutors to investigate allegations of violations of international humanitarian law in that country; and if he will encourage his international counterparts to make similar such representations.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58271","58271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661693","2017-01-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what biosecurity standards apply to equipment and construction materials imported into Ascension Island in order to resurface the island runway.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58275","58275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661694","2017-01-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his counterpart in China on sentencing of Drugdra, Lobsang Khedrub, Lobsang Gephel, Lodro, Ta're Kyi, Bonkho Kyi, Tsultrim (Trotsik Tsultrim), Tsultrim (Tsulte), Akyakya and Losang Sonam for their involvement in the Dalai Lama's 80th birthday celebrations.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58314","58314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661695","2017-01-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to protect (a) the Rohingya population in Myanmar and (b) children in that community.","Biography information for Julian Knight","Julian Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58202","58202"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661696","2017-01-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, who the diversity champion is on his departmental board.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58236","58236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661697","2017-01-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will take steps to ensure that British citizens travelling to the Cayman Islands are aware of the practice of farming the Cayman Turtle for use in the tourism industry.","Biography information for David Mackintosh","David Mackintosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58138","58138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661698","2017-01-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Cayman Island counterpart on preventing the practice of farming the Cayman Turtle for meat and tourist entertainment.","Biography information for David Mackintosh","David Mackintosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58136","58136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661699","2017-01-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment the Government has made of Iran's ballistic missile programme.","Biography information for Ian Paisley","Ian Paisley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58172","58172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661700","2017-01-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received on recent violence in Israel and the West Bank.","Biography information for Ian Paisley","Ian Paisley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58173","58173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661701","2017-01-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent reports he has received on renewed tunnel building into Israel by Hamas in Gaza.","Biography information for Ian Paisley","Ian Paisley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58174","58174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661702","2017-01-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent reports he has received on the size of Hezbollah's weapons arsenal.","Biography information for Ian Paisley","Ian Paisley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58175","58175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661703","2017-01-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment the Government has made of the human rights situation in Eritrea.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58206","58206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661704","2017-01-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions she has had with her Indian counterpart on preventing the practice of capturing and breaking young elephants in India for use in the tourism industry.","Biography information for David Mackintosh","David Mackintosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58132","58132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661705","2017-01-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what estimate he has made of the number of UK nationals who have visited Eritrea in the last five years.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58203","58203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661706","2017-01-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how much of his Department's spending falls under the definition of official development assistance in the current financial year.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58125","58125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661707","2017-01-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will take steps to discuss with his international counterparts plans to expedite air drops in Syria.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58123","58123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661708","2017-01-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his counterpart in Saudi Arabia on future arms deals with the UK.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58124","58124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661709","2017-01-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent steps he has taken to provide assistance to Nazanin Zaghari-Ratcliffe.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58088","58088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661710","2017-01-09","Department of Health","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he has taken to raise awareness among clinical commissioning groups of their responsibilities related to the commissioning of bisphosphonates for the indication and prevention of secondary breast cancer.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58086","58086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661711","2017-01-09","Department of Health","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with what frequency his Department assesses the work of the Human Fertilisation and Embryology Authority's regulation of private fertility clinics; and when the last such assessment was conducted.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58092","58092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661712","2017-01-09","Department of Health","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make an assessment of the implications for his Department's policies of the findings on IVF add-on procedures of the report by the Centre for Evidence-based Medicine, Lack of Evidence for interventions offered in UK fertility centres, published on 28 November 2016; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58111","58111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661713","2017-01-09","Department of Health","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the GP Forward Review published in April 2016, how many of the 3,000 mental health therapists will have been employed by the end of each year to 2020.","Biography information for David Mackintosh","David Mackintosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58210","58210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661714","2017-01-09","Department for Education","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what evaluation her Department has made of the Mental Health Services and Schools Link Pilots; and what plans she has to extend those pilots.","Biography information for Nicky Morgan","Nicky Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58211","58211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661715","2017-01-09","Department of Health","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to paragraph 1.4 of the Spending Review and Autumn Statement 2015 on local plans for health and social care integration, what steps the Government and NHS England are taking to ensure that (a) the needs of working age disabled people and (b) outcomes related to independent living are included in those plans.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58219","58219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661716","2017-01-09","Department of Health","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the implications for (a) his and (b) the NHS's policies of the findings of Cancer Research UK's report entitled, Testing times to come: an evaluation of pathology capacity in the UK, published in November 2016.","Biography information for Ian Paisley","Ian Paisley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58176","58176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661717","2017-01-09","Department of Health","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many child amputees there were in each of the past five years.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58214","58214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661718","2017-01-09","Department of Health","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the availability of pathology services.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58212","58212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661719","2017-01-09","Department of Health","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions he has had with Northern Ireland's Minister of Health on the resources available for pathology services.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58213","58213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661720","2017-01-09","Department of Health","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, who the diversity champion is on his departmental board.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58237","58237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661721","2017-01-09","Department of Health","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, who he, his ministerial colleagues and officials have met since 18 August 2016 to discuss Childhood Obesity: a plan for action, published on that date.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58162","58162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661722","2017-01-09","Department of Health","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress has been made in the building of 60 new multi-disciplinary centres for cancer diagnosis, announced by NHS England in January 2015.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58158","58158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661723","2017-01-09","Department of Health","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he plans to implement the cancer diagnosis test self-referral system, proposed by NHS England in January 2015.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58159","58159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661724","2017-01-09","Department of Health","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress has been made in reducing the sugar content of products for babies and young children.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58157","58157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661725","2017-01-09","Department of Health","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when his Department plans to publish the next Tobacco Control Plan for England.","Biography information for Dr Andrew Murrison","Dr Andrew Murrison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58197","58197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661726","2017-01-09","Department of Health","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment has been made and against what criteria of the success of the July 2011 Outcomes Strategy for Chronic Obstructive Pulmonary Disease and Asthma in England.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58226","58226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661727","2017-01-09","Department of Health","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much funding the Government plans to provide to which NHS services in Wansbeck constituency in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58253","58253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661728","2017-01-09","Department of Health","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the estimated life expectancy is for people who earn (a) below and (b) above the average household income.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58254","58254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661730","2017-01-09","Department of Health","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to reduce the disparity in smoking rates between people with and without mental health issues.","Biography information for Dr Andrew Murrison","Dr Andrew Murrison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58196","58196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661731","2017-01-09","Department of Health","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress has been made in implementing the Five Year Forward View commitment to increasing cancer diagnostic capacity.","Biography information for Jo Churchill","Jo Churchill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58198","58198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661732","2017-01-09","Department of Health","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 16 December 2016 to Question 57118, what plans he has to meet (a) the Food Innovation Network and (b) the Agri-Food Technology Council to discuss the delivery of the childhood obesity strategy.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58290","58290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661733","2017-01-09","Department of Health","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps are being taken to ensure physiotherapy is available to people with muscle-wasting conditions at Nottingham University Hospitals NHS Trust as a result of his Department's review of that hospital's therapy service provision.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58258","58258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661734","2017-01-09","Department of Health","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 13 December 2016 to Question 56221, if he will list the seven Enfield practices which have been identified for support under the General Practice Resilience Programme.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58286","58286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661735","2017-01-09","Department of Health","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how the National Diagnostic Capacity Fund will support NHS commissioners and providers to utilise independent sector providers of diagnostic services.","Biography information for Jo Churchill","Jo Churchill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58284","58284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661736","2017-01-09","Department of Health","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many medical assistants he plans to introduce into general practice in each year until 2020.","Biography information for David Mackintosh","David Mackintosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58295","58295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661737","2017-01-09","Department of Health","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department has made an assessment of the potential detriment to patients of NICE postponing until 2018 its decision on the use of bisphosphonates for breast cancer patients.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58296","58296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661738","2017-01-09","Department of Health","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment the Government has made of the role of independent sector providers of diagnostic services in meeting NHS cancer diagnosis targets.","Biography information for Jo Churchill","Jo Churchill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58283","58283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661739","2017-01-09","Department of Health","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of GP practices to receive support in 2016-17 under the General Practice Resilience Programme.","Biography information for David Mackintosh","David Mackintosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58294","58294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661740","2017-01-09","Department of Health","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the value of (a) staffing expenditure, (b) other revenue costs and (c) capital expenditure by his Department and its arms-length bodies in whole or in part in Yorkshire and the Humber in 2016-17.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58319","58319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661741","2017-01-09","Department of Health","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 13 December 2016 to Question 56390, what preparatory work has been done on the public consultation on the availability od homeopathic products in primary care to be announced in due course.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58288","58288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661742","2017-01-09","Cabinet Office","2016-12-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many recorded suicides there have been in York in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58339","58339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661743","2017-01-09","Ministry of Justice","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps she is taking to reduce the incidence of suicide in prisons.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58329","58329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661744","2017-01-09","Home Office","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much funding was allocated to the firearms licensing department of each police authority area in England and Wales in the last 12 months for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mr Ian Liddell-Grainger","Mr Ian Liddell-Grainger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58323","58323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661745","2017-01-09","Home Office","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many police (a) officers and (b) civilian staff were employed in firearms licensing departments in each police authority area in England and Wales in the last 12 months for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mr Ian Liddell-Grainger","Mr Ian Liddell-Grainger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58324","58324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661746","2017-01-09","Home Office","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 8 December 2016 to Question 55996, how many universities do not stick to the rules.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58285","58285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661747","2017-01-09","Home Office","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will take steps to ensure that 16 to 18 year olds are eligible to benefit from the additional £10 million funding for English language teaching for resettled (a) Syrian and (b) other Vulnerable Children's Resettlement Scheme refugees.","Biography information for Caroline Ansell","Caroline Ansell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58261","58261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661748","2017-01-09","Home Office","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Answer of 16 June 2016 to Question 38987, how many complaints have been made under paragraphs 4.5.1.2 and 4.5.1.3 of schedule 2 of the Compass contracts by complaint type and Compass region in each year since 2013.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58248","58248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661749","2017-01-09","Home Office","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many allegations against asylum accommodation users of (a) assault, (b) damage to property and (c) anti-social behaviour have been reported to her Department by G4S in connection with the operation of Compass asylum accommodation contracts since 2013; how many such allegations have been investigated by her Department or another independent body; and what the outcomes were of such investigations.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58149","58149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661750","2017-01-09","Home Office","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, who the diversity champion is on her departmental board.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58238","58238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661751","2017-01-09","Home Office","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many counter terrorism security advisers were employed in each police force in England and Wales in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58117","58117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661752","2017-01-09","Home Office","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans her Department has to introduce a training programme for immigration caseworkers on medical evidence of torture.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58122","58122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661753","2017-01-09","Home Office","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many failed asylum seekers under the age of 18 were deported in December in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58115","58115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661754","2017-01-09","Home Office","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much funding each police force in England and Wales received from her Department to employ counter terrorism security advisers in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58116","58116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661755","2017-01-09","Home Office","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the longest period of time a (a) UK or EEA national and (b) non-EU citizen had to wait during December before passing through border checks at (i) Heathrow, (ii) Gatwick, (iii) Manchester, (iv) Stansted and (v) Luton airports was in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58118","58118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661756","2017-01-09","Home Office","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department has suspended all processing and admission of migrants formerly at Calais.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58113","58113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661757","2017-01-09","Home Office","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many UK ports of entry have fallen below the 95 per cent target for completing border checks on (a) UK and EEA nationals within 25 minutes and (b) non-EU citizens within 45 minutes in December of each year since 2010.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58114","58114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661758","2017-01-09","Department for International Development","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, who the diversity champion is on her departmental board.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58239","58239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661759","2017-01-09","Department for International Development","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent reports she has received on the availability and accessibility of aid routes into Aleppo.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58223","58223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661760","2017-01-09","Department for International Development","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much Official Development Assistance funding was provided to mental health projects in the past three years.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58216","58216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661761","2017-01-09","Department for International Development","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what humanitarian assistance the Government is providing to (a) orphaned children, (b) the elderly, (c) the sick and (d) other vulnerable groups among Syrian civilians.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58222","58222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661762","2017-01-09","Department for International Development","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether the Government plans to undertake additional environmental impact assessments ahead of any further construction works required at St Helena airport.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58276","58276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661763","2017-01-09","Ministry of Justice","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what measures her Department will put in place to provide continued access to court services for people who cannot access those services online after the implementation of the proposals outlined in its Transforming our Justice System consultation paper, published in September 2016.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58200","58200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661764","2017-01-09","Ministry of Justice","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to paragraph 1.5 of her Department's paper on Transforming Our Justice System, published in September 2016, what estimate she has made of the funding required to train and remunerate court staff to make judicial decisions.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58260","58260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661765","2017-01-09","Ministry of Justice","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, who the diversity champion is on her departmental board.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58240","58240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661766","2017-01-09","Ministry of Justice","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many full-time equivalent staff have been employed in county courts in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58145","58145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661767","2017-01-09","Ministry of Justice","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what funding her Department provides for dispute resolution within the justice system; what progress her Department has made in its aim to settle more disputes out of court; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58140","58140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661768","2017-01-09","Ministry of Justice","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how her Department assesses the quality of service provided to it by The Big Word Ltd; and with what frequency such assessments take place.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58170","58170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661769","2017-01-09","Ministry of Justice","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much her Department has spent on developing and testing electronic file covers for magistrates' courts.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58141","58141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661770","2017-01-09","Ministry of Justice","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate she has made of the proportion of cases that will take place in virtual hearings in each jurisdiction in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58142","58142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661771","2017-01-09","Ministry of Justice","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many full-time equivalent staff have been employed in magistrates' courts in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58143","58143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661772","2017-01-09","Ministry of Justice","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many full-time equivalent staff have been employed in Crown courts in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58144","58144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661773","2017-01-09","Ministry of Justice","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what plans her Department has to increase social diversity among magistrates.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr   Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58084","58084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661774","2017-01-09","Ministry of Justice","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what data her Department holds on the socio-economic background of magistrates.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr   Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58085","58085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661775","2017-01-09","Ministry of Justice","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, by what date she plans to introduce a new power of guardianship for the families of missing persons.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58121","58121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661776","2017-01-09","Northern Ireland Office","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, who the diversity champion is on his departmental board.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58241","58241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661777","2017-01-09","Prime Minister","2016-12-19","To ask the Prime Minister, whether she discussed the conflict in Yemen with the Saudi government on (a) 15 September and (b) 7 December 2016.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58301","58301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661779","2017-01-09","Prime Minister","2016-12-19","To ask the Prime Minister, what discussions she has had with the Saudi government on its possession of internationally prohibited munitions.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58302","58302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661780","2017-01-09","Prime Minister","2016-12-19","To ask the Prime Minister, whether she had any individual meetings with (a) leaders and (b) officials from other EU member states during her visit to Brussels for the European Council meeting in December.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58228","58228"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661781","2017-01-09","Scotland Office","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, who the diversity champion is on his departmental board.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58242","58242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661782","2017-01-09","Scotland Office","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what discussions he has had with the Scottish Government regarding jobcentre closure proposals for Glasgow.","Biography information for Stewart Malcolm McDonald","Stewart Malcolm McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58152","58152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661783","2017-01-09","Scotland Office","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, whether his Office was consulted by the Department for Work and Pensions (DWP) on its proposals for the reduction of DWP estate in Glasgow.","Biography information for Stewart Malcolm McDonald","Stewart Malcolm McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58156","58156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661784","2017-01-09","Scotland Office","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what discussions he has had with representatives  of the Scottish Government on support for disabled people who currently rely on services at Castlemilk and Langside jobcentres.","Biography information for Stewart Malcolm McDonald","Stewart Malcolm McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58155","58155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661785","2017-01-09","Department for Transport","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what stake or degree of control the Government retains in Eurostar.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58166","58166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661786","2017-01-09","Department for Transport","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of legislative changes required for (a) the shipping industry, (b) the ports sector and (c) UK seafarers and dock workers once the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58146","58146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661787","2017-01-09","Department for Transport","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with ministerial colleagues on legislative changes required for the maritime services sector once the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58147","58147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661788","2017-01-09","Department for Transport","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what his Department's priorities will be for the maritime sector in negotiations with other EU countries before the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58148","58148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661789","2017-01-09","Department for Transport","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, who the diversity champion is on his departmental board.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58243","58243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661790","2017-01-09","Department for Transport","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to paragraphs 4.82 to 4.84 of the Maritime Growth Study: Keeping the UK competitive in a global market, published 7 September 2015, what actions the Maritime and Coastguard Agency (MCA) has taken to implement the conclusions of the Survey and Inspection Transformation Programme (SITP); and which conclusions from the SITP currently await implementation by the MCA.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58107","58107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661791","2017-01-09","Department for Transport","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he expects the Great Western Railway electrification scheme to be completed.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58103","58103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661792","2017-01-09","Department for Transport","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many Eurostar operating days in each of the last five years have been affected by people on the track.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58164","58164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661793","2017-01-09","Department for Transport","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the cost has been of policing the Eurotunnel and its associated rail services in each of the last five years  .","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58165","58165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661794","2017-01-09","Department for Transport","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what responsibility the Office of Rail and Road has for regulating the operation of Eurostar.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58163","58163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661795","2017-01-09","Department for Transport","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will name each of the external consultants contracted by his Department to carry out work to implement the recommendations of the Maritime Growth Study since September 2015; and what the (a) completion date and (b) value is of each such contract.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58094","58094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661796","2017-01-09","Department for Transport","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, for what reasons he did not exchange his details with the cyclist whom he was involved in a road incident with on 12 October 2016.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58090","58090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661798","2017-01-09","Department for Transport","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the incident between him and a cyclist on 12 October 2016 was reported to his Department's Permanent Secretary.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58091","58091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661799","2017-01-09","Department for Transport","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps the Government is taking to support a resolution of the dispute between Southern Rail and the Rail, Maritime and Transport Union.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58250","58250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661800","2017-01-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many civil servants are working on his Department's response to the consultation, Parking reform: tackling unfair practices.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58287","58287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661801","2017-01-09","Department for Transport","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with organisations representing cyclists since his appointment.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58191","58191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661802","2017-01-09","Department for Transport","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he has taken to improve safety for cyclists since his appointment.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58192","58192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661803","2017-01-09","Department for Transport","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make representations to Network Rail to ensure that it adds disabled access routes into (a) Brookmans Park railway station and (b) other suburban railway stations with limited access.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58270","58270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661804","2017-01-09","Department for Transport","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what criteria his Department uses when assessing whether to withdraw a franchise from a consistently poorly-performing railway operator.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58266","58266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661805","2017-01-09","Department for Transport","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what sanctions other than franchise withdrawal his Department has used to hold poorly performing railway operators to account.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58267","58267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661806","2017-01-09","Department for Transport","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the timetable is for the completion of the Great Western Railway's electrification scheme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58269","58269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661807","2017-01-09","Department for Transport","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, under what circumstances a railway franchise has been withdrawn from a poorly performing operator; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58268","58268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661808","2017-01-09","Department for Transport","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the value of (a) staffing expenditure, (b) other revenue costs and (c) capital expenditure by his Department and its arms-length bodies in whole or in part in Yorkshire and the Humber in 2016-17.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58316","58316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661809","2017-01-09","Department for Transport","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department is in communication with iNHouse Communications Ltd in relation to any ongoing commercial tender process.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58310","58310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661810","2017-01-09","Department for Transport","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department has awarded any commercial contracts to iNHouse Communications Ltd in the last five years.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58311","58311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661811","2017-01-09","Wales Office","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, who the diversity champion is on his departmental board.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58245","58245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661812","2017-01-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, who the diversity champion is on his departmental board.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58246","58246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661813","2017-01-09","HM Treasury","2016-12-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on wages for people in semi and unskilled jobs of changes to the proportion of non-UK nationals entering the adult workforce.","Biography information for John Penrose","John Penrose","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58257","58257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661814","2017-01-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment has been made of recent trends in the level of food poverty in the UK; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58293","58293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661815","2017-01-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the (a) number and (b) value of recoverable hardship payments awarded is.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58277","58277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661816","2017-01-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the total value is of (a) amounts recovered from claimants as recoverable hardship payments and (b) recoverable hardship payments written off due to the recipient being in 26 weeks of continuous qualifying employment in the last 12 months for which figures are available.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58278","58278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661817","2017-01-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether his Department has awarded any commercial contracts to iNHouse Communications Ltd in the last five years.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58309","58309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661818","2017-01-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether his Department is in communication with iNHouse Communications Ltd in relation to any ongoing commercial tender process.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58308","58308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661819","2017-01-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans he has to review the 10-year rule with respect to the prescription for osteoarthritis of the knee in former miners; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58344","58344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661820","2017-01-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of how many (a) parents and (b) lone parents with a youngest child aged three (i) nationally, (ii) by region, (iii) by local authority and (iv) by parliamentary constituency will be expected to look for work if they want to claim universal credit or tax credits from April 2017.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58104","58104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661821","2017-01-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of how many people in the disabled working-age population in the Glasgow South constituency are using services at (a) Castlemilk and (b) Langside jobcentres.","Biography information for Stewart Malcolm McDonald","Stewart Malcolm McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58153","58153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661822","2017-01-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many of his Department's staff are expected to be relocated as a result of proposed jobcentre closures in Glasgow.","Biography information for Stewart Malcolm McDonald","Stewart Malcolm McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58154","58154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661823","2017-01-09","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if the Government will publish a comparative assessment of the effect on the public purse of (a) a full sale, (b) retaining full or partial government ownership and (c) other ownership options of the Green Investment Bank.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58215","58215"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661824","2017-01-09","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, who the diversity champion is on his departmental board.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58229","58229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661825","2017-01-09","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what sanctions are available to his Department should construction of Hinkley Point C run behind schedule or over budget.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58102","58102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661826","2017-01-09","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many proposals have been submitted for the construction of new nuclear power stations since 2000.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58101","58101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661827","2017-01-09","Department for Education","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 13 December 2016 to Question 56452, when she plans to lay a statutory instrument providing that standard student support regulations enable healthcare students to apply for loans; and whether that statutory instruments affirmative will be made by the negative or resolution procedure.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58205","58205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661828","2017-01-09","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will undertake an environmental impact assessment of current and previous activities of the Government's preferred bidder for the UK Green Investment Bank; and if he will publish any such assessment before the sale of the Government's shares is agreed.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58119","58119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661829","2017-01-09","Department for International Trade","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what recent estimate his Department has made of the number of UK-based companies operating in Eritrea.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58207","58207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661830","2017-01-09","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how much is held in the investment reserve funds for the (a) Mineworkers' Pension Scheme and (b) British Coal Staff Superannuation Scheme.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58096","58096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661831","2017-01-09","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will assess the balance of the Mineworkers' Pension Scheme surplus-sharing arrangements.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58345","58345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661832","2017-01-09","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate he has made of the value of (a) staffing expenditure, (b) other revenue costs and (c) capital expenditure by his Department and its arms-length bodies in whole or in part in Yorkshire and the Humber in 2016-17.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58315","58315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661833","2017-01-09","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether a price has been agreed with the operators of Hinkley Point C to cover periods of low demand and oversupply in which the power station may have to stop generating.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58272","58272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661834","2017-01-09","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when he expects to publish the consultation on the Government's industrial strategy.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58321","58321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661835","2017-01-09","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will make it his policy to ensure that the Pubs Code Adjudicator notifies pub tenants of (a) his financial interests in large pub-owning businesses, (b) the size and value of his existing shareholding in Fleurets and (c) the value of loans owned to him by Fleurets.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58342","58342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661836","2017-01-09","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if his Department will publish the evidence collected by the Competition and Markets Authority supporting its compliance review into consumer protection law in the online secondary tickets market which was published on 19 December 2016.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58297","58297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661837","2017-01-09","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether his Department has made an estimate of the potential net benefit of smart meter roll-out in (a) cost savings for suppliers, (b) cost savings for consumers and (c) the transmission system; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for John Penrose","John Penrose","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58256","58256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661838","2017-01-09","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment his Department has made of the local community response to the pre-planning consultations for Bradwell B and Sizewell C Power Stations.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58262","58262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661839","2017-01-09","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what information his Department holds on plans to improve highway infrastructure around the construction sites of Sizewell C to facilitate additional construction traffic; and who will be responsible for funding such improvements.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58263","58263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661840","2017-01-09","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how much funding to which industries in the North East the Government plans to provide (a) over the next three years; and if he will estimate how many jobs will be created by that finding.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58251","58251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661841","2017-01-09","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how he plans to support industries located in the North East that receive funding in the event of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58252","58252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661842","2017-01-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the total amount levied in health and safety fines on businesses since 2014; and what amount has been levied in each business sector.","Biography information for Jo Churchill","Jo Churchill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58199","58199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661844","2017-01-09","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 30 June 2016 to Question 40488, if he will list his Department's director-level diversity champions.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58247","58247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661845","2017-01-09","Department for International Trade","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many foreign direct investment projects there have been into the UK in each six-month period in the last three years.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58220","58220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661846","2017-01-09","HM Treasury","2016-12-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment the Government has made of the potential cost to British exporters of increased red tape in the event of the UK leaving the EU customs union related to (a) quota requirements, (b) rules of origin, (c) inspection certifications, (d) advance cargo declarations and (f) customs checks.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58095","58095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661847","2017-01-09","Department for International Trade","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what his plans are for funding sector-specific (a) trade missions and (b) market research to encourage exports.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58078","58078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661848","2017-01-09","Department for International Trade","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what funding his Department plans to provide to support sector-specific trade delegations to (a) North America, (b) East Asia and (c) South Asia.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58079","58079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661849","2017-01-09","Department for International Trade","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether the Trade Access Programme scheme will continue in 2017-18.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58080","58080"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/661850","2017-01-09","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the Government's policy is on retaining the (a) CE and ATEX marks and (b) UK as a location to certify products for the European market.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 58081","58081"
