"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/808982","2017-12-21","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-12-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 12 December 2017 to Question 118970, on Non-domestic Rates: Liverpool City Region, when he plans to have concluded his considerations of the most effective way to deliver those powers to the Liverpool City Region Mayor.","Biography information for Mike Amesbury","Mike Amesbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120091","120091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/808983","2017-12-21","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-12-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 12 December 2017 to Question 118970 on Non-domestic Rates: Liverpool City Region, what the terms of reference are for his Department’s consideration of the most effective way to deliver those powers the Liverpool City Region Mayor.","Biography information for Mike Amesbury","Mike Amesbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120092","120092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/808984","2017-12-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-12-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government on giving the Liverpool City Region Mayor the power to place a supplement on business rates to fund infrastructure in that region.","Biography information for Mike Amesbury","Mike Amesbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120093","120093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/808985","2018-01-10","Home Office","2017-12-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when her Department plans to publish updated guidance on the use of Public Spaces Protection Orders and Community Protection Notices.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120094","120094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/808986","2017-12-20","HM Treasury","2017-12-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government on giving the Liverpool City Region Mayor the power to place a supplement on business rates to fund infrastructure with the agreement of the local business community through the Local Enterprise Partnership; and what timescale has been agreed for that power being granted.","Biography information for Mike Amesbury","Mike Amesbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120095","120095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/808987","2017-12-20","Department of Health","2017-12-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions or other communications his Department has had with the Action on Smoking and Health or representatives of the All Party Parliamentary Group on Smoking and Health on the proposed tender for tobacco control in England; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120096","120096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/808988","2017-12-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-12-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 15 December 2017 to Question 117837, what estimate his Department has made of the average length of time it takes from a new applicant for universal credit beginning their application and at the point at which their date of entitlement for that credit is triggered.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120097","120097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/808989","2017-12-21","Department of Health","2017-12-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people visited an NHS walk-in centre in each year since 2004-05.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120098","120098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/808990","2017-12-20","Department of Health","2017-12-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of the NHS budget has been spent (a) in the private sector and (b) on contracts awarded to the private sector since May 2010.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120099","120099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/808991","2017-12-21","Department of Health","2017-12-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many times he has met representatives of private healthcare providers since May 2010.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120100","120100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/808992","2017-12-21","Department of Health","2017-12-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much was spent in (a) cash and (b) real terms on child and adolescent mental health services per young person in England in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120101","120101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/808993","2017-12-21","Department of Health","2017-12-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much was spent in (a) cash and (b) real terms on mental health services per head of population in England in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120102","120102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/808994","2017-12-21","Department of Health","2017-12-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which hospitals he or Ministers of his Department have visited in an official capacity in 2017; and what the date was of each such visit.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120103","120103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/808995","2017-12-20","Ministry of Justice","2017-12-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the timetable is for the publication of the consultation on a Domestic Violence and Abuse Bill; and what steps his Department is taking to ensure that measure for the support of children who have witnessed domestic violence and abuse is included within that consultation.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120104","120104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/808996","2017-12-20","Department of Health","2017-12-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which primary care services he or Ministers of his Department have visited in an official capacity in 2016; and what the date was of each such visit.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120105","120105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/808997","2017-12-20","Department of Health","2017-12-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which residential and nursing homes he or Ministers of his Department have visited in an official capacity in 2016; and what the date was of each such visit.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120106","120106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/808998","2017-12-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-12-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he plans to open to public consultation the draft Animal Welfare (Licensing of Activities Involving Animals) Regulations 2018.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120107","120107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/808999","2017-12-20","Department of Health","2017-12-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what enhancement to pay rates officials of his Department receive for working on Saturdays and Sundays.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120108","120108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/809000","2017-12-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-12-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his Saudi Arabian counterpart on the humanitarian situation in Yemen.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120109","120109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/809001","2017-12-20","Department of Health","2017-12-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much Health Education England spent on clinical placements for (a) nursing, (b) midwifery and (c) allied health students in the last three years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120110","120110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/809002","2017-12-20","Department for Transport","2017-12-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he has had discussions with Great Western Railway on improving the connectivity of its on-board free WiFi; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120111","120111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/809003","2017-12-20","Department of Health","2017-12-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the recommendations set out in the Government’s national commitment to improve end of life care will be implemented in full by 2020; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120112","120112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/809004","2017-12-20","Department for International Development","2017-12-18","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent assessment she has made of the long-term economic effect of the International Citizen Service projects on communities in developing countries.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120113","120113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/809005","2017-12-20","Department of Health","2017-12-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of the level of access to mental health services for people with degenerative illnesses.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120114","120114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/809006","2017-12-20","HM Treasury","2017-12-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the value of assets held by the Government in digital currencies is.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120115","120115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/809007","2017-12-20","HM Treasury","2017-12-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the Government has made an estimate of potential savings to the public purse arising from UK taxpayers being able to pay their taxes in digital currencies.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120116","120116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/809008","2017-12-20","HM Treasury","2017-12-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the Government plans to introduce deposit guarantee protections for consumers holding digital currencies.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120117","120117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/809009","2017-12-20","HM Treasury","2017-12-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether under the 4th Money Laundering Directive there are minimum transaction thresholds below which customer due diligence is not required for trade and investment in digital currencies.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120118","120118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/809010","2017-12-21","Department of Health","2017-12-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to ensure that the increases in the number of staff recruited as a result of the Government’s cancer plan are in line with local implementation plans so as to guarantee equality of provision across the country.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120119","120119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/809011","2017-12-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-12-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 12 December 2017 to Question 118243, on Travellers: children, what formal process his Department has in place for local authorities to make requests for the sharing of personal data where the welfare or safeguarding of (a) children and (b) other vulnerable people is concerned.","Biography information for Andrew Selous","Andrew Selous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120120","120120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/809012","2017-12-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-12-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether the current funding system for farm payments will remain in place during the transition period after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120121","120121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/809013","2017-12-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-12-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of the 3 November 2017 to Question 110631, what steps the Government is taking to deliver the framework set out in Improving Lives: Helping Workless Families, published in April 2017.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120122","120122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/809014","2017-12-20","HM Treasury","2017-12-18","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent estimate his Department has made of the number of self-employed households which will benefit from the introduction of tax-free childcare.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120123","120123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/809015","2017-12-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-12-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 7 November 2017 to Question 111137, on local housing allowance, if he will make such an assessment.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120124","120124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/809016","2017-12-20","HM Treasury","2017-12-18","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate his Department has made of the number of low-wage earners who will be financially disadvantaged as a result of the introduction of tax-free childcare.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120125","120125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/809017","2017-12-21","Department of Health","2017-12-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of the 16 November 2017 to Question 112718, what the timetable is for the publication of a response to the consultation on the availability of gluten free foods.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120126","120126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/809018","2017-12-20","HM Treasury","2017-12-18","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assistance is available under the tax-free childcare scheme for families in which a parent (a) becomes unemployed and (b) stops working in order to care for a relative.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120127","120127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/809019","2017-12-20","HM Treasury","2017-12-18","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what financial impact assessment has been made of operating (a) childcare vouchers and (b) tax-free childcare concurrently.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120128","120128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/809020","2017-12-21","Department for Education","2017-12-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 13 November 2017 to Question 112696, if the Government will make an assessment of the potential merits of bringing forward legislative proposals to make the provision of children's centres a statutory requirement for councils.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120129","120129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/809021","2017-12-20","HM Treasury","2017-12-18","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what proportion of (a) public and (b) private sector organisations offer childcare vouchers.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120130","120130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/809022","2017-12-20","HM Treasury","2017-12-18","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what proportion of places of work signed up to the childcare voucher scheme during the last seven years; and how many parents decided to participate in that scheme over that period.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120131","120131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/809023","2017-12-21","Ministry of Defence","2017-12-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the decision making process was for choosing names for the new city class Type 26 frigates and when he expects further names to be released.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120132","120132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/809024","2017-12-21","Ministry of Defence","2017-12-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what representations his Department has received on the naming of one of the new city class Type 26 frigates HMS Exeter.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120133","120133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/809025","2017-12-21","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-12-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of the merits of negotiating with the EU, separately from any trade agreements, an adequacy declaration for data protection.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120134","120134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/809026","2017-12-21","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-12-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, when she plans to start discussions with the European Commission on a new UK-EU model for exchanging and protecting personal data.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120135","120135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/809027","2017-12-21","Department for Education","2017-12-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the retention figures are for newly qualified teachers who began their employment in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120136","120136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/809028","2017-12-21","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2017-12-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether he has identified any factors which could give rise to a hard border between Northern Ireland and the Republic of Ireland and which could be resolved though (i) general EU-UK negotiations or (ii) specific solutions to address the unique circumstances of the island of Ireland; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120137","120137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/809029","2017-12-20","Department for Education","2017-12-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to inform (a) parents and (b) children about the transfer of personal data from local authorities to her Department in the Alternative Provision census from 18 January 2018; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120138","120138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/809030","2017-12-21","Department for Education","2017-12-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to ensure the continued provision of an adequacy of people with cyber security skills into the future.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120139","120139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/809031","2017-12-21","Department of Health","2017-12-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information his Department holds on the number of 999 calls made in the London Borough of Newham in (a) each December and (b) each January since 2010.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120140","120140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/809032","2017-12-21","Department for Education","2017-12-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many requests for releases of children's sensitive personal confidential data at pupil-level from the National Pupil Database have been approved since March 2012.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120141","120141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/809033","2017-12-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-12-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 18 December 2017 to Question 118525, for what reasons his Department has not made an assessment of the changes in the cost of the price of liquid helium in the last 10 years.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120142","120142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/809034","2017-12-20","HM Treasury","2017-12-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many applications from Account Information Services Providers to become registered as a Registered Account Information Service Provider for the purposes of the Second EU Payment Services Directive have been approved by the Financial Conduct Authority; and what the number of such applications submitted to that authority is to date.","Biography information for Julian Knight","Julian Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120143","120143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/809035","2017-12-20","HM Treasury","2017-12-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many applications from Account Information Services Providers in the UK to become registered as a Registered Account Information Service Providers have been accompanied by a personally identifiable information policy in a form considered acceptable by the Financial Conduct Authority; and how many such insurance policies have been rejected by that authority on the grounds of not meeting PSD2 requirements or otherwise not being acceptable.","Biography information for Julian Knight","Julian Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120144","120144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/809036","2017-12-20","HM Treasury","2017-12-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many insurers in the market are providing personally identifiable information policies for Professional Indemnity Insurance Policies in a form considered acceptable by the Financial Conduct Authority and which meets the PSD2 requirement in the UK.","Biography information for Julian Knight","Julian Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120145","120145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/809037","2017-12-21","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-12-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will publish the criteria by which his Department is assessing the adequacy of local authorities' funding for the retrospective fitting of sprinklers in tower blocks.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120146","120146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/809038","2017-12-21","Ministry of Justice","2017-12-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answers of 13 November, 28 November and 14 December 2017 to Questions 112585, 112584 and 118460 on 14 December 2017, on domestic violence: convictions and prosecutions, what that data is by fiscal year.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120147","120147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/809039","2017-12-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-12-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Written Ministerial Statement of 14 December 2017, HCWS356, on employment and support allowance, how many of the 75,000 individuals who were identified as having been underpaid were resident in Scotland at the time of their reassessment for that allowance.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120148","120148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/809040","2017-12-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-12-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Written Ministerial Statement of 14 December 2017, HCWS356, on employment and support allowance, what the average amount is by which the 75,000 individuals identified have been underpaid.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120149","120149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/809041","2017-12-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-12-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Written Ministerial Statement of 14 December 2017, HCWS356, on employment and support allowance, whether the payments in arrears will be up-rated in line with current inflation.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120150","120150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/809042","2017-12-21","Department for Education","2017-12-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the change has been in the number of young people aged 18 to 25 who are not in education, employment or training in the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120151","120151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/809043","2017-12-20","Department of Health","2017-12-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, for what reasons the previously agreed Review of the Clinical Pathway for Sleep Apnoea is no longer included on NICE's priority lists.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120152","120152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/809044","2017-12-20","Department of Health","2017-12-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he plans to publish the Review of the Clinical Pathway for Sleep Apnoea.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120153","120153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/809045","2017-12-20","Department of Health","2017-12-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will assess the potential merits of establishing a national programme to provide fast-track treatment of Obstructive Sleep Apnoea for vocational drivers.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120154","120154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/809046","2017-12-21","Department for International Development","2017-12-18","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to help end childhood deaths from pneumonia globally by 2030.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120155","120155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/809047","2017-12-20","Cabinet Office","2017-12-18","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what recent progress has been made on the inquiry into the contaminated blood scandal.","Biography information for Sir Michael Fallon","Sir Michael Fallon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120156","120156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/809048","2017-12-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-12-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to encourage researchers to continue to make bids for Horizon 2020 funding.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120157","120157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/809049","2017-12-20","Home Office","2017-12-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment she has made of the effectiveness of current firearms legislation in controlling the risk to the public from the legal ownership of firearms.","Biography information for Sir Michael Fallon","Sir Michael Fallon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120158","120158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/809050","2017-12-20","Home Office","2017-12-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent discussions she has had with the Chancellor of the Exchequer on changes to police pay in 2018-19.","Biography information for Sir Michael Fallon","Sir Michael Fallon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120159","120159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/809051","2017-12-21","Ministry of Defence","2017-12-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much has been spent by the RAF from the public purse with (a) Halfords, (b) Screwfix, (c) Wickes, (d) HSS Tool Hire and (e) Maplin by accounting unit in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120160","120160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/809052","2017-12-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-12-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether it is compulsory for local authorities to offer residents a choice of how they wish to receive communications.","Biography information for Sir Michael Fallon","Sir Michael Fallon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120161","120161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/809053","2017-12-21","Cabinet Office","2017-12-18","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of ministerial travel by (a) commercial flights, (b) RAF flights, (c) Eurostar, (d) ferry, (e) road, (f) commercial helicopter in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120162","120162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/809054","2017-12-21","Home Office","2017-12-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what additional funding or resources were provided to South Wales Police in connection with the hosting of the 2017 UEFA Champions League Final.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120163","120163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/809055","2017-12-21","Home Office","2017-12-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many FTE Border Force officials were assigned to (a) ports and (b) airports in Wales in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120164","120164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/809056","2017-12-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-12-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of including a public interest test in the regulatory framework for decisions of the Competition and Markets Authority.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120165","120165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/809057","2017-12-21","Department of Health","2017-12-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department has received any reports of rickets in the Carnforth area in the last five years.","Biography information for David Morris","David Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120166","120166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/809058","2017-12-20","Department for Education","2017-12-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of students with learning difficulties were in full-time employment within one year of leaving that education during the (a) 2014-15, (b) 2015-16 and (c) 2016-17 academic years.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120167","120167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/809059","2017-12-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-12-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what measures are in place to provide support to students with learning difficulties after they leave full-time education.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120168","120168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/809060","2017-12-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-12-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people with learning difficulties have been supported through the Access to Work scheme in (a) 2015, (b) 2016 and (c) 2017.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120169","120169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/809061","2017-12-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-12-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the terms of reference for the SME productivity review will be.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120170","120170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/809062","2017-12-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-12-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment the Government has made of the potential effect of the UK leaving the EU on the work of the Competition and Markets Authority.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120171","120171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/809063","2017-12-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-12-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what criteria the Government used when deciding the six priority areas for the Office of Artificial Intelligence.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120172","120172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/809064","2017-12-21","HM Treasury","2017-12-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, for what reasons the Financial Conduct Authority uses a different definition of Account In formation service Providers to that (a) defined by his Department in the Payment Services Regulations 2017 and (b) set out in the Second Payment Services Directive.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120173","120173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/809065","2017-12-21","HM Treasury","2017-12-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on levels of financial inclusion of the LINK network's recent proposals to reduce the interchange fee paid by banks to independent ATM operators.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120174","120174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/809066","2017-12-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-12-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the (a) remit, (b) membership and (c) reporting requirements of the future sectors team as part of the industrial strategy will be.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120175","120175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/809067","2017-12-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-12-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the Government's Industrial Strategy, how the Department defines world-leading as it applies to (a) technologies and (b) industries.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120176","120176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/809068","2017-12-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-12-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what representations he has received as part of his Department's review of SME productivity.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120177","120177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/809069","2017-12-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-12-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether the Government plans to continue to fund Local Enterprise Partnerships in areas which have Mayoral Combined Authorities.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120178","120178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/809070","2017-12-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-12-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether the Government plans to consult businesses as part of its review of the activities and objectives of Local Enterprise Partnerships.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120179","120179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/809071","2017-12-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-12-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when the Government plans to publish its devolution framework to allow new areas to take advantage of devolution deals.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120180","120180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/809072","2017-12-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-12-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment the Government has made of the potential need to increase funding to the Competition and Markets Authority to enable it to take on new responsibilities after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120181","120181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/809073","2017-12-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-12-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of expanding the remit of the Competition and Markets Authority to create a research and development public interest test for proposed mergers and takeovers.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120182","120182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/809074","2017-12-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-12-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of expanding the remit of the Competition and Markets Authority to ensure that Critical National Infrastructure is protected by a public interest test.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120183","120183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/809075","2017-12-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-12-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to ensure that the Competition and Markets Authority continues to have access to confidential data held by other regulatory bodies (a) within the EU and (b) globally after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120184","120184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/809076","2017-12-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-12-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to enable private sector companies to manage the risks associated with artificial intelligence.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120185","120185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/809077","2017-12-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-12-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of expanding the six priority areas for the Office of Artificial Intelligence to include financial services.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120186","120186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/809078","2017-12-20","HM Treasury","2017-12-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, for what reasons the Financial Conduct Authority uses a different definition of Account Information Service Providers to that used in other EU member states.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120187","120187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/809079","2017-12-20","HM Treasury","2017-12-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions his Department has had with the Financial Conduct Authority and the Open Banking Implementation Entity on ensuring that financial data aggregation platforms that are not defined as Account Information Service Providers can gain direct access to standardised open banking application programming interfaces.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120188","120188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/809080","2017-12-20","HM Treasury","2017-12-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans the Financial Conduct Authority and Open Banking Implementation Entity have to ensure that financial data aggregation platforms that are not defined as Account Information Service Providers can gain direct access to the standardised open banking application programming interfaces.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120189","120189"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/809081","2017-12-20","Department of Health","2017-12-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps the Government is taking to support the NHS roll-out of new and innovative mechanical thrombectomy techniques in the treatment of strokes.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120190","120190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/809082","2017-12-20","Department of Health","2017-12-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps the Government plans to take to (a) promote innovation within the NHS and (b) support existing drives for innovation such as the recently commissioned stroke treatment mechanical thrombectomy.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120191","120191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/809083","2017-12-20","Department of Health","2017-12-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what support his Department provides to NHS England to ensure that NHS Trusts can provide mechanical thrombectomies for the treatment of stroke.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120192","120192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/809084","2017-12-20","Department of Health","2017-12-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of variations in the level of access to mechanical thrombecomy across England, Scotland and Wales; and how his Department plans to address those variations.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120193","120193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/809085","2017-12-20","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-12-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what the level of legal expertise on state aid and competition law is in his Department .","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120194","120194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/809086","2017-12-20","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2017-12-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether he plans for a new regime for state aid and competition rules to be covered by a future deal between the UK and the EU.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120195","120195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/809087","2017-12-20","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-12-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps she is taking to promote the portability of personal data between different digital platforms.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120196","120196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/809088","2017-12-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-12-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the potential quantum for changes in the workload of the Competition and Markets Authority after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120197","120197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/809089","2017-12-20","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2017-12-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of levels of expertise in respect of competition policy in officials engaged in negotiating the deal between the UK and the EU.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120198","120198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/809090","2017-12-21","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-12-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he has taken to ensure that the advice given to the hon. Member for Christchurch by his officials on 7 November 2017 about council tax equalisation and harmonisation is consistent with advice given by his officials to local government officers in Dorset.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120199","120199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/809091","2017-12-21","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-12-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will advise local authorities considering local government reorganisation that no exit payments for local government officers resulting from any such reorganisation should exceed £95,000; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120200","120200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/809092","2017-12-21","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-12-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answers of 18 December 2017 to Questions 119513 and 119514, on council tax: Dorset, on what dates officials of his Department received the request from Dorset Council; and if he will place a copy of that request in the Library.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120201","120201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/809093","2017-12-21","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-12-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 18 December 2017 to Question 119516, whether changes to financial information since December 2016 including that resulting from a reduced or zero period for equalisation and harmonisation are required during the current representation period.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120202","120202"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/809094","2017-12-21","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-12-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 18 December 2017 to Questions 119513 and 119514, on what date he first made public the factor of not allowing residents in one predecessor area to become concerned that they are effectively contributing more to the cost of services than others in the area; and what the maximum period is for harmonisation and equalisation which could satisfy that factor.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120203","120203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/809095","2017-12-20","Department of Health","2017-12-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of the number of trained interventional neuroradiologists to perform mechanical thrombectomies.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120204","120204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/807150","2017-12-20","Department for Education","2017-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which local authorities have contracted out their adoption services to a third party;  and what the name is of each such contractor.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119798","119798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/807151","2017-12-20","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, if her Department will take steps to cover the legal costs of UK  Anti-Doping as part of the ongoing tailored review.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119799","119799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/807152","2017-12-19","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if his Department will make an assessment of the adequacy of funding available to local authorities for the retrospective fitting of sprinklers in tower blocks; and if he will publish the criteria to be used in that assessment.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119800","119800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/807153","2017-12-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether he has any plans to address the loyalty penalty in essential markets.","Biography information for Patricia Gibson","Patricia Gibson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119801","119801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/807154","2017-12-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what discussions he has had with regulators on the loyalty penalty faced by consumers who don't switch provider.","Biography information for Patricia Gibson","Patricia Gibson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119802","119802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/807155","2017-12-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 12 December 2017 to Question 118073, if he will list the requests received by Manchester City Council.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119803","119803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/807156","2017-12-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 11 December 2017 to Question 117510, what discussions his Department has had with Ofwat to ensure that water and sewerage companies adopt the latest technology in leakage detection and that such technology provides value for money.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119804","119804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/807157","2017-12-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to his Department's publication ADM Memo 30/17, if he will publish the criteria used in the LEAP exercise to review awards of personal independent payment claimants who may be affected by the updated PIP Assessment Guidance detailed in the Written Statement of 2 November 2017, HCWS218.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119805","119805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/807158","2017-12-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Written Statement of 2 November 2017, HCWS218, whether previous personal independence payment applicants who may benefit from the update to PIP Assessment Guidance but whose applications were unsuccessful before 9 March 2017 should (a) reapply for PIP, (b) await contact from his Department regarding their claims or (c) request a review of their initial claim in light of the updated guidance.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119806","119806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/807159","2017-12-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to table 8D of the Personal Independence Payment: DLA to PIP reassessment outcomes, October 2017, what steps his Department is taking to address the disproportionate number of people with epilepsy who have seen their awards refused or reduced during the transition to personal independence payments; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119807","119807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/807160","2017-12-19","Ministry of Justice","2017-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will make it his policy for there to be a review of the options for law reform to ensure that large companies and financial institutions can be prosecuted for economic crime in the UK.","Biography information for Dr Rupa Huq","Dr Rupa Huq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119808","119808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/807161","2017-12-19","Ministry of Justice","2017-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what plans he has to publish a call for evidence on the need for legal reform to extend corporate criminal liability beyond bribery and tax evasion.","Biography information for Dr Rupa Huq","Dr Rupa Huq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119809","119809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/807162","2017-12-19","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when she plans to create a public register showing the beneficial owners of overseas legal entities which (a) own or buy property in the UK and (b) secure contracts from central Government.","Biography information for Dr Rupa Huq","Dr Rupa Huq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119810","119810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/807163","2017-12-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his counterparts in the UK Overseas Territories on the adoption of public registers of beneficial ownership in the UK Overseas Territories.","Biography information for Dr Rupa Huq","Dr Rupa Huq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119811","119811"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/807164","2017-12-19","Department for International Development","2017-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what measures she is taking to promote the adoption of public registers of beneficial ownership in other countries.","Biography information for Dr Rupa Huq","Dr Rupa Huq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119812","119812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/807165","2017-12-19","Home Office","2017-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions she has had with the Foreign Secretary on the active enforcement of the OECD Anti Bribery Convention.","Biography information for Dr Rupa Huq","Dr Rupa Huq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119813","119813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/807166","2017-12-19","Home Office","2017-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions she has had with the Secretary of State for International Trade on the promotion of anti-corruption measures through bilateral trade deals.","Biography information for Dr Rupa Huq","Dr Rupa Huq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119814","119814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/807167","2017-12-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what (a) multilateral and (b) bilateral initiatives he has taken to counter the illegal wildlife trade.","Biography information for Dr Rupa Huq","Dr Rupa Huq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119815","119815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/807168","2017-12-19","Home Office","2017-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 14 December 2017 to Question 117953,  whether her Department has access to operational details of requests made by UK law enforcement authorities for beneficial ownership information.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119816","119816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/807169","2017-12-20","Home Office","2017-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 8 September 2017 to Question 6341, when she expects to make a decision on fees for firearm and shotgun licences administered by the police.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119817","119817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/807170","2017-12-20","Scotland Office","2017-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, pursuant to the Answer of 6 September 2017 to Question 6287, what external advisers or companies his Department has used for advertising in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119818","119818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/807171","2017-12-19","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, under what powers the property of a person who is street homeless can be confiscated.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119819","119819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/807172","2017-12-19","Prime Minister","2017-12-15","To ask the Prime Minister, pursuant to the Answer of 12 December 2017 to Question 117199, what reports the Prime Minister receives from the delegate who attends a British-Irish Council on behalf of the Government following each meeting.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119820","119820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/807173","2017-12-19","Prime Minister","2017-12-15","To ask the Prime Minister, pursuant to the Answer of 12 December 2017 to Question 117199, if she will make it her policy to attend a meeting of the British-Irish Council when other heads of Government of the UK and the Republic of Ireland are in attendance.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119821","119821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/807174","2017-12-19","Prime Minister","2017-12-15","To ask the Prime Minister, pursuant to the Answer of 12 December 2017 to Question 117199, for what reasons a Prime Minister has not attended a meeting of the British-Irish Council since 2007.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119822","119822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/807175","2017-12-20","Cabinet Office","2017-12-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will publish the contract between the Government and Amazon Web Services covering Platform as a service.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119823","119823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/807176","2017-12-19","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of the potential implications of Disney's takeover of 21st Century Fox for the Competition and Markets Authority's investigation into the anticipated acquisition of Sky Plc by 21st Century Fox; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119824","119824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/807177","2017-12-20","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether she has made an assessment of the comprehensiveness and quality of Ofcom’s quarterly telecoms complaints data in terms of enabling consumers to make informed decisions; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119825","119825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/807178","2017-12-20","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether she has made an assessment of the potential merits of including data from Alternative Dispute Resolution schemes in Ofcom’s quarterly telecoms complaints data in order to enable consumers to make better informed decisions; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119826","119826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/807179","2017-12-19","Department of Health","2017-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people with cystic fibrosis have been prescribed Orkambi in (a) England and (b) Wales in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119827","119827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/807180","2017-12-19","Department of Health","2017-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with cystic fibrosis charities on the effectiveness of Orkambi.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119828","119828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/807181","2017-12-19","Home Office","2017-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make the non-emergency police phone number 101 a free-to-use service.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119829","119829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/807182","2017-12-19","Prime Minister","2017-12-15","To ask the Prime Minister, with reference to her oral contribution of 14 December 2017, Official Report, column 398, in what format she was briefed on the content of the Chancellor of the Exchequer’s oral evidence to the Treasury Committee of 6 December 2017.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119830","119830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/807183","2017-12-19","Home Office","2017-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department has examined the Canadian Provincial Nominee Programme scheme as part of its policy planning for a new UK immigration system after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Ged Killen","Ged Killen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119831","119831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/807186","2017-12-19","Home Office","2017-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many meetings she has had with Scottish Government Ministers on the Government's proposed reforms to the UK's immigration system after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Ged Killen","Ged Killen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119832","119832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/807187","2017-12-19","Home Office","2017-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department has made an assessment of the potential merits of reforming the immigration system with a view to increasing working age populations in regions where growth in that demographic has halted or is in decline; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Ged Killen","Ged Killen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119833","119833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/807188","2017-12-19","Home Office","2017-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which Scottish business sectors have made representations to her on immigration schemes for Scotland after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Ged Killen","Ged Killen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119834","119834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/807189","2017-12-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the Answer of 3 April 2017 to Question HL6413, on horses: animal welfare, what the timetable is for the update to that code of practice.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119835","119835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/807190","2017-12-19","Department for Transport","2017-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make it his policy in the forthcoming cycle safety review to include the Dutch Reach within the driving test to help reduce the number of serious injuries and deaths from the car-dooring of cyclists.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119836","119836"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/807191","2017-12-19","Department of Health","2017-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the commercial agreement announced by NHS England on 9 November 2017, what the timetable is for NICE to issue final guidance on Perjeta (pertuzumab) in combination with Herceptin (trastuzumab) and docetaxel for HER2 positive metastatic or locally recurrent unresectable breast cancer.","Biography information for Craig Tracey","Craig Tracey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119837","119837"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/807192","2017-12-19","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 15 December 2017 to Question 118099, for what reasons no reference was made as to whether support to small businesses forming part of the Government's assistance to small businesses as the UK leaves the EU was to be financial or just other support.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119838","119838"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/807193","2017-12-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to help reduce rising levels of plastic in the oceans.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119839","119839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/807194","2017-12-19","Home Office","2017-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 12 December 2017 to Question 118324, for what reasons no reference was made to the evidential basis for the recruitment of an additional 300 Border Force officers.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119840","119840"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/807195","2017-12-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many staff of his Department are responsible for dealing with reducing the levels of plastic in the oceans.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119841","119841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/807196","2017-12-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment the Government has made of potential human health hazards posed by rising levels of plastic in the oceans.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119842","119842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/807197","2017-12-19","Department for Education","2017-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 13 December 2017 to Question 117570, what steps her Department plans to take to increase social mobility in areas of Good and Outstanding Ofsted rated schools.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119843","119843"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/807198","2017-12-20","Department for Education","2017-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what has been the cost-per-child of children's school meals in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119844","119844"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/807199","2017-12-19","Attorney General","2017-12-15","To ask the Attorney General, what steps his offices are taking to implement the guidance set out by the Government Commercial Function in its paper entitled Exiting Major IT Contracts: Guidance for Departments, published in November 2017, in respect of (a) using market engagement, (b) setting up disaggregation work, (c) risk assessment, (d) developing a programme plan through the transition, (e) identifying the skills and capabilities that will be needed in the future and (f) any other work related to that guidance.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119845","119845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/807200","2017-12-19","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department is taking to implement the guidance set out by the Government Commercial Function in its paper entitled Exiting Major IT Contracts: Guidance for Departments, published in November 2017, in respect of (a) using market engagement, (b) setting up disaggregation work, (c) risk assessment, (d) developing a programme plan through the transition, (e) identifying the skills and capabilities that will be needed in the future and (f) any other work related to that guidance.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119846","119846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/807201","2017-12-19","Cabinet Office","2017-12-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps his Department is taking to implement the guidance set out by the Government Commercial Function in its paper entitled Exiting Major IT Contracts: Guidance for Departments, published in November 2017, in respect of (a) using market engagement, (b) setting up disaggregation work, (c) risk assessment, (d) developing a programme plan through the transition, (e) identifying the skills and capabilities that will be needed in the future and (f) any other work related to that guidance.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119847","119847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/807202","2017-12-19","Ministry of Defence","2017-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to implement the guidance set out by the Government Commercial Function in its paper entitled Exiting Major IT Contracts: Guidance for Departments, published in November 2017, in respect of (a) using market engagement, (b) setting up disaggregation work, (c) risk assessment, (d) developing a programme plan through the transition, (e) identifying the skills and capabilities that will be needed in the future and (f) any other work related to that guidance.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119848","119848"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/807203","2017-12-19","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport,  what steps her Department is taking to implement the guidance set out by the Government Commercial Function in its paper entitled Exiting Major IT Contracts: Guidance for Departments, published in November 2017, in respect of (a) using market engagement, (b) setting up disaggregation work, (c) risk assessment, (d) developing a programme plan through the transition, (e) identifying the skills and capabilities that will be needed in the future and (f) any other work related to that guidance.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119849","119849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/807204","2017-12-19","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to implement the guidance set out by the Government Commercial Function in its paper entitled Exiting Major IT Contracts: Guidance for Departments, published in November 2017, in respect of (a) using market engagement, (b) setting up disaggregation work, (c) risk assessment, (d) developing a programme plan through the transition, (e) identifying the skills and capabilities that will be needed in the future and (f) any other work related to that guidance.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119850","119850"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/807205","2017-12-19","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what steps his Department is taking to implement the guidance set out by the Government Commercial Function in its paper entitled Exiting Major IT Contracts: Guidance for Departments, published in November 2017, in respect of (a) using market engagement, (b) setting up disaggregation work, (c) risk assessment, (d) developing a programme plan through the transition, (e) identifying the skills and capabilities that will be needed in the future and (f) any other work related to that guidance.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119851","119851"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/807206","2017-12-19","Department for Education","2017-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education,  what steps her Department is taking to implement the guidance set out by the Government Commercial Function in its paper entitled Exiting Major IT Contracts: Guidance for Departments, published in November 2017, in respect of (a) using market engagement, (b) setting up disaggregation work, (c) risk assessment, (d) developing a programme plan through the transition, (e) identifying the skills and capabilities that will be needed in the future and (f) any other work related to that guidance.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119852","119852"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/807207","2017-12-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to implement the guidance set out by the Government Commercial Function in its paper entitled Exiting Major IT Contracts: Guidance for Departments, published in November 2017, in respect of (a) using market engagement, (b) setting up disaggregation work, (c) risk assessment, (d) developing a programme plan through the transition, (e) identifying the skills and capabilities that will be needed in the future and (f) any other work related to that guidance.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119853","119853"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/807208","2017-12-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs,  what steps his Department is taking to implement the guidance set out by the Government Commercial Function in its paper entitled Exiting Major IT Contracts: Guidance for Departments, published in November 2017, in respect of (a) using market engagement, (b) setting up disaggregation work, (c) risk assessment, (d) developing a programme plan through the transition, (e) identifying the skills and capabilities that will be needed in the future and (f) any other work related to that guidance.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119854","119854"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/807209","2017-12-19","Department of Health","2017-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health,  what steps his Department is taking to implement the guidance set out by the Government Commercial Function in its paper entitled Exiting Major IT Contracts: Guidance for Departments, published in November 2017, in respect of (a) using market engagement, (b) setting up disaggregation work, (c) risk assessment, (d) developing a programme plan through the transition, (e) identifying the skills and capabilities that will be needed in the future and (f) any other work related to that guidance.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119855","119855"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/807210","2017-12-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department has taken to halt the decline of the Aquatic Warbler, Marsh Warbler, Wood Warbler and Savi's Warbler over the last five years.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119856","119856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/807211","2017-12-19","Department for International Development","2017-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development,  what steps her Department is taking to implement the guidance set out by the Government Commercial Function in its paper Exiting Major IT Contracts: Guidance for Departments, published in November 2017, in respect of (a) using market engagement, (b) setting up disaggregation work, (c) risk assessment, (d) developing a programme plan through the transition, (e) identifying the skills and capabilities that will be needed in the future and (f) any other work related to that guidance.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119857","119857"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/807212","2017-12-19","Department for International Trade","2017-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps his Department is taking to implement the guidance set out by the Government Commercial Function in its paper entitled Exiting Major IT Contracts: Guidance for Departments, published in November 2017, in respect of (a) using market engagement, (b) setting up disaggregation work, (c) risk assessment, (d) developing a programme plan through the transition, (e) identifying the skills and capabilities that will be needed in the future and (f) any other work related to that guidance.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119858","119858"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/807213","2017-12-19","Department for Transport","2017-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport,  what steps his Department is taking to implement the guidance set out by the Government Commercial Function in its paper entitled Exiting Major IT Contracts: Guidance for Departments, published in November 2017, in respect of (a) using market engagement, (b) setting up disaggregation work, (c) risk assessment, (d) developing a programme plan through the transition, (e) identifying the skills and capabilities that will be needed in the future and (f) any other work related to that guidance.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119859","119859"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/807214","2017-12-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions,  what steps his Department is taking to implement the guidance set out by the Government Commercial Function in its paper entitled Exiting Major IT Contracts: Guidance for Departments, published in November 2017, in respect of (a) using market engagement, (b) setting up disaggregation work, (c) risk assessment, (d) developing a programme plan through the transition, (e) identifying the skills and capabilities that will be needed in the future and (f) any other work related to that guidance.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119860","119860"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/807215","2017-12-19","HM Treasury","2017-12-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer,  what steps I) his Department and ii) HMRC is taking to implement the guidance set out by the Government Commercial Function in its paper entitled Exiting Major IT Contracts: Guidance for Departments, published in November 2017, in respect of (a) using market engagement, (b) setting up disaggregation work, (c) risk assessment, (d) developing a programme plan through the transition, (e) identifying the skills and capabilities that will be needed in the future and (f) any other work related to that guidance.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119861","119861"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/807216","2017-12-19","Home Office","2017-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to implement the guidance set out by the Government Commercial Function in its paper entitled Exiting Major IT Contracts: Guidance for Departments, published in November 2017, in respect of (a) using market engagement, (b) setting up disaggregation work, (c) risk assessment, (d) developing a programme plan through the transition, (e) identifying the skills and capabilities that will be needed in the future and (f) any other work related to that guidance.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119862","119862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/807217","2017-12-19","Ministry of Justice","2017-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice,  what steps his Department is taking to implement the guidance set out by the Government Commercial Function in its paper entitled Exiting Major IT Contracts: Guidance for Departments, published in November 2017, in respect of (a) using market engagement, (b) setting up disaggregation work, (c) risk assessment, (d) developing a programme plan through the transition, (e) identifying the skills and capabilities that will be needed in the future and (f) any other work related to that guidance.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119863","119863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/807218","2017-12-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 12 December 2017 to Question 116788, how many households from (a) Barandon Walk, (b) Hurstway Walk, (c) Testerton Walk, (d) Treadgold House, (e) Bramley House and (f) other surrounding blocks in the Lancaster West Estate remain in emergency accommodation following the Grenfell Tower fire.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119864","119864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/807219","2017-12-19","Department for Transport","2017-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, on how many occasions West Coast Mainline services were suspended in (a) 2015, (b) 2016 and (c) 2017.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119865","119865"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/807220","2017-12-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 12 December 2017 to Question 116791, if he will provide details of the (a) times, (b) dates and (c) attendees of the meetings that have taken place between his Department and representatives from the Royal Borough of Kensington and Chelsea on allowing council tenants who formerly resided in Grenfell Tower to retain the right to buy.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119866","119866"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/807221","2017-12-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to his answer of 12 December 2017 to Question 116791, when he expects a resolution to the outstanding issues regarding council tenants who formerly resided in Grenfell Tower retaining the right to buy.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119867","119867"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/807222","2017-12-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the regulatory framework is which is used to accredit Green Deal Assessors; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Paul Sweeney","Mr Paul Sweeney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119868","119868"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/807223","2017-12-19","Department of Health","2017-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to raise awareness of Charles Bonnet Syndrome among NHS trust clinicians.","Biography information for Dr Rupa Huq","Dr Rupa Huq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119869","119869"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/807224","2017-12-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many companies accredited under the Green Deal were subsequently investigated for breaches of the Green Deal Code of Practice.","Biography information for Mr Paul Sweeney","Mr Paul Sweeney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119870","119870"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/807225","2017-12-19","HM Treasury","2017-12-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent estimate his Department has made of the number of parents under the Childcare Voucher scheme who will not be eligible for Tax-Free Childcare.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119871","119871"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/807226","2017-12-19","HM Treasury","2017-12-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans he has to provide support to parents who benefit from the Childcare Voucher scheme but who are not eligible for the Tax-Free Childcare scheme.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119872","119872"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/807227","2017-12-19","HM Treasury","2017-12-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what reports he has received on the number of people who have experienced technical problems with the Childcare Service site in accessing Tax-Free Childcare.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119873","119873"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/807228","2017-12-19","HM Treasury","2017-12-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of the replacement of Childcare Vouchers with Tax-free Childcare on basic rate tax payers with child-care costs of £4000 or less per annum.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119874","119874"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/807229","2017-12-20","Home Office","2017-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, for what reasons section 50 of the Crime and Courts Act 2013 has not been commenced in Scotland.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119875","119875"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/807230","2017-12-20","Home Office","2017-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the timetable is for the commencement of section 50 of the Crime and Courts Act 2013 in Scotland.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119876","119876"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/807231","2017-12-20","Home Office","2017-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions she has had with the Lord Advocate on the commencement of section 50 of the Crime and Courts Act 2013 in Scotland.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119877","119877"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/807232","2017-12-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he plans to bring forward proposals to support smaller scale fleets in the UK by allocating fishing rights according to social and ecological criteria; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Holly Lynch","Holly Lynch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119878","119878"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/807233","2017-12-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he plans to discuss with major supermarket chains a proposal to make surplus food available to the food-hungry and to food banks instead of its being treated as food waste; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119879","119879"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/807234","2017-12-20","Home Office","2017-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she plans to introduce legislative proposals to protect abortion clinics from on-going demonstrations outside their premises; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119880","119880"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/807235","2017-12-19","Department for Education","2017-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 15 December 21017 to Question 117797, for what reasons her Department has not set a target for the uptake of apprenticeships over the year following the introduction of the Apprenticeship Levy.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119881","119881"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/807236","2017-12-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what role the devolved assemblies will play in the UK’s new pesticide regulatory regime after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119882","119882"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/807237","2017-12-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if his Department will include in its 25-year plan for the environment an objective to reduce the UK’s use of pesticides.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119883","119883"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/807238","2017-12-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to assess the costs of ill health caused by exposure to pesticides in the UK.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119884","119884"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/807239","2017-12-19","Department of Health","2017-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department plans to undertake or commission research into low dose and combinatory effects of pesticide exposure; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119885","119885"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/807240","2017-12-19","Department of Health","2017-12-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of trends in children's mental health; and what step he is taking to tackle mental ill health among children.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119886","119886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/805297","2017-12-14","Department for International Trade","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what discussions he has had with his international counterparts on the barring of civil society groups from this year's WTO summit; and if he will make statement.","Biography information for Chris Williamson","Chris Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 118969","118969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806413","2017-12-14","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-12-14","Whether his Department is preparing contingency plans for use across Government in the event of there being no deal on the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Eddie Hughes","Eddie Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 902948","902948"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806414","2017-12-14","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-12-14","What recent discussions he has had with representatives of the UK financial sector on the effect on that sector of the UK leaving the single market.","Biography information for Christine Jardine","Christine Jardine","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 902951","902951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806415","2017-12-14","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-12-14","What assessment the Government has made of the effect on the UK economy of the (a) European Medicines Agency and (b) European Banking Authority relocating from London to other EU countries.","Biography information for Marsha De Cordova","Marsha De Cordova","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 902952","902952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806444","2017-12-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to the Government of the People's Republic of China on the treatment of refugees from North Korea in China.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119520","119520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806445","2017-12-18","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, if she will make an assessment of the effect of fixed-odds betting terminals on gambling addiction rates in Midlothian constituency in the last three years.","Biography information for Danielle Rowley","Danielle Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119521","119521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806446","2017-12-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make a statement on the outcome of the 36th Annual Meeting of the Commission for the Conservation of Antarctic Marine Living Resources.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119522","119522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806447","2017-12-19","Department for Education","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether there are any contingency plans for a replacement for the ERASMUS+ scheme for UK Universities in the event that the UK does not renegotiate access to ERASMUS+.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119523","119523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806448","2017-12-18","Department for Transport","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect of the new Lower Thames Crossing on traffic congestion on the (a) A229 (b) A249 (c) M2 Junctions 3, 5 and 7.","Biography information for Helen Whately","Helen Whately","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119524","119524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806449","2017-12-18","Department for Education","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of care leavers were (a) UK and (b) non-UK EU nationals in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119525","119525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806450","2017-12-18","Department for Education","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of initial teacher training at (a) primary and (b) secondary level is related to children with special educational needs and disabilities.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119526","119526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806451","2017-12-19","Department for International Trade","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what his policy is on engagement by the UK defence industry with the proposed European Defence Industrial Development Programme (a) before and (b) after the UK leaves the EU; and whether he has made an assessment of the potential effect of that programme on his Department's policies.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119527","119527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806452","2017-12-19","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what steps he is taking to ensure that the terms of the UK's new partnership with the EU after March 2019 enable the UK to reach new free trade agreements with non-EU countries; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119528","119528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806453","2017-12-18","Home Office","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much has been raised by the Immigration Health Surcharge for the NHS in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119529","119529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806454","2017-12-18","Department of Health","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to ensure that private abortion providers give clients adequate time to make their own decisions on abortion; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119530","119530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806455","2017-12-18","Department of Health","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether homeless people are able to register with the GP at hand service.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119531","119531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806456","2017-12-19","Ministry of Justice","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when his Department was made aware of reports that 15,000 meetings between offenders and the London Community Rehabilitation Company had been missed.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119532","119532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806457","2017-12-19","Ministry of Justice","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will publish the analysis conducted by his Department and HM Treasury on the financial implications of community sentences for women.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119533","119533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806458","2017-12-19","Ministry of Justice","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether he has been made aware of allegations of Community Rehabilitation Companies falsifying records, other than the London Community Rehabilitation Company.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119534","119534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806459","2017-12-18","Department for Education","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment her Department has made of the effect of the number of hours worked on teachers’ job satisfaction.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119535","119535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806460","2017-12-19","Ministry of Justice","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the change has been to the prisons budget in real terms in each year since 2010; and what the projected change will be in real terms in each year to 2022.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119536","119536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806461","2017-12-18","Ministry of Justice","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the change in the number of full-time equivalent staff employed by private probation firms since 2016.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119537","119537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806462","2017-12-18","Department of Health","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many external medical appointments have been missed by prisoners due to insufficient numbers of prison staff in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119538","119538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806463","2017-12-19","Ministry of Justice","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prison officers have been deployed on detached duty in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119539","119539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806464","2017-12-18","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 7 December 2017 to Question 116715, if he will list the levies that were imposed on non-exempted industries and consumers as a result of compensation paid to Energy Intensive Industries in respect of payments under (a) Contracts for Difference under the Electricity Supplier Obligations (Amendment & Excluded Electricity) Regulations 2015 and (b) the Renewables Obligation.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119540","119540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806465","2017-12-19","Department for Education","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference the Oral Answer of the Prime Minister of 6 December 2017, Official Report, column 1023, what assessment her Department has made of which local authorities are operating the 30 hours of funded childcare policy effectively.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119541","119541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806466","2017-12-18","House of Commons Commission","2017-12-14","To ask the right hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington, representing the House of Commons Commission, pursuant to the Answer of 30 November 2017 to Question HL3576, what steps he is taking to strengthen the families of Members and staff working in Parliament.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119542","119542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806467","2017-12-18","Cabinet Office","2017-12-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, to which legislation his Department has applied the Family Test, published in August 2014.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119543","119543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806468","2017-12-19","Department of Health","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which prescription drugs increased proportionately the most in cost to the public purse in each of the last 10 years for which data is available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119544","119544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806469","2017-12-19","Ministry of Justice","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what discussions he has had on ensuring that restraining orders remain legally enforceable across the EU after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119545","119545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806470","2017-12-18","Department of Health","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the reasons for recent changes in the number of (a) educational psychologists, (b) NHS psychiatrists and (c) school nurses.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119546","119546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806471","2017-12-18","Home Office","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what relationship the Government has with (a) Cifas and (b) other fraud prevention organisations; and what steps the Government has taken to regulate the operation of such organisations.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119547","119547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806472","2017-12-19","Department for Education","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 12 December 2017 to Question 118327 on Children: Day Care, and with reference to the Early years national funding formula updated on 17 November 2017, whether the funding rates for financial year 2018-19  will be (a) amended or (b) if further funding will be announced later in December 2017.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119548","119548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806473","2017-12-18","Department for Education","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will take steps during the absence of a devolved administration to hold discussions with the Permanent Secretary on the best way to allocate the apprenticeship levy to maximum effect for promoting skills among young people.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119549","119549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806474","2017-12-19","Department of Health","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate the Government has made of how many more people will access mental health treatment between 2017 and 2020.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119550","119550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806475","2017-12-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the average monthly total amount per person, comprising employee employer and tax relief contributions, paid into pensions under the compulsory workplace pension scheme in 2017.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119551","119551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806476","2017-12-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent discussions he has had with Atos on making improvements to how that provider conducts personal independence payment assessments for people with a haematological disease; and what steps that provider is taking to improve such assessments.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119552","119552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806477","2017-12-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent discussions he has had with Capita on making improvements to how that provider conducts personal independence payment assessments for people with an infectious disease; and what steps that provider is taking to improve such assessments.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119553","119553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806478","2017-12-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent discussions he has had with Maximus on making improvements to how that provider conducts employment and support allowance assessments for people with a skin disease; and what steps that provider is taking to improve such assessments.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119554","119554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806479","2017-12-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent discussions he has had with Maximus on making improvements to how that provider conducts employment and support allowance assessments for people with a musculoskeletal disease; and what steps that provider is taking to improve such assessments.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119555","119555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806480","2017-12-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent discussions he has had with Maximus on making improvements to how that provider conducts employment and support allowance assessments for people with an injury; and what steps that provider is taking to improve such assessments.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119556","119556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806481","2017-12-18","HM Treasury","2017-12-14","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether HM Revenue and Customs uses fully automated processes to (a) calculate under or overpayments of tax and (b) notify taxpayers of such under or overpayments of tax..","Biography information for Darren Jones","Darren Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119557","119557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806482","2017-12-18","HM Treasury","2017-12-14","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether HM Revenue and Customs has sent any inaccurate notifications of under or over payments of tax due to the use of fully automated processes.","Biography information for Darren Jones","Darren Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119558","119558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806483","2017-12-19","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether there is any funding pending to the London Borough of Southwark for the retrofitting of sprinklers in tower blocks.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119559","119559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806484","2017-12-18","Department for Education","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much her Department has spent on the (a) consultation on (b) preparation for and (c) introduction of the National Assessment and Accreditation Systems for social workers, social work supervisors and leaders.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119560","119560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806485","2017-12-18","Department for Education","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much funding her Department has allocated to (a) phase 1 and (b) phase 2 of the implementation of the National Assessment and Accreditation system.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119561","119561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806486","2017-12-18","Department for Education","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of the funding allocated to the consultation on the National Assessment and Accreditation system was spent on (a) private sector consultants and (b) local authorities.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119562","119562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806487","2017-12-18","Department for Education","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what information her Department holds on what the conditions, illnesses or other reasons are for which children have an Education, Health and Care plan; how such reasons are categorised by her Department; and what proportion of all children in England who have such a plan have a plan for each of those categories.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119563","119563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806488","2017-12-19","Department for Transport","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which overseas airports are currently subject to a UK flight ban.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119564","119564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806489","2017-12-19","Department of Health","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department taking to ensure the future of medical supplies that are linked to the UK's membership of Euratom.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119565","119565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806490","2017-12-19","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether the Information Commissioner's Office will continue to be a member of the Article 29 Working Party after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119566","119566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806491","2017-12-19","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether Ofcom will continue to be a member of the Body of European Regulators for Electronic Communications after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119567","119567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806492","2017-12-19","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, which body or bodies will potentially take over the role in telecommunications regulation that is currently played by the European Commission after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119568","119568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806493","2017-12-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, to which legislation his Department has applied the Family Test, published in August 2014.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119569","119569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806494","2017-12-19","Department for Education","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of the number of young people who leave care and later take their own lives; and what steps she is taking to reduce the number of young people who leave care and later take their own lives.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119570","119570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806495","2017-12-19","Department for Education","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to monitor the development of young people who have left care.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119571","119571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806496","2017-12-19","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how the Government plans to communicate with the public the potential changes required to reduce emissions associated with heating buildings in line with the UK’s emissions reduction targets.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119572","119572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806497","2017-12-19","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps the Government is taking to increase the roll-out of energy efficiency measures for non-fuel poor households.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119573","119573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806498","2017-12-18","Department for Transport","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to improve rail connectivity between (a) Congleton and Crewe, (b)  Congleton and Macclesfield, (c) Congleton and Chester and (d) Congleton and Liverpool.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119574","119574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806499","2017-12-19","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate he has made of the additional cost of meeting emissions reduction targets without the widespread roll-out of energy efficiency measures for buildings.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119575","119575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806500","2017-12-19","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what the Government's policy is on net neutrality.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119576","119576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806501","2017-12-19","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that new buildings are constructed to such a standard that they will not require energy-efficiency upgrades before 2050.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119577","119577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806502","2017-12-18","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what plans he has to learn lessons from the devolved Administrations on improving the energy-efficiency of buildings.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119578","119578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806503","2017-12-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he plans to send an expert team to gather evidence on sexual violence as a weapon of war against Rohingya women in Myanmar, and other possible crimes.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119579","119579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806504","2017-12-19","Home Office","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether it is Government policy that UK citizens who are suspected of committing criminal offences while fighting abroad will be dealt with by UK courts.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119580","119580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806505","2017-12-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether his policy on recognising animals as sentient beings encroaches on the rights of religious minorities to slaughter animals in accordance with Muslim and Jewish faith traditions.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119581","119581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806506","2017-12-18","Home Office","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she will direct Her Majesty’s Inspectorate of Constabulary to review (a) the use by the police of powers in Schedule 7 to the Terrorism Act 2007 to stop and search people at ports and airports and (b) whether those powers are used disproportionately on ethnic minority groups.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119582","119582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806507","2017-12-18","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent discussions he has had with manufacturers of consumer products and electrical appliances about the safety of their products and risk assessments.","Biography information for Patricia Gibson","Patricia Gibson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119583","119583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806508","2017-12-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he plans to maintain subsidies to UK farmers after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Colin Clark","Colin Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119584","119584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806509","2017-12-18","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to encourage UK researchers to bid for Horizon 2020 funding.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119585","119585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806510","2017-12-18","Home Office","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of allowing non-EEA nationals who were granted permanent residency under EEA Regulations but who are no longer family members of EEA nationals to switch to settled status.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119586","119586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806511","2017-12-19","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent discussions he has had  with manufacturers of consumer products and electrical appliances about product safety and risk assessments.","Biography information for Patricia Gibson","Patricia Gibson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119587","119587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806512","2017-12-18","Home Office","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to ensure that non-EEA nationals who were granted permanent residency but who are no longer family members of EEA nationals can obtain settled status when the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119588","119588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806513","2017-12-18","Department of Health","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent estimate he has made of trends in the number of older people being admitted to hospital for cold-related illnesses since 2012.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119589","119589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806514","2017-12-18","Department of Health","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average cost to the NHS was of a (a) hip replacement, (b) knee replacement, (c) cataract operation and (d) hernia operation in England in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119590","119590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806515","2017-12-19","Department of Health","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make an assessment of the effect of recent changes in the social care budget on people with dementia.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119591","119591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806516","2017-12-19","Department of Health","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of (a) NHS trusts and (b) NHS foundation trusts that will be in deficit at the end of the 2017-18 financial year; and whether he expects the NHS trust sector as a whole to be in deficit at the end of that year.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119592","119592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806517","2017-12-19","Department of Health","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many GPs there were in England per 100,000 population in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119593","119593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806518","2017-12-19","Department of Health","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much his Department spent on NHS staff redundancies in each year since 2011-12.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119594","119594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806519","2017-12-19","Department of Health","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many NHS staff were made redundant and subsequently re-employed by NHS organisations on a (a) permanent basis and (b) fixed-term contract basis since May 2010.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119595","119595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806520","2017-12-18","Department of Health","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what contingency arrangements are in place to ensure that the NHS is prepared for an influenza epidemic.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119596","119596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806521","2017-12-19","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what conditions he plans to impose on the recipients of grants from the recently announced £17 million fund for life sciences to ensure that patients achieve affordable access to the health technologies developed.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119597","119597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806522","2017-12-18","Department of Health","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the cost to the public purse was of cancer services in each year since 2001-02.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119598","119598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806523","2017-12-18","Department of Health","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many units of blood were collected by NHS Blood and Transplant England in each of the last 12 months for which data is available.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119599","119599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806524","2017-12-19","Cabinet Office","2017-12-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many excess winter deaths there were in England in each year since 1997.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119600","119600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806525","2017-12-18","Department of Health","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many students entered training to become a (a) nurse, (b) midwife and (c) GP in England in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119601","119601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806526","2017-12-18","Department of Health","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of people with learning disabilities whose care is paid for by the NHS are being cared for in facilities owned by private companies.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119602","119602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806527","2017-12-18","Department of Health","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients have been prescribed (a) benzodiazepines and (b) z-drugs for four months or longer in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119603","119603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806528","2017-12-18","Department of Health","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many NHS patients participated in a clinical trial in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119604","119604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806529","2017-12-18","Department of Health","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average salary was of a (a) nurse, (b) midwife and (c) health visitor in (i) the latest period for which figures are available and (ii) each year since 1997.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119605","119605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806530","2017-12-18","Department of Health","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much his Department spent on advertising to encourage people to donate blood in (a) 2010-11 and (b) 2011-12.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119606","119606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806531","2017-12-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to Memo ADM 30/17, whether previously unsuccessful personal independence payments claimants who had their claims refused after 9 March 2017 will have their claim reviewed according to a (a) LEAP exercise, (b) full case review or (c) any other review.","Biography information for Craig Tracey","Craig Tracey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119607","119607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806532","2017-12-18","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on businesses in Hampshire of the industrial strategy.","Biography information for Mr Ranil Jayawardena","Mr Ranil Jayawardena","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119608","119608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806533","2017-12-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what appeals process is available to personal independence payment claimants whose claims are subject to review under the personal independence payment assessment guidance set out in the Written Statement of 2 November 2017, HCWS218.","Biography information for Craig Tracey","Craig Tracey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119609","119609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806534","2017-12-19","Department of Health","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, where in the NHS approvals process Kettering General Hospital's bid for an urgent care hub has reached; and what the next stages are in that process.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119610","119610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806535","2017-12-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent progress he has made on plans to include Dupuytren's disease in the list of Industrial Injuries Disablement Benefit diseases.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119611","119611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806536","2017-12-19","Ministry of Defence","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many armed forces personnel lived in private rented accommodation in (a) 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012, (d) 2013, (e) 2014, (f) 2015, (g) 2016 and (h) 2017.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119612","119612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806537","2017-12-19","Prime Minister","2017-12-14","To ask the Prime Minister, pursuant to her oral answer to the Right Honourable Member for Cynon Valley of 9 October 2017, Official Report, column 59, what progress she has made on setting a date to address a plenary session of the European Parliament.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119613","119613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806538","2017-12-19","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what progress has been made of the review of UK Anti-Doping; and when he expects the review to be complete.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119614","119614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806539","2017-12-19","Prime Minister","2017-12-14","To ask the Prime Minister, pursuant to the oral answer to the Right Honourable Member for Cynon Valley on 9 October 2017, Official Report, column 59, whether it remains her policy to address a plenary session at the European Parliament.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119615","119615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806540","2017-12-18","Department of Health","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect of implementation of the recommendations of the Accelerated Access review on services to people with (a) Cystic Fibrosis and (b) other long-term conditions; and will he make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike  Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119616","119616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806541","2017-12-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to his Department's publication Personal Independence Payment: DLA to PIP reassessment outcomes, October 2017, what assessment he has made of trends in the level of claimants with epilepsy that have seen awards (a) refused and (b) reduced during the transition from DLA to PIP; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119617","119617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806542","2017-12-18","Department of Health","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that the drug Orkambi is made available on the NHS to people in England with Cystic Fibrosis who have been waiting two years for that prescription; and will he make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike  Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119618","119618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806543","2017-12-18","Department of Health","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many times Corneal Cross-Linking (CXL) treatment has been undertaken by the NHS in each of the last five financial years.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119619","119619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806544","2017-12-18","Department of Health","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the use of (a) the drug Orkambi and (b) other new medicines for long-term conditions on (i) the budget of the NHS and (ii) resources available for hospital inpatients.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike  Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119620","119620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806545","2017-12-18","Department of Health","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the potential benefits for people with long-term conditions such as cystic fibrosis of implementing the recommendations of the accelerated access review; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike  Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119621","119621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806546","2017-12-18","Ministry of Defence","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to page 16 of  Defence Equipment & Support Annual Report and Accounts 2016-17, if he will provide further details of the cost overruns associated with demonstration and manufacture phase projects under the DG Nuclear Command Acquisition and Support Plan.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119622","119622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806547","2017-12-18","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to oral contribution of the Minister for Housing and Planning on 24 October 2017, Official Report, column 53WH, what the timetable is for the consultation on the use of powers to move unauthorised encampments; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ms Nadine Dorries","Ms Nadine Dorries","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119623","119623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806548","2017-12-18","Ministry of Defence","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he plans to announce the awarding of contracts for his Department's Air Support to Defence Operational Training programme.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119624","119624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806549","2017-12-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking with his EU counterparts to support anti-corruption programmes in Ukraine.","Biography information for Ms Nadine Dorries","Ms Nadine Dorries","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119625","119625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806550","2017-12-18","Ministry of Justice","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many drones were discovered in the prison estate in 2016.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119626","119626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806551","2017-12-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations the Government has received from the Government of Germany on planned UK-Turkey defence cooperation following that country's decision to freeze defence exports to Turkey.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119627","119627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806552","2017-12-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the effectiveness of recent steps taken by the Government of Ukraine to tackle anti-corruption; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ms Nadine Dorries","Ms Nadine Dorries","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119628","119628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806553","2017-12-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent steps his Department has taken to support the Government of Ukraine's policies on (a) upholding the rule of law and (b) economic transition in that country.","Biography information for Ms Nadine Dorries","Ms Nadine Dorries","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119629","119629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806554","2017-12-18","Department for International Trade","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, (a) how many and (b) what proportion of his Department's Answers to Written Parliamentary Questions have advised that the requested information was not available on the grounds of disproportionate cost associated with data collection and collation in the current session.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119630","119630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806555","2017-12-18","Department for Transport","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the potential future capacity on the Chat Moss railway line as a result of the plans for the Northern Powerhouse Rail; and whether those plans include the opening of additional stations on that line.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119631","119631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806556","2017-12-18","Department for Transport","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to support Thameslink Railways in its management of capacity on trains between Bedford and St Pancras as a result of East Midland trains not stopping at (a) Luton and (b) Bedford from May 2018.","Biography information for Ms Nadine Dorries","Ms Nadine Dorries","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119632","119632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806557","2017-12-18","Department for Transport","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department made of the effect on capacity of the Thameslink line between Bedford and St Pancras of East Midland line trains not stopping at (a) Bedford and (b) Luton from May 2018.","Biography information for Ms Nadine Dorries","Ms Nadine Dorries","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119633","119633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806558","2017-12-19","Ministry of Justice","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when he plans to respond to the letter of the hon. Member for Bishop Auckland of 20 November 2017 on the release of a child sex offender.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119634","119634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806559","2017-12-18","Department for Transport","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of trends in the level overcrowding on Thameslink trains between Bedford and St Pancras during peak times.","Biography information for Ms Nadine Dorries","Ms Nadine Dorries","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119635","119635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806560","2017-12-18","Department for Transport","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make an assessment of the feasibility of improving disabled access to platforms at Flitwick station; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ms Nadine Dorries","Ms Nadine Dorries","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119636","119636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806561","2017-12-18","Department for Transport","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many passengers travelled to London from Bedford during peak hours on East Midlands trains in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Ms Nadine Dorries","Ms Nadine Dorries","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119637","119637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806562","2017-12-18","Department for Transport","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the average spare capacity was on Thameslink trains from Bedford to St Pancras during peak hours in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Ms Nadine Dorries","Ms Nadine Dorries","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119638","119638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806563","2017-12-18","Northern Ireland Office","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, whether his Department has made an assessment of the ability of orchestras in Northern Ireland to recruit freelance musicians from the Republic of Ireland after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Sammy Wilson","Sammy Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119639","119639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806564","2017-12-18","Northern Ireland Office","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what steps his Department is taking to promote Northern Ireland's professional orchestral sector.","Biography information for Sammy Wilson","Sammy Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119640","119640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806565","2017-12-18","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether her Department has made an assessment of whether orchestras in Northern Ireland will remain eligible for Creative Europe funding for EO-Lab ii after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Sammy Wilson","Sammy Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119641","119641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806566","2017-12-18","Department for International Development","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much her Department has allocated to the prevention of childhood pneumonia in developing countries in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sammy Wilson","Sammy Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119642","119642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806567","2017-12-19","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what recent discussions she has had with her EU counterparts on market access for audio-visual services after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119643","119643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806568","2017-12-19","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what recent assessment she has made on levels of employment in the audio-visual sector of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119644","119644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806569","2017-12-19","Home Office","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many non-UK EU citizens have been deported to their home country in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119645","119645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806570","2017-12-19","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what recent representations she has received from the audio-visual sector on the Country of Origin principle; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119646","119646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806571","2017-12-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when the Fisheries Bill will be published; for what reasons it will not be published by the end of the year; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119647","119647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806572","2017-12-19","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what recent discussions she has had with her EU counterparts on whether UK broadcasters' licenses will be valid in the EU after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119648","119648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806573","2017-12-19","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the letter to the Minister for the Northern Powerhouse and Local Growth from the Metro Mayor Liverpool on the Mersey Gateway Tolls, dated 4 December 2017.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119649","119649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806574","2017-12-19","Department of Health","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what examination his Department has made of the system of long-term care insurance in Japan; and what conclusions have been reached as a result of that examination.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119650","119650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806575","2017-12-19","Department of Health","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what models of long-term care used in other countries his Department has examined; and what conclusions he has drawn from that examination.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119651","119651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806576","2017-12-19","Ministry of Justice","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many cases under the Treasure Act 1996 have been reported in the last year in which it has been claimed by finders that the items discovered date to before commencement of that Act; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119652","119652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806577","2017-12-19","Department for International Trade","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what estimate he has made of the value of UK defence exports based on orders and agreed contracts to each EU member state in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119653","119653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806578","2017-12-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has held any recent discussions with his international counterparts on the prospect of resuming the six-party talks in relation to North Korea’s nuclear weapons programme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119654","119654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806579","2017-12-18","HM Treasury","2017-12-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he last met the hon. Member for Moray to discuss duty rates on Scotch Whisky.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119655","119655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806580","2017-12-18","Ministry of Defence","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he plans to deploy the Queen Elizabeth class aircraft carrier near the Korean peninsula when it enters service.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119656","119656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806581","2017-12-18","HM Treasury","2017-12-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he last met the hon. Member for Gordon to discuss duty rates on Scotch Whisky.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119657","119657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806582","2017-12-19","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps her Department is taking to improve the number of accessible sports facilities in the West Midlands.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119658","119658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806583","2017-12-18","HM Treasury","2017-12-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he last met the hon. Member for Aberdeenshire and West Kincardine to discuss duty rates on Scotch Whisky.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119659","119659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806584","2017-12-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when he last met his Spanish counterpart; and what issues were discussed at that meeting.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119660","119660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806585","2017-12-18","HM Treasury","2017-12-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he last met the hon. Member for Banff and Buchan to discuss duty rates on Scotch Whisky.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119661","119661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806586","2017-12-19","Department of Health","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department has taken to raise awareness of bowel cancer since 2015.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119662","119662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806587","2017-12-18","HM Treasury","2017-12-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he last met the hon. Member for Stirling to discuss duty rates on Scotch Whisky.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119663","119663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806588","2017-12-19","Department of Health","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department has taken to raise awareness of cystic fibrosis since 2015.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119664","119664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806589","2017-12-18","HM Treasury","2017-12-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he last met the hon. Member for Angus to discuss duty rates on Scotch Whisky.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119665","119665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806590","2017-12-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when he last met his counterpart in Singapore; and what issues were discussed at that meeting.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119666","119666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806591","2017-12-18","HM Treasury","2017-12-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he last met the hon. Member for Ochil and South Perthshire to discuss duty rates on Scotch Whisky.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119667","119667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806592","2017-12-18","HM Treasury","2017-12-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he last met the hon. Member for Ayr, Carrick and Cumnock to discuss duty rates on Scotch Whisky.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119668","119668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806593","2017-12-18","HM Treasury","2017-12-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he last met the hon. Member for Aberdeen South to discuss duty rates on Scotch Whisky.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119669","119669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806594","2017-12-18","HM Treasury","2017-12-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he last met the hon. Member for Berwickshire, Roxburgh and Selkirk to discuss duty rates on Scotch Whisky.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119670","119670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806595","2017-12-18","HM Treasury","2017-12-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he last met the hon. Member for East Renfrewshire to discuss duty rates on Scotch Whisky.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119671","119671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806596","2017-12-18","Department for Education","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment her Department has made of the proportion of secondary schools rated (a) good or (b) outstanding in the North East compared to (i) London and (ii) other regions of the UK.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119672","119672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806597","2017-12-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to his Department's publication ADM Memo 30/17, whether (a) all qualified PIP assessors and (b) other assessors are qualified to undertake a LEAP exercise review of a claimant's awards.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119673","119673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806598","2017-12-18","Department for Education","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to tackle disparities in education and skill levels between the North East and (a) London and (b) other regions of the UK.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119674","119674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806599","2017-12-18","Department of Health","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to support acute services at South Tyneside District Hospital.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119675","119675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806600","2017-12-18","Department of Health","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will review the Path to Excellence proposals made by South Tyneside and Sunderland NHS Partnership.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119676","119676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806601","2017-12-18","Department of Health","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the responses to the Path to Excellence proposals made by South Tyneside and Sunderland NHS Partnership.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119677","119677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806602","2017-12-18","Ministry of Defence","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent progress he has made on the development of the Type 31e General Purpose Frigate programme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119678","119678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806603","2017-12-18","Ministry of Defence","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if will visit shipyards in Jarrow constituency to demonstrate support for their potential future role in the new National Shipbuilding Strategy and the Type 31e General Purpose Frigate programme.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119679","119679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806604","2017-12-18","Department for International Development","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether her Department is providing humanitarian assistance to Eastern Ghouta in Syria.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119680","119680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806605","2017-12-18","Department for Transport","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to ensure private parking companies undertake land ownership checks before submitting data requests to the DVLA and issuing parking tickets on private land.","Biography information for Alex Chalk","Alex Chalk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119681","119681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806606","2017-12-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with UN bodies and his international counterparts on ending the siege of Eastern Ghouta.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119682","119682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806607","2017-12-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has made representations to his counterparts in Russia, Iran and Turkey on air and artillery attacks in Eastern Ghouta since it was designated a de-escalation zone.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119683","119683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806608","2017-12-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has made recent representations to UN bodies on air and artillery attacks in Eastern Ghouta since it was designated a de-escalation zone.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119684","119684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806609","2017-12-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to UN bodies and his counterpart in the Syrian Government on civilian protection and ending the siege in Eastern Ghouta and other besieged communities in Syria.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119685","119685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806610","2017-12-18","Department for International Development","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will make representations to UN bodies and the Syrian Government on humanitarian access to and urgent medical evacuations from Eastern Ghouta and other besieged areas in Syria.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119686","119686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806611","2017-12-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to Security Council Resolution 2165, if he will make representations to UN bodies on the need to ensure the delivery of humanitarian assistance to Eastern Ghouta and other besieged areas in Syria.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119687","119687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806612","2017-12-18","Department for International Development","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many aid air-drops the UK has made in besieged areas in Syria since the start of the conflict.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119688","119688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806613","2017-12-18","Department for International Development","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent discussions she has had with UN bodies on aid air-drops to besieged areas of Syria.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119689","119689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806614","2017-12-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he raised human rights issues with the Sudanese Foreign Minister, Ibrahim Ghandour, at his recent meeting.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119690","119690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806615","2017-12-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent progress has been made in finding the British-trained Barrister Mir Ahmed Bin Quasem, following his disappearance in Bangladesh In 2016.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119691","119691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806616","2017-12-18","Cabinet Office","2017-12-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the timetable is for his Department's publication of a response to the pre-legislative scrutiny of the draft Public Service Ombudsman Bill.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119692","119692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806617","2017-12-18","Cabinet Office","2017-12-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will place copies of the written responses to the draft Public Service Ombudsman Bill in the Library.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119693","119693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806618","2017-12-18","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the average waiting time was  for complaints to the Independent Housing Ombudsman to be investigated.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119694","119694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806619","2017-12-19","Cabinet Office","2017-12-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the break down is by (a) Department and (b) grade for the Civil Service sickness absence data for Q1 2017  published on 14 December 2017.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119695","119695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806620","2017-12-19","Cabinet Office","2017-12-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the break down is by (a) Department and (b) grade for the Civil Service sickness absence data for 2016 published on 14 December 2017.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119696","119696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806621","2017-12-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when he last met the hon. Member for Aberdeen South to discuss fishing quotas.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119697","119697"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806622","2017-12-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his Indonesian counterpart on the right to freedom of association for members of the United Liberation Movement for West Papua in that country.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119698","119698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806623","2017-12-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when he last met the hon. Member for Banff and Buchan to discuss fishing quotas.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119699","119699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806624","2017-12-18","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how much coal has been used in the manufacture of sugar from sugar beat in each year since 1992 to the latest year for which figures are available; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119700","119700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806625","2017-12-18","Ministry of Justice","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent assessment he has made of the trends in the level of county court judgements; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119701","119701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806626","2017-12-18","HM Treasury","2017-12-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of the implications for his policies of the report of United Nations Economic Commission for Africa's High Level Panel on Illicit Financial Flows from Africa.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119702","119702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806627","2017-12-19","Department for Education","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 5 July to Question 2169 on Parkfield School, Bournemouth, whether that project is now complete.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119703","119703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806628","2017-12-19","Ministry of Defence","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, for what reasons there are no key industrial capabilities with regard to the UK complex warship building industry identified in the National Shipbuilding Strategy.","Biography information for Mr Paul Sweeney","Mr Paul Sweeney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119704","119704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806629","2017-12-18","Department of Health","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect of minimum unit pricing on alcohol on reducing the incidence of cancer.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119705","119705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806630","2017-12-18","Department of Health","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has for the NHS to prescribe (a) tamoxifen to reduce the risk of breast cancer for those with a family history of the disease and (b) bisphosphonates to reduce the risk of secondary breast cancer in menopausal women.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119706","119706"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806631","2017-12-18","Department of Health","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of minimum unit pricing of alcohol on the number of cancer deaths.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119707","119707"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806632","2017-12-18","Department of Health","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has for (a) workforce planning and (b) investment to ensure there is  diagnostic capacity for breast cancer in the NHS.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119708","119708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806633","2017-12-19","Ministry of Defence","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the decision to decommission HMS Ocean in 2018 was finalised before the refit of that warship in 2014.","Biography information for Mr Paul Sweeney","Mr Paul Sweeney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119709","119709"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806634","2017-12-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 7 December 2017 to Question 116610, whether his Department intends to pay to each claimant whose entitlements were miscalculated between 2011 and 2014 the full amount dating back to when the miscalculation was made.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119710","119710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806635","2017-12-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer on 3 July 2017 to Question 882, whether the reformed welfare contract piloted at Birkenhead Jobcentre Plus is now operational across the whole Jobcentre Plus network.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119711","119711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806636","2017-12-19","Ministry of Defence","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the National Shipbuilding Strategy is planned to achieve upper quartile performance in the UK complex warship building industry as previously set out in the Terms of Business Agreement signed in 2009 between his Department and the company currently known as BAE Surface Systems Ships Ltd.","Biography information for Mr Paul Sweeney","Mr Paul Sweeney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119712","119712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806637","2017-12-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 3 July 2017 to Question 882 on Benefit Rules, what recent representations has he received from the Jobcentre Plus network on the roll-out of the Reformed Welfare Contract piloted by Feeding Britain in Birkenhead Jobcentre Plus.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119713","119713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806638","2017-12-19","Ministry of Defence","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, for what reasons his Department has decided no longer explicitly to commit to achieving the national sovereign capability to achieve a build interval of one shipbuild every 12 months and a design interval of every six years for complex warships as previously set out in the Terms of Business Agreement signed between his Department and the company currently known as BAE Surface Systems Ships Ltd.","Biography information for Mr Paul Sweeney","Mr Paul Sweeney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119714","119714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806639","2017-12-19","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to section 6.1 of his Department's single departmental plan, published on the 14 December 2017, what analysis his Department has conducted on its effect on housing and local government sectors.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119715","119715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806640","2017-12-19","Ministry of Defence","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which aspects of the Terms of Business Agreement signed in 2009 between his Department and the company currently known as BAE Systems Surface Ships Ltd have been transferred to the National Shipbuilding Strategy.","Biography information for Mr Paul Sweeney","Mr Paul Sweeney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119716","119716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806641","2017-12-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 3 July 2017 to Question 882, on Benefit Rules, what recent discussions he has received from the Jobcentre Plus network on the roll-out of the reformed welfare contract piloted by Feeding Britain at Birkenhead Jobcentre Plus.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119717","119717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806642","2017-12-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he plans to take further to support agricultural cooperatives; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119718","119718"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806643","2017-12-19","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 6 July to Question 1449 on planning permission: Christchurch, when he expects the enforcement appeals to be determined.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119719","119719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806644","2017-12-19","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 10 July to Question 3273 when he expects to announce the extension of right to buy discounts to housing association tenants across England.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119720","119720"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806645","2017-12-19","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he plans to refer the local government reorganisation proposal for Dorset to the Local Government Boundary Commission.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119721","119721"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806646","2017-12-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the recent political instability in western Cameroon; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119722","119722"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806647","2017-12-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how information on a tenant's rent arrears against housing payments are provided to social landlords within the transaction information entered in the universal credit landlords' portal.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119723","119723"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806648","2017-12-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average waiting time was for claimants of universal credit from (a) the opening of a universal credit account and (b) an interview at a job centre to the first payment of universal credit.","Biography information for Ged Killen","Ged Killen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119724","119724"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806649","2017-12-18","Home Office","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many and what proportion of Domestic Violence Protection Orders have been approved in court in England and Wales in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mark Tami","Mark Tami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119725","119725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806650","2017-12-18","Ministry of Justice","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent assessment he has made of trends in the level of  county court actions for debt recovery, and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119726","119726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806651","2017-12-18","Home Office","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many Domestic Violence Protection Orders have been approved in England and Wales in each of the past five years.","Biography information for Mark Tami","Mark Tami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119727","119727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806652","2017-12-18","Department of Health","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health,  what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect  on patients with (a) rare and (b) ultra-rare diseases of NICE and NHS England’s proposals for changes to the arrangements for evaluating and funding drugs and other health technologies appraised through NICE’s technology appraisal and highly specialised technologies programme, published in October 2016.","Biography information for Mark Tami","Mark Tami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119728","119728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806653","2017-12-18","Department of Health","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many drugs for very rare diseases were declined funding by NHS England after assessment through the specialised commissioning prioritisation process in (a) 2015-16 and (b) 2016-17.","Biography information for Mark Tami","Mark Tami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119729","119729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806654","2017-12-18","Department of Health","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many drugs for very rare conditions NHS England plans to assess through its specialised commissioning prioritisation process in (a) 2017-18 and (b) 2018-19.","Biography information for Mark Tami","Mark Tami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119730","119730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806655","2017-12-18","Department of Health","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what responsibility NHS England has to fund the pneumococcal vaccination of patients who have undergone a stem-cell transplant under the pneumococcal immunisation service specification in the NHS public health functions agreement 2017-18.","Biography information for Mark Tami","Mark Tami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119731","119731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806656","2017-12-18","Department of Health","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department has taken to monitor the effectiveness NHS England's delivery of immunisation services for patients who have undergone a stem-cell transplant.","Biography information for Mark Tami","Mark Tami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119732","119732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806657","2017-12-21","Ministry of Justice","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many convictions there have been for public order offences involving vigil participants outside abortion clinics in England and Wales in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119733","119733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806658","2017-12-18","Department of Health","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps Public Health England is taking to measure the uptake of Green Book recommended immunisations among adult patients in clinical risk groups.","Biography information for Mark Tami","Mark Tami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119734","119734"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806659","2017-12-18","Department for International Development","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether any of her Department's funding given to Marie Stopes International goes towards the provision of or advertising for abortion in Kenya.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119735","119735"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806660","2017-12-18","Department of Health","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information her Department holds on how many occasions ellaOne, ulipristal acetate 30 mg tablet, has been sold in the UK in 2016.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119736","119736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806661","2017-12-19","Department for Education","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary for Education, what assessment her Department has made of the economic effect of the UK leaving the EU on the university sector.","Biography information for Matt Western","Matt Western","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119737","119737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806662","2017-12-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether he has received any representations on technical and administration problems regarding the transfer of claimants from employment and support allowance to universal credit.","Biography information for Ged Killen","Ged Killen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119738","119738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806663","2017-12-18","Department of Health","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if his Department will undertake a review of the potential abortifacient effect of ellaOne, the ulipristal acetate 30 mg tablet; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119739","119739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806664","2017-12-18","Department of Health","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department plans to conduct controlled studies into the effects of ellaOne in pregnant women; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119740","119740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806665","2017-12-18","Department of Health","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, for what reasons guidance for doctors completing the HSA4 form states that recording the NHS number is optional when abortion providers are mandated by the NHS Number Programme Implementation Policy 2008 to record the NHS numbers for their patients.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119741","119741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806666","2017-12-18","Department of Health","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information his Department holds on the number of fetuses which were (a) incinerated, (b) cremated and (c) buried after induced abortions at (i) NHS hospitals and (ii) independent abortion providers in 2016.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119742","119742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806667","2017-12-18","Department for International Development","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent assessment she has made of her Department's funding to Marie Stopes International in developing countries, in light of the suspension of Marie Stopes’ abortion services in the UK.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119743","119743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806668","2017-12-19","Home Office","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many Palestinians living in Israel and Palestine have been refused entry to the UK in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Matt Western","Matt Western","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119744","119744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806669","2017-12-19","Home Office","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many Israeli citizens have been refused entry to the UK in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Matt Western","Matt Western","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119745","119745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806670","2017-12-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the change in the real terms value of the maximum amount of benefit entitlement as a result of inflation since the introduction of the benefit cap in November 2016.","Biography information for Ged Killen","Ged Killen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119746","119746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806671","2017-12-18","HM Treasury","2017-12-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the number of Equitable Life policyholders who have received payments (a) of less than a quarter of their relative losses, (b) more than a quarter of their relative losses and (c) totalling their relative losses.","Biography information for Sir Michael Fallon","Sir Michael Fallon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119747","119747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806672","2017-12-18","Department for Transport","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to pursue outstanding payments owed by the drivers of vehicles from non-UK EU Member States who have travelled through the Dartford tunnel.","Biography information for Sir Michael Fallon","Sir Michael Fallon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119748","119748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806673","2017-12-18","Home Office","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of the effect of the proposals in the consultation on offensive and dangerous weapons, published in October 2017, to prohibit the private ownership of items on the offensive weapons list on people who currently possess such items; and what guidance her Department plans to issue to people on the legality of continued possession of such items.","Biography information for Sir Michael Fallon","Sir Michael Fallon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119749","119749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806674","2017-12-19","Scotland Office","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, pursuant to the Answer of 14 December 2017 to Question 118330 on Scotland Office: official hospitality, what the events spend of his Department was in 2016-17","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119750","119750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806675","2017-12-19","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to paragraph 52 of the Joint Report of the Negotiators of the European Union and the United Kingdom Government, published on 8 December 2017, what assessment he has made of the compatibility of a Withdrawal Agreement respecting the rights, opportunities, and identity of one part of the UK population with section 149 of the Equality Act 2010.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119751","119751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806676","2017-12-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department has taken to ensure staff at a JobCentre Plus are adequately trained in their duties to improve the level of claimant satisfaction rates.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119752","119752"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806677","2017-12-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of work capability assessment decisions overturned in Redcar in each of the last five years where figures are available; and what steps he is taking to improve the accuracy of benefit entitlement awards.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119753","119753"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806678","2017-12-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the implications for his Department's policies on Sudan of the as a result of the meeting of the UK-Sudan Trade and Investment Forum, held in London on 12 December 2017.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119754","119754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806679","2017-12-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to ensure that benefit claimants who cannot attend appointments due to adverse weather conditions will not be sanctioned.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119755","119755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806680","2017-12-19","Department of Health","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of the number of patients receiving treatment for arthritis in (a) South Tees NHS Trust, (b) the North East and (c) England.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119756","119756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806681","2017-12-19","Department of Health","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of the number of full-time practising GPs in (a) South Tees NHS Trust, (b) the North East and (c) England for each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119757","119757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806682","2017-12-18","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate his Department has made of the number of people sleeping rough in (a) Redcar and Cleveland, (b) the North East and (c) England for each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119758","119758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806683","2017-12-18","Department for Education","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment her Department has made of the effect of teachers' working patterns on job satisfaction.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119759","119759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806684","2017-12-18","Scotland Office","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, pursuant to his oral contribution on 6 December 2017, Official Report, column, 1014, what the outcome was of his discussions with RBS on bank branches across Scotland; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ged Killen","Ged Killen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119760","119760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806685","2017-12-19","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, if he will ensure that any agreement in respect of the UK withdrawal from the EU does not extend to Spain an exclusive right to determine or veto the future commercial and trading status of Gibraltar between (a) UK and Gibraltar and (b) Gibraltar and the EU; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mike Gapes","Mike Gapes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119761","119761"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806686","2017-12-19","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether the implementation phase of the UK leaving the EU will be the same for Gibraltar as the rest of the UK; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mike Gapes","Mike Gapes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119762","119762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806687","2017-12-19","Department for Education","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children attend early years settings which are rated either satisfactory or inadequate by Ofsted.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119763","119763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806688","2017-12-19","Department of Health","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that current levels of service quality are maintained for patients seeking mental health treatment between 2017 and 2020.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119764","119764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806689","2017-12-18","Ministry of Justice","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 14 December 2017 to Question 118434, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of private providers managing custodial sentences in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119765","119765"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806690","2017-12-19","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether the implementation phase of the UK leaving the EU will be the same for Anguilla as the rest of the UK; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mike Gapes","Mike Gapes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119766","119766"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806691","2017-12-19","Department for Education","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of the number of children who were eligible for the 30 funded hours of childcare this term, but are not eligible in the January term because their parents (a) now exceed the earnings limit and (b) now earn below the minimum amount.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119767","119767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806692","2017-12-19","Department of Health","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to support the mental health needs of children and young people in the next 12 months.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119768","119768"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806693","2017-12-19","Home Office","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of her Department's procedures for identifying the exploitation and human trafficking of undocumented non-EEA nationals working in the UK fishing industry; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119769","119769"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806694","2017-12-19","Department for Transport","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what measures the Maritime and Coastguard Agency has implemented to support victims of slavery found on vessels in British waters.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119770","119770"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806695","2017-12-19","Department for Education","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of eligible children received 15 hours of free childcare in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119771","119771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806696","2017-12-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate has made of the number of single parent households who will be in receipt of universal credit when it is rolled out in (a) the UK,  (b) London (c) London Borough of Ealing and (d) Ealing Central and Acton constituency.","Biography information for Dr Rupa Huq","Dr Rupa Huq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119772","119772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806697","2017-12-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to issue guidance to single parents on their (a) rights and (b) entitlements in respect of (i) universal credit and (ii) other benefits.","Biography information for Dr Rupa Huq","Dr Rupa Huq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119773","119773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806698","2017-12-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of notices of entitlement to advance payments of universal credit for single parents.","Biography information for Dr Rupa Huq","Dr Rupa Huq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119774","119774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806699","2017-12-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effect of the introduction of universal credit on encouraging single parents into employment.","Biography information for Dr Rupa Huq","Dr Rupa Huq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119775","119775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806700","2017-12-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effect of the introduction of universal credit on the ability of single parents' to remain in employment.","Biography information for Dr Rupa Huq","Dr Rupa Huq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119776","119776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806701","2017-12-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the accessibility of the universal credit helpline for people who work between 8am and 6pm.","Biography information for Dr Rupa Huq","Dr Rupa Huq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119777","119777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806702","2017-12-18","Department for International Development","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether her Department has rejected an application for funding on the grounds that the applicant does not provide abortion and contraception services during the last ten years.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119778","119778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806703","2017-12-18","Women and Equalities","2017-12-14","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, whether her Department had discussions with (a) the Northern Ireland Assembly and (b) Cabinet colleagues on the decision to extend the Northern Ireland abortion scheme to include the provision of free travel to women resident in Northern Ireland from low-income backgrounds.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119779","119779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806704","2017-12-18","Department of Health","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department has undertaken an assessment of the potential effect on the wellbeing of NHS nursing staff of their involvement in the provision of late-term abortions; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119780","119780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806705","2017-12-18","Department of Health","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the effect on the mental health of women of (a) experiencing an unplanned pregnancy and birth and (b) having an abortion.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119781","119781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806706","2017-12-18","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how much funding his Department has allocated for embryonic stem cell research to date; and what estimate he has made of the number of such funded research projects involving embryonic stem cells which have yielded results clearly beneficial to public health.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119782","119782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806707","2017-12-18","Department of Health","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the amount of funding from the public purse allocated to the provision of abortion and abortion-related services in the UK in 2016.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119783","119783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806708","2017-12-18","Department of Health","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many foetuses were incinerated after abortions at (a) NHS hospitals and (b) private abortion clinics in 2016.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119784","119784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806709","2017-12-18","Department of Health","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if his Department will undertake an assessment of the compatibility of the Abortion Act 1967 with Article 3 of the UN Declaration on Human Rights.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119785","119785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806710","2017-12-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations officials in his Department have made to representatives of (a) the Government of El Salvador and (b) other countries on changes to the abortion law of those countries.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119786","119786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806711","2017-12-18","Home Office","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to ensure the protection of the right of freedom of expression for people who are opposed to the practice of abortion.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119787","119787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806712","2017-12-18","Department of Health","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent representations he has received from disabled people about terminations on the grounds of disability.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119788","119788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806713","2017-12-18","Department of Health","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department has carried out or commissioned recent research into the potential effect of the repeated use of the morning after pill on women.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119789","119789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806714","2017-12-18","Department of Health","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether minors resident in Northern Ireland who are eligible for free travel under the extension of the Government's Northern Ireland abortion scheme are required to have permission from their parents before travelling to procure an abortion in England.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119790","119790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806715","2017-12-18","Women and Equalities","2017-12-14","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, whether the extension to the Government's Northern Ireland abortion scheme covers (a) free travel and (b) free accommodation; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119791","119791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806716","2017-12-18","Department of Health","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department has made a recent assessment of the prevalence of gender-selective abortion in the UK.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119792","119792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806717","2017-12-18","Women and Equalities","2017-12-14","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, with reference to the extension of the Government's Northern Ireland abortion scheme, if the Government will take steps to provide financial support for disadvantaged women who plan to continue with their pregnancies.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119793","119793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806718","2017-12-18","Department of Health","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Care Quality Commission report on the Marie Stopes International clinic in Maidstone, whether he plans to exercise his right to withdraw the licence to perform abortions from that abortion provider.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119794","119794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806719","2017-12-18","Department of Health","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the extension of the Government's Northern Ireland abortion scheme, whether the Government plans to cover the costs of minors resident in Northern Ireland to travel and procure abortions in England.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119795","119795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806720","2017-12-18","Department of Health","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the Social Care Funding Reform Impact Assessment of 3 February 2015 is the most recent impact assessment on social care funding reform.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119796","119796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806721","2017-12-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-12-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 7 December 2017 to Question 116610, whether his Department plans to pay to each claimant whose entitlements were miscalculated in those years the amount they have been underpaid since 21 October 2014.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119797","119797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/805517","2017-12-13","Wales Office","2017-12-13","If he will meet with Cabinet colleagues to discuss the merits of removing child burial fees in England in line with policy in Wales.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 902839","902839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/805521","2017-12-18","Home Office","2017-12-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many non-UK EU nationals started employment in her Department since 23 June 2016.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119161","119161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/805967","2017-12-18","Department of Health","2017-12-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people have been diagnosed with Crohn's Disease in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119177","119177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/805968","2017-12-18","Department for International Trade","2017-12-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps his Department is taking to secure future trade deals with Nigeria.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119178","119178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/805969","2017-12-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-12-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking with his international counterparts to monitor and regulate the arrival of migrants from Tunisia to Europe.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119179","119179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/805970","2017-12-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-12-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has had discussions with his Chinese counterpart on that Government's recent interference with Radio 4's Today Programme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119180","119180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/805971","2017-12-18","Department for Education","2017-12-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what strategy his Department has in place to ensure sufficient skills for the housing construction programme.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119181","119181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/805972","2017-12-18","Department of Health","2017-12-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to ensure that people attending A&E are seen within an hour of their arriving.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119182","119182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/805973","2017-12-18","Department for Education","2017-12-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to prevent foreign students from not repaying outstanding loans in respect of private university fees.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119183","119183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/805974","2017-12-18","Department of Health","2017-12-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that blood transfusion donations are carefully monitored to prevent recipients from getting ill as a result.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119184","119184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/805975","2017-12-18","Department of Health","2017-12-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of whether the UK not being part of the Clinical Trials Regulation coming into effect in 2019 will be able to take part in such trials after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119185","119185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/805976","2017-12-18","Department of Health","2017-12-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the legislation that will be required in the UK to ensure that the UK becomes compatible with the EU Clinical Trials Regulation coming into force in 2019.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119186","119186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/805977","2017-12-18","Ministry of Defence","2017-12-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if his Department will commemorate the contribution of the White Helmet Motor Cycle Team to defence.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119187","119187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/805978","2017-12-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-12-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Office, if he will make representations to his counterpart in the Government of Algeria on the forced closure of a Protestant Church in North West Algeria on 9 November 2017.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119188","119188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/805979","2017-12-18","Department of Health","2017-12-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make it his Department's policy to ensure that all clinical commissioning groups provide the full cycle of IVF treatment for patients that meet the NICE fertility guidelines for treatment.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119189","119189"
