"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/900180","2018-05-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many UK civil servants have been working on contracts in Saudi Arabia in each of the last five years; and what the roles of those civil servants have been.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141759","141759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/900181","2018-05-10","Home Office","2018-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether he has plans to bring forward legislative proposals on the length of sentences for drug-related crimes.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141754","141754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/900182","2018-05-11","Department for Education","2018-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what funding sources are available for schools with derelict or dilapidated buildings.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141862","141862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/900183","2018-05-10","Ministry of Defence","2018-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Royal Air Force personnel were seconded to serve in Saudi Arabia in each of the last five years; and what the roles and responsibilities have been of those personnel.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141760","141760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/900184","2018-05-10","Ministry of Defence","2018-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the cost to the public purse has been of UK civil servants operating in Saudi Arabia in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141761","141761"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/900185","2018-05-10","Ministry of Defence","2018-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the cost to the public purse has been of Royal Air Force personnel serving in Saudi Arabia in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141762","141762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/900186","2018-05-10","Ministry of Defence","2018-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what role Royal Air Force personnel play in respect of Saudi Tornado IDS fighter-bombers in Saudi Arabia.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141763","141763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/900187","2018-05-10","Ministry of Defence","2018-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the UK’s ongoing military commitments are with the Saudi Government.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141764","141764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/900188","2018-05-10","Ministry of Defence","2018-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will publish the Al Yamamah memorandum of agreement between the UK and Saudi Arabia.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141765","141765"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/900189","2018-05-10","Ministry of Defence","2018-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, in which countries which are in a state of war UK armed forces personnel are serving as support staff.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141766","141766"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/900190","2018-05-10","Ministry of Defence","2018-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will publish the 2005 Al Salam agreement between the UK and Saudi Arabia.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141767","141767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/900191","2018-05-10","Ministry of Defence","2018-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will publish the 2017 Military and Security Cooperation Agreement between the UK and Saudi Arabia.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141768","141768"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/900192","2018-05-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 21 December 2017 to Question 120069, on Prescriptions: Universal Credit, when free prescription forms will be amended to include universal credit.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141704","141704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/900193","2018-05-10","Ministry of Defence","2018-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the procedure is for UK military personnel working on his Department's contracts in Saudi Arabia to report violations of international humanitarian law.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141769","141769"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/900194","2018-05-11","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, when he plans to respond to the letters from the hon. Member for Hornsey and Wood Green dated 25 January, 8 March and 18 April 2018 on a leaseholder dispute within that hon. Member's constituency.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141863","141863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/900195","2018-05-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many patients have died whilst under the care of inpatient children and adolescent mental health services since January 2013.","Biography information for Mary Robinson","Mary Robinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141812","141812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/900196","2018-05-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect on local social care providers who are unable to fund historic back-pay liabilities for sleep-in shifts.","Biography information for Wera Hobhouse","Wera Hobhouse","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141872","141872"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/900197","2018-05-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department has made an assessment of the potential merits of creating a fund to pay the historic back pay for sleep-in shifts directly to care workers.","Biography information for Wera Hobhouse","Wera Hobhouse","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141873","141873"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/900198","2018-05-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what role charities will play in the planned inquiry into the failure to invite women aged 68-71 to breast screening since 2009.","Biography information for Karen Lee","Karen Lee","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141898","141898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/900199","2018-05-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department plans to take to meet demand for ophthalmology treatment in hospitals.","Biography information for Wera Hobhouse","Wera Hobhouse","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141874","141874"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/900200","2018-05-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of staff who work in his Department’s Financial Investigation Unit are tasked with seeking to identify the assets and income of people alleged to be hiding those assets and income from the Child Maintenance Service; of how many people at what grades that proportion consists; and what recent assessment has been made of the adequacy of that number for the task those staff perform.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141841","141841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/900201","2018-05-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many cases the Financial Investigation Unit (FIU) has dealt with in the last twelve months for which data are available; in what proportion of those cases has a member of staff in the FIU been tasked with identifying assets and income of those alleged to be hiding such income or assets from the Child Maintenance Service; and how many such cases are outstanding as of 1 May 2018.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141842","141842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/900202","2018-05-11","Home Office","2018-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 8 May 2018 to Question 136029, on Immigrants: Commonwealth, whether his Department made an assessment of the potential effect of the Immigration Act 2014 on (a) older Commonwealth citizens, (b) undocumented British citizens and (c) other vulnerable groups prior to its implementation.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141833","141833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/900203","2018-05-11","Ministry of Defence","2018-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many UK personnel have been deployed on UN peacekeeping missions in each year since 2000.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141731","141731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/900204","2018-05-11","Ministry of Defence","2018-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many female UK personnel have been deployed on UN peacekeeping missions in each year since 2000.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141732","141732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/900205","2018-05-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department plans to promote the U=U campaign to reduce self-stigma of people who have HIV.","Biography information for Wera Hobhouse","Wera Hobhouse","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141875","141875"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/900206","2018-05-11","Wales Office","2018-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what support the UK Government has offered to the Welsh Government to gain European funding for the South Wales Metro project.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141834","141834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/900207","2018-05-11","Wales Office","2018-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what (a) quantitative and (b) qualitative analysis his Department has conducted with the Department for International Trade to identify trading opportunities for Wales with countries with which the European Union does not have a trade deal.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141835","141835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/900208","2018-05-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many investigations have taken place in each of the last five years relating to alleged breaches of Regulation 7 of the Conduct of Employment Agencies and Employment Business Regulations 2003; and how many prosecutions there have been under that regulation in that same period.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141823","141823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/900209","2018-05-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment made of the effect of leaving the customs union on manufacturing costs in the automotive sector.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141824","141824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/900210","2018-05-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many ward closures in each of the last five years were due to novovirus outbreaks.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141825","141825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/900211","2018-05-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether clinical commissioning group areas that are subject to the capped expenditure process will continue to be so subject in the event that are merged with another clinical commissioning group.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141826","141826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/900212","2018-05-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for the Home Department on visa restrictions for potential NHS staff.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141827","141827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/900213","2018-05-10","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what assessment his Department has made of the (a) short-term and (b) long-term risks to the UK financial services after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141705","141705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/900214","2018-05-10","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many new homes were sold on a leasehold basis in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141828","141828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/900215","2018-05-10","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many claimants at employment tribunals were represented by a qualified professional in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141829","141829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/900216","2018-05-10","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what assessment his Department has made of the potential risks to the economic sustainability of the financial services sector in each constituent part of the UK after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141706","141706"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/900217","2018-05-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average length of time is that PIP appeals take to reach a hearing.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141830","141830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/900218","2018-05-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average amount of back payments was made for successful PIP appeals for each of the last twelve months for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141831","141831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/900219","2018-05-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many domestic solar panels have been installed in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141832","141832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/900220","2018-05-11","Department for Education","2018-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to increase awareness among teaching staff of (a) diagnosed and (b) undiagnosed ADHD in pupils.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141912","141912"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/900221","2018-05-10","Treasury","2018-05-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what opportunities his Department has identified for the financial services sector after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141707","141707"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/900222","2018-05-11","Department for Education","2018-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to increase the support available to pupils with ADHD.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141913","141913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/900223","2018-05-11","Department for Education","2018-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that teaching staff are adequately trained to (a) identify and (b) assist pupils with ADHD.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141914","141914"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/900224","2018-05-10","Treasury","2018-05-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many UK financial services institutions have a presence in other EU countries.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141708","141708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/900225","2018-05-11","Treasury","2018-05-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he plans to consult on increasing the rate of landfill tax beyond 2020.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141846","141846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/900226","2018-05-11","Treasury","2018-05-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he plans to reintroduce the landfill tax escalator from 2020.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141847","141847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/900227","2018-05-11","Treasury","2018-05-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of increasing the rate of landfill tax beyond 2020 on the UK’s existing waste reduction and recycling targets.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141848","141848"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/900228","2018-05-11","Treasury","2018-05-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of increasing the rate of landfill tax beyond 2020 on stimulating innovation and investment in the waste and recycling supply chain.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141849","141849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/900229","2018-05-10","Treasury","2018-05-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of the risk to the financial services sector in the event that the UK does not secure an adequacy decision on data.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141709","141709"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/900230","2018-05-10","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what the (a) Government and (b) EU position is on the enforceability of financial contract continuity after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141710","141710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/900231","2018-05-10","Treasury","2018-05-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what elements of his Department's preparations for the UK leaving the EU will not be completed by March 2019.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141711","141711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/900232","2018-05-10","Treasury","2018-05-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of the structures that the Government will need to put in place to prepare for new rules affecting UK financial services during the transition period of exiting the EU.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141712","141712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/900233","2018-05-10","Treasury","2018-05-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the effect of leaving the EU on Euro clearing.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141713","141713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/900234","2018-05-10","Treasury","2018-05-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of the effect on the confidence of the UK financial services sector in (a) London, (b) the rest of England and (c) Wales of no agreement being reached between the UK and the EU on the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141714","141714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/900235","2018-05-11","Ministry of Defence","2018-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what information his Department holds on the number of occasions on which companies holding contracts with his Department have been subject to cyber attacks in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141733","141733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/900236","2018-05-11","Department for Education","2018-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether his Department has carried out an assessment of the effect of (a) endometriosis and (b) other menstrual condition on the performance of children and young people in school; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141843","141843"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/900237","2018-05-11","Ministry of Defence","2018-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what progress is being made with repairs to the runway on Ascension Island.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141855","141855"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/900238","2018-05-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether it is his policy that the British Standards Institute should be able to continue to CE Mark medical devices after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141773","141773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/900239","2018-05-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he has undertaken an impact analysis of the cost to the medical device industry of switching from a UK based Notified Body for CE marking to one in an EU Member State after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141774","141774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/900240","2018-05-11","Department for Education","2018-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the response of 23 April 2018 to Question 136295 on children’s centres, what assessment his department has made of the performance of the Get Information About Schools database since it was introduced in September 2017.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141867","141867"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/900241","2018-05-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average payment has been to the top (a) one, (b) five and (c) 10 per cent of benefit claimants by amount received in each of the last two years.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141727","141727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/900242","2018-05-11","Home Office","2018-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications for visas from highly skilled professionals were refused by his Department between January 2010 and January 2014.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141777","141777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/900243","2018-05-11","Home Office","2018-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications for visas from highly skilled professionals were refused by his Department between February 2014 and March 2018.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141778","141778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/900244","2018-05-11","Home Office","2018-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people who applied for visas as highly skilled professionals were deported in each year between January 2010 and January 2014.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141779","141779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/900245","2018-05-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, for what reasons statutory adoption pay is not available for people undertaking guardianship orders.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141868","141868"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/900246","2018-05-10","Home Office","2018-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people who applied for visas as highly skilled professionals were deported in each year between February 2014 and March 2018.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141780","141780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/900247","2018-05-11","Home Office","2018-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average time to process and make a decision on a visa application for a highly skilled professional has been in the last three months for which information is available.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141781","141781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/900248","2018-05-11","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether he has plans to visit Celtic Park football stadium to make an assessment of the merits of their rail seating installation.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141844","141844"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/900249","2018-05-11","Home Office","2018-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the (a) mean and (b) median time spent is by the current cohort of detainees at the Gatwick detention centres.","Biography information for Sir Desmond Swayne","Sir Desmond Swayne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141663","141663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/900250","2018-05-10","Home Office","2018-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the Government’s compensation scheme for the Windrush generation will take into account missed (a) national insurance contributions, (b) pensions contributions and (c) life insurance or medical insurance premiums.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141856","141856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/900251","2018-05-10","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how many bonuses were awarded to senior civil servants working at his Department and its agencies in each of the last six years; and what the total cost of those bonuses was.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141815","141815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/900252","2018-05-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many bonuses were awarded to senior civil servants working at his Department and its agencies in each of the last six years; and what the total cost of those bonuses was.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141816","141816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/900253","2018-05-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many bonuses were awarded to senior civil servants working at his Department and its agencies in each of the last six years; and what the total cost of those bonuses was.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141817","141817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/900254","2018-05-10","Ministry of Defence","2018-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many bonuses were awarded to senior civil servants working at his Department and its agencies in each of the last six years; and what the total cost of those bonuses was.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141818","141818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/900255","2018-05-10","Wales Office","2018-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how many bonuses were awarded to senior civil servants working at his Department and its agencies in each of the last six years; and what the total cost of those bonuses was.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141819","141819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/900256","2018-05-10","Northern Ireland Office","2018-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many bonuses were awarded to senior civil servants working at his Department and its agencies in each of the last six years; and what the total cost of those bonuses was.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141820","141820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/900257","2018-05-10","Cabinet Office","2018-05-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many bonuses were awarded to senior civil servants working at his Department and its agencies in each of the last six years; and what the total cost of those bonuses was.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141821","141821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/900258","2018-05-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many bonuses were awarded to senior civil servants working at his Department and its agencies in each of the last six years; and what the total cost of those bonuses was.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141822","141822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/900259","2018-05-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how much was disbursed from the public purse by his Department to fund UK election observers overseas in each of the last five years.","Biography information for John Grogan","John Grogan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141685","141685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897903","2018-05-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to increase the number of GPs.","Biography information for Sir Edward Leigh","Sir Edward Leigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 905168","905168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897908","2018-05-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure that mental health services for children and young people are able to benefit from an annual uplift in their recurrent additional funding as originally envisaged by NHS England.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141360","141360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897909","2018-05-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he will issue statutory guidance to local authorities and health service providers to ensure the quality and implementation of local transformation plans for children and young people's mental health.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141361","141361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897910","2018-05-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure that local transformation plans for children and young people’s mental health provide transparency on total spend in each area and not just spend of additional funding allocated by NHS England.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141362","141362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897911","2018-05-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 7 September 2017 to Question 8231, for what reasons his Department is unable to provide a breakdown of how the £30 million of additional money for community eating disorders services for children and young people was allocated to clinical commissioning groups when it was able to provide that information in the Answer of 2 November 2016 to Question 50911.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141363","141363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897912","2018-05-10","Treasury","2018-05-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he has taken to limit profit levels over the duration of private finance initiative contracts.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141367","141367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897913","2018-05-10","Department for Education","2018-05-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether he has made an assessment of the cost of servicing private finance initiative contracts on school budgets.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141368","141368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897914","2018-05-10","Department for Education","2018-05-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what his policy is on the role of schools in the (a) negotiation and (b) renegotiation of private finance initiative contracts.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141369","141369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897915","2018-05-10","Department for Education","2018-05-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment his Department has made of the level of profit made by private finance agencies on private finance initiative contracts with schools.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141370","141370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897916","2018-05-10","Department for Education","2018-05-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the real terms net change in funding per pupil will be for schools in Birkenhead under the new national funding formula.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141313","141313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897917","2018-05-09","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-05-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate he has made of the effect of a £2 maximum stake on B2 gaming machines on the number of (a) betting shop jobs that would potentially be lost and (b) betting shops that would potentially close.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141341","141341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897918","2018-05-09","Home Office","2018-05-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether any recommendations for improvement were made relating to the North Yorkshire police force after its most recent inspection by Her Majesty’s Inspectorate of Constabulary and Fire & Rescue Services.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141364","141364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897919","2018-05-09","Home Office","2018-05-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will encourage the Police and Crime Commissioner for North Yorkshire to support and fund the emerging partnership against modern slavery in the North Yorkshire area.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141365","141365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897920","2018-05-09","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-05-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, when he plans to bring forward legislative proposals to implement commercial radio deregulation.","Biography information for Mr Edward Vaizey","Mr Edward Vaizey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141343","141343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897921","2018-05-10","Scotland Office","2018-05-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what steps his Department is taking to enable Gaelic speakers to complete official documents in that language.","Biography information for Carol Monaghan","Carol Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141353","141353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897922","2018-05-09","Scotland Office","2018-05-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what training his Department has provided to (a) general civil servants, (b) fast stream civil servants and (c) senior civil servants on devolution and inter-governmental relations; how many such courses have taken place; and how many civil servants have attended such training courses in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141323","141323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897923","2018-05-09","Northern Ireland Office","2018-05-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what training his Department has provided to (a) general civil servants, (b) fast stream civil servants and (c) senior civil servants on devolution and inter-governmental relations; how many such courses have taken place; and how many civil servants have attended such training courses in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141324","141324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897924","2018-05-09","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-05-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what training his Department has provided to (a) general civil servants, (b) fast stream civil servants and (c) senior civil servants on understanding the scrutiny and legislative roles of the UK Parliament; how many such courses have taken place; and how many civil servants have attended such training courses in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141325","141325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897925","2018-05-09","Department for International Trade","2018-05-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what training his Department has provided to (a) general civil servants, (b) fast stream civil servants and (c) senior civil servants on understanding the scrutiny and legislative roles of the UK Parliament; how many such courses have taken place; and how many civil servants have attended such training courses in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141326","141326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897926","2018-05-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-05-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what training his Department has provided to (a) general civil servants, (b) fast stream civil servants and (c) senior civil servants on understanding the scrutiny and legislative roles of the UK Parliament; how many such courses have taken place; and how many civil servants have attended such training courses in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141327","141327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897927","2018-05-09","Department for International Development","2018-05-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what training her Department has provided to (a) general civil servants, (b) fast stream civil servants and (c) senior civil servants on understanding the scrutiny and legislative roles of the UK Parliament; how many such courses have taken place; and how many civil servants have attended such training courses in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141328","141328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897928","2018-05-09","Ministry of Defence","2018-05-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what training his Department has provided to (a) general civil servants, (b) fast stream civil servants and (c) senior civil servants on understanding the scrutiny and legislative roles of the UK Parliament; how many such courses have taken place; and how many civil servants have attended such training courses in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141329","141329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897929","2018-05-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what training his Department has provided to (a) general civil servants, (b) fast stream civil servants and (c) senior civil servants on understanding the scrutiny and legislative roles of the UK Parliament; how many such courses have taken place; and how many civil servants have attended such training courses in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141330","141330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897930","2018-05-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what training her Department has provided to (a) general civil servants, (b) fast stream civil servants and (c) senior civil servants on understanding the scrutiny and legislative roles of the UK Parliament; how many such courses have taken place; and how many civil servants have attended such training courses in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141331","141331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897931","2018-05-09","Home Office","2018-05-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what training his Department has provided to (a) general civil servants, (b) fast stream civil servants and (c) senior civil servants on understanding the scrutiny and legislative roles of the UK Parliament; how many such courses have taken place; and how many civil servants have attended such training courses in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141332","141332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897932","2018-05-09","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what training his Department has provided to (a) general civil servants, (b) fast stream civil servants and (c) senior civil servants on understanding the scrutiny and legislative roles of the UK Parliament; how many such courses have taken place; and how many civil servants have attended such training courses in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141333","141333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897933","2018-05-09","Department for Education","2018-05-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what training his Department has provided to (a) general civil servants, (b) fast stream civil servants and (c) senior civil servants on understanding the scrutiny and legislative roles of the UK Parliament; how many such courses have taken place; and how many civil servants have attended such training courses in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141334","141334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897934","2018-05-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what training his Department has provided to (a) general civil servants, (b) fast stream civil servants and (c) senior civil servants on understanding the scrutiny and legislative roles of the UK Parliament; how many such courses have taken place; and how many civil servants have attended such training courses in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141335","141335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897935","2018-05-09","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what training his Department has provided to (a) general civil servants, (b) fast stream civil servants and (c) senior civil servants on understanding the scrutiny and legislative roles of the UK Parliament; how many such courses have taken place; and how many civil servants have attended such training courses in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141336","141336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897936","2018-05-09","Wales Office","2018-05-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what training his Department has provided to (a) general civil servants, (b) fast stream civil servants and (c) senior civil servants on understanding the scrutiny and legislative roles of the UK Parliament; how many such courses have taken place; and how many civil servants have attended such training courses in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141337","141337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897937","2018-05-09","Northern Ireland Office","2018-05-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what training his Department has provided to (a) general civil servants, (b) fast stream civil servants and (c) senior civil servants on understanding the scrutiny and legislative roles of the UK Parliament; how many such courses have taken place; and how many civil servants have attended such training courses in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141338","141338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897938","2018-05-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many hospital admissions related to ecstasy use there have been in (a) Manchester and (b) the UK in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jeff Smith","Jeff Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141356","141356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897939","2018-05-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many hospital admissions related to cocaine use there have been in (a) Manchester and (b) the UK in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jeff Smith","Jeff Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141357","141357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897940","2018-05-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many hospital admissions related to (a) fentanyl and (b) carfentanyl there have been in (a) Manchester and (b) the UK in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Jeff Smith","Jeff Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141358","141358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897941","2018-05-09","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-05-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate he has made of the potential switch from fixed odds betting terminals to online gambling if a £2 maximum stake is introduced.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141342","141342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897942","2018-05-10","Treasury","2018-05-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many tax credit claimants whose claims were wrongly suspended by Concentrix in previous tax years have since similarly had their claims wrongly suspended for the same reasons by HMRC.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141314","141314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897943","2018-05-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of universal credit claimants in employment who have restarted their claim having been paid twice during a single assessment period.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141315","141315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897944","2018-05-09","Ministry of Defence","2018-05-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 14 March 2018 to Question 131423, what progress he has made on reviewing his Department's policy of redistributing surplus ration packs to the homeless.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141316","141316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897945","2018-05-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of parents who did not report income increases of 25 per cent or more to Child Maintenance Services in (a) 2013, (b) 2014, (c) 2015, (d) 2016 and (e) 2017.","Biography information for Antoinette Sandbach","Antoinette Sandbach","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141371","141371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897946","2018-05-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment she has made of the compatibility of the operation of universal credit with the earning patterns of claimants who are not paid once a month.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141317","141317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897947","2018-05-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will introduce greater flexibility to the monthly assessment period for universal credit to allow people not paid a regular wage each month a more stable income.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141318","141318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897948","2018-05-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many parents have been prosecuted for failing to report increases in their income to the Child Maintenance Service or Child Support Agency in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Antoinette Sandbach","Antoinette Sandbach","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141372","141372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897949","2018-05-09","Home Office","2018-05-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which NHS trusts have been identified as high risk in relation to the compliant environment and immigration status checking systems.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141305","141305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897950","2018-05-09","Home Office","2018-05-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will publish the Memorandum of Understanding each NHS Trust has signed with the Home Office in relation to immigration status checking systems.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141306","141306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897951","2018-05-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what support General Practitioners provide to mothers experiencing perinatal mental health problems.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141351","141351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897952","2018-05-09","Treasury","2018-05-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of air passenger duty on levels of tourism in (a) England, (b) Scotland and (c) Wales.","Biography information for Steve Double","Steve Double","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141355","141355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897953","2018-05-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-05-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions he had with animal welfare organisations between the publication of the draft Animal Welfare Bill and the publication of his Department’s response to the Second Report of the Environment, Food and Rural Affairs Committee, Pre-Legislative Scrutiny of the draft Animal Welfare (Sentencing and Recognition of Sentience) Bill 2017, HC709.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141354","141354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897954","2018-05-09","Home Office","2018-05-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the North Yorkshire police force was recently inspected by HM Inspectorate of Constabulary and Fire and Rescue Services.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141366","141366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897955","2018-05-10","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-05-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, pursuant to the oral contribution by the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union on 3 May 2018, Official Report, column 459, if he will name the countries that have stated that they will not enter into a free trade agreement with the UK if the UK remains in the Customs Union.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141359","141359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897956","2018-05-10","Home Office","2018-05-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many Windrush generation cases involve people who live in the Glasgow North East constituency.","Biography information for Mr Paul Sweeney","Mr Paul Sweeney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141374","141374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897957","2018-05-09","Department for Transport","2018-05-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made on the comparative effectiveness of conspicuous and inconspicuous speed cameras on reducing speeding.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141348","141348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897958","2018-05-09","House of Commons Commission","2018-05-04","To ask the right hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington, representing the House of Commons Commission, pursuant to the Answer of 23 February 2018 to Question 128463, on Parliamentary Estate: Plastics, what the outcome was of the Administration Committee’s consideration of the proposed 25p charge for disposable cups on the parliamentary estate; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141344","141344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897959","2018-05-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that NHS England rapidly adopts innovative medicines.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141346","141346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897960","2018-05-10","Ministry of Defence","2018-05-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which foreign governments have been alerted to the potential availability of Royal Navy (a) frigates and (b) amphibious ships that are currently in commission.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141339","141339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897961","2018-05-09","Home Office","2018-05-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made on the effect of the modern slavery strategy on preventing human trafficking.","Biography information for Joanna Cherry","Joanna Cherry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141352","141352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897962","2018-05-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the number of women in (a) Wansbeck Constituency, (b) Northumberland County and (c) the North East who might have been affected by the breast cancer screening error.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141347","141347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897963","2018-05-10","Home Office","2018-05-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many Windrush generation cases involve people who live in the Midlothian constituency.","Biography information for Danielle Rowley","Danielle Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141373","141373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897964","2018-05-10","Treasury","2018-05-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, on what date HMRC plans to close its office in Sidlaw House, Dundee.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141349","141349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897965","2018-05-10","Treasury","2018-05-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the oral contribution by the Financial Secretary to the Treasury on 7 March 2018, Official Report, column 427, how many HM Revenue & Customs staff have moved since November 2015 to a regional centre because their office closed.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141350","141350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897966","2018-05-10","Treasury","2018-05-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the oral contribution of the Financial Secretary to the Treasury on 7 March 2018, Official Report, Column 428, how many HM Revenue & Customs staff have been made redundant as a result of the closure of an HMRC office since November 2015.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141382","141382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897967","2018-05-10","Ministry of Defence","2018-05-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the average age was of regular (a) officers and (b) other ranks joining the (i) Infantry, (ii) Royal Artillery, (iii) Royal Corps of Signals, (iv) Army Medical Services, (v) Adjutant General's Corps, (vi) Royal Armoured Corps, (vii) Army Air Corps, (viii) Royal Engineers, (ix) Royal Logistics Corps, (x) Royal Electrical and Mechanical Engineers and (xi) Intelligence Corps in each of the last ten years.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141340","141340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897968","2018-05-10","Home Office","2018-05-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have been wrongly identified by automated facial recognition CCTV cameras at deployments by (a) Metropolitan Police and (b) South Wales Police.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141375","141375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897969","2018-05-09","Home Office","2018-05-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment his Department has made of the accuracy rate of real-time automated facial recognition technology on public CCTV cameras used by (a) Metropolitan Police and (b) South Wales Police.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141376","141376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897970","2018-05-10","Home Office","2018-05-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether his Department consulted mental health professionals on targeting fixated individuals not wanted for arrest on Remembrance Sunday 2017 by the Metropolitan Police.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141383","141383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897971","2018-05-10","Home Office","2018-05-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the (a) start and (b) end date is for the Metropolitan Police’s trial of real-time automated facial recognition on CCTV cameras.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141377","141377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897972","2018-05-10","Home Office","2018-05-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the (a) start and (b) end date is of South Wales Police’s trial of real-time automated facial recognition on CCTV cameras.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141378","141378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897973","2018-05-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many women in Kirkcaldy and Cowdenbeath constituency who have been affected by the changes in state pension age have (a) lodged a complaint with and (b) had that complaint reviewed by the Independent Case Examiner’s office.","Biography information for Lesley Laird","Lesley Laird","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141380","141380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897974","2018-05-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the time taken by the Independent Case Examiners Office to (a) allocate a case manager, (b) investigate a case for women affected by changes to the state pension age.","Biography information for Lesley Laird","Lesley Laird","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141381","141381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897975","2018-05-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to encourage all parties to participate in the peace process in South Sudan.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141307","141307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897976","2018-05-10","Department for Education","2018-05-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many schools will not receive a cash terms increase in their budget per pupil in (a) Coventry and (b) the West Midlands in 2018-19.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141308","141308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897977","2018-05-10","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what recent assessment he has made of the effect of the Local Government Finance Settlement 2018-19 on the ability of local authorities to fulfil their statutory responsibilities.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141309","141309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897978","2018-05-10","Ministry of Defence","2018-05-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent assessment he has made of the effect on the defence and aerospace industry of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141310","141310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897979","2018-05-09","Treasury","2018-05-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what his Department's policy is on the introduction of a cap on the total cost of rent-to-own goods; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141345","141345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897980","2018-05-09","Department for Education","2018-05-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to increase the number of apprenticeships available in the Jarrow constituency.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141384","141384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897981","2018-05-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to his oral statement of 2 May 2018, Official Report, column 315, on Breast Cancer Screening, how many women have been affected by the NHS breast screening programme failure in (a) Newcastle Gateshead clinical commissioning group and (b) South Tyneside clinical commissioning group.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141319","141319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897982","2018-05-09","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 30 April 2018 to Question 137953 on Affordable Housing: Young People, if he will publish the Government's definition of affordable housing.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141320","141320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897983","2018-05-09","Department for Transport","2018-05-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 5 March 2018 to Question 129752 on A19: Accidents, if he will publish the information for 2017.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141321","141321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897984","2018-05-09","Department for Transport","2018-05-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will undertake a review of road safety on the A19.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141322","141322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897985","2018-05-10","Department for Education","2018-05-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 3 May 2018 to Question 139388, on Teachers Pensions: Capita, which organisation conducts the external benchmarking and what criteria it applies.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141311","141311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897986","2018-05-10","Cabinet Office","2018-05-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 3 May 2018 to Question 139388, what criteria are used to rate contracts.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141312","141312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897987","2018-05-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-05-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what comparative estimate he has made of the proportion of (a) PM 10 and (b) PM 2.5 particulate matter emissions in the vicinity of an incinerator that come from the incinerator and those that exist independently in the vicinity of an incinerator.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141385","141385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897988","2018-05-09","Women and Equalities","2018-05-04","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what discussions she has had since her appointment as Minister for Women and Equalities with (a) disabled people and (b) Cabinet colleagues on the future of the Access to Elected Office Fund; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141379","141379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/895398","2018-05-03","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-05-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether UK exporters of industrial products within the EU that currently rely on conformity assessments carried out by a UK Notified Body will (a) be required to apply for new certificates issued by an EU27 Notified Body after the UK has exited the EU and (b) be provided with UK Government support to manage the effect on their business caused by changes to conformity assessment procedures when exporting to the EU after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140139","140139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897181","2018-05-08","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the extent to which family court judges are identifying families who have not attended a mediation information and assessment meeting prior to coming to court as part of the post-implementation review of the Legal Aid, Sentencing and Punishment of Offenders Act (2012).","Biography information for James Frith","James Frith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141047","141047"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897182","2018-05-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the report entitled Faith and a Future: Discrimination on the Basis of Religion or Belief in Education, published by Christian Solidarity Worldwide in February 2018, whether he has has made an assessment of the implications for his policies of that report's conclusions on discrimination against Baha’i students and school-children in Iran; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Mrs Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141000","141000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897183","2018-05-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many leak enquiries her Department has undertaken in the last two years.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140990","140990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897184","2018-05-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of NHS stocks of EpiPens; and what steps he is taking to ensure pharmacies can meet demand for EpiPens.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140985","140985"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897185","2018-05-08","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment the Government has made of the potential cost to landlords of the introduction of a cap of four week's rent on deposits.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140987","140987"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897186","2018-05-09","Cabinet Office","2018-05-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 2 May 2018 to Question137437, which of his Department's invitations to tender not published in the Official Journal of the EU during the period from April 2016 to March 2018 received no bids.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140991","140991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897187","2018-05-08","Department for Education","2018-05-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether his Department provides training for teachers to identify visual impairments in primary school children.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141023","141023"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897188","2018-05-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-05-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many kittens and cats entered the UK under the EU Pet Travel Scheme in 2016 and 2017.","Biography information for Andrea Jenkyns","Andrea Jenkyns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141045","141045"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897189","2018-05-10","Home Office","2018-05-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the subsistence rates are for victims of modern slavery supported by the National Referral Mechanism living in (a) accommodation in a safe house with food provided and (b) a safe house where they purchase their own food; and how many of such people (i) have applied for asylum and (ii) are receiving outreach support.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140986","140986"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897190","2018-05-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the proportion of mandatory reconsiderations for (a) PIP and (b) ESA applications which changed the original assessment in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140994","140994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897191","2018-05-08","Treasury","2018-05-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what representations he has received on the effectiveness of affordability checks in place by rent-to-own lenders.","Biography information for Neil Parish","Neil Parish","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141022","141022"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897192","2018-05-09","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-05-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, pursuant to the Answer of 2 May 2018 to Question 139057, on customs union, whether he plans to ensure that the analysis is conducted and made available to hon. Members before any decision in the House on a final deal on the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141056","141056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897193","2018-05-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department has taken to rectify the problems in the IT systems for the breast cancer screening programme.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141021","141021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897194","2018-05-08","Ministry of Defence","2018-05-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate his Department made (a) the volume and (b) the cost of the fuel used by the Royal Navy in its maritime operations in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141040","141040"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897195","2018-05-08","Ministry of Defence","2018-05-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) desktop, (b) laptop and (c) tablet computers were lost by his Department in the years (i) 2015-16, (ii) 2016-17 and (iii) 2017-18.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141041","141041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897196","2018-05-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 2 May 2018 to Question 139040, what written correspondence has taken place between her Department and utility companies on the effect of the introduction of universal credit on levels of debt and arrears; and if she will place copies of that correspondence in the Library.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141048","141048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897197","2018-05-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 2 May 2018 to Question 139040, on universal credit, on what dates this Utility Company Debt Group has met; who was present at each meeting of that group; and if she will place minutes of those meetings in the Library.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141049","141049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897198","2018-05-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 2 May 2018 to Question 139040, what assessment her Department has made of the effect of the introduction of universal credit on levels of utility debt and arrears; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141050","141050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897199","2018-05-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 2 May 2018 to Question 139040, on universal credit, what improvements are planned to the service her Department provides for utility companies.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141051","141051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897200","2018-05-09","Home Office","2018-05-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many asylum cases his Department has identified as complex in each of the last 10 years for which data are available.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141052","141052"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897201","2018-05-09","Home Office","2018-05-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many asylum cases his Department has identified as complex in Glasgow East constituency in each of the last 10 years for which data are available.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141053","141053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897202","2018-05-09","Home Office","2018-05-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 6 March 2018 to Question 129973 on Slavery: what the status is of victims of modern slavery for whom a decision on the grant of a residence permit has been made under the interim Home Office guidance.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140998","140998"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897203","2018-05-09","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-05-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, when he plans to respond to the letter of 29 March 2018 from the hon. Members for Birkenhead and for Ellesmere Port on the car and van manufacturing industry and the negotiations on the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140999","140999"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897204","2018-05-09","Cabinet Office","2018-05-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people were employed in the Civil Service in July 2016.","Biography information for Tommy Sheppard","Tommy Sheppard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141042","141042"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897205","2018-05-09","Cabinet Office","2018-05-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people were employed in the Civil Service in April 2018.","Biography information for Tommy Sheppard","Tommy Sheppard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141043","141043"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897206","2018-05-08","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many children in young offender institutions were locked in their cells for (a) 22 hours a day and (b) more than 22 hours a day in each of the last 5 years.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141024","141024"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897207","2018-05-08","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which young offender institutions have facilities for children to eat their meals communally.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141025","141025"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897208","2018-05-09","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 2 May 2018 to Question 137440 on Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government: Procurement, if he will publish all invitations to tender issued by his Department that received no bidders.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140992","140992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897209","2018-05-08","Home Office","2018-05-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what role (a) Capita and (b) other private contractors play in the immigration enforcement system.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140983","140983"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897210","2018-05-08","Home Office","2018-05-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what functions of Border Force have been contracted out to (a) Capita and (b) other third-party contractors.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140984","140984"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897211","2018-05-08","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-05-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the level of consistency between the recent advice of the Gambling Commission to his Department and the proposed reduction in the maximum stake for fixed-odds betting terminals to £2.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141044","141044"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897212","2018-05-08","Cabinet Office","2018-05-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to paragraph 74 of the Government Response to the 30 Year Rule Review, whether the review of the strategy for managing digital records has taken place.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140993","140993"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897213","2018-05-08","Treasury","2018-05-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the job titles are of civil servants in his Department who have been provided with (a) an official car and (b) a driver.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141001","141001"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897214","2018-05-08","Home Office","2018-05-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the job titles are of civil servants in his Department who have been provided with (a) an official car and (b) a driver.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141002","141002"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897215","2018-05-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the job titles are of civil servants in his Department who have been provided with (a) an official car and (b) a driver.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141003","141003"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897216","2018-05-08","Attorney General","2018-05-03","To ask the Attorney General, what the job titles are of civil servants in his Department who have been provided with (a) an official car and (b) a driver.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141004","141004"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897217","2018-05-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-05-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the job titles are of civil servants in his Department who have been provided with (a) an official car and (b) a driver.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141005","141005"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897218","2018-05-08","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-05-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what the job titles are of civil servants in his Department who have been provided with (a) an official car and (b) a driver.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141006","141006"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897219","2018-05-08","Department for Education","2018-05-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the job titles are of civil servants in his Department who have been provided with (a) an official car and (b) a driver.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141007","141007"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897220","2018-05-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-05-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the job titles are of civil servants in his Department who have been provided with (a) an official car and (b) a driver.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141008","141008"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897221","2018-05-08","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-05-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what the job titles are of civil servants in his Department who have been provided with (a) an official car and (b) a driver.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141009","141009"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897222","2018-05-08","Department for International Development","2018-05-03","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what the job titles are of civil servants in her Department who have been provided with (a) an official car and (b) a driver.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141010","141010"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897223","2018-05-08","Department for International Trade","2018-05-03","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what the job titles are of civil servants in his Department who have been provided with (a) an official car and (b) a driver.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141011","141011"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897224","2018-05-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the job titles are of civil servants in her Department who have been provided with (a) an official car and (b) a driver.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141012","141012"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897225","2018-05-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the job titles are of civil servants in his Department who have been provided with (a) an official car and (b) a driver.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141013","141013"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897226","2018-05-08","Ministry of Defence","2018-05-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the job titles are of civil servants in his Department who have been provided with (a) an official car and (b) a driver.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141014","141014"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897227","2018-05-08","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the job titles are of civil servants in his Department who have been provided with (a) an official car and (b) a driver.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141015","141015"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897228","2018-05-08","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to ensure that letter boxes confirm with European Standard EN 13724.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140988","140988"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897229","2018-05-08","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the physical effect on postal workers of properties with low level letterboxes.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140989","140989"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897230","2018-05-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the Government will have a role in monitoring the forthcoming general election in Bangladesh.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141017","141017"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897231","2018-05-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effect of the imprisonment of the main opposition party leader in Bangladesh on free, fair, and transparent electoral processes in that country.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141018","141018"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897232","2018-05-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what progress has been made on voter registration in rural areas in Bangladesh for the forthcoming general election in that country.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141019","141019"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897233","2018-05-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with representatives of the Bangladesh Government at the recent Commonwealth Heads of Government Meeting in London on ensuring free and fair elections in that country.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141020","141020"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897234","2018-05-09","Department for Transport","2018-05-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he has taken steps to commission a strategic environmental assessment for the proposed routes for the Oxford to Cambridge Expressway.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Dame Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140978","140978"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897235","2018-05-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-05-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate he has made of the amount of coal reserves that have planning permission to be mined for each year since 2010; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141016","141016"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897236","2018-05-09","Department for International Trade","2018-05-03","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many preferential trade agreements he plans to have (a) in draft and (b) agreed with which countries by March 2019.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140981","140981"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897237","2018-05-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 2 May, 2018 to Question 138935 and with reference to the Answer of 26 May 2016 to Question 38904, to what he attributes the increase of 10,865 in the number of bed days lost due to delayed transfers of care in Brighton and Sussex University Hospitals NHS Trust in 2017 compared with 2015.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140982","140982"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897238","2018-05-09","Department for Transport","2018-05-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the cost to the public purse was of the administrative error that resulted in personalised envelopes and communications being sent to people in Garthdee and Ferryhill in Scotland on work due to take place in Calvert in Buckinghamshire.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Dame Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140979","140979"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897239","2018-05-08","Department for Transport","2018-05-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the reasons were for notices relating to work on High Speed Two in Birmingham being sent to residents in Scotland; and what steps his Department is taking to ensure that communications errors on High Speed Two are not repeated.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Dame Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140980","140980"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897240","2018-05-08","Department for Education","2018-05-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much has been spent from the public purse under section 17 of the Children’s Act 1989 by public bodies in 2017-2018.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141026","141026"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897241","2018-05-08","Department for Education","2018-05-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which (a) schools and (b) colleges received funding from the £520 million allocated by his Department to disadvantaged students aged 16-19 years old; and how much of that funding was spend by each institution.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141027","141027"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897242","2018-05-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many applications for Social Fund funeral payments were made in each year between 2015 and 2018; how many such applications were refused; and what the (a) average and (b) lowest payment that was made.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141028","141028"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897243","2018-05-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many Social Fund Budgeting loans to cover funeral costs were (a) approved and (b) rejected in each of the last five years; and what the (a) average and (b) lowest payment was for a Social Fund Budgeting loans.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141029","141029"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897244","2018-05-09","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-05-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate he has made of the (a) cost to the public purse and (b) time-scale for setting up a British Global Navigation Satellite System.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141054","141054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897245","2018-05-09","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-05-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the UK Space Agency's announcement on the development of a British Global Navigation Satellite System published on 2 May 2018, what contingency plans his Department has put in place in the event that the UK is denied access to data for satellite navigation.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141055","141055"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897246","2018-05-08","Department for Education","2018-05-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what pathways his Department has established at schools for the identification of children with dyslexia.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141030","141030"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897247","2018-05-08","Department for Education","2018-05-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what comparative estimate he has made of the number of school children with dyslexia who were subject to (a) education, health and care plans and (b) statements under the previous SEN and learning difficulties assessments in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141031","141031"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897248","2018-05-08","Department for Education","2018-05-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether his Department provides training for teachers to identify dyslexia in primary school children.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141032","141032"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897249","2018-05-08","Department for Education","2018-05-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what pathways his Department has established at schools for the identification of children with autism in schools.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141033","141033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897250","2018-05-08","Department for Education","2018-05-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether his Department provides training for teachers to identify autism in primary school children.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141034","141034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897251","2018-05-08","Department for Education","2018-05-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what comparative estimate he has made of the number of school children with autism who were subject to (a) education, health and care plans and (b) statements under the previous SEN and learning difficulties assessments in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141035","141035"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897252","2018-05-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many job seekers diagnosed with dyslexia have been sanctioned for failure to submit (a) paperwork and (b) online documentation in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141036","141036"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897253","2018-05-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many job seekers diagnosed with autism have been sanctioned for failure to submit (a) paperwork and (b) online documentation in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141037","141037"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897254","2018-05-08","Cabinet Office","2018-05-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the number of people with dyslexia who are (a) unemployed and (b) not in training or further education.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141038","141038"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897255","2018-05-08","Cabinet Office","2018-05-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the number of school leavers and adults with dyslexia who are (a) in work and (b) in training or further education.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141039","141039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897256","2018-05-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of internal advice given by her Department on pension rights to employees being made redundant on medical grounds.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140995","140995"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897257","2018-05-09","Treasury","2018-05-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what procedures his Department has in place to (a) support and (b) audit local authority (i) procurement and (ii) management of private finance initiative contracts.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141046","141046"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897258","2018-05-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of procedures in her Department to enable employees whose health has been shown by to be affected by intensive online and computer work as part of their employment to be redeployed to alternative work in her Department.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140996","140996"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897259","2018-05-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will publish the current (a) procedures and (b) safeguards her Department operates for employees who (a) have and (b) are developing disabilities.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140997","140997"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897302","2018-05-08","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will ensure that the review of the Legal Aid, Sentencing and Punishment of Offenders Act 2012 includes a cross-departmental analysis of the overlapping personal, social and economic effects of that Act on people who were previously entitled to legal aid.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141077","141077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897303","2018-05-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 26 March 2018 to Question 134167, what the timescale is for bringing forward legislative proposals to bring into effect automatic split payments of universal credit.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141078","141078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896165","2018-05-02","Wales Office","2018-05-02","What recent discussions he has had with the Welsh Government on building a new prison in South Wales.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 905019","905019"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896241","2018-05-08","Department for Education","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he made of the change in the number of children entering the care system since 2010.","Biography information for Lucy Allan","Lucy Allan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140794","140794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896242","2018-05-08","Treasury","2018-05-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will made an assessment of the potential merits of a lower rate tax-band for the hospitality industry in Northern Ireland to better compete with the tax system for the hospitality industry in the Irish Republic.","Biography information for Paul Girvan","Paul Girvan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140853","140853"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896243","2018-05-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what criteria are used for judging whether a Support for Mortgage Interest claimant has the mental capacity to make a decision about the new loan.","Biography information for Margaret Greenwood","Margaret Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140788","140788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896244","2018-05-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, which groups of people will be brought into in-work conditionality under Universal Credit who would not previously have been subject to it and the estimated numbers in each group.","Biography information for Margaret Greenwood","Margaret Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140789","140789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896245","2018-05-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what her Department's current estimate is of the total number of additional people who will be brought into in-work conditionality under universal credit by the time that the roll-out of universal credit has been completed.","Biography information for Margaret Greenwood","Margaret Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140790","140790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896246","2018-05-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 14 March to Question 131104 on Drugs: Costs, what assessment he has made of the cost of branded medicines (a) to the NHS and (b) in comparison with the health systems in other EU countries.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140557","140557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896247","2018-05-08","Home Office","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 23 February to Question 128850 on motor vehicles: theft, if she will (a) review her policy of charging victims of car theft to retrieve their vehicles and (b) exempt stolen vehicles from the statutorily prescribed charges for the recovery and storage of vehicles recovered by the emergency services.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140558","140558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896248","2018-05-08","Northern Ireland Office","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what recent discussions she has had with representatives of the devolved administrations on waiving the costs of child burials.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140616","140616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896249","2018-05-08","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what plans he has to visit Northern Ireland to meet with representatives of the creative industries.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140617","140617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896250","2018-05-08","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many and what proportion of decisions of public planning inquiries did not follow the advice of the planning inspector in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140674","140674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896251","2018-05-09","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the potential effectiveness of introducing legislation in order to prevent the use of employer-mandated insurance as a means of controlling the activities of workers in the gig economy.","Biography information for Darren Jones","Darren Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140850","140850"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896252","2018-05-09","Cabinet Office","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, for what reasons his Department has not launched a public consultation on the potential changes to the Consolidated Guidance to Intelligence Officers and Service Personnel on the Detention and Interviewing of Detainees Overseas, and on the Passing and Receipt of Intelligence Relating to Detainees.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140559","140559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896253","2018-05-09","Department for Transport","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will disqualify Stagecoach from bidding for (a) the east coast main line and (b) all future rail franchise contracts.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140560","140560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896254","2018-05-08","Department for Education","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether his Department provides training for teachers to identify development co-ordination disorder in primary school children.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140755","140755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896255","2018-05-08","Department for Education","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what comparative estimate he has made of the number of school children with dyspraxia who are subject to Education Health Care Plans and those with statements under the previous SEN and learning difficulties assessments in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140756","140756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896256","2018-05-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many job seekers diagnosed with (a) dyspraxia and (b) other neurodivergent conditions have been sanctioned for failure to submit (i) paperwork or (ii) online documentation in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140757","140757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896257","2018-05-08","Department for Education","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what meetings he has held with representatives of local authorities on private fostering arrangements in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140758","140758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896258","2018-05-09","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of all energy network companies refunding excess profits to consumers.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140693","140693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896259","2018-05-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the time frame set by her Department is within which staff should correct a payment error following notification.","Biography information for Margaret Greenwood","Margaret Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140791","140791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896260","2018-05-09","Treasury","2018-05-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what legislative changes were made to enable employers to report real-time information on taxation to HMRC.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140787","140787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896261","2018-05-08","Attorney General","2018-05-02","To ask the Attorney General, what steps he is taking to improve levels of prosecutions for domestic violence against men.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140675","140675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896262","2018-05-08","Treasury","2018-05-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of the withdrawal of credit card payment facilities on changes to the level of personal tax collected by HMRC.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140676","140676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896263","2018-05-08","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of intermediaries were used for (a) witnesses, (b) victims and (c) defendants in the latest year for which information is available.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140677","140677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896264","2018-05-08","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) absconds and (b) escapes from prison occurred in each month of the most recent year for which information is available.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140678","140678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896265","2018-05-08","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many offenders serving a sentence for murder (a) absconded and (b) escaped in the last year for which data is available; and what the circumstances were in which each of those offenders absconded or escaped.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140679","140679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896266","2018-05-08","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners in open prisons as of 1 May 2018 have previously (a) absconded or failed to return to prison or (b) breached the conditions of their temporary licence.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140680","140680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896267","2018-05-08","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) offences in West Yorkshire were committed by offenders on bail and (b) offenders in West Yorkshire committed offences while on bail during the most recent year for which information is available.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140681","140681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896268","2018-05-08","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many offenders had (a) between 15 and 49, (b) between 50 and 99 and (c) 100 or more convictions in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140682","140682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896269","2018-05-08","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average cost to the public purse has been of preparing a (a) full pre-sentence report and (b) fast delivery report in magistrates' courts which includes the time spent by probation staff in court whilst the report is being delivered and considered in the last twelve months for which data are available.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140683","140683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896270","2018-05-08","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will estimate the cost to the public purse of the production of pre-sentence reports for courts in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140684","140684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896271","2018-05-08","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the rate of utilisation was of each magistrates' court in the latest year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140685","140685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896272","2018-05-08","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been murdered since 2012 by people who were previously convicted of murder and then released having served their prison sentences.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140686","140686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896273","2018-05-08","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of changes in the prevalence of squatting in commercial premises following the introduction of the criminal provisions contained in the Legal Aid, Sentencing and Punishment of Offenders Act 2012.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140687","140687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896274","2018-05-08","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent research his Department has commissioned into the cost implications of increasing magistrates sentencing powers to 12 months for a single offence; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140688","140688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896275","2018-05-08","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether he has plans to increase magistrates' sentencing powers to 12 months for a single offence; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140689","140689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896276","2018-05-08","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many offenders were sentenced to a custodial sentence of 12 months or less by offence by each Crown Court in the latest year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140690","140690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896277","2018-05-08","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of offenders who received a custodial sentence have previously served (a) no, (b) between one and four, (c) between five and nine and (d) more than 10 community sentences in the most recent year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140691","140691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896278","2018-05-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, to what projects and programmes the entries in the spreadsheet published as his Department’s transparency document, entitled DWP payments over £25,000 for December 2017, relate.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140574","140574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896279","2018-05-09","Department for Education","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the school roll was of pupils at state schools in (a) West Sussex and (b) England; and what the school roll was in (a) reception and (b) sixth form for those schools in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140544","140544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896280","2018-05-08","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what representations he has received from legal representatives of UK citizens on fair and equitable justice for UK victims of terrorists attacks by ETA.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140618","140618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896281","2018-05-09","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, if he will hold discussions with the BBC on increasing the level of transparency of its commissioning processes.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140642","140642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896282","2018-05-09","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many appeals there have been against Education and Health Care Plan decisions; how many such appeals have been successful; and what the cost to the public purse was of each appeal.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140759","140759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896283","2018-05-08","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what information his Department holds on which UK organisations receive funding from the EU Rights, Equality and Citizenship Programme.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140760","140760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896284","2018-05-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment she has made of trends in the level of (a) detection and (b) reporting of hydrocarbon releases from oil and gas installations on the UK continental shelf since 2010.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140715","140715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896285","2018-05-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what legal identity is planned to be in place to prevent EU vessels operating inside the Orkney and Shetland 12 nautical mile zone during the proposed 21-month implementation period after EU treaties and the derogation for exclusive use of the Orkney and Shetland 12 nautical mile zone cease to apply to the UK.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140647","140647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896286","2018-05-08","Northern Ireland Office","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what discussions the Government held with the EU Commission on the (a) administrative arrangements, (b) visit programme and (c) agenda items for the visit by Michel Barnier to Northern Ireland on 30 April and 1 May 2018.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140619","140619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896287","2018-05-08","Home Office","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many notices of removal from the UK were issued in error by his Department in the last 10 years.","Biography information for Hugh Gaffney","Hugh Gaffney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140846","140846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896288","2018-05-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people claiming universal credit in Easington constituency have been reclassified at the mandatory reconsideration stage from being from fit to work to having limited capability to work in each month since the full roll out of universal credit in October 2017.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140702","140702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896289","2018-05-09","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of promoting the UK's visit economy by providing (a) financial and (b) other support to destination marketing organisations.","Biography information for Wera Hobhouse","Wera Hobhouse","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140841","140841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896290","2018-05-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what plans he has to vary the work commitments under Petroleum Exploration and Development Licence 189.","Biography information for Christian Matheson","Christian Matheson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140793","140793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896291","2018-05-09","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to Annex 2 of Ofcom’s Public Sector Spectrum Release of 2 March 2016, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of the 1375 to 1400 MHz band as a longer-term option for sharing.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140640","140640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896292","2018-05-08","Treasury","2018-05-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the average length of time was for HMRC to notify people of their failure to complete their tax self-assessment by the deadline in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Chris Elmore","Chris Elmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140833","140833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896293","2018-05-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information his Department holds on the timetable for the beds being used by non-spinal cord injured patients in the (a) National Spinal Injuries Centre at Stoke Mandeville and (b) Yorkshire Regional Spinal Injuries Centre, Pinderfields to be returned to use by spinal cord injured patients.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140655","140655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896294","2018-05-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information his Department holds on the number and proportion of spinal cord injured patients who are treated in a specialist spinal cord injury centre for their initial rehabilitation relative to those who receive that rehabilitation in a different clinical or other setting (a) nationally, (b) by country and (c) by region.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140656","140656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896295","2018-05-08","Department for Transport","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the most recent acceptance rate was for Need to Sell applications for phase 2b of High Speed 2.","Biography information for Antoinette Sandbach","Antoinette Sandbach","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140832","140832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896296","2018-05-08","Department for Education","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when he plans to respond to Question 137063 on Social Mobility Commission: Public Appointments, tabled by the hon. Member for Ashton-under Lyne on 23 April 2018.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140774","140774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896297","2018-05-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what comparative assessment he has made of the UK's ranking in life expectancy at birth for (a) males and (b) females over the last eight years against that of other EU member states.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140604","140604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896298","2018-05-09","Home Office","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether non-UK EU nationals who were resident in the UK before 1973 have a legal right to abode in the UK that is separate from their rights as EU citizens under the Treaties of the European Union.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140712","140712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896299","2018-05-08","Department for Transport","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of downgrading (a) C and (b) unsurfaced unclassified roads to bridleways.","Biography information for Sir Hugo Swire","Sir Hugo Swire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140641","140641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896300","2018-05-09","Department for International Development","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent assessment she has made of the humanitarian situation in Kachin and Karen states in Myanmar.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140552","140552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896301","2018-05-09","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 30 April 2018 to Question 137976 on Social Media: Children, and with reference to the ASA news release of 30 June 2017 stating Ads that directly or indirectly promote an HFSS product cannot appear in children’s media, if he will provide a list of those websites which cannot display such adverts.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140649","140649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896302","2018-05-09","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 30 April 2018 to Question 137975 on Social Media: Children, which organisation holds that information.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140650","140650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896303","2018-05-09","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, for what reason the draft revised National Planning Policy Framework does not make reference to local wildlife sites.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140657","140657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896304","2018-05-09","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will include local wildlife sites in Footnote 7 of the revised National Planning Policy Framework that lists the sites that are protected by policies that should restrict development.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140658","140658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896305","2018-05-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much funding has been allocated by (a) Government (b) the EU to Natural England for the implementation of  Shared Nitrogen Action Plans; what annual spend was of Natural England for that work; and how many employees of National England have been located to the delivery of that work.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140659","140659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896306","2018-05-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what representations his Department has received on plans for an opencast mine at a site in Bradley, County Durham; and what discussions he has had with (a) Natural England and (b) Durham County Council on mitigation plans for managing the impact of that mining on the great crested newts in the south of the development area.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140660","140660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896307","2018-05-08","Home Office","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the timetable is for all Biometric Residence Permits to include national insurance numbers.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140822","140822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896308","2018-05-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans the Government has to include proposals on improving social care and support for people with learning difficulties in its forthcoming Green Paper on care and support for older people.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140718","140718"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896309","2018-05-09","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prison officers that work at prisons where the overall performance is rated as being of concern worked on detached duty at another prison at for a period in 2018.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140828","140828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896310","2018-05-09","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prison officers that worked at prisons in special measures worked on detached duty at another prison for a period in 2018.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140829","140829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896311","2018-05-09","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average waiting time was for an employment tribunal appeal hearing at each Immigration and Asylum tribunal hearing venue in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140830","140830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896312","2018-05-09","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average waiting time was for an employment tribunal appeal hearing at each First-tier Social Security and Child Support tribunal hearing venue in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140831","140831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896313","2018-05-09","Home Office","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether he plans to bring forward legislative proposals to give effect to the agreement reached with the EU on (a) the rights of Irish citizens living in the UK and (b) the operation of the Common Travel Area after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140594","140594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896314","2018-05-09","Home Office","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many citizens of the Republic of Ireland living in the UK have (a) applied for and (b) been granted British citizenship in each of the last 5 years.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140595","140595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896315","2018-05-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans he has to amend the pollution inventory reporting guidance sent to incinerator operators.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140553","140553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896316","2018-05-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of personal independence payment recipients receive the mobility element of the benefit due solely to a visual impairment.","Biography information for Jo Swinson","Jo Swinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140666","140666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896317","2018-05-09","Prime Minister","2018-05-02","To ask the Prime Minister, pursuant to the Answer of 27 April 2018 to Question 137505, what information Prime Minister Modi provided on Jagtar Singh Johal's case and treatment.","Biography information for Jo Swinson","Jo Swinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140667","140667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896318","2018-05-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to improve the monitoring of consultants in the independent sector who operate under practising privileges.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140596","140596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896319","2018-05-08","Home Office","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when he plans to publish the outcome of the Government's review of air weapon regulation, announced on 12 December 2017.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140603","140603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896320","2018-05-09","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 19 April 2018 to Question 134643, on Housing: Construction, in the event that all other options have been explored whether a Local Plan that does not meet objectively assessed need can still be passed by a Planning Inspector.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140597","140597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896321","2018-05-09","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the oral answer to the hon. Member for Halton on 30 April 2018, Official Report column 16, what the evidential basis is for the answer.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140598","140598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896322","2018-05-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when he plans to publish the new national stroke plan for England.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140599","140599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896323","2018-05-08","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the effect of his Department's review of gaming machines on trends in the level of betting shop closures.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140703","140703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896324","2018-05-08","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment his Department has made the effect of potential betting shop closures as a result of changes to the maximum stake on fixed-odds betting terminals on trends in the level of illegal gambling.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140704","140704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896325","2018-05-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the Written Ministerial Statement of 20 March 2018 on NHS Planning in 2018-19, HCWS571, when he plans to lay before Parliament the NHS Mandate for 2018-19.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140719","140719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896326","2018-05-09","Home Office","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 22 February 2018 to Question 128120, on Doctors: Migrant Workers, how many applications there were for visas for work using sponsorship certificates for Human Health and Social Work Activities; and how many of those applications were (a) successful and (b) refused, in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140720","140720"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896327","2018-05-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to improve the detection and treatment of (a) food and (b) other allergies.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140721","140721"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896328","2018-05-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent representations he has received from (a) charities, (b) medical professionals and (c) patient groups on the (i) detection and (ii) treatment of allergic diseases.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140722","140722"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896329","2018-05-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information his Department holds on the number of people who have suffered from migraine in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140723","140723"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896330","2018-05-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what research his Department has (a) undertaken and (b) commissioned on the effect of the length of distance a patient travelled to an A&E Department on the level of fatalities after admission.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140724","140724"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896331","2018-05-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions (a) Ministers, (b) special Advisers and (c) senior officials of his Department have had with representatives of (i) the Food and Drink Federation, (ii) Coca-Cola, (iii) PepsiCo and (iv) the British Soft Drinks Association in each of the last 18 months; and what the subject of each of those meetings was.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140725","140725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896332","2018-05-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions Ministers of his Department have had with the insurance industry on cover for NHS buildings in the last three years.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140726","140726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896333","2018-05-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, which hospitals he has visited in an official capacity since 2016-17; and what the date of each such visit was.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140727","140727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896334","2018-05-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, which (a) organisations and (b) individuals were consulted by NHS England when it was developing its proposal to move commissioning of dialysis to clinical commissioning groups; and if he will publish the contents of the submissions which were received in response to that consultation.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140728","140728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896335","2018-05-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what his policy is on use of grant funding provided by his Department to third parties to lobby his Department.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140729","140729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896336","2018-05-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many patients died due to a hospital acquired infection in primary care trusts in (a) 2017, (b) 2016, (c) 2015, (d) 2014 and (e) 2013.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140730","140730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896337","2018-05-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many defibrillators are provided in each building his Department manages.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140731","140731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896338","2018-05-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what data the Government collects centrally on whether (a) standard fire safety checks around building structures, (b) escape routes, (c) fire alarms and (d) sprinklers are up to date across all NHS sites.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140732","140732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896339","2018-05-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans he has to improve the matching of donated lungs with people waiting for lung transplants.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140733","140733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896340","2018-05-08","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the level of the contribution of the heritage aviation sector to the UK economy.","Biography information for Leo Docherty","Leo Docherty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140839","140839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896341","2018-05-08","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department is taking to support airshows throughout the UK.","Biography information for Leo Docherty","Leo Docherty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140840","140840"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896342","2018-05-09","Ministry of Defence","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many women have been recruited to the Army in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140643","140643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896343","2018-05-08","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department is taking to promote tourism in outer London.","Biography information for Sir David Evennett","David Evennett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140608","140608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896344","2018-05-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans he has to bring forward legislative proposals for integrated care systems in the NHS.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140568","140568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896345","2018-05-08","Home Office","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have been stopped and searched in (a) London, (b) the London Borough of Bexley and (c) Bexleyheath and Crayford constituency in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sir David Evennett","David Evennett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140609","140609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896346","2018-05-08","Ministry of Defence","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to ensure that the 296 Stoke Newington Air Training Corps will be relocated following the closure of the site on the Albion Road.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140694","140694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896347","2018-05-08","Home Office","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department,  how many people were stopped and searched by the Police in each of the last five years; and how many of those people were subsequently arrested.","Biography information for Sir David Evennett","David Evennett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140610","140610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896348","2018-05-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his counterpart in Myanmar on the treatment of minority communities in that country’s Rakhine and Kachin provinces.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140569","140569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896349","2018-05-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of providing flour fortified with folic acid to (a) pregnant women and (b) children; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140570","140570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896350","2018-05-09","Home Office","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the criteria are for recruitment of Border Force personnel; and whether those criteria are applied consistently throughout the UK.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140644","140644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896351","2018-05-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what estimate he has made of the number of UK citizens that will travel to Russia for the 2018 World Cup.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140651","140651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896352","2018-05-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what information his Department holds on the number of UK citizens that have cancelled a visit to Russia for the World Cup as a result of security concerns after the attempted murder of Sergei Skripal and his daughter.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140652","140652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896353","2018-05-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with NATO partners on tackling terrorism by groups based in Pakistan.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140620","140620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896354","2018-05-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many updates have been made to the Be on the Ball travel advice since June 2017; and on what dates those updates were published.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140653","140653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896355","2018-05-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many officials from the Foreign and Commonwealth Office will be in Russia for the duration of the 2018 World Cup to provide assistance to UK citizens.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140654","140654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896356","2018-05-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations his Department has made to the Iranian government on the 1991 policy which requires that Baha’i students are blocked from admission to universities or expelled once it becomes known that they are Baha’is; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Mrs Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140602","140602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896357","2018-05-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the effect of disease on trees.","Biography information for Neil Parish","Neil Parish","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140711","140711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896358","2018-05-08","Home Office","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of knife crime incidents recorded in England in the last year for which figures are available were linked to criminal drug taking activity; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Selous","Andrew Selous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140648","140648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896359","2018-05-09","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what discussions he has had with the Minister for the Northern Powerhouse on the Shop Direct closure in Greater Manchester.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140773","140773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896360","2018-05-08","Department for Transport","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when his Department last audited the Civil Aviation Authority's airspace change process.","Biography information for Robert Courts","Robert Courts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140838","140838"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896361","2018-05-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 30 April 2018 to Question 137984, on seas and oceans: environment protection, whether the UK Government voted in support of measure 053 on increasing marine protected area coverage for effective marine biodiversity conservation at the IUCN World Conservation Congress 2016.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140661","140661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896362","2018-05-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many households are not able to access the Warm Home Discount Scheme due to their energy supplier being exempt from the obligation to offer that discount to its customers.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140532","140532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896363","2018-05-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many vulnerable energy customers are not able to access the Warm Home Discount Scheme due to their energy supplier being exempt from providing that scheme.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140533","140533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896364","2018-05-09","Department for Education","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what information his Department holds on the subject content of personal, social health education and citizenship teaching in (a) primary and (b) secondary schools; and if he will make that subject a statutory component of the national curriculum.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140834","140834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896365","2018-05-09","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 30 April 2018 to Question 138105, whether regulations pertaining to fire safety are included within those assessed for the business impact target.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140867","140867"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896366","2018-05-09","Treasury","2018-05-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with Royal Bank of Scotland representatives on branch closures in Manchester.","Biography information for Jeff Smith","Jeff Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140823","140823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896367","2018-05-09","Treasury","2018-05-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many Royal Bank of Scotland branches have been closed in (a) Manchester and (b) England in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Jeff Smith","Jeff Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140824","140824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896368","2018-05-09","Home Office","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions he has had with his Canadian counterpart on the provision of legal access to medicinal cannabis.","Biography information for Jeff Smith","Jeff Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140825","140825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896369","2018-05-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate his Department has made of the number of child and adolescent mental health psychiatrists who have been hired in (a) Manchester and (b) the UK in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jeff Smith","Jeff Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140826","140826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896370","2018-05-09","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department has taken to support the live music industry in (a) Manchester and (b) the UK.","Biography information for Jeff Smith","Jeff Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140827","140827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896371","2018-05-09","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what discussions he has had with his EU counterparts on (a) UK access to the Galileo project after the UK leaves the EU and (b) a rebate for UK monies paid to that project in the event that full access is not granted; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140611","140611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896372","2018-05-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the level of destruction and damage caused by scallop dredging; and if he will review that practice in order to limit its potentially detrimental effects..","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140612","140612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896373","2018-05-08","Cabinet Office","2018-05-02","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what training is provided to (a) general civil servants, (b) fast stream civil servants and (c) senior civil servants on the scrutiny and legislative role of Parliament.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140621","140621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896374","2018-05-08","Cabinet Office","2018-05-02","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will make an assessment of the effectiveness of the KPMG Civil Service Learning contract for the provision of civil service training.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140622","140622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896375","2018-05-09","Department for Transport","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will issue guidance to local highway authorities to ensure they have comprehensive and effective programmes to identify and repair potholes that require urgent attention.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140613","140613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896376","2018-05-08","Department for Transport","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he plans to issue space port licences for (a) horizontal and (b) vertical take off.","Biography information for Bill Grant","Bill Grant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140842","140842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896377","2018-05-08","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what training his Department has provided to (a) general civil servants, (b) fast stream civil servants and (c) senior civil servants on devolution and inter-governmental relations; how many such courses have taken place; and how many civil servants have attended such training courses in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140623","140623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896378","2018-05-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether the Government has made an assessment of the potential merits of reducing the cervical cancer screening age.","Biography information for Colleen Fletcher","Colleen Fletcher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140779","140779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896379","2018-05-08","Department for International Trade","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what training his Department has provided to (a) general civil servants, (b) fast stream civil servants and (c) senior civil servants on devolution and inter-governmental relations; how many such courses have taken place; and how many civil servants have attended such training courses in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140624","140624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896380","2018-05-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what training his Department has provided to (a) general civil servants, (b) fast stream civil servants and (c) senior civil servants on devolution and inter-governmental relations; how many such courses have taken place; and how many civil servants have attended such training courses in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140625","140625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896381","2018-05-08","Department for International Development","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what training her Department has provided to (a) general civil servants, (b) fast stream civil servants and (c) senior civil servants on devolution and inter-governmental relations; how many such courses have taken place; and how many civil servants have attended such training courses in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140626","140626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896382","2018-05-08","Ministry of Defence","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what training his Department has provided to (a) general civil servants, (b) fast stream civil servants and (c) senior civil servants on devolution and inter-governmental relations; how many such courses have taken place; and how many civil servants have attended such training courses in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140627","140627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896383","2018-05-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what training his Department has provided to (a) general civil servants, (b) fast stream civil servants and (c) senior civil servants on devolution and inter-governmental relations; how many such courses have taken place; and how many civil servants have attended such training courses in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140628","140628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896384","2018-05-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what training her Department has provided to (a) general civil servants, (b) fast stream civil servants and (c) senior civil servants on devolution and inter-governmental relations; how many such courses have taken place; and how many civil servants have attended such training courses in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140629","140629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896385","2018-05-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of social media on young people's mental health.","Biography information for Colleen Fletcher","Colleen Fletcher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140780","140780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896386","2018-05-08","Treasury","2018-05-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what training his Department has provided to (a) general civil servants, (b) fast stream civil servants and (c) senior civil servants on devolution and inter-governmental relations; how many such courses have taken place; and how many civil servants have attended such training courses in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140630","140630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896387","2018-05-08","Department for Transport","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what training his Department has provided to (a) general civil servants, (b) fast stream civil servants and (c) senior civil servants on devolution and inter-governmental relations; how many such courses have taken place; and how many civil servants have attended such training courses in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140631","140631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896388","2018-05-08","Home Office","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what training his Department has provided to (a) general civil servants, (b) fast stream civil servants and (c) senior civil servants on devolution and inter-governmental relations; how many such courses have taken place; and how many civil servants have attended such training courses in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140632","140632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896389","2018-05-08","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what training his Department has provided to (a) general civil servants, (b) fast stream civil servants and (c) senior civil servants on devolution and inter-governmental relations; how many such courses have taken place; and how many civil servants have attended such training courses in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140633","140633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896390","2018-05-08","Women and Equalities","2018-05-02","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what training her Department has provided to (a) general civil servants, (b) fast stream civil servants and (c) senior civil servants on devolution and inter-governmental relations; how many such courses have taken place; and how many civil servants have attended such training courses in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140634","140634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896391","2018-05-08","Department for Education","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what training his Department has provided to (a) general civil servants, (b) fast stream civil servants and (c) senior civil servants on devolution and inter-governmental relations; how many such courses have taken place; and how many civil servants have attended such training courses in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140635","140635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896392","2018-05-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what training his Department has provided to (a) general civil servants, (b) fast stream civil servants and (c) senior civil servants on devolution and inter-governmental relations; how many such courses have taken place; and how many civil servants have attended such training courses in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140636","140636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896393","2018-05-08","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what training his Department has provided to (a) general civil servants, (b) fast stream civil servants and (c) senior civil servants on devolution and inter-governmental relations; how many such courses have taken place; and how many civil servants have attended such training courses in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140637","140637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896394","2018-05-08","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what training his Department has provided to (a) general civil servants, (b) fast stream civil servants and (c) senior civil servants on devolution and inter-governmental relations; how many such courses have taken place; and how many civil servants have attended such training courses in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140638","140638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896395","2018-05-08","Wales Office","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what training his Department has provided to (a) general civil servants, (b) fast stream civil servants and (c) senior civil servants on devolution and inter-governmental relations; how many such courses have taken place; and how many civil servants have attended such training courses in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140639","140639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896396","2018-05-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department has made an assessment of the effect of the UK leaving the EU on medical research into blood cancer.","Biography information for Colleen Fletcher","Colleen Fletcher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140781","140781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896397","2018-05-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate his Department has made of the number of NHS staff shortages in (a) Coventry and (b) the West Midlands.","Biography information for Colleen Fletcher","Colleen Fletcher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140782","140782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896398","2018-05-09","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of appeals to tribunals in (a) Coventry, (b) the West Midlands and (c) England which related to (i) personal independence payments, (ii) employment and support allowance, (iii) income support, (iv) jobseeker's allowance and (v) tax credits were successful in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Colleen Fletcher","Colleen Fletcher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140783","140783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896399","2018-05-09","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average cost to the public purse is to administer a First-tier Tribunal (Social Security and Child Support Appeal) in respect of personal independence payments.","Biography information for Colleen Fletcher","Colleen Fletcher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140784","140784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896400","2018-05-09","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many appellants in (a) Coventry, (b) the West Midlands and (c) England are waiting for the Tribunals Service to list their First-Tier Tribunal Social Security and Child Support appeal in relation to personal independence payments.","Biography information for Colleen Fletcher","Colleen Fletcher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140785","140785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896401","2018-05-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the oral contribution of the Parliamentary Under Secretary of State for Family Support, Housing and Child Maintenance of 26 March 2018, Official Report, column 506, whether there is a time limit for Support for Mortgage Interest claimants to reconsider their decision not to apply for a loan and apply for that loan backdating their claim to 6 April 2018.","Biography information for Margaret Greenwood","Margaret Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140792","140792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896402","2018-05-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many children aged four and under in (a) Coventry North East constituency and (b) Coventry local authority area were admitted to hospital for a tooth extraction due to decay in each of the last two years.","Biography information for Colleen Fletcher","Colleen Fletcher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140786","140786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896403","2018-05-09","Attorney General","2018-05-02","To ask the Attorney General, if he will make it his policy to disburse the monies held by the National Fund to good causes.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140746","140746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896404","2018-05-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of (a) the availability of current options for treatment on the NHS for patients with acute myeloid leukaemia and (b) the need for new options for treatment to be made available on the NHS in that area of disease.","Biography information for Mark Tami","Mark Tami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140614","140614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896405","2018-05-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions he has had with NICE on the need for (a) new treatment options to be made available on the NHS for patients with acute myeloid leukaemia and (b) open and ongoing dialogue with pharmaceutical companies throughout the technology appraisal process to ensure that patients are able to access new and innovative medicines on the NHS.","Biography information for Mark Tami","Mark Tami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140615","140615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896406","2018-05-09","Attorney General","2018-05-02","To ask the Attorney General, what restrictions are in place to prevent the National Fund being freed for use for good causes.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140747","140747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896407","2018-05-09","Attorney General","2018-05-02","To ask the Attorney General, what steps would need to be taken to enable the National Fund to be released for use for good causes.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140748","140748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896408","2018-05-09","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Government's consultation, Powers for dealing with unauthorised development and encampments, launched on 5 April 2018, what meetings he has had with representatives of the Gypsy, Traveller and Roma communities (a) prior to and (b) since launching that consultation.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140713","140713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896409","2018-05-09","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Government's consultation, Powers for dealing with unauthorised development and encampments, launched on 5 April 2018, what meetings he plans to have with representatives of the Gypsy, Traveller and Roma communities before that consultation closes on 15 June 2018.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140714","140714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896410","2018-05-09","Attorney General","2018-05-02","To ask the Attorney General, what assessment he has made of the timescale required for the National Fund be be of equal value to the National Debt.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140749","140749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896411","2018-05-08","Cabinet Office","2018-05-02","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to his Department's publication entitled Expenditure over £25,000 - March 2018, published on 2 May 2018, what the payments to Calder World of Travel were for.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140575","140575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896412","2018-05-08","Cabinet Office","2018-05-02","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to his Department's publication entitled Expenditure over £25,000 - March 2018, published on 2 May 2018, for what parts of the grants efficiency accelerator programme the payments to Ernst & Young were made.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140576","140576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896413","2018-05-09","Cabinet Office","2018-05-02","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to his Department's publication entitled Expenditure over £25,000 - March 2018, published on 2 May 2018, for what parts of Civil Service Learning are the payments to Capita Business Services Ltd.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140577","140577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896414","2018-05-08","Home Office","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether he has commissioned research on the motivations of the perpetrators of gang-grooming crimes against young girls; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lucy Allan","Lucy Allan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140795","140795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896415","2018-05-09","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he has taken to tackle racism in grassroots football.","Biography information for Fiona Onasanya","Fiona Onasanya","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140852","140852"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896416","2018-05-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the Takeover Code following the take over of GKN by Melrose.","Biography information for Lucy Allan","Lucy Allan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140796","140796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896417","2018-05-08","Department for Education","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to increase the number of degree apprenticeships available in the Telford constituency.","Biography information for Lucy Allan","Lucy Allan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140797","140797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896418","2018-05-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to the Sudanese Government on its alleged use of chemical weapons; and what steps the Government is taking to ensure that those allegations are investigated.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140554","140554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896419","2018-05-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what plans he has to amend Schedule 3 of the Gas Safety (Management) Regulations 1996 to prepare for increased use of hydrogen gas being conveyed in the network.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140534","140534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896420","2018-05-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer the 6 April 2018 to Question 134603 on fracking, what the timetable is for up-to-date estimates of the number of fracking wells to be published.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140535","140535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896421","2018-05-08","Department for Transport","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment has been made of the potential effect on the Blick Mead archaeological site of the proposed alterations to the A303 around Stonehenge.","Biography information for Alex Burghart","Alex Burghart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140843","140843"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896422","2018-05-08","Department for Transport","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 29 March 2018 to Question 133829 on aviation, whether he still plans to publish the Aviation Strategy in 2018.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140536","140536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896423","2018-05-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, which NHS ambulance trusts (a) do and (b) do not have a policy of giving IV tranexamic acid to bleeding trauma patients.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140593","140593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896424","2018-05-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of mandatory reconsiderations have upheld the original decision on personal independence payment in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Matt Western","Matt Western","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140847","140847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896425","2018-05-08","Department for Transport","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the Government has set a publication date for the Pathway to Zero Emission Road Transport Strategy document.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140537","140537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896426","2018-05-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of mandatory reconsiderations have upheld the original decision on employment support allowance in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Matt Western","Matt Western","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140848","140848"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896427","2018-05-09","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of personal independence payment appeals have been successful at Tribunal in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Matt Western","Matt Western","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140849","140849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896428","2018-05-08","Department for Transport","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate his Department has made of the number of cars which use (a) diesel, (b) petrol, (c) hybrid power and (d) electric power which were sold in the UK in (i) 2017 and (ii) 2016.","Biography information for Paul Girvan","Paul Girvan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140854","140854"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896429","2018-05-08","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department is taking to encourage the take-up of volleyball in the UK.","Biography information for Paul Girvan","Paul Girvan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140855","140855"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896430","2018-05-08","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of bringing forward legislative proposals to grant charitable status to grass-root sports clubs.","Biography information for Paul Girvan","Paul Girvan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140856","140856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896431","2018-05-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 2 May 2018 to Question 138009, what estimate he has made of the cost of answering that Question; and if he will publish a breakdown of those costs.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140692","140692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896432","2018-05-08","Cabinet Office","2018-05-02","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many leak enquiries his Department has undertaken in the last two years.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140578","140578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896433","2018-05-08","Attorney General","2018-05-02","To ask the Attorney General, how many leak enquiries his Department has undertaken in the last two years.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140579","140579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896434","2018-05-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to his Oral Statement of 2 May 2018, Breast Cancer Screening, what the timetable is for his Department to contact in writing, the 309,000 women affected by the failure of the breast cancer screening programme.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140668","140668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896435","2018-05-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many leak enquiries his Department has undertaken in the last two years.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140580","140580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896436","2018-05-08","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how many leak enquiries his Department has undertaken in the last two years.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140581","140581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896437","2018-05-08","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many leak enquiries his Department has undertaken in the last two years.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140582","140582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896438","2018-05-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to his Oral Statement of 2 May 2018, Breast Cancer Screening, how many women have been affected by the breast screening programme failure in each clinical commissioning group area.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140669","140669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896439","2018-05-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many leak enquiries his Department has undertaken in the last two years.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140583","140583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896440","2018-05-09","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many leak enquiries his Department has undertaken in the last two years.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140584","140584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896441","2018-05-08","Department for Transport","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department has made an assessment of the potential merits of up-grading charging points for electric vehicles from slow charge to rapid charge.","Biography information for Paul Girvan","Paul Girvan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140857","140857"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896442","2018-05-09","Department for Education","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many leak enquiries his Department has undertaken in the last two years.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140585","140585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896443","2018-05-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many leak enquiries his Department has undertaken in the last two years.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140586","140586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896444","2018-05-09","Home Office","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many leak enquiries his Department has undertaken in the last two years.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140587","140587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896445","2018-05-08","Department for International Development","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many leak enquiries her Department has undertaken in the last two years.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140588","140588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896446","2018-05-08","Department for International Trade","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many leak enquiries his Department has undertaken in the last two years.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140589","140589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896447","2018-05-08","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many leak enquiries his Department has undertaken in the last two years.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140590","140590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896448","2018-05-08","Department for Transport","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many leak enquiries his Department has undertaken in the last two years.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140591","140591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896449","2018-05-08","Treasury","2018-05-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many leak enquiries his Department has undertaken in the last two years.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140592","140592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896450","2018-05-08","Home Office","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if his Department will make an assessment of the potential merits of using a non-plastic alternative to cones used by police forces.","Biography information for Paul Girvan","Paul Girvan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140858","140858"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896451","2018-05-09","Department for Transport","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 26 April 2018 to Question 138336 on Roads: Stonehenge, if he will publish the terms of reference of the archaeological surveys planned by the independent Scientific Committee; and when he plans to publish the results of those surveys.","Biography information for Alex Burghart","Alex Burghart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140844","140844"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896452","2018-05-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether his Department has made an assessment of the potential merits of providing subsidies to UK flower producers after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Paul Girvan","Paul Girvan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140859","140859"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896453","2018-05-08","Department for Education","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 19 March 2018 to Question 131803 on Unemployment: Young People, if he will provide the same figures for children of the Gypsy, Traveller and Roma communities.","Biography information for Alex Burghart","Alex Burghart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140845","140845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896454","2018-05-08","House of Commons Commission","2018-05-02","To ask the right hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington, representing the House of Commons Commission, how many non-disclosure agreements the House of Commons has signed with employees of the House in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140802","140802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896455","2018-05-08","Department for Transport","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make an assessment of the potential means of encouraging local authorities to use part-solar-powered street lighting.","Biography information for Paul Girvan","Paul Girvan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140860","140860"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896456","2018-05-08","Cabinet Office","2018-05-02","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many non-disclosure agreements his Department has signed with employees in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140803","140803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896457","2018-05-08","Treasury","2018-05-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many non-disclosure agreements his Department has signed with employees in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140804","140804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896458","2018-05-08","Home Office","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many non-disclosure agreements his Department has signed with employees in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140805","140805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896459","2018-05-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many non-disclosure agreements his Department has signed with employees in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140806","140806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896460","2018-05-08","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many non-disclosure agreements his Department has signed with employees in each year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140807","140807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896461","2018-05-08","Ministry of Defence","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many non-disclosure agreements his Department has signed with employees in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140808","140808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896462","2018-05-08","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many non-disclosure agreements his Department has signed with employees in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140809","140809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896463","2018-05-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many non-disclosure agreements his Department has signed with employees in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140810","140810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896464","2018-05-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many non-disclosure agreements his Department has signed with employees in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140811","140811"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896465","2018-05-08","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many non-disclosure agreements his Department has signed with employees in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140812","140812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896466","2018-05-08","Department for International Trade","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, ow many non-disclosure agreements his Department has signed with employees in each year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140813","140813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896467","2018-05-08","Department for Education","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many non-disclosure agreements his Department has signed with employees in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140814","140814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896468","2018-05-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many non-disclosure agreements his Department has signed with employees in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140815","140815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896469","2018-05-08","Department for Transport","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many non-disclosure agreements his Department has signed with employees in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140816","140816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896470","2018-05-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many non-disclosure agreements her Department has signed with employees in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140817","140817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896471","2018-05-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of introducing a grant to encourage farmers with slurry tanks to erect more effective safety railings around those tanks.","Biography information for Paul Girvan","Paul Girvan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140861","140861"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896472","2018-05-08","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how many non-disclosure agreements his Department has signed with employees in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140818","140818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896473","2018-05-08","Department for International Development","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many non-disclosure agreements her Department has signed with employees in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140819","140819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896474","2018-05-08","Scotland Office","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how many non-disclosure agreements his Department has signed with employees in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140820","140820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896475","2018-05-08","Northern Ireland Office","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many non-disclosure agreements her Department has signed with employees in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140821","140821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896476","2018-05-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many farm accidents were reported involving a slurry tank or other slurry storage in the last three years.","Biography information for Paul Girvan","Paul Girvan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140862","140862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896477","2018-05-08","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will make an assessment of the level of (a) use and (b) value for money of park exercise equipment.","Biography information for Paul Girvan","Paul Girvan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140863","140863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896478","2018-05-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department plans to prohibit smoking on publicly owned property not covered by the Health Act 2006.","Biography information for Paul Girvan","Paul Girvan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140864","140864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896479","2018-05-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to the Algerian Government on the forced closure of Christian churches in that country.","Biography information for Paul Girvan","Paul Girvan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140865","140865"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896480","2018-05-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate he has made of the total amount allocated to UK aquaculture through the European Fisheries Fund for the period 2007 to 2013.","Biography information for Paul Girvan","Paul Girvan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140866","140866"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896481","2018-05-08","Home Office","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the Government has made an assessment of the human rights implications of Ealing Council using a Public Spaces Protection Order to criminalise peaceful protest; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Edward Leigh","Sir Edward Leigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140571","140571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896482","2018-05-09","Home Office","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 27 April to Question 137536, on Engineers and Scientists: Visas, whether the number of engineers and scientists who were refused a Tier 2 (General) Certificate of Sponsorship between May 2015 and November 2017 increased because the annual cap had been reached.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140710","140710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896483","2018-05-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how his Department intends to contact women who have moved to Wales who may not have been invited to their final breast screening due to computer failure as identified in the national breast screening programme in England; and what the timetable is for contacting those people.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140671","140671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896484","2018-05-09","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate his Department has made of the number of women who have moved to Wales who may not have been invited to their final breast screening as a result of the computer failure in the national breast screening programme in England.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140672","140672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896485","2018-05-09","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when he next plans to convene a Steel Council.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140673","140673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896486","2018-05-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he has taken to mitigate the costs to the public purse relating to recovery of environmental damage in the event that a company engaged in fracking becomes insolvent after fracking operations have begun.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140538","140538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896487","2018-05-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 6 April 2018 to Question 133883, on what date he plans to publish the prospectus for the 2018 International Carbon Capture Utilisation and Storage event.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140539","140539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896488","2018-05-08","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 27 April 2018 to Question 136573 on Construction: Standards, what steps he is taking with his EU counterparts to ensure that the UK's design and civil engineering standards are maintained after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140662","140662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896489","2018-05-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the effect on the energy bills of (a) households and (b) businesses of the requirement for energy suppliers to pay EU transmission charges for access to the EU’s internal energy market after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140540","140540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896490","2018-05-08","Wales Office","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what discussions he has had with ministers in the Welsh Government on the NHS in Wales' breast-screening process being scrutinised by an independent reviewer.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140605","140605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896491","2018-05-08","Wales Office","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, whether the computing system used by the NHS in England which was responsible for the failure to register thousands of women for breast screening is the same system that is used in Wales.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140606","140606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896492","2018-05-08","Wales Office","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what information he holds on when the Welsh Government became aware of the possibility that a faulty computing system in the NHS in Wales may have been responsible as in England for the failure to register thousands of women for breast screening.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140607","140607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896493","2018-05-09","Department for Education","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much funding has been allocated from the public purse to the Northern Powerhouse Education Fund in each year since it was established; and what estimate he has made of the level of funding from the public purse to that Fund in each of the next three financial years.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140737","140737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896494","2018-05-08","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 27 April 2018 to Question 136658 on Local Government Finance, answered 27 April 2018, whether his Department has plans to produce impact assessments based on the different EU exit scenarios.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140663","140663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896495","2018-05-09","Department for Education","2018-05-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much and what proportion of funding for the Northern Powerhouse Education Fund has been spent in each year since the fund was established.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140738","140738"
