"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130874","2019-06-12","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the amount of housing required in Essex in the next (a) five, (b) 10 and (c) 15 years.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262359","262359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130875","2019-06-12","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the potential contribution of the reform of society lotteries to (a) charities and (b) good causes in the next five years; and when he plans to respond to his consultation on that reform.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262360","262360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130876","2019-06-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the UN-mediated talks in Amman between officials in Yemen’s Central bank, what steps he is taking to address concerns raised by international humanitarian organisations on ambiguities in the implementation of the Stockholm Agreement.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262239","262239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130877","2019-06-13","Department for Education","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will publish the allocation of revenues from the Immigration Skills Charge in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262354","262354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130878","2019-06-13","Department for Education","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the Immigration Skills Charge in increasing skills provision in England.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262355","262355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130879","2019-06-13","Women and Equalities","2019-06-10","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what steps she is taking to ensure that people with HIV are not discriminated against when seeking tattoo, piercings and other similar services.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262416","262416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130880","2019-06-13","Treasury","2019-06-10","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that (a) investment choices available to workplace pension customers are regularly reviewed by Independent Governance Committees and (b) those investment choices are aligned with the interests of customers.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262255","262255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130881","2019-06-13","Treasury","2019-06-10","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make it his policy that Independent Governance Committees attached to contract-based workplace pensions have a duty to monitor the suitability of the retail fund choices available to scheme members.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262256","262256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130882","2019-06-13","Treasury","2019-06-10","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of scrutiny by Independent Governance Committees of the retail funds offered within workplace pensions products.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262257","262257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130883","2019-06-13","Treasury","2019-06-10","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if his Department will make an assessment of the potential conflict of interests in the business model of vertically integrated companies offering retail investment platforms, asset management and workplace pensions products.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262258","262258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130884","2019-06-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment the Government has made of the potential merits of providing a statutory entitlement to up to 10 days paid care leave.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262228","262228"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130885","2019-06-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of providing the statutory right for employees taking longer-term unpaid care leave to return to their original employment after their caring duties have finished.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262229","262229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130886","2019-06-13","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what comparative estimate his Department has made of the average cost of (a) caring for a dementia patient at home with care provided by family and (b) care provided in an in-patient setting.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262230","262230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130887","2019-06-13","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment his Department has made of the effect of the removal of bursaries for undergraduate nurses on the level of nursing places filled in each institution that provides such places.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262214","262214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130888","2019-06-13","Cabinet Office","2019-06-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people in Northern Ireland have reached their hundredth year in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262265","262265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130889","2019-06-13","Home Office","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people are employed (a) full-time and (b) part-time by Border Force in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262266","262266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130890","2019-06-13","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many placements NHS England has commissioned at St Andrew's in-patient Child & Adolescent Mental Health Service in Northampton in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262331","262331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130891","2019-06-13","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what NHS England’s policy is on moving patients in NHS commissioned placements when the setting they are in receives a rating of Inadequate from the Care Quality Commission.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262332","262332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130892","2019-06-13","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what guidance NHS England has given to (a) clinical commissioning groups and (b) other NHS bodies on moving patients in NHS commissioned placements when the setting they are in receives a rating of Inadequate from the Care Quality Commission.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262333","262333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130893","2019-06-13","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many placements in Assessment and Treatment Units NHS England have commissioned for patients under the age of 18 in each of the past 3 years.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262334","262334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130894","2019-06-13","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many placements in in-patient mental health hospitals for children and young people under the age of 18 with (a) autism, (b) a learning disability and (c) a mental health condition NHS England has commissioned in each of the past 3 years.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262335","262335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130895","2019-06-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the NHS Long Term Plan and NHS Planning Guidance commitments for 2019-20, what progress his Department has made against the commitment to invest up to £2 million a year in programmes to reduce violence, bullying and harassment toward NHS staff; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262376","262376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130896","2019-06-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the NHS Long Term Plan and NHS Planning Guidance commitments for 2019-20, what progress his Department has made against the commitment to do more to nurture the next generation of leaders, including a systematic regional and local approach for identifying, assessing, developing, deploying and supporting talent; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262377","262377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130897","2019-06-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the NHS Long Term Plan and NHS Planning Guidance commitments for 2019-20, what progress his Department has made against the commitment to fund clinical placements for an extra 5,000 places from 2019-20 for use by higher education institutions; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262378","262378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130898","2019-06-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the NHS Long Term Plan and NHS Planning Guidance commitments for 2019-20, what progress his Department has made against the commitment to continue to invest in the growth of nursing apprenticeships; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262379","262379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130899","2019-06-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the NHS Long Term Plan and NHS Planning Guidance commitments for 2019-20, what progress his Department has made against the commitment to invest over half of the £200 million apprenticeship levy back into the NHS in 2019-20; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262380","262380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130900","2019-06-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the NHS Long Term Plan and NHS Planning Guidance commitments for 2019-20, what progress his Department has made against the commitment to work with Royal Colleges to pilot a new credentialing programme for hospital consultants to offer mechanical thrombectomy; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262381","262381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130901","2019-06-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the NHS Long Term Plan and NHS Planning Guidance commitments for 2019-20, what progress his Department has made against the commitment to publish a workforce implementation plan in 2019; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262382","262382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130902","2019-06-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the NHS Long Term Plan and NHS Planning Guidance commitments for 2019-20, what progress his Department has made against the commitment to ensure that 100,000 women are able to access their maternity record digitally in 2019-20; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262383","262383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130903","2019-06-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the NHS Long Term Plan and NHS Planning Guidance commitments for 2019-20, what progress his Department has made against the commitment to develop and expand the Diabetes Prevention Programme to offer digital access; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262384","262384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130904","2019-06-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the NHS Long Term Plan and NHS Planning Guidance commitments for 2019-20, what progress his Department has made against the commitment to begin work to roll out technology standards, as set out in The Future of Healthcare, to ensure data is interoperable and accessible; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262385","262385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130905","2019-06-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the NHS Long Term Plan and NHS Planning Guidance commitments for 2019-20, what progress his Department has made against the commitment to ensure that (a) each NHS organisation delivers its agreed financial position and (b) that the NHS budget overall is balanced during 2019-20; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262386","262386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130906","2019-06-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the NHS Long Term Plan and NHS Planning Guidance commitments for 2019-20, what progress his Department has made against the commitment to reduce year-on-year the number of trusts and CCGs individually in deficit so that (a) all NHS organisations are in balance by 2023-24 and (b) the expectation is met that the number of Trusts reporting a deficit in 2019-20 will be reduced by more than half; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262387","262387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130907","2019-06-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the NHS Long Term Plan and NHS Planning Guidance commitments for 2019-20, what progress his Department has made against the commitment to phase in an updated Market Forces Factor over the next five years, applying it to payment arrangements and allocations for 2019-20; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262388","262388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130908","2019-06-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the NHS Long Term Plan and NHS Planning Guidance commitments for 2019-20, what progress his Department has made against the commitment to extend The Getting It Right First Time programme across to community health services and primary care; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262389","262389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130909","2019-06-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the NHS Long Term Plan and NHS Planning Guidance commitments for 2019-20, what progress his Department has made against the commitment to reduce patient harm and the substantial costs associated with it through a new ten-year national strategy; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262390","262390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130910","2019-06-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the NHS Long Term Plan and NHS Planning Guidance commitments for 2019-20, what progress his Department has made against the commitment to continue to implement existing commitments in the Five Year Forward View and national strategies for (a) cancer, (b) mental health, (c) learning disability, (d) general practice and (e) maternity; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262391","262391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130911","2019-06-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the NHS Long Term Plan and NHS Planning Guidance commitments for 2019-20, what progress his Department has made against the commitment to set out the principles and practice for Putting Health into Place guidelines for how local communities should plan and design a healthy built environment; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262392","262392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130912","2019-06-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the NHS Long Term Plan and NHS Planning Guidance commitments for 2019- with reference to the NHS Long Term Plan and NHS Planning Guidance commitments for 2019-20, what progress his Department has made against the commitment to work across Government to develop a Healthy New Towns standard including a Healthy Homes Quality Mark to be awarded to places that meet the high standards and principles that promote health and wellbeing; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262393","262393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130913","2019-06-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Written Statement of 5 June 2018, on Personal Independence Payments, HCWS733, if she will provide an update on the progress of the pilot to introduce video recordings of personal independence payment assessments.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262247","262247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130914","2019-06-13","Church Commissioners","2019-06-10","To ask the right hon. Member for Meriden, representing the Church Commissioners, pursuant to the Answer of 5 June 2019 to Question 259013, how many affordable homes have been built by the Church of England or its agents in each local authority area since 2015; and what the affordable housing requirement is in each of those local authority areas.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262248","262248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130915","2019-06-13","Home Office","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 6 June 2019 to Question 259015, if he will centrally collate the data on anti-social behaviour case review requests.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262249","262249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130916","2019-06-13","Home Office","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 6 June 2019 to Question 259015, Antisocial Behaviour, what recent assessment he has made of the importance of anti-social behaviour case reviews to reducing levels of anti-social behaviour.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262250","262250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130917","2019-06-13","Ministry of Justice","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 5 June 2019 to Question 257595, what the estimated cost is of establishing how many women were released from prison into homelessness in each year from 2010-11 to 2016-17.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262417","262417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130918","2019-06-13","Ministry of Justice","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, for what reason all accredited programmes run by (a) prisons and (b) the Probation Service have not been subject to an impact and outcome evaluation.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262418","262418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130919","2019-06-12","Ministry of Justice","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of the availability of courses for prisoners to demonstrate safety for release.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262419","262419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130920","2019-06-12","Ministry of Justice","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what data his Department holds on the rate of self-inflcted deaths among (a) people serving sentences under imprisonment for public protection and (b) the prison population.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262420","262420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130921","2019-06-13","Ministry of Justice","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what data his Department holds on the (a) number and (b) type of parole board recommendations for courses to be undertaken by prisoners.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262421","262421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130922","2019-06-13","Ministry of Justice","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether it is his policy that future programmes authorised by his Department be subject to an impact evaluation.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262422","262422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130923","2019-06-12","Ministry of Justice","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 15 May 2019 to Question 251411 on Prisons: Contracts, through what management information requirements is information on staffing levels submitted.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262423","262423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130924","2019-06-13","Ministry of Justice","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what criteria his Department uses to assess the suitability for courses for prisoners.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262424","262424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130925","2019-06-13","Department for Education","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much Wakefield City Academies Trust spent on services provided by Deloitte from 1 September 2017 to 31 May 2019.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262315","262315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130926","2019-06-13","Department for Education","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many (a) part-time and (b) full-time staff were employed by Wakefield City Academies Trust; and what the cost was of those staff, in each financial year from 1 September 2017 to 31 May 2019.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262316","262316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130927","2019-06-13","Department for Education","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the value is of Wakefield City Academies Trust pension deficit.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262317","262317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130928","2019-06-13","Department for Education","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many multi-academy trusts have collapsed since the introduction of such trusts.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262318","262318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130929","2019-06-12","Ministry of Justice","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many UK nationals have been convicted of offences relating to the online sexual exploitation of children in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262240","262240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130930","2019-06-12","Ministry of Justice","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of sentences for people convicted of offences relating to the online sexual exploitation of children; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262241","262241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130931","2019-06-12","Ministry of Justice","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average length of sentence (a) awarded and (b) served has been for individuals found guilty of the online sexual exploitation of children in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262242","262242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130932","2019-06-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the Government's policy is on recent diplomatic relations between Turkey and Cyprus.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262337","262337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130933","2019-06-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the process is through which eligibility for child maintenance payments is verified.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262338","262338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130934","2019-06-13","Treasury","2019-06-10","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what processes his Department uses with further education institutions to verify a child's full-time attendance in education in relation to the eligibility for child benefit payments.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262339","262339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130935","2019-06-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what safeguards her Department have put in place to ensure that the system for child maintenance payments is not open to abuse by people who have left full time education.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262340","262340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130936","2019-06-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many individual projects he plans to establish to test and trial the environmental land management scheme in (a) 2018-19, (b) 2019-20 and (c) 2020-21.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262215","262215"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130937","2019-06-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many individual environmental land management scheme projects he plans to establish to test and trial (a) climate change mitigation and adaptation, (b) supporting public access to farmland and better understanding of the countryside, (c) preventing, reducing or protecting from environmental hazards (including pesticides) and (d) widening the range of farm sectors represented, including agri-environment programmes, horticulture, pigs and poultry.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262216","262216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130938","2019-06-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what funding has been allocated to individual environmental land management scheme projects to test and trial (a) climate change mitigation and adaptation, (b) supporting public access to farmland and better understanding of the countryside, (c) preventing, reducing or protecting from environmental hazards (including pesticides) and (d) widening the range of farm sectors represented, including agri-environment programmes, horticulture, pigs and poultry.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262217","262217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130939","2019-06-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the timetable is for the roll out of (a) detailed objectives, (b) tests and trials, (c) payment methodology, (d) sufficient advisor numbers, (e) the pilot scheme and (f) the final launch of the environmental land management scheme.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262218","262218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130940","2019-06-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will publish the risk register for the environmental land management scheme programme.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262219","262219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130941","2019-06-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many staff at each grade are working full-time on the environmental land management scheme programme.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262220","262220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130942","2019-06-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he plans to make to his Sudanese counterpart on the cases of (a) Mohamed Esmat, (b) Ismael Jalab and (c) Mubarak Ardol.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262221","262221"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130943","2019-06-13","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many GP practices consist of (a) one, (b) two, (c) three to five, (d) six to ten, (d) 11-15, (e) 16 - 20 and (f) more than 20 GPs in each Clinical Commissioning Group area.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262222","262222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130944","2019-06-13","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many GPs have been (a) permanently employed and (b) employed as locums for a continuous period of more than six months in each Clinical Commissioning Group area.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262223","262223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130946","2019-06-13","Home Office","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of recognising forced marriage as a form of modern day slavery.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262231","262231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130947","2019-06-13","Home Office","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people are living in forced marriages in the UK.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262232","262232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130948","2019-06-13","Home Office","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps his Department has taken to help people trapped in forced marriages.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262233","262233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130949","2019-06-13","Home Office","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many academics have been refused visas to travel to the UK for work-related purposes by his Department in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262234","262234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130950","2019-06-13","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate his Department has made of the number of days taken as sick leave by care workers who were attacked by patients in 2017-18.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262235","262235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130951","2019-06-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions he has had with the Royal College of Nursing on the relationship between herpes, chlamydia and Alzheimers.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262367","262367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130952","2019-06-13","Ministry of Defence","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether there is a pre-approved list under section 22 of his Department's November 2018 policy on the passing or receipt of intelligence relating to detained or captured persons of people on whom intelligence can be shared.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262306","262306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130953","2019-06-13","Ministry of Defence","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the criteria are for pre-approving sharing intelligence on an individual under section 22 of his Department's November 2018 policy on the passing or receipt of intelligence relating to detained or captured persons.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262307","262307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130954","2019-06-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions he has had with the Royal College of Nursing on the relationship between carbohydrates and lung cancer.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262368","262368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130955","2019-06-13","Home Office","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the media report of 9 June 2019 that Hezbollah stockpiled explosive materials in North West London in 2015, whether that stockpiling was included in the decision to proscribe Hezbollah in February 2019.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262425","262425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130956","2019-06-13","Home Office","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when (a) the Home Secretary (b) Ministers in his Department and (c) officials in his Department were informed of the reported stockpiling of explosive materials by individuals with suspected of links to Hezbollah, in North West London; and what steps his Department took to (i) inform and (ii) protect communities in North West London as a result of that stockpiling.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262426","262426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130957","2019-06-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how much the UK embassy in Colombia spent on each of its projects and programmes in that country in 2018.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262294","262294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130958","2019-06-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure the accuracy of financial charges made by private clinics.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262369","262369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130959","2019-06-12","Ministry of Justice","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the accuracy of reports on the health of Julian Assange while in custody in the UK.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262427","262427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130960","2019-06-13","Church Commissioners","2019-06-10","To ask the right hon. Member for Meriden, representing the Church Commissioners, whether the Church Commissioners have the authority to make grants to the Archbishop's Council.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262341","262341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130961","2019-06-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions he has had with Royal College of Nursing on the effectiveness of antibiotics in children.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262370","262370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130962","2019-06-12","Ministry of Justice","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) public and (b) private law cases were referred to the Family Courts in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262428","262428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130963","2019-06-12","Ministry of Justice","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many private law cases were referred to the Family Courts in which (a) both, (b) one and (c) neither parent or carer were represented by a solicitor in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262429","262429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130964","2019-06-13","Women and Equalities","2019-06-10","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, how many Black, Asian and Minority Ethnic people have been employed at each civil service grade in the (a) Government Equalities Office and (b) Civil Service in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Dawn Butler","Dawn Butler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262295","262295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130965","2019-06-13","Women and Equalities","2019-06-10","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, if she will publish the gender pay gap in each UK parliamentary constituency in 2018-19.","Biography information for Dawn Butler","Dawn Butler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262296","262296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130966","2019-06-13","Women and Equalities","2019-06-10","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, if she will publish the number of staff employed by the Government Equalities Office by (a) grade and (b) policy areas those staff are assigned to.","Biography information for Dawn Butler","Dawn Butler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262297","262297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130967","2019-06-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps the Government is taking to prevent workplace discrimination against fathers taking parental leave.","Biography information for Dawn Butler","Dawn Butler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262298","262298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130968","2019-06-13","Home Office","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that adequate safeguards will be included in the Domestic Abuse Bill to protect migrant survivors of domestic abuse.","Biography information for Dawn Butler","Dawn Butler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262299","262299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130969","2019-06-13","Department for Transport","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many anonymous fitness to drive complaints were received in 2018; and how many of those complains were investigated.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262430","262430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130970","2019-06-13","Department for Transport","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many drivers were sent for assessment following anonymous fitness to drive complaints, and what the outcomes of those assessments were in 2018.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262431","262431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130971","2019-06-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he has plans to make the bionic spine available on the NHS.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262371","262371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130972","2019-06-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent steps the Government has taken to promote carbon capture, utilisation and storage technologies.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262267","262267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130973","2019-06-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to tackle the rise in the incidence of cancer in young people under 25.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262372","262372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130974","2019-06-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to help reduce the number of people over the age of 60 that have had to retire as a result of ill-health.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262373","262373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130975","2019-06-13","Department for International Development","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that Official Development Assistance is allocated to (a) ethical, (b) sustainable and (c) environmentally-sound projects.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262268","262268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130977","2019-06-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions he has had with representatives of NICE on increasing the capacity for undertaking highly specialised technology evaluations.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262374","262374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130978","2019-06-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions his Department has had with representatives of the Umbrella Movement in Hong Kong.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262375","262375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130979","2019-06-12","Treasury","2019-06-10","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much revenue accrued to the public purse from VAT on audiobooks in each of the last three years for which data is available.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262401","262401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130980","2019-06-13","Treasury","2019-06-10","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people in Hull North have annual incomes of £80,000 or more.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262305","262305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130981","2019-06-12","Department for Education","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of bringing forward legislative proposals to make it mandatory for universities to provide 365-day access to accommodation for estranged students with independent status.","Biography information for Paul Girvan","Paul Girvan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262432","262432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130982","2019-06-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether she has made an assessment of the effect of universal credit on the level of rent arrears owed to Scottish local authorities; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Hugh Gaffney","Hugh Gaffney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262433","262433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130983","2019-06-13","Department for Education","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 15 March 2019 to Question 231556, what assessment he has made of changes in the level of take-up of pupil premium in Oxford in each year since 2015.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262434","262434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130984","2019-06-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to manage ammonia emissions from dairy and beef farming.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262269","262269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130985","2019-06-12","Treasury","2019-06-10","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to improve free access to cash in Scotland.","Biography information for Hugh Gaffney","Hugh Gaffney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262435","262435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130986","2019-06-13","Treasury","2019-06-10","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people in (a) St Helens borough, (b) Liverpool City Region, (c) the North West and (d) the UK paid tax in the tax bands (i) up to £8,632, (ii) £8,632 to £12,500, (iii) £12,500 to £50,000, (iii) £50,000 to £100,000 and (iv) above £100,000 in the most recent period for which information is available.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262410","262410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130987","2019-06-12","Scotland Office","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what recent assessment he has made of the effect of the suspension of European Social Fund payments on third sector organisations in Scotland.","Biography information for Hugh Gaffney","Hugh Gaffney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262436","262436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130988","2019-06-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-06-10","To ask the  Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, which local authorities have (a) declared a climate emergency and (b) resolved to go carbon net zero emissions by 2030.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262224","262224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130989","2019-06-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department is taking to improve public awareness of scams in Scotland.","Biography information for Hugh Gaffney","Hugh Gaffney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262437","262437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130990","2019-06-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent assessment he has made of trends in the level of fuel poverty in the UK.","Biography information for Hugh Gaffney","Hugh Gaffney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262438","262438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130991","2019-06-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate his Department has made of the number of people whose personal independence payment has (a) increased, (b) decreased, (c) reduced to zero and (d) stayed the same as a result of an appeal decision in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262439","262439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130992","2019-06-12","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department will take to replace all types cladding on apartment blocks.","Biography information for Paul Girvan","Paul Girvan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262440","262440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130993","2019-06-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to the Government of People's Republic of China on the suppression of political activists in Hong Kong.","Biography information for Paul Girvan","Paul Girvan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262441","262441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130994","2019-06-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, which (a) businesses and (b) business organisations have declared an intention be net-zero carbon by 2030.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262225","262225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130995","2019-06-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what representations he has received from medical organisations in support of a policy of net zero carbon emissions by 2030.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262226","262226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130996","2019-06-12","Home Office","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps his Department is taking to identify the age of people placed in care facilities with minors when requesting asylum.","Biography information for Paul Girvan","Paul Girvan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262442","262442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130997","2019-06-13","Department for Education","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if his Department will publish the analysis of graduates that will be net beneficiaries from the proposed changes under the post-18 education and funding review by income decile.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262443","262443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130998","2019-06-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what diplomatic steps the Government is taking to promote human rights in Egypt.","Biography information for Angela Crawley","Angela Crawley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262444","262444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130999","2019-06-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his Egyptian counterpart on the case of Ahmed Saddouma.","Biography information for Angela Crawley","Angela Crawley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262445","262445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131000","2019-06-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 10 June 2019 to Question 260085 on Department for Work and Pensions: Ministerial Policy Advisers, for what reason her Department does not routinely publish the number of alleged breaches of the Special Advisers’ Code of Conduct by her Department's Special Advisers.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262446","262446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131001","2019-06-13","Home Office","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate he has made of the number of recorded hate crimes by each protected characteristic defined in the Equality Act 2010 in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262259","262259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131002","2019-06-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans he has to provide advice to farmers on the potential dangers of mixing slurry.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262227","262227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131003","2019-06-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the Russian authorities on the recent arrest and alleged physical abuse of investigative journalist Ivan Golunov.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262397","262397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131004","2019-06-13","Treasury","2019-06-10","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to ensure that insurance companies do not unfairly discriminate against consumers with (a) historical and (b) current mental health conditions.","Biography information for Hannah Bardell","Hannah Bardell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262447","262447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131005","2019-06-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations his Department has made to the Government of Lebanon on the proposed destruction of Syrian refugees’ shelters in Arsal, Lebanon.","Biography information for Tommy Sheppard","Tommy Sheppard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262409","262409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131006","2019-06-13","Treasury","2019-06-10","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make it his policy to issue a waiver for the tax due on redundancy payments to be received by Ford Bridgend workers.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262300","262300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131007","2019-06-12","Department for Transport","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent progress he has made on maintaining flights between the UK and Europe after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262347","262347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131008","2019-06-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will hold discussions with representatives of Ford UK on that company meeting 50 per cent of the tax deductions from redundancy payments to workers at Ford Bridgend; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262301","262301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131009","2019-06-13","Treasury","2019-06-10","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the value of reducing tax deductions from redundancy payments to workers at Ford Bridgend;  and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262302","262302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131010","2019-06-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what his Department's timeframe is for the publication of the energy white paper.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262348","262348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131011","2019-06-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what information his Department holds on whether blister packs for medicines are recyclable.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262448","262448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131012","2019-06-12","Department for Transport","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent progress he has made on announcing the successful bidder of the South Eastern Rail Franchise.","Biography information for Sir David Evennett","Sir David Evennett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262263","262263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131013","2019-06-12","Department for Transport","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 20 November 2018 to Question 190369, what the average journey time was to cross the Dartford Crossing (a) northbound and (b) southbound at peak times in each of the last six months.","Biography information for Sir David Evennett","Sir David Evennett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262264","262264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131014","2019-06-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Association of British Insurer's report: Principles for tailoring retirement risk warnings, published in May 2019, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of ensuring that age-appropriate warnings are provided when information is given on (a) pension scams, (b) employer contributions in relation to pensions, (c) tax matters in relation to pensions, (c) life expectancy in relation to financial planning and (d) lasting power of attorney in relation to financial and health matters.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262270","262270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131015","2019-06-12","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the ScreenSkills campaign entitled, Find your future in film and TV.","Biography information for Mr Edward Vaizey","Mr Edward Vaizey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262321","262321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131016","2019-06-13","Treasury","2019-06-10","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment she has made of the adequacy of advice given to retirees accessing their pension funds for the first time.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262271","262271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131017","2019-06-13","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what recent estimate his Department has made of the number of homes purchased using the Help to Buy equity loan scheme in Wolverhampton North East constituency in each year since that policy was introduced.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262361","262361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131018","2019-06-13","Home Office","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps he is taking to reduce alcohol-related crime.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262342","262342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131019","2019-06-13","Home Office","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps he is taking to tackle domestic abuse of (a) adults and (b) children that is linked to excessive alcohol consumption.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262343","262343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131020","2019-06-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to the Sudanese authorities on its response to pro-democracy protesters in that country; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Dame Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262254","262254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131021","2019-06-13","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he is taking to help ensure that alcohol is marketed responsibly.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262344","262344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131022","2019-06-13","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps is he taking to protect children and young people from the potential adverse effects of alcohol marketing.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262345","262345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131023","2019-06-13","Treasury","2019-06-10","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent estimate the Government has of the effect of the alcohol duty freeze on (a) public health and (b) alcohol-related deaths.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262346","262346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131024","2019-06-12","Department for Transport","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many Enhanced Partnerships have been set up with local authorities since the Bus Services Act 2017 came into force.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262398","262398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131025","2019-06-12","Department for Transport","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many Voluntary Partnerships have been set up with local authorities since the Bus Services Act 2017 came into force.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262399","262399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131026","2019-06-12","Department for Transport","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many Advanced Quality Partnerships have been set up with local authorities since the Bus Services Act 2017 came into force.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262400","262400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131027","2019-06-12","Ministry of Defence","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many British troops seconded to the Brunei armed forces are serving in a Bruneian uniform.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262212","262212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131028","2019-06-12","Ministry of Defence","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what roles are being carried out by the British troops seconded to the Brunei armed forces.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262213","262213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131029","2019-06-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his Cuban counterpart on the potential effect of that country's new constitution on freedom of religion or belief.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262349","262349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131030","2019-06-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the accuracy of reports of harassment of Cuban church leaders in the lead-up to the constitutional referendum in Cuba in February 2019.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262350","262350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131031","2019-06-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what plans his Department has to monitor freedom of religion or belief in Cuba following revisions to that country's constitution.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262351","262351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131032","2019-06-12","Home Office","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many widows and widowers of police officers in England and Wales whose spouses were killed on duty or as a result of injuries sustained on duty have had their pensions revoked as a result of their remarriage or cohabitation before 1 April 2015.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262352","262352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131033","2019-06-12","Home Office","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment he has made of the financial effect on police widows and widowers of the loss of their survivor pension due to remarrying or cohabiting.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262353","262353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131034","2019-06-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much Government funding was provided to UK Wild Camp.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262319","262319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131035","2019-06-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what body is responsible for monitoring progress against the 2017 Conservative manifesto commitment to plant 1 million trees in towns and cities; and (a) what progress his Department has made towards and (b) what his timescale is for achieving that commitment.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262320","262320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131036","2019-06-12","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what estimate his Department has made of the additional cost to the public purse of establishing two local authorities in Shropshire.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262309","262309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131037","2019-06-12","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment his Department has made of the potential efficiency savings of merging local authorities.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262310","262310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131038","2019-06-12","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what the per capita funding is for Telford and Wrekin Council.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262311","262311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131039","2019-06-12","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what estimate his Department has made of the efficiencies accrued as a result of the merger of Shrewsbury, North Shropshire and South Shropshire Borough Councils with Shropshire Council.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262312","262312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131040","2019-06-12","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what the per capita funding is for Shropshire Council.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262313","262313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131041","2019-06-12","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of a merger of Shropshire and Telford Councils.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262314","262314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131042","2019-06-12","Ministry of Justice","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what plans his Department has to ensure that the capacity at HMP Berwyn is fully utilised.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262449","262449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131043","2019-06-12","Ministry of Justice","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what criteria his Department applies when deciding which prisoners are located at HMP Berwyn; and what assessment his  Department has made of the adequacy of that criteria.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262450","262450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131044","2019-06-12","Ministry of Justice","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the suitability of prisoners located at HMP Berwyn.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262451","262451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131045","2019-06-12","Ministry of Justice","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what discussions he has had with the Welsh Government on the (a) suitability of prisoners located at HMP Berwyn, (b) prospect of moving additional prisoners to HMP Berwyn to fill its capacity and (c) criteria for deciding which prisoners are located at HMP Berwyn.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262452","262452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131046","2019-06-12","Speaker's Committee for the Independent Parliamentary Standards Authority","2019-06-10","To ask the hon. Member for Broxbourne, representing the Speaker's Committee for the Independent Parliamentary Standards Authority, for what reason the Authority did not consider locations for its offices outside London and the South-East.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262236","262236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131047","2019-06-13","Speaker's Committee for the Independent Parliamentary Standards Authority","2019-06-10","To ask the hon. Member for Broxbourne, representing the Speaker's Committee for the Independent Parliamentary Standards Authority,  pursuant to the Answer of 5 June 2019 to Question 257645 on Independent Parliamentary Standards Authority: Buildings, which organisation's commercial interests would be prejudiced; and in what manner by disclosing the size of IPSA's office and the rate paid per metre.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262237","262237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131048","2019-06-13","Home Office","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 4 June 2017 to Question 257442 on Biometrics: Applications, what the timeframe is for (a) reviewing SSL's performance against its key performance indicators and (b) reporting that performance.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262238","262238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131049","2019-06-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many complaints submitted to his Department by (a) hon. Members and (b) people in each parliamentary constituency in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262405","262405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131050","2019-06-13","Home Office","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of the accuracy of statements reportedly made by the French authorities that the nine unaccompanied children who are being processed under the Dubs scheme will be the last children to be processed before the allocation for the Dubs scheme is reached.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262362","262362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131051","2019-06-13","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of implications for his policies on the design of the Shared Prosperity Fund of the report entitled, Communities in Charge, published by Locality.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262260","262260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131052","2019-06-13","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions the Government held with pensioner groups prior to his Department's decision to transfer responsibility for funding TV licences for people aged over 75 to the BBC.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262261","262261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131053","2019-06-13","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate he has made of the number of pensioners who will be affected by the BBC's decision to charge people aged over 75 for tv licences.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262262","262262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131054","2019-06-12","Home Office","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many individuals were (a) charged with and (b) convicted of offences under the Modern Slavery Act 2015 in connection with county lines criminal activity in (i) 2016, (ii) 2017, (iii) 2018 and (iv) 2019 up to 31 May 2019.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262322","262322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131055","2019-06-12","Home Office","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether any individuals have been (a) charged with and (b) convicted of conspiracy to commit offences under the Modern Slavery Act 2015 in connection with county lines criminal activity since the commencement of that Act.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262323","262323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131056","2019-06-12","Home Office","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will make an assessment of the adequacy of resources allocated to (a) police services in England and Wales and (b) the National Crime Agency to (i) all investigate active branded county lines and (ii) adopt an investigative focus on identifying and charging individuals involved in conspiracy to commit offences under the Modern Slavery Act 2015.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262324","262324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131057","2019-06-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the compliance with international law of the reported plan by the Government of Saudi Arabia to execute Murtaja Qureiris at the age of 18 for alleged offences committed when he was 10 years old.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262325","262325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131058","2019-06-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his Saudi Arabian counterpart in relation to the reported plan by that Government to execute Murtaja Qureiris at the age of 18 for alleged offences committed when he was 10 years old.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262326","262326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131059","2019-06-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the accuracy of recent reports of (a) violence, (b) sexual violence, (c) looting and (d) intimidation of medical professionals by military groups in Khartoum following continued pro-democracy protests in that capital.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262327","262327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131060","2019-06-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what support his Department is providing to his Sudanese counterpart to (a) prevent further violence in that country and (b) ensure a swift and peaceful transition to civilian-led government.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262328","262328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131061","2019-06-13","Treasury","2019-06-10","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of the No Recourse to Public Funds condition on local authority budgets by local authority area.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262363","262363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131062","2019-06-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the timeframe is for the publication of the Government’s response to the public consultation on extending redundancy protection for pregnant women and new parents.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262329","262329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131063","2019-06-13","Ministry of Defence","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many people from (a) state and (b) independent schools were accepted to the Royal Military Academy Sandhurst in the last five years.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262308","262308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131064","2019-06-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the Answer of 22 May 2019 to Question 257452 on Cameroon: Politics and Government, whether he has made an assessment of the potential merits on reducing security cooperation with the Cameroon government as a result of allegations of human rights abuses in that country.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262330","262330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131065","2019-06-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the recent Scope report Now is the Time 2018, whether the Government has made an assessment of the potential merits of a cross-departmental approach to support the families of disabled children.","Biography information for Michael Tomlinson","Michael Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262453","262453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131066","2019-06-12","Department for Education","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will change the measure of disadvantage used in the Student Premium to capture individual-level socio-economic disadvantage as recommended in the May 2019 Post-18 education and funding review: independent panel report.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262303","262303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131067","2019-06-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the role of the Minister for Disabled People is in co-ordinating children and families policy across Government.","Biography information for Michael Tomlinson","Michael Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262454","262454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131068","2019-06-13","Home Office","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether he plans to publish on his Department's website (a) the Darra Singh review of the Home Office response to the mandating of DNA for immigration purposes and (b) his Department's response to that review.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262455","262455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131069","2019-06-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the merits of the statement by the Prime Minister of Mauritius at the UN general Assembly on 22 May 2019 that the eviction of the population of the Chagos Islands by the UK Government was akin to a crime against humanity.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262406","262406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131070","2019-06-13","Attorney General","2019-06-10","To ask the Attorney General, how many complaints of rape were made in each region; and how many of these cases resulted in a (a) prosecution and (b) conviction in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262243","262243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131071","2019-06-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether her Department has plans to collect and publish data on the numbers of people who die after (a) failing or (b) being found fit for work at an assessment for benefits relating to sickness or disability.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262252","262252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131072","2019-06-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average time taken is for an award of employment support allowance to be made to an applicant suffering from cancer.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262244","262244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131073","2019-06-12","Cabinet Office","2019-06-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of requiring Government Departments to (a) provide similar information and (b) undertake a sample collection of data over a given period in the event that a Department does not hold the information requested by hon. Members in Parliamentary Questions.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262253","262253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131074","2019-06-13","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether ThermoWood class D cladding is permitted on buildings below 18 metres in height.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262394","262394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131075","2019-06-13","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to increase the availability of support for children and young people with mental health needs who are not receiving statutory mental health treatment.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262336","262336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131076","2019-06-12","Church Commissioners","2019-06-10","To ask the right hon. Member for Meriden, representing the Church Commissioners, what the Church of England's landholdings are in Scotland.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262402","262402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131077","2019-06-13","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether his Department commissioned the Building Research Establishment to carry out any tests on High Pressure Laminate cladding prior to June 2017.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262395","262395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131078","2019-06-13","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether his Department is aware of any fire safety tests carried out in the UK on High Pressure Laminate cladding prior to June 2017.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262396","262396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131079","2019-06-12","Church Commissioners","2019-06-10","To ask the right hon. Member for Meriden, representing the Church Commissioners, what estimate the Church of England has made of the profits from its operations in Scotland in the last 12 months for which information is available.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262403","262403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131080","2019-06-12","Church Commissioners","2019-06-10","To ask the right hon. Member for Meriden, representing the Church Commissioners, what EU funding the Church of England has received in each of the last ten years.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262404","262404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131081","2019-06-13","Ministry of Justice","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the Ministry of Justice press release of 21 May 2019 entitled Spotlight on child protection in family courts (a) if he will list the panel of experts assembled and (b) whether any survivors or victims of domestic abuse will sit on the panel.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262456","262456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131082","2019-06-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what discussions has he had with (a) university groups and (b) UK Research and Innovation on the sustainability of current funding for PHD qualifications.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262245","262245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131083","2019-06-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 7 February 2019 to Question 216371 on River Thames: Cocaine, what progress his Department has made on tackling the level of cocaine found in eels in the Thames.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262457","262457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131084","2019-06-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many households with active green deals are in receipt of Universal Credit.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262458","262458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131085","2019-06-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the effect on the UK economy of the Government's Industrial Strategy proposals to increase the number of people undertaking a high-tech PhD.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262246","262246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131086","2019-06-13","Home Office","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of whether it is safe to deport nationals of the Democratic Republic of Congo to that country.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262356","262356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131087","2019-06-13","Home Office","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of the safety of nationals of the Democratic Republic of Congo who are returned to that country.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262357","262357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131088","2019-06-13","Home Office","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions his officials have had with officials in the Foreign and Commonwealth Office on issuing advice on the safety of returning nationals of the Democratic Republic of Congo to that country.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262358","262358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131089","2019-06-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many residents in Glasgow South West constituency (a) applied for and (b) received pension credits in the last 12 months for which figures are available; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262459","262459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131090","2019-06-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps her Department is taking to promote the uptake of Pension Credits; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262460","262460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131091","2019-06-13","Department for Education","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to consult on a new National Plan for Music Education; and what the timetable is for the publication of that plan.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262411","262411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131092","2019-06-13","Department for Education","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much funding has been allocated from the public purse to Music Education Hubs in local authority areas in (a) Merseyside, (b) the North West and (c) England and Wales since 2011.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262412","262412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131093","2019-06-13","Department for Education","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, on which dates the National Plan for Music Education monitoring board met since 2011; and if he will publish the minutes of those meetings.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262461","262461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131094","2019-06-13","Department for Education","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the number and proportion of children in (a) primary and (b) post-primary schools in (i) St Helens, (ii) Merseyside, (iii) the North West and (iv) England and Wales that play musical instruments.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262462","262462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131095","2019-06-12","Department for International Trade","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, when he plans to publish a response to his Department's public consultations on (a) Trade with the US, (b) Trade with Australia, (c) Trade with New Zealand and (d) Trade with the Comprehensive and Progressive Agreement for Trans-Pacific Partnership which concluded on 26 October 2018.","Biography information for Stewart Hosie","Stewart Hosie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262304","262304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131096","2019-06-12","Department for Education","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to encourage more people from disadvantaged backgrounds to study the Classics.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262272","262272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131097","2019-06-12","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps the Government is taking to ensure the BBC remains economically competitive against video streaming services.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262273","262273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131098","2019-06-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the cancellation of the Queen's birthday party in Mauritius on 4 June 2019 on the negotiation of a settlement over Chagos and the Chagossians with Mauritius.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262274","262274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131099","2019-06-12","Home Office","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps he is taking to ensure the provision of compensation to victims of financial fraud.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262275","262275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131100","2019-06-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will publish the political parties that UK Embassies and High Commissions overseas have a policy not to engage with.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262276","262276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131101","2019-06-12","Home Office","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps he is taking to tackle the potential use of drones in terrorist attacks.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262277","262277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131102","2019-06-12","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the procurement contract award process for London 2012 and the Olympic Games.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262278","262278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131103","2019-06-12","Department for Education","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to encourage the establishment of Combined Cadet Force units in state schools in (a) Havering and (b) England.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262279","262279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131104","2019-06-12","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department has taken to tackle potential corruption in the awarding of procurement contracts for London 2012 and the Olympic Games.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262280","262280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131105","2019-06-12","Department for Education","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to encourage the establishment of combined Cadet force units in state schools in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262281","262281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131106","2019-06-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to prevent plastic waste from the UK entering the world's oceans.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262282","262282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131107","2019-06-12","Department for Education","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to encourage children from Black and Minority Ethnic backgrounds to participate in Combined Cadet Force units in states schools.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262283","262283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131108","2019-06-12","Ministry of Justice","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many serious assaults there have been on staff in HM prisons in the last five years for which information is available.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262284","262284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131109","2019-06-12","Department for International Trade","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps his Department has taken to promote UK businesses for the award of Olympic Games contracts.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262285","262285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131110","2019-06-12","Department for International Trade","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether the Government has received assurances that UK businesses will be able to tender for the provision of clay pigeon shooting traps for the Tokyo Olympics 2020 and for Paris 2024.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262286","262286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131111","2019-06-12","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps are being taken to ensure that sub-contractors used for the provision of equipment for Tokyo 2020, Paris 20204 and other major international sports contests comply with the Foreign Corrupt Practices Act.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262287","262287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131114","2019-06-12","Department for International Trade","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what guarantees of financial stability are required from firms tendering to supply sports equipment for Olympic and Paralympic Games in Tokyo 2020 and Paris 2024.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262290","262290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131115","2019-06-12","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, to which organisations the shooting traps used in the London 2012 Olympic Games were donated.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262291","262291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131116","2019-06-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what representations his Department has received on the effect of the Wild Animals in Circuses Bill on human rights.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262292","262292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131117","2019-06-12","Home Office","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps he is taking to reduce fraud in the financial sector.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262293","262293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1131215","2019-06-17","Department for Education","2019-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the number of children caught with a knife at school in each of the last 10 years in (a) the UK and (b) Coventry.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 263049","263049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130664","2019-06-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will publish the full key data on young people's access to mental health services, as requested by the Public Accounts Committee in their report into mental health services for children and young people, published on 11 January 2019.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261541","261541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130665","2019-06-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the Public Accounts Committee report, Mental health services for children and young people, published on 11 January 2019, what steps his Department plans to take to assess whether parity of esteem for children and young people's mental health services has been achieved.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261542","261542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130666","2019-06-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the Public Accounts Committee report, Mental health services for children and young people, published on 11 January 2019, if his Department will publish information on what happens to young people with mental health issues who do not receive any or timely treatment.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261543","261543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130667","2019-06-12","Department for Education","2019-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when his Department plans to publish information on the responses to the asbestos management assurance process at responsible body and school level.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261544","261544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130668","2019-06-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will increase funding for sexual health services in local communities.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261463","261463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130669","2019-06-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of sexual health services for local communities.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261464","261464"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130670","2019-06-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he plans to bring forward legislative proposals to enable a claimant be able to make an application for industrial injuries disabled benefit for Dupuytren’s contracture.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261503","261503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130671","2019-06-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much the NHS spent on the NHS app before NHSX announced plans to scale back development of that App on 31 May 2019.","Biography information for Jo Swinson","Jo Swinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261489","261489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130672","2019-06-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much his Department has spent on setting up and running NHSX to date.","Biography information for Jo Swinson","Jo Swinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261490","261490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130673","2019-06-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many staff have been (a) transferred from his Department or other public bodies to NHSX and (b) recruited externally.","Biography information for Jo Swinson","Jo Swinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261491","261491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130674","2019-06-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care,  if he will publish a response to Early Day Motion 2173, on World Glaucoma Week and access to effective treatments.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261514","261514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130675","2019-06-12","Ministry of Justice","2019-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 21 May 2019 to Question 253551 on Ministry of Justice: telephone services, on what date that helpline was set up; how many calls that helpline received in each month from the date it was set up to 30 April 2019; what promotional material was used to advertise that helpline's use; and whether that helpline is still in use.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261502","261502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130676","2019-06-12","Home Office","2019-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of whether test centres have submitted the same voice recording clips for all students even when the Toeic English language test was taken in test conditions; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261462","261462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130677","2019-06-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the reasons for the increase in mumps cases in the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261485","261485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130678","2019-06-12","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment his Department has made of the extent of coverage of the (a) national and (b) local DAB network as at 1 January 2019.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261486","261486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130679","2019-06-12","Ministry of Defence","2019-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the (a) nature and (b) purpose is of the Special Instructions Intelligence Networks workshops provided by his Department to the Saudi military.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261540","261540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130680","2019-06-11","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what representations she has received on the extent of physical and verbal abuse directed at volunteers in the charity sector.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261527","261527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130681","2019-06-11","Home Office","2019-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussion he has had with Police and Crime Commissioners on tackling crime targeted at charity shops.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261528","261528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130682","2019-06-11","Home Office","2019-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will ensure that the call for evidence on violence and abuse toward shop staff receives representations from charity shop volunteers.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261529","261529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130683","2019-06-11","Home Office","2019-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will create a place for representatives of charity retail volunteers on the national retail crime steering group.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261530","261530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130684","2019-06-12","Department for International Development","2019-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, which (a) countries and (b) regions of those countries have Ebola outbreaks; and what support his Department is providing to (i) tackle and (ii) prevent the spread of that disease.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261465","261465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130685","2019-06-11","Ministry of Justice","2019-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the overall budget for the Criminal Injuries Compensation Scheme was in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261492","261492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130686","2019-06-12","Ministry of Justice","2019-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the overall budget of the Criminal Injuries Compensation Scheme was for covering the costs of acquiring medical evidence for applicants in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261493","261493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130687","2019-06-11","Home Office","2019-06-07","To ask Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment the Minister for Crime, Safeguarding and Vulnerability has made of the extent of (a) violence towards and (b) abuse of shop staff and volunteers in the charity retail sector.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261479","261479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130688","2019-06-11","Home Office","2019-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps the Minister for Crime, Safeguarding and Vulnerability is taking to ensure her investigation into violence and abuse toward shop staff takes into account the views and experiences of charity shop volunteers.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261480","261480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130689","2019-06-11","Home Office","2019-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will take steps to ensure that the views of charity retailers are represented on the National Retail Crime Steering Group.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261481","261481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130690","2019-06-11","Home Office","2019-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if the Minister for Crime, Safeguarding and Vulnerability will meet with the Charity Retail Association to discuss the extent of violence and abuse in the charity retail sector.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261482","261482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130691","2019-06-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what plans does the Government have for the (a) future and (b) funding of the renewable heat initiative.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261466","261466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130692","2019-06-11","Home Office","2019-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will ensure any future protections for shop staff selling age-restricted products apply to charity shop volunteers who sell those products.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261531","261531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130693","2019-06-12","Department for Education","2019-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent discussions he has had with the Regional Schools Commissioner for Yorkshire and Lancashire on the closure of Emslie Morgan Academy.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261478","261478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130694","2019-06-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to help promote flexible working for (a) doctors and (b) nurses in the NHS.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261468","261468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130695","2019-06-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to improve mental health support for NHS doctors.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261469","261469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130696","2019-06-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will hold discussions with industry on the use of packaging on junk food designed to appeal to children.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261470","261470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130697","2019-06-12","Ministry of Justice","2019-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many legal aid applications for domestic violence have been made in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261494","261494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130698","2019-06-11","Ministry of Justice","2019-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of legal aid applications for civil cases of domestic violence have been accepted in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261495","261495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130699","2019-06-12","Ministry of Justice","2019-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many applications for legal aid for injuction cases have been made in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261496","261496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130700","2019-06-11","Ministry of Justice","2019-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of applications for legal aid for injunction cases were accepted in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261497","261497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130701","2019-06-11","Home Office","2019-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many reported instances of rape led to a criminal charge in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261498","261498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130702","2019-06-12","Home Office","2019-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what percentage of reported instances of rape led to a criminal charge in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261499","261499"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130703","2019-06-11","Attorney General","2019-06-07","To ask the Attorney General, (a) how many and (b) what proportion of cases of rape reported to the CPS were administratively finalised in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261500","261500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130704","2019-06-12","Attorney General","2019-06-07","To ask the Attorney General, what the average number of days taken from a report of rape to a decision to charge was in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261501","261501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130705","2019-06-11","Women and Equalities","2019-06-07","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, when she plans to implement section 36 of the Equality Act 2010; and will she make a statement.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Dame Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261477","261477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130706","2019-06-11","Scotland Office","2019-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what proportion of organisations that hold contracts with his Department pay the National Living Wage.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261515","261515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130707","2019-06-11","Northern Ireland Office","2019-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what proportion of organisations that hold contracts with her Department pay the National Living Wage.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261516","261516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130708","2019-06-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he plans to take with the US Administration and the Government of Norway to help tackle recent violence in Khartoum.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261467","261467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130709","2019-06-11","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, if he will place copies of the representations he has received on behalf of the National Lottery and Camelot on the reorganisation of society lotteries in the Library.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261505","261505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130710","2019-06-12","Department for Transport","2019-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many D4 medical examination reports have been completed during (a) each of the five years prior to December 2014 and (b) each year since December 2014.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261517","261517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130711","2019-06-12","Department for Transport","2019-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many D4 medical examination applications have been refused during (a) each of the five years prior to December 2014 and (b) each year since December 2014.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261518","261518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130712","2019-06-12","Department for Transport","2019-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many DVLA centres are licensed to complete D4 medical examination reports.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261519","261519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130713","2019-06-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if will bring forward legislative proposals on animal re-homing before the ban on the third party selling of puppies and kittens comes into effect in April 2020.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261545","261545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130714","2019-06-11","Department for Education","2019-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the value for money of the national school breakfast programme.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261506","261506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130715","2019-06-11","Department for Education","2019-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether his Department plans to extend the national school breakfast programme.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261507","261507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130716","2019-06-11","Department for Education","2019-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to lower the number of children at risk of starting the school day hungry.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261508","261508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130717","2019-06-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will publish his Department's plans for rural communities in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Drew Hendry","Drew Hendry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261526","261526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130718","2019-06-11","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether he has plans to widen his Department’s review into council tax collection to include how local authorities collect council tax debt under The Council Tax (Administration and Enforcement) Regulations 1992.","Biography information for Bambos Charalambous","Bambos Charalambous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261538","261538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130719","2019-06-11","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether he has plans to amend The Council Tax (Administration and Enforcement) Regulations 1992 to prevent people becoming liable for their full annual council tax bill after missing one payment.","Biography information for Bambos Charalambous","Bambos Charalambous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261539","261539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130720","2019-06-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to help ensure the protection of Christians from persecution in (a) Africa, (b) the Middle East and (c) East Asia.","Biography information for Luke Hall","Luke Hall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261520","261520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130721","2019-06-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to promote religious tolerance throughout the world.","Biography information for Luke Hall","Luke Hall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261521","261521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130722","2019-06-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to support Christians on death row in Pakistan on charges of blasphemy.","Biography information for Luke Hall","Luke Hall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261522","261522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130723","2019-06-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of establishing a fund to support persecuted Christians through help with legal fees and access to justice.","Biography information for Luke Hall","Luke Hall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261523","261523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130724","2019-06-11","Department for International Development","2019-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that UK aid reaches persecuted Christians.","Biography information for Luke Hall","Luke Hall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261524","261524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130725","2019-06-11","Department for International Development","2019-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of requiring international NGOs to consider religious vulnerability in their definition of need.","Biography information for Luke Hall","Luke Hall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261525","261525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130726","2019-06-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many trees were (a) planted and (b) cut down in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261476","261476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130727","2019-06-11","Department for International Development","2019-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, with reference to recent UN-mediated talks in Amman between officials of Yemen’s Central bank what steps he is taking to support further such meetings.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261473","261473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130728","2019-06-11","Department for International Development","2019-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, with reference to the UN-mediated talks in Amman between officials in Yemen’s Central bank, what steps he is taking to ensure civil servants are paid as set out in the Stockholm Agreement.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261474","261474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130729","2019-06-11","Department for International Development","2019-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment he has made of the economic effect of regulating (a) imports, (b) commercial banks and (c) money exchangers in Yemen on Houthi revenues in that country.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261475","261475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130730","2019-06-12","Department for International Development","2019-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps the Government is taking to help tackle counterfeit anti-malaria medication in Africa.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261471","261471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130731","2019-06-12","Department for Transport","2019-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 6 June 2019 to Question 259184, how many railway stations have been (a) opened and (b) closed in the north of England since 2010.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261504","261504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130732","2019-06-12","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, on what date his Department plans to write to building owners eligible for the aluminium composite material cladding fund.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261509","261509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130733","2019-06-12","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what criteria his Department is using to determine whether building owners should be sent a letter regarding the aluminium composite material Cladding Fund.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261510","261510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130734","2019-06-12","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what the timescale is for (a) the testing regime for non-aluminium composite material cladding to be completed and (b) publishing the results from the testing regime for non-aluminium composite material cladding.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261511","261511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130735","2019-06-12","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department plans to take in cases where building owners eligible for the aluminium composite material Cladding Fund do not apply within three months of being written to.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261512","261512"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130736","2019-06-11","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many letters his Department is planning to send regarding the ACM Cladding fund; and if he will publish the (a) names of the residential buildings and (b) constituencies in which those buildings are located that his Department is sending such letters to.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261513","261513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130737","2019-06-12","Ministry of Defence","2019-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of total spending on veterans' support services in each region of the UK in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261532","261532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130738","2019-06-12","Ministry of Defence","2019-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of total spending on veterans' support services in (a) Barnsley, (b) South Yorkshire and (c) the UK in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261533","261533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130739","2019-06-12","Ministry of Defence","2019-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much has been spent by the Aged Veterans Fund in each year since 2015.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261534","261534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130740","2019-06-12","Ministry of Defence","2019-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much funding from the Aged Veterans Fund has been allocated to projects and groups in (a) South Yorkshire and (b) Barnsley in each year since 2015.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261535","261535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130741","2019-06-11","Treasury","2019-06-07","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what reports he has received on young people not receiving their national insurance number on time; and what the reason is for delays in sending out national insurance numbers.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261487","261487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130742","2019-06-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much funding has been allocated to the (a) the Veterans' Mental Health Transition, Intervention and Liaison Service and (b) the NHS Veterans' Mental Health Complex Treatment Service in (i) the UK, (ii) South Yorkshire and (iii) Barnsley in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261536","261536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130743","2019-06-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of trends in the level of child poverty (a) before and (b) after housing costs have been taken into account in each local authority in Wales in each year for which data is available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261483","261483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130744","2019-06-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effect of housing costs on the level of child poverty; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261484","261484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130745","2019-06-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pusuant to the Answers of 5 June 2019 to Questions 257798 and 257799, and in the format of the Answer of 11 April 2019 to Question 241458, what proportion of jobs in (a) the UK, (b) Yorkshire, (c) South Yorkshire and (c) Barnsley are paid the (i) National Living Wage and (ii) National Minimum Wage.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261537","261537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130746","2019-06-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many women born in the 1950s and affected by the change of the state pension age received less than five years notice of that change.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261488","261488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130747","2019-06-12","Cabinet Office","2019-06-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the number of people below 18 years of age who are married.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261472","261472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130976","2019-06-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if the Government will make an assessment of the potential merits of allocating an additional bank holiday to commemorate the 75th anniversary of VJ Day.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262251","262251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130098","2019-06-10","Home Office","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions he had with the Scottish Government before the appointment of the first Investigatory Powers Commissioner in 2017.","Biography information for Stewart Malcolm McDonald","Stewart Malcolm McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 260679","260679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130274","2019-06-06","Department for International Trade","2019-06-06","What recent discussions he has had with his international counterparts on the maintenance of the rules-based system for international trade.","Biography information for Damien Moore","Damien Moore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 911199","911199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130339","2019-06-11","Treasury","2019-06-06","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the number of people working in the public sector that are subject to the 2019 loan charge; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261176","261176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130340","2019-06-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the correspondence between the Prime Minister and Haemophilia Scotland in May 2019, what steps the Department is taking to provide people (a) infected and (b) affected by contaminated blood with a fair and transparent support scheme; and what steps he is taking to tackle the disparity in financial support across the Devolved Administrations.","Biography information for Paul Girvan","Paul Girvan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261271","261271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130341","2019-06-11","Ministry of Defence","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the open skeleton argument of the Secretary of State for hearing 7,8,10 February 2017, claim number CO/1306/2016, (a) how many and (b) on what dates the Government has provided (i) International Targeting Courses and (ii) senior airmen's workshops on SPINS since March 2015.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261272","261272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130342","2019-06-11","Treasury","2019-06-06","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many firms registered under the Registered Exporter system in (a) 2017 and (b) 2018.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261120","261120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130343","2019-06-11","Cabinet Office","2019-06-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the number of people earning less than (a) £7.70 per hour and (b)  £8.21 per hour.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261121","261121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130344","2019-06-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what information his Department holds on the (a) underpayment of the national minimum wage by employers, (b) amount of arrears and fines paid by employers for underpayment of the national minimum wage and (c) number of successful prosecutions of employers for underpayment of the national minimum wage for the 2018-19 financial year.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261273","261273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130346","2019-06-10","Department for Education","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent discussions he has had with the post-18 education sector in (a) Scotland, (b) Wales and (c) Northern Ireland on the proposals set out in the post-18 education and funding review.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261274","261274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130347","2019-06-11","Department for Education","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what inquiries his Department is undertaking into financial irregularities at (a) Bright Tribe Trust and (b) Adventure Learning Academies Trust.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261231","261231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130348","2019-06-10","Department for Education","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether his Department has made an assessment of the implications for its policies of the September 2018 Panorama programme on Bright Tribe Trust and Adventure Learning Academies Trust; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261232","261232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130349","2019-06-10","Department for Education","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what reports Bright Tribe Trust has submitted to his Department since 1 July 2018.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261233","261233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130350","2019-06-11","Department for Education","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether (a) his Department or (b) the Education and Skills Funding Agency hold copies of the minutes of any board meetings of Bright Tribe Trust Limited.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261234","261234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130351","2019-06-10","Department for Education","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what his policy is on (a) inspection and (b) regulation of semi-independent accommodation for looked-after 16 and 17 year-olds.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261235","261235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130352","2019-06-10","Department for Education","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of ensuring that the receiving authority has shared responsibility with the home authority for looked after children and young people who are placed out of area.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261236","261236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130353","2019-06-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether the Government has made an estimate of the cost of electricity in the steel sectors in (a) the UK, (b) Germany and (c) France.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261196","261196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130355","2019-06-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the effect of uncompetitive electricity prices in the UK steel sector on that sector’s ability to compete internationally.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261197","261197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130356","2019-06-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the effect of high electricity prices on the resilience of the UK steel industry.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261198","261198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130357","2019-06-11","Department for Education","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 5 June 2019 to Question 257589 on Academies: Lighting, if he will place those documents in the Library.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261237","261237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130358","2019-06-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to UK Steel's report entitled The Energy Price Scandal, published in December 2018, whether his Department has made an assessment of the potential merits of implementing the recommendations made in that report to reduce the disparity between industrial electricity prices in the UK and those in Germany and France.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261199","261199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130359","2019-06-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if the Government will commit to providing competitive power prices for the steel sector.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261200","261200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130360","2019-06-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when the Government plans to provide a higher level of exemption to the UK steel sector for the costs of renewables.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261201","261201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130361","2019-06-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of introducing (a) German, French and Netherlands-style discounts on network costs, (b) a Capacity Market Levy exemption, (c) 100 per cent compensation for the indirect costs of carbon and (d) other substantive measures to lower the high electricity prices faced by the UK steel sector.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261202","261202"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130362","2019-06-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether (a) he, (b) his Ministers and (c) his officials have had meetings with the former Sudanese Intelligence Chief Salah Gosh since 1 May 2019.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261095","261095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130364","2019-06-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the total emissions were in England of (a) PM2.5, (b) PM1 and (c) PM0.1 in (i) 2018 and (ii) 2017.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261096","261096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130365","2019-06-10","Department for Education","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what guidance his Department has published on suicide prevention strategies for universities.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261189","261189"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130366","2019-06-10","Home Office","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what guidance has been published for police services on the use of spit guards for arrested persons.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261190","261190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130367","2019-06-10","Ministry of Justice","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many recorded knife crime offences were disposed of with a conviction in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261191","261191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130368","2019-06-10","Home Office","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment his Department has made of the effectiveness of the opportunities for the police to seek financial redress when police officers are called to attend civil matters.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261192","261192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130369","2019-06-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many companies have gone into liquidation in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261193","261193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130370","2019-06-10","Department for Education","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to encourage pay restraint among university vice chancellors.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261194","261194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130371","2019-06-11","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether he has pans to encourage local authorities to reduce rates of council tax.","Biography information for Stephen McPartland","Stephen McPartland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261214","261214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130372","2019-06-10","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether he has plans to reduce the two per cent referendum threshold on council tax increases to zero.","Biography information for Stephen McPartland","Stephen McPartland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261215","261215"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130373","2019-06-10","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what progress he has made on encouraging local authorities to invest more of their reserves in local communities.","Biography information for Stephen McPartland","Stephen McPartland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261216","261216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130374","2019-06-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what guidance his Department has issued on the (a) use and (b) retention of information produced from Guthrie tests.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261195","261195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130375","2019-06-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of trends in the level of public health spending on the local authority public health services.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261268","261268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130376","2019-06-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of trends in the level of public health funding of on the provision of local authority sexual health services.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261269","261269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130377","2019-06-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans his Department has to ensure the maintenance of the provision of local authority sexual health services.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261270","261270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130378","2019-06-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when he plans to publish the Code of Practice for Liberty Protection Safeguards.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261206","261206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130379","2019-06-10","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many affordable houses have been built in (a) the UK, (b) Greater London and (c) Ealing in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Dr Rupa Huq","Dr Rupa Huq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261275","261275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130380","2019-06-10","Ministry of Defence","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, where the planned centre of excellence for human security will be based, on what date it will start; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261160","261160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130381","2019-06-10","Ministry of Defence","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what funding her Department plans to allocate to the centre of excellence for human security; what the (a) priorities and (b) objectives of that centre will be; how many staff will be employed in that centre; and of those staff how many will be gender advisers; what training her Department plans to provide; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261161","261161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130382","2019-06-10","Ministry of Defence","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate she has made of the number of recommendations in the (a) 2016, (b) 2017 and (c) 2018 Service Complaints Ombudsman's annual report have been complied with; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261162","261162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130383","2019-06-10","Ministry of Defence","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many service personnel in the (a) Army, (b) Royal Navy and (c) the RAF have been (i) investigated by and (ii) discharged from the services as a result of (A) membership of national action (B) membership of a far right organisation, (C) anti-Semitic organisations and (D) Islamophobic organisations; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261163","261163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130384","2019-06-10","Department for Education","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether he has made an assessment of the effect on the impartiality of Ofsted of that organisation being responsible for the inspection of the quality of apprenticeships.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261188","261188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130385","2019-06-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Armenian counterpart on the protection of endangered brown bears in that country.","Biography information for Mr Ranil Jayawardena","Mr Ranil Jayawardena","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261266","261266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130386","2019-06-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will increase funding allocated to (a) rehabilitation centres to help bears rescued from cages in restaurants and (b) the protection of endangered species more widely.","Biography information for Mr Ranil Jayawardena","Mr Ranil Jayawardena","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261267","261267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130387","2019-06-11","Department for Education","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he has made an assessment of the effect of trends in the level of school finances on the ability of schools to procure environmentally sound services from contractors and suppliers.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261276","261276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130388","2019-06-11","Department for International Development","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the oral contribution of 6 June 2019 on the amount spend on climate and the environment, what baseline his Department will use to measure the doubling; and what the timeframe is for that target to be achieved.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261277","261277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130389","2019-06-11","Department for Education","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if his Department will make an assessment of the education sector to identify steps that can be taken to help that sector become carbon neutral.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261278","261278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130390","2019-06-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps the Government is taking to reduce waiting times for dietetic services in the NHS.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261167","261167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130391","2019-06-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he plans to take as part of the interim NHS People’s Plan to increase the number of dietetic posts with the (a) primary care and (b) the NHS.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261168","261168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130392","2019-06-11","Cabinet Office","2019-06-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 5 June 2019 to Question 257533 on Huawei: 5G, what recent assessment he has made of the risks to the (a) security and (b) reliability of UK 5G networks from Huawei Cyber Security Evaluation Centre evaluating 5G equipment after deployment.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261279","261279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130393","2019-06-10","Department for Education","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many (a) schools and (b) children are participating in the National School Breakfast Programme each day.","Biography information for Siobhain McDonagh","Siobhain McDonagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261078","261078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130394","2019-06-10","Department for Education","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children the National School Breakfast Programme (a) was projected to reach and (b) has reached.","Biography information for Siobhain McDonagh","Siobhain McDonagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261079","261079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130395","2019-06-10","Department for Education","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether his Department has plans to maintain funding for the National School Breakfast Programme.","Biography information for Siobhain McDonagh","Siobhain McDonagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261080","261080"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130396","2019-06-10","Department for Education","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the timeframe is for his Department's decision on funding for the National School Breakfast Programme in 2020-2022.","Biography information for Siobhain McDonagh","Siobhain McDonagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261081","261081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130397","2019-06-10","Department for Education","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the National School Breakfast Programme on social mobility.","Biography information for Siobhain McDonagh","Siobhain McDonagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261082","261082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130398","2019-06-11","Cabinet Office","2019-06-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 5 June to Question 257533, when the Huawei Cyber Security Evaluation Centre plans to begin its assessment of 5G equipment.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261280","261280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130399","2019-06-10","Department for Education","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of effectiveness of the National School Breakfast Programme.","Biography information for Siobhain McDonagh","Siobhain McDonagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261083","261083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130400","2019-06-10","Department for Education","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking in response to the finding of the National Association of Head Teachers Report that four out of five school leaders have seen a rise in the number of pupils arriving at school hungry in the last five years.","Biography information for Siobhain McDonagh","Siobhain McDonagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261084","261084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130401","2019-06-10","Department for Education","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how the revenue from the Soft Drinks Industry Levy was spent in 2018-2019.","Biography information for Siobhain McDonagh","Siobhain McDonagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261085","261085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130402","2019-06-10","Department for Education","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Treasury new story of 5 April 2018, Soft Drinks Industry Levy comes into effect, what assessment he has made of the effect of the Soft Drinks Industry Levy on the number of children starting the day with a healthy breakfast.","Biography information for Siobhain McDonagh","Siobhain McDonagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261086","261086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130403","2019-06-11","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 5 June 2019 to Question 257533 and the statement in that Answer that the Huawei Cyber Security Evaluation Centre has not begun assessing any 5G equipment, how the Supply Chain Review will ensure the secure and resilient roll-out of 5G.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261281","261281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130404","2019-06-11","Treasury","2019-06-06","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the Financial Times article entitled UK net zero emissions target will cost more than £1tn, published on 5 June 2019, if he will place a copy of his letter to the Prime Minister on the costs and benefits of moving to a net zero target for UK greenhouse gas emissions in the House of Commons Library.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261071","261071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130405","2019-06-11","Treasury","2019-06-06","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what programmes were allocated funding from the Soft Drinks Industry Levy in 2018-2019.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261102","261102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130406","2019-06-11","Department for International Development","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, with reference to his Department's Memorandum of Understanding with the Palestinian Authority (PA), what discussions his Department has had with the PA on reports that the PA President's spokesperson describing convicted Palestinian terrorists as soldiers who act on their behalf and receive orders from them.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261073","261073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130407","2019-06-11","Department for International Development","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what the average salary is of employees of the Palestinian Authority Ministry of Education whose salaries are paid for by his Department through the PEGASE scheme.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261074","261074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130408","2019-06-11","Department for International Development","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many employees of the Palestinian Authority Ministry of Education employees whose salaries are paid for by his Department through the PEGASE scheme receive a salary in excess of 2000 NIS per month.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261075","261075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130409","2019-06-11","Department for International Development","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what the average salary is of employees of the Palestinian Authority Ministry of Health whose salaries are paid for by his Department through the PEGASE scheme.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261076","261076"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130410","2019-06-11","Department for International Development","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many employees of the Palestinian Authority Ministry of Health employees whose salaries are paid for by his Department through the PEGASE scheme receive a salary in excess of 2000 NIS per month.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261077","261077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130411","2019-06-11","Treasury","2019-06-06","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what progress has been made on amending the tapered annual allowance for NHS doctors.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261103","261103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130412","2019-06-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, in response to the recent Public Health England statistics that showed an increase in new sexually transmitted infections, if he will commit to a national sexual health strategy.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261089","261089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130413","2019-06-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, for what reason his Department does not allocate funding for testing for (a) mycoplasma genitalium and (b) trichomoniasis vaginitis sexually transmitted infections.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261090","261090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130414","2019-06-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what proportion of sexual health clinics are not able to fully test for (a) gonorrhoea and (b) drug-resistant strains of gonorrhoea.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261091","261091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130415","2019-06-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department's policy is to ensure that HIV pre-exposure prophylaxis is available to all people who could benefit from it.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261092","261092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130416","2019-06-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will consider including sexual health and HIV in his Department's forthcoming prevention green paper.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261093","261093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130417","2019-06-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment he has made of the potential effect of compulsory relationships and sex education on rates of sexually transmitted infections in young people.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261094","261094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130418","2019-06-11","Home Office","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many extradition requests were made by the US for UK citizens in each year since 2014; and how many of those requests are outstanding.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261104","261104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130419","2019-06-11","Department for International Development","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent support his Department has provided to people in Somalia affected by drought.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261105","261105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130420","2019-06-10","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what recent discussions he has had with community groups affected by the Grenfell Tower fire on the potential reform of fire safety legislation.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261282","261282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130421","2019-06-10","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many survivors of the Grenfell Tower fire are waiting for permanent housing.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261283","261283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130422","2019-06-10","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what recent steps his Department is taking to encourage the retro-fitting of sprinklers in housing developments.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261284","261284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130423","2019-06-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent steps he has taken to enhance diplomatic relations between the UK and Honduras.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261126","261126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130424","2019-06-11","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether he has made a recent estimate of the number of young people who live in their (a) home and (b) university towns due to unaffordable rent in large cities and regional centres.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261106","261106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130425","2019-06-10","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer or 20 May 2019 to Question 254756 on Historic County Flags Day, whether borough council leaders are also encouraged to engage in local activities to celebrate their historic counties.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261127","261127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130426","2019-06-11","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answers of 8 May 2019 and 15 May 2019 to Questions 250034 and 252869, if he will publish an updated regional breakdown of (a) blocks with aluminium composite material cladding systems unlikely to meet building regulations which are yet to be remediated and (b) dwellings in those blocks as of May 2019 based on the building safety programme figures due to be published on 10 June 2019.","Biography information for Sarah Jones","Sarah Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261285","261285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130427","2019-06-10","Department for Transport","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the potential environmental merits of hydrogen fuel cell vehicles.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261128","261128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130428","2019-06-10","Department for Transport","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans he has to increase the accessibility of private hire vehicles for wheelchair users.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261129","261129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130429","2019-06-10","Department for Transport","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions he has had with representatives of London City Airport on noise complaints.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261130","261130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130430","2019-06-10","Department for Transport","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions he has had with cruise lines on pollution.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261131","261131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130431","2019-06-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the recent trends in the UK bee population.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261132","261132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130432","2019-06-11","Department for Education","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many students (a) in total and (b) eligible for free school meals took physical education at A level in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261158","261158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130433","2019-06-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to increase biodiversity in (a) London and (b) the South East.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261133","261133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130434","2019-06-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to protect (a) solitary bees, (b) honey bees and (c) bumblebees.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261134","261134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130435","2019-06-10","Department for Transport","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment he has made of the potential merits of increasing the rail freight capacity for the economy.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261135","261135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130436","2019-06-10","Department for International Development","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether he plans to support the International Fund for Animal Welfare's initiative to provide detection dogs in Benin which can sniff out shipments of animal parts, in order to disrupt trafficking networks.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261136","261136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130437","2019-06-10","Home Office","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of the decision by the US Administration to designate the Muslim Brotherhood a terrorist group; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261137","261137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130438","2019-06-11","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 6 June 2019 to Question 259402 on high rise flats: insulation, what estimate he made of the number of blocks that would potentially draw on the fund when calculating the £200 million private sector cladding remediation fund.","Biography information for Sarah Jones","Sarah Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261286","261286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130439","2019-06-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent steps he has taken to support diplomatic relations between the UK and Jamaica.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261138","261138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130440","2019-06-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he has taken to improve diplomatic relations with Mozambique.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261139","261139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130441","2019-06-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he plans to make representations to his Indonesian counterpart on ending virginity tests for women applying to the Indonesian military.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261140","261140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130442","2019-06-11","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department will take to ensure that (a) music and (b) the evening economy are embedded in local industrial strategies.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261119","261119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130443","2019-06-10","Home Office","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people from Kirkcaldy and Cowdenbeath constituency have been held in (a) Dungavel and (b) other UK immigration removal centres since their inception.","Biography information for Lesley Laird","Lesley Laird","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261287","261287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130444","2019-06-10","Home Office","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people from Kirkcaldy and Cowdenbeath constituency are being held in (a) Dungavel and (b) other immigration removal centres in the UK.","Biography information for Lesley Laird","Lesley Laird","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261288","261288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130445","2019-06-10","Home Office","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many children from Kirkcaldy and Cowdenbeath constituency are being held in (a) Dungavel and (b) other UK immigration removal centres.","Biography information for Lesley Laird","Lesley Laird","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261289","261289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130446","2019-06-10","Home Office","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average duration of stay is at (a) Dungavel and (b) other immigration detention centres in the UK in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Lesley Laird","Lesley Laird","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261290","261290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130447","2019-06-10","Department for International Trade","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what assessment he has made of recent trends of the level of foreign direct investment into the UK FinTech industry in the (a) 2017-18 and (b) 2016-17 financial years.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261177","261177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130448","2019-06-10","Treasury","2019-06-06","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much the UK FinTech industry paid the Exchequer in tax revenue in (a) 2017-18 and (b) 2016-17 financial years.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261178","261178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130449","2019-06-10","Treasury","2019-06-06","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what key performance indicators his Department uses to assess the performance of Open Banking; and what recent assessment he has made of the performance of Open Banking.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261179","261179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130450","2019-06-10","Treasury","2019-06-06","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment the Government has made of the potential merits of cryptocurrencies as a means of payment.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261180","261180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130451","2019-06-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he has made an assessment of the potential effect of cellular agriculture on reducing greenhouse gas emissions.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261181","261181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130452","2019-06-10","Cabinet Office","2019-06-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of using distributed ledger technology across the public sector.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261182","261182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130453","2019-06-10","Home Office","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the weekly cost is to detain an individual from Kirkcaldy and Cowdenbeath constituency in (a) Dungavel and (b) other UK immigration removal centres.","Biography information for Lesley Laird","Lesley Laird","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261291","261291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130454","2019-06-10","Home Office","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what education provision is provided to children detained at (a) Dungavel and (b) other UK immigration removal centres.","Biography information for Lesley Laird","Lesley Laird","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261292","261292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130455","2019-06-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure each hospital diabetes team includes a mental health professional.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261213","261213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130456","2019-06-11","Ministry of Defence","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many deduction of earning requests made by the Child Maintenance Service have been declined by the (a) MoD Defence Council and (b) Authorised Officer; and if she will publish the reasons for those requests being declined.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261264","261264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130457","2019-06-10","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what fees are being charged for HMO Licences by each Council.","Biography information for Anne-Marie Trevelyan","Anne-Marie Trevelyan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261293","261293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130458","2019-06-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the average waiting time was between appointments for people with (a) Type 1 and (b) Type 2 diabetes who have diabetes-related renal conditions in each (i) hospital and (ii) clinic in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261109","261109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130459","2019-06-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the average waiting time was between appointments for people with diabetes-related psychological conditions who have (a) Type 1 and (b) Type 2 diabetes in each (i) hospital and (ii) clinic in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261110","261110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130460","2019-06-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the level of uptake of the most recent flu vaccine.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261072","261072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130461","2019-06-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people with (a) Type 1 and (b) Type 2 diabetes are on the waiting list for an appointment for psychological support in each NHS (i) hospital and (ii) clinic.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261111","261111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130462","2019-06-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people are on the waiting list for an appointment with a psychologist in each NHS (a) hospital and (b) clinic.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261112","261112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130463","2019-06-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people with (a) Type 1 and (b) Type 2 diabetes are on the waiting list for an appointment with a psychologist.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261113","261113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130464","2019-06-10","Department for International Development","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment he has made of whether the Global Fund to Fight AIDS, TB and Malaria has adequate resources to successfully treat 40 million people with TB by 2022, as set out in the commitments of the UN High-Level Meeting on TB; and what progress has been made toward meeting those commitments.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261203","261203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130465","2019-06-10","Department for International Development","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps he is taking with international counterparts to promote the allocation of additional funding for the sixth replenishment of the Global Fund.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261204","261204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130466","2019-06-10","Department for International Development","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of strengthening TB prevention, diagnosis and treatment on (a) rates of antimicrobial resistance and (b) health systems around the world.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261205","261205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130467","2019-06-10","Treasury","2019-06-06","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to ensure that people without internet access can continue to receive paper bills and statements from their banks.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261294","261294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130468","2019-06-10","Treasury","2019-06-06","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to help ensure the credit ratings of victims of identity fraud are protected.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261141","261141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130469","2019-06-10","Department for International Trade","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps he is taking to support free trade between the UK and Jamaica.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261142","261142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130470","2019-06-11","Cabinet Office","2019-06-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether any Government departments (a) offer free sanitary products in the workplace and (b) have plans to introduce such provision.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261295","261295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130471","2019-06-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will extend top ups for personal health budgets for products other than wheelchairs.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261171","261171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130472","2019-06-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make it his policy to introduce personal health budgets for wigs.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261172","261172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130473","2019-06-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will introduce minimum standards for wigs required by people.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261173","261173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130474","2019-06-10","Department for International Trade","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether he plans to make increased trade with Indonesia conditional on the removal of virginity tests for women applying to the Indonesian military.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261143","261143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130475","2019-06-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make it his policy that NHS England appoints a person responsible for (a) Alopecia and (b) the provision of wigs.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261174","261174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130476","2019-06-10","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of emergency and out of hours NHS dental cover in the (a) Shipley constituency and (b) Bradford district.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261175","261175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130477","2019-06-10","Department for International Trade","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps he has taken to negotiate a free trade deal with Honduras.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261144","261144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130478","2019-06-10","Department for International Trade","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what progress he has made in negotiating a free trade deal with Israel.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261145","261145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130479","2019-06-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent discussions he has had with Cabinet colleagues on mandatory calorie labelling for restaurants, cafes and takeaways.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261122","261122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130480","2019-06-10","Department for International Trade","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps he has taken to promote free trade with Mali after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261146","261146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130481","2019-06-10","Department for International Trade","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps he has taken to negotiate a free trade deal with Malawi after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261147","261147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130482","2019-06-10","Department for International Trade","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what progress has he made on strengthening the trade relationship with Togo after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261148","261148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130483","2019-06-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to encourage the Government of Oman to ensure the fair treatment of the Shuhuh 6.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261149","261149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130484","2019-06-11","Department for Transport","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that (a) cities and (b) towns include under represented groups when planning cycling infrastructure in England and Wales.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261123","261123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130485","2019-06-10","Ministry of Defence","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps her Department is taking to increase defence and security cooperation with Greece.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261150","261150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130486","2019-06-11","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Building a Safer Future: an implementation plan, if he will publish the (a) membership of the Joint Regulators Group and (b) minutes of that Group's meetings to date.","Biography information for Sarah Jones","Sarah Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261296","261296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130487","2019-06-10","Ministry of Defence","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether she plans for a continued UK presence in the Baltic following the conclusion of the current six-month patrol by HMS Westminster.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261151","261151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130488","2019-06-10","Ministry of Defence","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps she is taking to strengthen defence and security cooperation between the UK and Sweden.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261152","261152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130489","2019-06-10","Department for International Development","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether he plans to make aid to Indonesia conditional on the removal of virginity tests for women applying to the Indonesian military.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261153","261153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130490","2019-06-10","Ministry of Defence","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps she is taking to increase defence and security cooperation with Denmark.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261154","261154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130491","2019-06-10","Ministry of Justice","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many Failure to Appear warrants were issued (a) in each year between 2014 and 2018 and (b) from 1 January to 30 April 2019.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261185","261185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130492","2019-06-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what progress his Department has made on the draft legislation to include Dupuytren's Contracture to the list of prescribed diseases for the purpose of Industrial Injuries Disablement Benefit.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261187","261187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130493","2019-06-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to increase biodiversity in UK gardens.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261155","261155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130494","2019-06-10","Department for Transport","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment the Government has made of the potential economic benefits to the UK of the (a) manufacture and (b) use of autonomous vehicles.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261156","261156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130495","2019-06-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what progress the Government is making on achieving EU environmental quality standards for surface water by 2027.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261124","261124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130496","2019-06-11","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 11 February 2019 to Question 217592 on Buildings: Insulation, if he will publish the advice sent to building owners on how to (a) investigate and (b) remediate non-ACM cladding systems on their buildings.","Biography information for Sarah Jones","Sarah Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261297","261297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130497","2019-06-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to upgrade drainage systems to treat pollutants before they reach rivers.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261125","261125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130498","2019-06-10","Department for Education","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if the Government will bring forward plans to reduce university tuition fees to £7,500.","Biography information for Faisal Rashid","Faisal Rashid","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261298","261298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130499","2019-06-11","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what the timeframe is for the publication of legislative proposal to reform the charges levied on the owners of leasehold properties; and whether that legislation include reform of the charges levied on freeholders.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261164","261164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130500","2019-06-11","Home Office","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 14 May 2019 to Question 252534 on Immigration: EU Nationals, if he will place in the Library, a copy of the Equality Impact Assessment on the EU Settlement Scheme.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261207","261207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130501","2019-06-11","Home Office","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 20 May 2019 to Question 254185 on Immigration: EU Nationals, if he will place in the Library, a copy of the algorithm applied by his Department during automated residency checks.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261208","261208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130502","2019-06-11","Home Office","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 22 May 2019 to Question 254812, whether staff at the Home Office and Her Majesty’s Revenue and Customs will access that data for the purposes of the EU Settlement Scheme exclusively.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261209","261209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130503","2019-06-11","Home Office","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the letter dated 1 May 2019 from the Minister of State for Immigration to the Chair of the Home Affairs Select Committee, if his Department will include data on the responses received to the question of whether applicants have been continuously resident for less than five years, or more than five years, in relation to the outcome of the application in the monthly Official Statistics report on the EU Settlement Scheme.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261210","261210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130504","2019-06-10","Home Office","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 20 May 2019 to Question 254186 and with reference to page 9 of the Memorandum of Understanding between his Department and the Department for Work and Pensions and to pages 12-13 of the Memorandum of Understanding between his Department and HMRC, for what reasons automated residency checks will not check applicants' records on working tax credit and child tax credit.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261211","261211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130505","2019-06-10","Home Office","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 22 May 2019 to Question 254812 on Immigration: EU Nationals and with reference to page 14 of the Memorandum of Understanding on the EU Settlement Scheme between his Department and the Department for Work and Pensions, whether staff at the Department for Work and Pensions access to that data is restricted to the purposes of the EU Settlement Scheme.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261212","261212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130506","2019-06-10","Department for Transport","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment his Department has made of the potential economic benefits of commercial drone use.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261157","261157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130507","2019-06-10","Department for Transport","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans he has to undertake local noise surveys in communities that will be affected by the expansion of capacity at Heathrow.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261241","261241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130508","2019-06-10","Department for Transport","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he plans to conduct an optimism bias assessment on public sensitivity to aviation noise in communities that are likely to be affected by expansion at Heathrow.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261242","261242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130509","2019-06-10","Department for Transport","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans he has to survey local communities on the effect on quality of life of aircraft noise below 51 dB LAeq.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261243","261243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130510","2019-06-10","Department for Transport","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will update the Survey of Noise Attitudes 2017 report to incorporate the most recent WHO guidance on the lowest acceptable level of noise.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261244","261244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130511","2019-06-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his Chinese counterpart on the protection of civil society groups and human rights in that country.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261229","261229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130512","2019-06-10","Department for Transport","2019-06-06","suggested redraft: To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate his Department has made of the potential effect on the viability of rail freight of a 25 per cent reduction in (a) mode shift revenue support and (b) waterborne freight grant.","Biography information for Martin Vickers","Martin Vickers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261186","261186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1130513","2019-06-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the human rights situation in China in (a) 2019 comparative to (b) 1989.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261230","261230"
