"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947296","2018-09-04","Department for Education","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 29 January 2018 to Question 123752, whether he plans to carry out a further review of childcare costs in England.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167903","167903"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947297","2018-09-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the cost to the NHS in England of special medicinal products over the last 12 months.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167951","167951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947298","2018-09-04","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, if he will publish documentation for the computable general equilibrium model used by the Planning and Analysis Directorate.","Biography information for Mr Steve Baker","Mr Steve Baker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168188","168188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947299","2018-09-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to NICE's draft guideline entitled Abdominal aortic aneurysm: diagnosis and management, published in May 2018, if he will make an assessment of the effectiveness of the interventions for patients with complex abdominal aortic aneurysms there listed under the term Complex EVAR; and what comparative assessment he has made of the effect on patient outcomes of (a) customised fenestrated endografts and (b) physician-modified endografts for complex abdominal aortic aneurysms.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167952","167952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947300","2018-09-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make an assessment of the (a) prevalence of non-authorised, physician-modified products in the treatment of abdominal aortic aneurysms and (b) effect of those products on such aneurysms.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167953","167953"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947301","2018-09-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 9 July 2018 to Questions 159561 and 159563, what type of data has been included to inform the Abdominal aortic aneurysm: diagnosis and management draft guidance; and whether that data includes up-to-date registry data.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167954","167954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947302","2018-09-04","Home Office","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 23 July 2018 to Question 164381, what information his Department holds on the number of on-duty officers of UK Border Force and its predecessor body who were deployed at airports in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167955","167955"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947303","2018-09-04","Department for Transport","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions his Department has had with TfL on improving the availability of mobile phone coverage on TfL Rail services.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167904","167904"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947304","2018-09-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what information his Department holds on the proposed closure of Eggborough Power Station; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168084","168084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947305","2018-09-04","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department is taking to increase support for victims of crime in Nottinghamshire.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168085","168085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947306","2018-09-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps are being taken to support the coordination and joining-up of the health and care systems in the East Midlands; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168086","168086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947307","2018-09-05","Treasury","2018-07-24","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether his Department has made a recent assessment of the potential effect on encouraging people and businesses to be more environmentally-friendly and on energy security of establishing an exemption from any valuation uplift of business premises for business rates purposes when solar panels have been fitted.","Biography information for Craig Mackinlay","Craig Mackinlay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168087","168087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947308","2018-09-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much money each local authority received via clinical commissioning groups in 2017-18 to provide breaks for carers as a proportion of the £130 million of Government funding for carers' breaks included annually in the Better Care Fund.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168088","168088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947309","2018-09-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the criteria are for a social landlord to gain access to the universal credit landlord portal.","Biography information for Angela Crawley","Angela Crawley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168089","168089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947310","2018-09-05","Home Office","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether death penalty assurances have been waived in any cases prior to those of Alexanda Kotey and El Shafee Elsheikh.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167956","167956"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947311","2018-09-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps her Department is taking to simplify the universal credit application process.","Biography information for Angela Crawley","Angela Crawley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168090","168090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947312","2018-09-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether the Government plans to change from 2019 the level of the £130 million of funding for carers' breaks designated annually in the Better Care Fund; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168091","168091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947313","2018-09-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to encourage more fathers to take shared parental leave.","Biography information for Angela Crawley","Angela Crawley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168092","168092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947314","2018-09-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether future operating guidance on the Better Care Fund will include a clear reference to funding for breaks for carers; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168093","168093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947315","2018-09-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when and for what reasons her Department changed its procedures on dealing with members of the Scottish Parliament in respect of access to the Job Centre Complaints’ Resolution Team; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Angela Crawley","Angela Crawley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168094","168094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947316","2018-09-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans he has to incorporate incentives to improve the accessibility and upkeep of public rights of way in any future scheme of agricultural payments.","Biography information for Sandy Martin","Sandy Martin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168095","168095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947317","2018-09-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans he has to incorporate incentives to enhance and maintain higher animal welfare standards in any future scheme of agricultural payments.","Biography information for Sandy Martin","Sandy Martin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168096","168096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947318","2018-09-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans he has to incorporate incentives to enhance and maintain wildlife habitat in any future scheme of agricultural payments.","Biography information for Sandy Martin","Sandy Martin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168097","168097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947319","2018-09-04","Home Office","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people from the Windrush generation have been identified as living in (a) Scotland, (b) South Lanarkshire and (c) Lanark and Hamilton East constituency.","Biography information for Angela Crawley","Angela Crawley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168098","168098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947320","2018-09-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he has plans to incorporate incentives to enhance and maintain (a) heritage buildings, (b) monuments, (c) structures and (d) landscape features in any future scheme of agricultural payments.","Biography information for Sandy Martin","Sandy Martin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168099","168099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947321","2018-09-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure that the next Pharmaceutical Price Regulation Scheme sets an ambitious framework for delivering quick patient access to new and clinically-effective medicines.","Biography information for Liz Twist","Liz Twist","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168100","168100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947322","2018-09-04","Home Office","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps his Department is taking with other government departments to ensure that asylum seekers are able to present in their substantive asylum interview all information relevant to their claim and are able to access legal representation and advice.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167957","167957"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947323","2018-09-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking in the pharmaceutical price regulation scheme negotiations to ensure that modern cancer therapies are categorised as cost-effective.","Biography information for Liz Twist","Liz Twist","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168101","168101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947324","2018-09-04","Home Office","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps his Department is taking with the Ministry of Justice to ensure that legal aid availability meets the needs of asylum seekers.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167958","167958"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947325","2018-09-05","Department for Education","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment his Department has made of trends in the number of suspensions in primary and secondary schools in Coventry; and what discussions he has had with the Chancellor of the Exchequer on support for schools with high numbers of suspensions.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167855","167855"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947326","2018-09-05","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what criteria his Department used to decide which areas would be chosen to work with the Government to develop their local industrial strategies.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167959","167959"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947327","2018-09-04","Department for Transport","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what impact assessment his Department carried out on legislative changes to the operating weight of MCBP vehicles.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167960","167960"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947328","2018-09-04","Department for Transport","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what economic impact assessment his Department has carried out on changes to the regulation of MCBP vehicles.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167961","167961"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947329","2018-09-05","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, for what reason his Department did not choose to work with the Sheffield City Region on a local industrial strategy.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167962","167962"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947330","2018-09-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will place in the Library a list of all the (a) affirmative and (b) negative statutory instruments exercising powers under the European Union (Withdrawal) Act 2018 which he plans to lay before Parliament in (i) 2018-19 and (ii) 2019-20.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167963","167963"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947331","2018-09-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will place in the Library a copy of his Department's risk register listing the key risks identified in the event of the UK leaving the EU in 2019 without agreement.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167964","167964"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947332","2018-09-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the effect on the (a) viability of the food industry and (b) cost of food to consumers of the UK leaving the EU in 2019 without an agreement.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167965","167965"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947333","2018-09-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he has plans to maintain the responsibilities and functions in the UK of the (a) EU Environment Agency and (b) European Environment Information and Observation Network (i) after the UK leaves the EU and (ii) in the event of the UK leaving the EU in 2019 without an agreement.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167966","167966"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947334","2018-09-04","Department for Transport","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what impact assessment he made prior to concluding that 10 years is an adequate derogation period for MCBP operators to adjust to new regulations.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167967","167967"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947335","2018-09-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he has plans for Regulation (EC) No 401/2009 to form part of the common rule book envisaged in the White Paper entitled The Future Relationship Between the United Kingdom and the European Union, published in July 2018, Cm 9593.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167968","167968"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947336","2018-09-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he plans to maintain the responsibilities and functions in the UK of the Community Plant Variety Office (a) when the UK leaves the EU and (b) in the event of the UK leaving the EU in 2019 without agreement; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167969","167969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947337","2018-09-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he plans to maintain the responsibilities and functions in the UK of the European Food Safety Authority (a) when the UK leaves the EU and (b) in the event of the UK leaving the EU in 2019 without an agreement.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167970","167970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947338","2018-09-04","Department for Transport","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what impact assessment he made prior to concluding that seven months was an adequate timeframe for manufacturers to significantly redesign MCBP vehicles.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167971","167971"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947339","2018-09-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he plans to maintain the responsibilities and functions in the UK of the European Fisheries Control Agency (a) when the UK leaves the EU and (b) in the event of the UK leaving the EU in 2019 without an agreement.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167972","167972"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947340","2018-09-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he has plans for Regulation (EC) No 178/2002 to form part of the common rule book envisaged in the White Paper, The Future Relationship Between the United Kingdom and the European Union, published in July 2018, Cm 9593.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168102","168102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947341","2018-09-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he has plans for Regulation (EC) No 2100/94 to form part of the common rule book envisaged in the White Paper, The Future Relationship Between the United Kingdom and the European Union, published in July 2018, Cm 9593.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168103","168103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947342","2018-09-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he has plans for Regulation (EC) No 768/2005 to form part of the common rule book envisaged in the White Paper, The Future Relationship Between the United Kingdom and the European Union, published in July 2018, Cm 9593.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168104","168104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947343","2018-09-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he plans to provide continuity of public and animal health protection through the Rapid Alert System for Food and Feed (a) when the UK leaves the EU and (b) in the event of the UK leaving the EU in 2019 without agreement.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168105","168105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947344","2018-09-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether it is the Government's policy that future trade deals on food and feed will provide for public and animal health protection equivalent to the Rapid Alert System for Food and Feed after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168106","168106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947345","2018-09-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will include proposals to create national marine parks in his review of National Parks.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168107","168107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947346","2018-09-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions his Department has had with the Foreign Office on (a) the experience of creating marine protected areas around British Overseas Territories and (b) lessons that could be used in creating UK national marine parks.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168108","168108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947347","2018-09-04","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he plans to publish the basing decisions for the Type 26 frigate.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168109","168109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947348","2018-09-04","Department for Transport","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he plans to announce funding decisions for the second Road Investment Strategy funding period.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168110","168110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947349","2018-09-04","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of creating a register of male and female statues to chart progress towards greater female representation.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168111","168111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947350","2018-09-04","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, when he plans to publish proposals for 5G signal on the Great Western Mainline between Paddington and Penzance.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168112","168112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947351","2018-09-04","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Answer of 8 March 2005 to Question 217295 on Military Aircraft Crashes, whether military personnel and their families were made aware that crossing the English-Scottish border would in the event of death in Scotland result in the loss of the degree of legal protection afforded them by Coroners’ Inquests in the rest of the UK; and if will he now release an un-redacted copy of the Board of Inquiry report to the families.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168113","168113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947352","2018-09-04","Home Office","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many pregnant women have been deported after being detained in an immigration detention centre.","Biography information for Angela Crawley","Angela Crawley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168114","168114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947353","2018-09-04","Treasury","2018-07-24","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of changes in the rate of insurance premium tax on the cost of insurance premiums since 2011.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168115","168115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947354","2018-09-04","Treasury","2018-07-24","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many investigations HMRC has launched against firms using the Employment Allowance avoidance scheme referred to in the HMRC guidance of 29 June 2015.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168116","168116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947355","2018-09-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the judgment of Beatt v Croydon Health Services NHS Trust [2017] EWCA Civ 401, what steps are being taken to ensure that responses to disclosures by NHS whistleblowers are not influenced by the personal feelings of staff towards those people making such disclosures.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168117","168117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947356","2018-09-04","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether he plans to publish the Estates and Transformation Team report on the feasibility of the public sector bidding to run new-build prisons; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168118","168118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947357","2018-09-04","Department for Transport","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what (a) communications and (b) meetings Ministers and officials of his Department have had with (i) Halton Borough Council, (ii) Mersey Gateway since the ruling of the Traffic Penalty Tribunal on the legal enforceability of the Mersey Gateway Bridge tolls; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167905","167905"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947358","2018-09-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the effectiveness of congestion zone areas in reducing pollution to legally permissible limits.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168119","168119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947359","2018-09-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of climate change on the prevalence of wildfires in the UK.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168120","168120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947360","2018-09-05","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which foreign armed forces the UK armed forces has trained in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168121","168121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947361","2018-09-04","Women and Equalities","2018-07-24","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what steps she is taking to ensure that indicator 5.c.1 of the Sustainable Development Goals is assessed effectively across Government.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168122","168122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947362","2018-09-05","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether the Shared Prosperity Fund is planned to be allocated on the basis of the Barnett formula.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168123","168123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947363","2018-09-05","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of recent trends in the number of pubs closing on the night time economy.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168124","168124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947364","2018-09-05","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what step his Department is taking to encourage good practice in cyber security for businesses.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168125","168125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947365","2018-09-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether his Department has commissioned research on the costs to local authorities of administering (a) congestion charges and (b) ultra-low emission zone charges for (i) commercial and (ii) domestic vehicles.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168126","168126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947366","2018-09-04","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the statement in the letter of 13 March 2018 from the Parliamentary Under Secretary of State (Minister for Housing and Homelessness) to the hon. Member for Oxford East, whether the statement that the Government wants to support all landlords to offer longer tenancies where they are wanted means that it is the Government's policy that local authorities will be provided with the flexibility to retain secure tenancies as standard in local Tenancy Strategies under the responsibilities conveyed by the Housing and Planning Act 2016.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168127","168127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947367","2018-09-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the Adjournment debate of 17 July 2018 on Access to Orkambi, Official Report, columns 377-386, if he will take steps to keep hon. Members updated over the summer recess in the event that any progress is made between Vertex and NHS England on making the drug Orkambi available on the NHS for people with Cystic Fibrosis.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167906","167906"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947368","2018-09-04","Department for Transport","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will undertake research to identify the economic impact on the Liverpool City Region of tolls on the (a) Mersey Gateway Bridge, (b) Silver Jubilee Bridge, (c) Kingsway Tunnel and (d) Queensway Tunnel.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167907","167907"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947369","2018-09-05","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to help protect tenants from increasing property maintenance charges.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168128","168128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947370","2018-09-04","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent progress his Department has made on procuring (a) Type 31e frigates and (b) fleet support ships for the Royal Fleet Auxiliary; and if they will be built at UK shipyards.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167908","167908"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947371","2018-09-04","Department for Transport","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the trends in the (a) quantity and (b) frequency of bus services in (i) Jarrow Constituency (ii) South Tyneside and (iii) Tyne and Wear since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167909","167909"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947372","2018-09-04","Department for Transport","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much funding his Department has allocated to Nexus in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167910","167910"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947373","2018-09-04","Department for Transport","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much his department has spent on bus services in (a) Jarrow Constituency (b) South Tyneside and (c) Tyne and Wear in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167911","167911"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947374","2018-09-04","Department for Transport","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much funding his Department has allocated to Nexus for (a) commercial bus services and (b) supported bus services in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167912","167912"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947375","2018-09-04","Treasury","2018-07-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much revenue is projected to be raised in the 2018-19 financial year from the sugar tax.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168129","168129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947376","2018-09-04","Treasury","2018-07-24","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will publish what information his Department holds on overall public spending per capita in (a) Jarrow Constituency (b) South Tyneside and (c) Tyne and Wear and (d) the North East since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167913","167913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947377","2018-09-04","Department for Education","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to tackle any disparities in education and skill levels in North East England compared to other regions of the UK.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167914","167914"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947378","2018-09-04","Department for Transport","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the financial guarantee given to ensure the operators of the Mersey Gateway Bridge have no financial shortfall as a result of lower than expected traffic across that bridge has yet been called upon.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167915","167915"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947379","2018-09-05","Treasury","2018-07-24","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 23 July 2018 to Question 165182, by what means HMRC plans to distinguish between a good settled in its final destination in the UK and a good destined to travel on to the EU.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168130","168130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947380","2018-09-04","Department for Transport","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many penalty charge notices issued by Merseyflow to people for failure to pay the toll on the Mersey Gateway Bridge have been appealed to the Traffic Penalty Tribunal; and how many of those appeals were successful.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167916","167916"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947381","2018-09-05","Home Office","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when he plans to answer Questions 146839 and 163094, on criminal proceedings, tabled on 22 May and 11 July 2018 respectively by the hon. Member for Scunthorpe; and for what reasons he has so far not responded to those Questions.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167973","167973"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947382","2018-09-04","Treasury","2018-07-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the introduction of the sugar tax on reducing the sugar content of soft drinks.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168131","168131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947383","2018-09-04","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that the system for prisoner transfers between different categories of prison is effectively monitored.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168132","168132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947384","2018-09-04","Treasury","2018-07-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much revenue has been collected since the introduction of the soft drinks industry levy; and that money has been spent on.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168133","168133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947385","2018-09-04","Treasury","2018-07-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions his Department has had with the soft drink industry on reducing the levels of sugar in their drinks.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168134","168134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947386","2018-09-04","Department for Education","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what information his Department holds on how many applications to study academic A-Level courses have been received  by SK College Group's Knowsley campus for the 2018-19 academic year.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167917","167917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947387","2018-09-04","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what criteria his Department use to determine whether an international deployment of the Armed Forces is designated combat or non-combat.","Biography information for Crispin Blunt","Crispin Blunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167831","167831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947388","2018-09-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when the Public Health England review of minimum unit pricing for alcohol is planned to be published; and what assessment he has made of the effect on public health of the time taken to implement a minimum unit pricing alcohol policy in England.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167974","167974"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947389","2018-09-04","Department for Education","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what information his Department holds on how many academic A- Level courses set out in the curriculum offer of SK College Group's prospectus for September 2018 at it's Knowsley campus will be provided rather than simply offered.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167918","167918"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947390","2018-09-04","Treasury","2018-07-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether his Department has had any discussions on extending the soft drinks industry levy to other high sugar consuming food and drink.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168135","168135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947391","2018-09-04","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 23 July to Question 165122, if he will collect data centrally on how many male prisoners whose security category is D (eligible for open prisons) are awaiting transfer to an open prison in Category (a) B and (b) C Prisons in England and Wales.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168136","168136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947392","2018-09-04","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 23 July 2018 to Question 165122, if he will collect data centrally on how many female prisoners whose security category is D (eligible for open prisons) are awaiting transfer to an open prison in Category (a) B and (b) C Prisons in England and Wales.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168137","168137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947393","2018-09-04","Treasury","2018-07-24","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he has made an assessment of the extent to which the Check Employment Status for Tax tool aligns with (a) case law relating to the test of mutuality of obligation used to establish that an employment relationship exists and (b) other such case law; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168138","168138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947394","2018-09-04","Department for Transport","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what information his Department holds on the average cost of a train ticket purchased in the (a) South East, (b) South West, (c) North East, (d) North West, (e) West Midlands, (f) East Midlands, (g) East Anglia, (h) Yorkshire and the Humber and (i) Greater London; and if he will make a comparative assessment of the average costs of those train tickets for each of those regions in each of the last ten years.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168139","168139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947395","2018-09-04","Home Office","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when he plans to respond to Question 155249, on Immigration: Windrush Generation, tabled on 19 June 2018 by the hon. Member for Ealing, Southall.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167975","167975"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947396","2018-09-04","Treasury","2018-07-24","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 11 July 2018 to Question 160282, what specific methods of testing have been used to assess the accuracy of the Check Employment Status for Tax; and whether regression testing has been used on that system.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168140","168140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947397","2018-09-04","Department for Transport","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what information his Department holds on the average cost of a train ticket per mile of track covered for the journey covered by that ticket in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168141","168141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947398","2018-09-04","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what recent discussions his Department has had with the advertising industry on reducing the promotion of unhealthy food before the watershed.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168142","168142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947399","2018-09-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department plans to take to reduce the time taken for GP referrals of patients for cancer treatment.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168143","168143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947400","2018-09-04","Treasury","2018-07-24","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 11 July 2018 to Question 160282, whether he plans to publish the results of accuracy tests performed on the Check Employment Status for Tax tool.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168144","168144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947401","2018-09-05","Department for Transport","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 18 July 2018 to Question 165618, what his Department’s policy is on the construction of a new fixed link between Britain and France.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168145","168145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947402","2018-09-04","Home Office","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 13 July 2018 to Question 164380, what recent assessment he has made of how UK Border Force has performed against its target of processing non-EEA passengers at UK airports.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167976","167976"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947403","2018-09-04","Cabinet Office","2018-07-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the survival rates for people with breast cancer have been in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168146","168146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947404","2018-09-05","Department for Transport","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 16 July 2018 to Question 163101 on Rolling Stock, if he will list the specific economic benefits.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167977","167977"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947405","2018-09-05","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if his Department will make an assessment of the potential merits of establishing an independent statutory inquiry on the family courts’ handling of domestic abuse.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167978","167978"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947406","2018-09-05","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what the timetable is for the publication of his Department’s civil society strategy; and what the scope of that strategy will be.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167979","167979"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947407","2018-09-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps are being taken at international level to advocate for the protection of the Antarctic.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168147","168147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947408","2018-09-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his Department has received reports on the condition of Mr Hamed bin Haydara, a Baha’i prisoner in Sana’a, Yemen; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168148","168148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947409","2018-09-04","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the I CAN and Royal College of Speech and Language Therapists' report, Bercow: ten years on, published on 20 March 2018, what steps his Department is taking with the Department for Education and the Department of Health and Social Care to implement the recommendations in that report.","Biography information for Nick Smith","Nick Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167980","167980"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947410","2018-09-05","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether his Department has conducted an impact assessment of the potential effects on businesses in (a) the North East and (b) the UK of leaving the EU VAT area.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167981","167981"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947411","2018-09-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what information his Department holds on reports of the Government of Iran encouraging  the Houthi to persecute the Baha’i community in Sana’a, Yemen.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168149","168149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947412","2018-09-05","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Written Statement of 24 July 2018 on Ministry of Defence -Update, HCWS909, when the 0.9 per cent non-consolidated one-off payment will be implemented.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167982","167982"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947413","2018-09-05","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when his Department first received a copy of the Armed Forces Pay Review Body’s 2018 report.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167983","167983"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947414","2018-09-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to encourage the United Nations Security Council to refer the people responsible for the situation of the Rohinga in Myanmar to the International Criminal Court.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168150","168150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947415","2018-09-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Answer of 23 July to Question 165701 on universal credit, when he expects updated figures to be available.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168151","168151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947416","2018-09-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what diplomatic assistance the Government is providing to Japan as a result of recent floods in that country.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167919","167919"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947417","2018-09-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his international counterparts on consolidating the end of the state of war recently agreed by the Governments of Eritrea and Ethiopia.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167920","167920"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947418","2018-09-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations the Government has made to the Government of Nicaragua on respect for religious freedom in that country.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167921","167921"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947419","2018-09-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his Laos counterpart on potential legislative changes which threaten freedom of religion and belief in that country.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167922","167922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947420","2018-09-04","Northern Ireland Office","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, whether he has made an assessment of the implications for the (a) government of Northern Ireland and (b) role of the Northern Ireland civil service of the recent court ruling against the granting of planning permission for the Arc21 incinerator; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167923","167923"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947421","2018-09-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many out-of-area placements there have been for children and adolescents with psychosis in (a) England and (b) Birmingham in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167856","167856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947422","2018-09-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what proportion of people in (a) Birmingham and (b) England referred for early intervention in psychosis services received help within two weeks of being referred in the last twelve months.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167857","167857"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947423","2018-09-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what guidance her Department issues to businesses on their responsibilities as employers during periods of hot weather.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167858","167858"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947424","2018-09-04","Department for Education","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of funding levels for maintained nursery schools in (a) Birmingham, (b) the West Midlands and (c) England.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167859","167859"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947425","2018-09-04","Department for Education","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the role of maintained nursery schools in improving educational attainment among children from families living in poverty.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167860","167860"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947426","2018-09-04","Department for Education","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what representations he has received from local authorities on supplementary funding for maintained nursery schools beyond 2020.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167861","167861"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947427","2018-09-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the levels of care and support available for women with breast cancer in (a) the West Midlands and (b) England.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167862","167862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947428","2018-09-04","Department for Transport","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment he has made of the levels of uptake for Cycle to Work Scheme; and what steps he is taking to encourage uptake of that scheme.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167863","167863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947429","2018-09-04","Department for Transport","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many Bikeability training places his Department funded in schools in each of the last two academic years.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167864","167864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947430","2018-09-04","Department for Transport","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect of regulations governing working hours of professional drivers on (a) public safety and (b) the safety and wellbeing of drivers.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168152","168152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947431","2018-09-04","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of reducing the Small Business Multiplier to (a) help small traders and (b) support high streets.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168153","168153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947432","2018-09-04","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many meetings have taken place between officials of his Department and representatives of the European Round Table of Industrialists since July 2016.","Biography information for Mr David Jones","Mr David Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167924","167924"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947433","2018-09-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many locum doctors are subject to the 2019 Loan Charge.","Biography information for Drew Hendry","Drew Hendry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168154","168154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947434","2018-09-04","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many meetings with representatives of businesses headquartered (a) outside the UK and (b) within the UK have been arranged by his Department's Directorate of Communications and Stakeholders since July 2016.","Biography information for Mr David Jones","Mr David Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167925","167925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947435","2018-09-04","Women and Equalities","2018-07-24","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what the timetable is for the introduction of legislative proposals to ban gay conversion therapy.","Biography information for Dawn Butler","Dawn Butler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167926","167926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947436","2018-09-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if the Government will make it its policy to fund PrEP from central government funding for all at risk groups.","Biography information for Dawn Butler","Dawn Butler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167927","167927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947437","2018-09-04","Women and Equalities","2018-07-24","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what steps the Government is taking to tackle biphobia.","Biography information for Dawn Butler","Dawn Butler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167928","167928"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947438","2018-09-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what preparations his Department has made to ensure that the UK is able to use its border arrangements to protect plant and animal health in the event of no withdrawal agreement being reached pursuant to Article 50 of the Treaty on European Union.","Biography information for Mr David Jones","Mr David Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167929","167929"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947439","2018-09-04","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what meetings have taken place between officials of his Department and representatives of (a) CER, (b) the CBI, (c) the Institute of Directors, (d) Greenpeace, (e) Oxfam, (f) Friends of the Earth, (g) British Chambers of Commerce, (h) Society of Motor Manufacturers and Traders and (i) the EEF in the last twelve months.","Biography information for Charlie Elphicke","Charlie Elphicke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167984","167984"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947440","2018-09-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions he has had with mobile phone providers on enabling their customers to access the NHS Digital website without incurring a mobile data usage charge.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167985","167985"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947441","2018-09-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what discussions she has had with mobile phone providers on enabling their customers to make online claims for benefits and access online information without incurring a mobile data usage charge.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167986","167986"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947442","2018-09-04","Department for International Trade","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what meetings have taken place between officials of his Department and representatives of (a) CER, (b) the CBI, (c) the Institute of Directors, (d) Greenpeace, (e) Oxfam, (f) Friends of the Earth, (g) British Chambers of Commerce, (h) Society of Motor Manufacturers and Traders and (i) the EEF in the last twelve months.","Biography information for Charlie Elphicke","Charlie Elphicke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167987","167987"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947443","2018-09-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what meetings have taken place between officials of his Department and representatives of (a) CER, (b) the CBI, (c) the Institute of Directors, (d) Greenpeace, (e) Oxfam, (f) Friends of the Earth, (g) British Chambers of Commerce, (h) Society of Motor Manufacturers and Traders and (i) the EEF in the last twelve months.","Biography information for Charlie Elphicke","Charlie Elphicke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167988","167988"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947444","2018-09-04","Treasury","2018-07-24","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what meetings have taken place between officials of his Department and representatives of (a) CER, (b) the CBI, (c) the Institute of Directors, (d) Greenpeace, (e) Oxfam, (f) Friends of the Earth, (g) British Chambers of Commerce, (h) the Society of Motor Manufacturers and Traders and (i) the EEF in the last twelve months.","Biography information for Charlie Elphicke","Charlie Elphicke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167989","167989"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947445","2018-09-04","Cabinet Office","2018-07-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what meetings have taken place between officials of his Department and representatives of (a) CER, (b) the CBI, (c) the Institute of Directors, (d) Greenpeace, (e) Oxfam, (f) Friends of the Earth, (g) British Chambers of Commerce, (h) Society of Motor Manufacturers and Traders and (i) the EEF in the last twelve months.","Biography information for Charlie Elphicke","Charlie Elphicke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167990","167990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947446","2018-09-04","Department for Transport","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the Rail Minister is (a) consulted and (b) signs off on decisions on changes to the timetabling of Gatwick Express services run under the GTR Management Contract.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167991","167991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947447","2018-09-05","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to establish an alternative governance body than the Football Association to administer women's football in England.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167992","167992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947448","2018-09-05","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions he has had with the Football Association on promoting women's football in the North East.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167993","167993"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947449","2018-09-05","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how much funding from the public purse the Football Association has received in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167994","167994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947450","2018-09-05","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how much funding from the public purse the Football Association has received in each of the last five years to facilitate women's football.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167995","167995"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947451","2018-09-04","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, if he will take steps to increase the number of G4 football pitches in (a) Easington constituency and (b) the North East.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167996","167996"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947452","2018-09-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if his Department will take steps to support Portsmouth Hospitals NHS Trust's proposal for the redevelopment of the emergency department at Queen Alexandra Hospital.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168155","168155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947453","2018-09-05","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions his Department has had with UK Sport on the future sustainability of sports which do not currently receive any funding.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168156","168156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947454","2018-09-05","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department is taking to limit children’s exposure to gambling adverts during live sporting events.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168157","168157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947455","2018-09-04","Department for Education","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 11 June to Question 150142 on Selective Schools Expansion Fund, how many applications had been received for funding from the Selective Schools Expansion Fund by 19 July 2018; and from whom such applications were received.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167997","167997"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947456","2018-09-04","Department for Education","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether it is his policy that the Chartered College of Teaching should be led by practising teachers.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167998","167998"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947457","2018-09-04","Department for Education","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to his Department's press release entitled New Chair of the Social Mobility Commission recommended, published by his Department on 23 May 2018 on Social Mobility Commission: Public Appointments, what the timetable is for the appointment process for the remaining Social Mobility and Child Poverty Commissioners.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167999","167999"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947458","2018-09-04","Home Office","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when the Government plans to bring forward legislative proposals on immigration.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167930","167930"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947459","2018-09-04","Department for Education","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many nursing associates had begun apprenticeship courses by the end of (a) April 2018 and (b) June 2018.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168000","168000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947460","2018-09-04","Department for Education","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the oral contribution of the Minister for Universities, Science, Research and Innovation of 14 May 2018, Official Report, column 15, by what date he plans that evaluation into disabled students’ allowances to conclude.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168001","168001"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947461","2018-09-04","Department for Education","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to Spring Budget 2017, when he plans to set out plans for the £5 million fund for transport to selective schools for disadvantaged pupils.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168002","168002"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947462","2018-09-04","Department for Education","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which academy schools are awaiting rebrokering as of 24 July 2018.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168003","168003"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947463","2018-09-04","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what provisions he has made to ensure that in the event of no agreement being reached under Article 50 of the Treaty on European Union no data that originates outside the UK will be transmitted to the EU without a data adequacy arrangement.","Biography information for Mr David Jones","Mr David Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167931","167931"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947464","2018-09-05","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to page 29, paragraph 3.23, of the Armed Forces Pay Body Review Report 2018, for what reason the Review Body’s recommendation of an across-the-board increase of 2.9 per cent in base pay for 2018-19 was not accepted.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168004","168004"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947465","2018-09-04","Department for Education","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 2 May 2018 to Question 138485 on Education Fellowship Trust, how many of the Education Fellowship Trust schools are awaiting rebrokering.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168005","168005"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947466","2018-09-04","Department for Education","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 19 April 2018 to Question 135939 on Wakefield City Academies Trust, how much funding his Department provided to (a) former Wakefield City Academy Trust schools and (b) their new trusts by 1 April 2018.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168006","168006"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947467","2018-09-04","Department for Education","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what progress is being made on the School Exclusions Review.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168007","168007"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947468","2018-09-04","Cabinet Office","2018-07-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what discussions members of his Department's Europe Unit had prior to 12 July 2018 with representatives of EU member states and EU institutions on the White Paper on the future relationship between the UK and the EU.","Biography information for Mr David Jones","Mr David Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167932","167932"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947469","2018-09-04","Treasury","2018-07-24","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 3 April 2018 to Question 133821 on Children: Day Care, what advice his Department has provided to the Northern Ireland parties and the Northern Ireland Civil Service based on the experience of developing and administering the 30 hours free childcare policy in England.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168008","168008"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947470","2018-09-04","Cabinet Office","2018-07-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what discussions his Department's Europe Unit had prior to 12 July  2018 with ministers or officials of the devolved administrations on the contents of the White Paper on the future relationship between the UK and the EU.","Biography information for Mr David Jones","Mr David Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167933","167933"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947471","2018-09-04","Department for Transport","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether it is the Government's policy seek to maintain membership of the EU's Open Skies system.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167848","167848"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947473","2018-09-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, on what date was the former Foreign Secretary, the Member for Uxbridge and South Ruislip's recent visit to Afghanistan was first discussed.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168158","168158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947474","2018-09-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, on what date was the final schedule for former the Foreign Secretary's visit to Afghanistan was confirmed.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168159","168159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947475","2018-09-05","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what meetings Ministers or officials of his Department had with representatives of (a) Airbus and (b) BMW at which company announcements relating to the UK leaving the EU were discussed in May and June 2018.","Biography information for Mr David Jones","Mr David Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167934","167934"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947476","2018-09-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, from which airport the former Foreign Secretary departed from for his visit to Afghanistan on 25 June 2018.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168160","168160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947477","2018-09-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what screening procedures are in place to monitor the effect of industrial pig and poultry production on the trans-boundary environment and health of Northern Ireland and Ireland.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167935","167935"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947478","2018-09-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what communications there were between Ministers or officials of his Department and Katherine Bennett of Airbus in May and June 2018.","Biography information for Mr David Jones","Mr David Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167936","167936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947479","2018-09-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, prior to the former Foreign Secretary's visit to Afghanistan on 25 June 2018, when the last meeting was between Ministers of the Afghan and UK Governments.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168161","168161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947480","2018-09-05","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, when it is planned that ratification of the 2004 second amendment to the Espoo Convention on Transboundary Impact will take place in relation to Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167937","167937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947481","2018-09-05","Department for Transport","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he has made an assessment of the potential merits of introducing into the airline industry a delay-repay scheme similar to that in the rail industry; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168009","168009"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947482","2018-09-04","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether legislative changes (a) are necessary and (b) have been made to ensure compliance in Northern Ireland with obligations under the (i) Environmental Impact Assessment Directive and (ii) Espoo Convention on Transboundary Impact.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167938","167938"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947483","2018-09-04","Northern Ireland Office","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what plans the Government has for the construction of new infrastruture on the UK border in Northern Ireland in the event of no withdrawal agreement being concluded under Article 50 of the Treaty on European Union.","Biography information for Mr David Jones","Mr David Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167939","167939"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947484","2018-09-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, for how many hours the former Foreign Secretary was in Afghanistan on his visit of 25 June; and what proportion of that time was spent in meetings.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168162","168162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947486","2018-09-05","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, for what reasons the Type 31e frigate acquisition process has been halted; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167940","167940"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947487","2018-09-05","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what his plans are for the new Type 31e frigate procurement competition.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167941","167941"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947488","2018-09-05","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department's new procurement competition for the Type 31e frigate will maintain the policy of capping the price of each vessel at £250 million.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167942","167942"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947489","2018-09-04","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he has discussed the UK’s first strike policy with the Prime Minister since his appointment; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168163","168163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947490","2018-09-05","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what progress his Department is making on taking forward with the European Commission the concerns of entertainment venues and lighting designers about the effect of the proposed EU Lighting Regulation 2020 to replace EU1194/2012 on theatre and other entertainment lighting.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167943","167943"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947491","2018-09-04","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the implications for the UK’s first strike capability of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168164","168164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947492","2018-09-05","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the target in-service date for the first Type 31 frigates is; and what assessment he has made of the implications of operating Type 23 frigates beyond the dates on they were due to be replaced by Type 31 frigates.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167944","167944"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947493","2018-09-05","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether DE&S plans to issue a new pre-qualification questionnaire to industry for the Type 31e frigate competition.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167945","167945"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947494","2018-09-04","Department for Education","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of the staff employed in each group of his Department are apprentices.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168011","168011"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947495","2018-09-04","Treasury","2018-07-24","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the oral contribution of the Secretary of State for Education of 13 March 2018, Official Report, Column 802, what steps he has taken during the six month extension to the childcare voucher scheme to address the concerns raised in that debate.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168165","168165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947496","2018-09-04","Attorney General","2018-07-24","To ask the Attorney General, with reference to the injunction granted by the Family Division of 22 June 2001 in respect of Jon Venables and Robert Thompson, what applications to vary that decision have been made and on behalf of whom; how such applications were funded; and what grounds were given in support of each such application.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167865","167865"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947497","2018-09-04","Department for Education","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Government response to the consultation on Eligibility for free school meals, the early years pupil premium and the free early education entitlement for two-year-olds under Universal Credit, published in March 2018, what estimate he has made of additional costs to his Department per year as a result of the proposed Free School Meal eligibility criteria.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168166","168166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947498","2018-09-04","Department for Education","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Government response to the consultation on Eligibility for free school meals, the early years pupil premium and the free early education entitlement for two-year-olds under Universal Credit, published in March 2018, whether his Department will be be the only Department funding additional costs accumulated due to the proposed changes in free school meals eligibility criteria.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168167","168167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947499","2018-09-04","Attorney General","2018-07-24","To ask the Attorney General, with reference to the injunction granted by the Family Division of 22 June 2001 in respect of Jon Venables and Robert Thompson, how many allegations for breach of that injunction have been received by his Department; on what dates and on behalf of whom such allegations were received; how communication of such allegations was funded; and what grounds were given in support of each such allegation.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167866","167866"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947500","2018-09-04","Attorney General","2018-07-24","To ask the Attorney General, with reference to the injunction granted by the Family Division on 22 June 2001 in respect of Jon Venables and Robert Thompson, what costs were incurred by his and other government departments in respect of matters relating to that injunction, including any amounts paid by way of the fees of any counsel and other disbursements.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167867","167867"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947501","2018-09-04","Treasury","2018-07-24","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the oral contribution of the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions of 13 March 2018, Official Report, column 767, what steps he has taken to address the specific circumstances affecting public sector employees in relation to childcare vouchers are; and what discussions he has had with colleagues from Northern Ireland in relation to those steps.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168168","168168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947502","2018-09-04","Attorney General","2018-07-24","To ask the Attorney General, with reference to the injunction granted by the Family Division on 22 June 2001 in respect of Jon Venables and Robert Thompson, what data security policies and procedures apply to his and other government departments and all counsel instructed in connection with that injunction, including communicating information by email; and what role his Department's Data Protection Officer and the data protection officers of other government departments play in instructing counsel in regard to data protection.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167868","167868"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947503","2018-09-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what information his Department holds on trends in and the extent of radicalisation by Hamas of Palestinian civilians in Gaza.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168169","168169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947504","2018-09-04","Department for Education","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what Ministerial responsibility he has for the student loan book.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168012","168012"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947505","2018-09-04","Department for Education","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the additional ring-fenced RDEL his Department will require to fund the increased RAB charge resulting from the increase to post-2012 loan repayment thresholds in each of the next three financial years.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168013","168013"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947506","2018-09-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what information his Department holds on the number of Hamas-led rocket attacks against Israel there have been in each of the last twelve months.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168170","168170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947507","2018-09-04","Department for Education","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of providing for a route whereby schools in difficulty which have been converted to academy status can revert to local authority control; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168014","168014"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947508","2018-09-04","Department for Education","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many student residential buildings have been identified as having aluminium composite material cladding; and what steps he is taking to ensure that such buildings are safe.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168015","168015"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947509","2018-09-04","Department for Education","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 16 November 2017 to Question 111967 on Wakefield City Academies Trust, whether he plans to publish the  Education and Skills Funding Agency report into Wakefield City Academies Trust after all the schools are transferred to new trusts.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168016","168016"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947510","2018-09-04","Department for Education","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Written Statement of 24 July 2018 on Schools Update, HCWS911, whether he consulted with the Welsh Government on the pay rise for teachers announced in that Written Statement.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168171","168171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947511","2018-09-04","Treasury","2018-07-24","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the Written Statement of 24 July 2018 on Schools Update, HCWS911, whether the Welsh Government is planned to receive any additional funding for the pay rise for teachers announced in that Written Statement.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168172","168172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947512","2018-09-04","Department for Education","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether the Multi-Academy Trust Development and Improvement Fund is planned to continue into the 2019-20 financial year.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168017","168017"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947513","2018-09-05","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to the Answer of 30 October 2017 to Question 109351 on Olympic Games 2012, if he will provide an update on what proportion of the assets at the Olympic Park have been sold; what revenue those sales have yielded; and what further such sales of assets are planned.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168018","168018"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947514","2018-09-05","Treasury","2018-07-24","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether it is his policy to extend IR35 off-payroll tax rules to the private sector.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167869","167869"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947515","2018-09-05","Treasury","2018-07-24","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on private sector (a) employment and (b) workforce structures of extending IR35 off-payroll tax rules to the private sector.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167870","167870"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947516","2018-09-05","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to amend the definition of worker in employment law to clarify and strengthen the rights of off-payroll workers, dependent contractors and participants in the gig economy.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167871","167871"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947517","2018-09-05","Treasury","2018-07-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what work has been undertaken to understand the technology and processes required to remove the need for infrastructure related to checks and controls at the Irish border itself aside from that on the Facilitated Customs Arrangement referred to in the Government's White Paper on the future relationship between the EU and the UK.","Biography information for Mr Marcus Fysh","Mr Marcus Fysh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168173","168173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947518","2018-09-04","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the Advertising Standards Authority’s decision that Internet Service Providers can advertise using the term fibre even when their network relies on copper and aluminium wiring.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167872","167872"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947519","2018-09-04","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to the Government's UK Digital Strategy 2017, what progress he has made in ensuring that the advertising of full fibre broadband services is accurate and fair.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167873","167873"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947520","2018-09-04","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he is taking to help ensure that consumers are aware of the comparative benefits of full fibre broadband compared with connections which use copper or aluminium wiring.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167946","167946"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947521","2018-09-04","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what safeguards will be put in place on the proposed entry level exception sites to prevent homes being resold at market rates.","Biography information for John Grogan","John Grogan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167874","167874"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947522","2018-09-04","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment has he made of the effect of the proposed entry level exception sites on the provision of affordable rented homes in England.","Biography information for John Grogan","John Grogan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167875","167875"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947523","2018-09-04","Department for Transport","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent progress has been made on the feasibility study for the restorations of the Skipton-Colne Railway; and what the timetable is for his receiving the final report from that study.","Biography information for John Grogan","John Grogan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167876","167876"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947524","2018-09-04","Department for Education","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to encourage the establishment of Combined Cadet Force units in state schools in (a) Kent and (b) England.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168019","168019"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947525","2018-09-04","Department for Transport","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to improve the (a) number and (b) quality of rail services in the South East.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168020","168020"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947526","2018-09-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when he plans to publish his policy proposals for rooftop solar after the closure of the Feed-In Tariffs Scheme in 2019.","Biography information for Dr Rupa Huq","Dr Rupa Huq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168174","168174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947527","2018-09-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether the export tariff for solar PV for energy exported to the grid will be maintained at 5.24 per kilo watt hour after April 2019.","Biography information for Dr Rupa Huq","Dr Rupa Huq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168175","168175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947530","2018-09-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of the introduction of net metering for solar PV and the renewables industry to provide value for money to consumers.","Biography information for Dr Rupa Huq","Dr Rupa Huq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168176","168176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947533","2018-09-04","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department is taking to support sports facilities in (a) Medway and (b) Kent.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168021","168021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947536","2018-09-04","Northern Ireland Office","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what information her Department holds on whether the (a) Republic of Ireland and (b) the EU has plans for building new infrastructure on the UK border in Northern Ireland in the event of no agreement being reached under Article 50 of the Treaty on European Union; and whether the UK Government has any such plans.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168022","168022"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947539","2018-09-04","Department for Education","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent steps his Department has taken to increase the number of pupils studying STEM subjects.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168023","168023"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947542","2018-09-04","Department for Education","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment his Department has made of the number of pupils studying STEM subjects after the age of 16.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168024","168024"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947545","2018-09-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the White Paper, The future relationship between the United Kingdom and the European Union, publish in July 2018, Cm 9593, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect on innovation within UK agriculture of ongoing harmonisation under a common rulebook set out in that white paper.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168025","168025"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947548","2018-09-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps her Department is taking to help young disabled people into work in (a) Medway and (b) England.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168026","168026"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947549","2018-09-04","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department and HM Prison and Probation Service are taking to speed up security clearance for health and social care staff commencing employment in prisons.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168027","168027"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947550","2018-09-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent steps his Department has taken to increase the number of defibrillators available in public places.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168028","168028"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947552","2018-09-05","Cabinet Office","2018-07-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of the Government's hosting of national democracy week; how many events the Government held; and how many people attended each such event.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168177","168177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947556","2018-09-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the effect of the time taken to obtain security clearance for health and social care staff on the delivery of healthcare in prisons.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168029","168029"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947559","2018-09-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information his Department holds on the number of publically accessible defibrillators in Medway.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168030","168030"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947562","2018-09-04","Department for Education","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent steps his Department has taken to recruit and retain teachers and teaching staff in (a) Medway, (b) Kent and (c) England.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168031","168031"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947565","2018-09-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what information his Department holds on the proportion of waste from Medway which ended up in landfill in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168032","168032"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947568","2018-09-04","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average number of days taken was to gain security clearance for health and social care professionals seeking to commence employment in prisons in each of the last five financial years.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168033","168033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947571","2018-09-04","Home Office","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans his Department has to ensure that in the event of no agreement being reached under Article 50 of the treaty on the European Union there will be a UK immigration policy that does not give special preference to EU migrants.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168034","168034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947574","2018-09-04","Department for Transport","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the timetable is for introducing Delay Repay 15 on Greater Anglia services; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168035","168035"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947581","2018-09-05","Department for Education","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Written Statement of 24 July 2018 on Teachers Update, WS912, when he plans to publish the funding sources for the teachers pay grant for (a) 2018-19 and (b) 2019-20.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168036","168036"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947584","2018-09-05","Department for Education","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to his Written Statement of 24 July on Teachers Update, WS912, how will the savings from his Department’s budget to fund the teachers pay grant be made.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168037","168037"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947587","2018-09-05","Department for Transport","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will publish the report of the task and finish group on taxi and private hire vehicle licensing in September.","Biography information for Sir Graham Brady","Sir Graham Brady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167877","167877"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947590","2018-09-04","Home Office","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans his Department has to ensure that in the event of no agreement being reached under Article 50 of the Treaty on European Union there will be a UK immigration policy that does not give special preference to EU migrants.","Biography information for Sir Bernard Jenkin","Sir Bernard Jenkin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167821","167821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947593","2018-09-04","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Armed Forces Pay Body Review Report 2018, page 2, paragraph 1.11, how many personnel have been on short notice to move for each of the last five years.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168038","168038"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947597","2018-09-04","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Armed Forces Pay Body Review Report 2018, page 2, paragraph 1.11, what the average length of notice given was for personnel being called for operational tours by Service for each of the last five years.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168039","168039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947600","2018-09-04","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Armed Forces Pay Body Review Report 2018, page 3, paragraph 1.1, on how many occasions in the last 12 months personnel have held acting or temporary ranks for each Service and at what rank.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168040","168040"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947603","2018-09-04","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Armed Forces Pay Body Review Report 2018, page 8, paragraph 2.7, what the average length of deployment has been by Service in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168041","168041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947607","2018-09-04","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Armed Forces Pay Body Review Report 2018, page 9, paragraph 2.9, when his Department plans to bring forward further details on future staffing levels and targets.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168042","168042"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947610","2018-09-04","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Armed Forces Pay Body Review Report 2018, page 10, paragraph 2.16, what steps his Department is taking to improve morale in the armed forces.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168043","168043"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947613","2018-09-04","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Armed Forces Pay Body Review Report 2018, page 10, paragraph 2.16, on how many occasions Reserve deployments have been cancelled due to gapping in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168044","168044"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947616","2018-09-04","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Armed Forces Pay Body Review Report 2018, page 20, paragraph 2.59, what plans his Department has to extend military medical and dental care to reserve personnel on Full Time Reserve Service.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168045","168045"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947619","2018-09-04","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Armed Forces Pay Body Review Report 2018, page 29, paragraph 3.25, what steps his Department is taking to increase awareness and understanding of the Armed Forces Pension scheme among armed forces personnel.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168046","168046"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947622","2018-09-04","Cabinet Office","2018-07-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the White Paper, The future relationship between the United Kingdom and the European Union, published in July 2018, Cm 9593, how many staff members in the Europe Unit worked on that white paper.","Biography information for Sir Bernard Jenkin","Sir Bernard Jenkin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167822","167822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947625","2018-09-04","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Armed Forces Pay Body Review Report 2018, page 34, paragraph 3.45, what plans his Department has to re-examine the policy of Recruitment and Retention Payments being completely removed upon a member of Service personnel submitting their notice to terminate.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168047","168047"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947628","2018-09-04","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of giving up the UK's share of European Investment Bank assets in the event that the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168179","168179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947631","2018-09-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the White Paper entitled The future relationship between the United Kingdom and the European Union, publish in July 2018, Cm 9593, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect on innovation within UK agriculture of ongoing harmonisation under a common rulebook set out in that white paper.","Biography information for Sir Bernard Jenkin","Sir Bernard Jenkin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167823","167823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947634","2018-09-04","Home Office","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many reports to Action Fraud have been dismissed by a computer system before they are read by a member of staff in each of the last three years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168180","168180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947637","2018-09-04","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, if he will list all the external analysis that has been commissioned by his Department since its inception; and what amount of money was spent on each such piece.","Biography information for Sir Bernard Jenkin","Sir Bernard Jenkin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167824","167824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947640","2018-09-04","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, if he will list (a) all the economic qualifications held by staff in his Department's Planning and Analysis Directorate and (b) what level those qualifications are.","Biography information for Sir Bernard Jenkin","Sir Bernard Jenkin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167825","167825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947643","2018-09-04","Home Office","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many and what proportion of reports made to Action Fraud have been reviewed by (a) a computer system and (b) a member of staff in each of the last three years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168181","168181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947646","2018-09-04","Home Office","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps he is taking to support fraud victims whose cases do not meet Action Fraud's threshold for investigation.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168182","168182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947648","2018-09-04","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many staff work in his Department's Planning and Analysis Directorate.","Biography information for Sir Bernard Jenkin","Sir Bernard Jenkin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167826","167826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947649","2018-09-04","Home Office","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of the budget for (a) Action Fraud and (b) National Fraud Intelligence Bureau to tackle cyber crime.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168183","168183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947650","2018-09-05","Treasury","2018-07-24","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what information he holds on the current status of the EU's review of compensation due to Robert McCoy; what official UK involvement there has been in investigating the criminal allegations originally made by him; what legal support has been provided to him; if he will ensure that all outstanding anti-fraud cases relating to EU institutions and involving UK nationals as eye-witnesses are resolved as part of negotiations on the UK leaving the EU; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168048","168048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947651","2018-09-04","Cabinet Office","2018-07-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when officials in the Europe Unit first had discussions with officials of the Department for Exiting the European Union on the Government's Chequers plan for leaving the EU.","Biography information for Sir Bernard Jenkin","Sir Bernard Jenkin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167832","167832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947652","2018-09-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when he plans to bring forward a property sector deal.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168049","168049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947653","2018-09-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to support the commercialisation of social science research.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168050","168050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947654","2018-09-04","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what preparations he has made to support the resilience of UK companies' ability to send data across international borders in the event of no agreement being reached under Article 50 of the Treaty on European Union; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Bernard Jenkin","Sir Bernard Jenkin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167833","167833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947655","2018-09-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to promote productivity in the construction sector.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168051","168051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947656","2018-09-04","Department for Transport","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the recent statement of the Irish Prime Minister on the use of Irish airspace by UK airlines in the event of no deal being reached under Article 50 of the Treaty on European Union; what advice the Government is providing to UK airlines as a result of that statement; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Bernard Jenkin","Sir Bernard Jenkin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167834","167834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947657","2018-09-05","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many outstanding (a) official investigations and (b) legal cases there are led by the European Commission and involving UK nationals employed within EU institutions who have acted as whistle-blowers against alleged malpractice or fraud; what steps the Government is taking to pursue these investigations and cases notwithstanding the negotiations on the UK leaving the EU; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168052","168052"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947658","2018-09-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans she has to bring forward legislative proposals on workplace health and safety regulations to ensure that employers provide appropriate first aid training for their staff.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168053","168053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947659","2018-09-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the number of mental health staff that have been recruited to the NHS since June 2017.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168054","168054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947660","2018-09-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the number members of the public who have been trained in basic mental health awareness and first aid by the Government since June 2017.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168055","168055"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947661","2018-09-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what proportion of the proposed budget for child and adolescent mental health services transformation has been allocated to local clinical commissioning groups; and how much was allocated in each year since that budget was announced.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168056","168056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947662","2018-09-05","Department for Education","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether his Department has made contingency plans for the implementation of the first three T Levels in the event that the planned timetable is not met.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168057","168057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947663","2018-09-04","Department for Education","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, on what date the Mexborough Academy was re-brokered after sponsorship from Wakefield City Academies Trust ended.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168058","168058"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947664","2018-09-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to encourage uptake by GP surgeries of online access systems for patients.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168059","168059"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947665","2018-09-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent steps he has taken to lower the maternal mortality rate.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168060","168060"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947666","2018-09-04","Treasury","2018-07-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment he has made of the effect of the soft drinks industry levy on sugar consumption levels in the UK.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168061","168061"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947667","2018-09-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions he has had with appropriate officials in Northern Ireland on extending access to the HPV vaccination to that part of the UK.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168062","168062"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947668","2018-09-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will meet members of the All-Party Parliamentary Group on Childhood Cancer to discuss its recent report.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168063","168063"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947669","2018-09-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make it his policy to maintain the current cost-effectiveness threshold per quality-adjusted life year in the next Pharmaceutical Price Regulation Scheme.","Biography information for Darren Jones","Darren Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168184","168184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947670","2018-09-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make it his policy to establish a formal mechanism to (a) involve and (b) listen to patient groups during the next Pharmaceutical Price Regulation Scheme negotiations.","Biography information for Darren Jones","Darren Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168185","168185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947671","2018-09-05","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will ensure that any unresolved disputes around General Data Protection Regulation implementation will not prevent National Association of Child Contact Centres accredited support contact centres from receiving grants from the Children and Family Court Advisory and Support Service in 2019.","Biography information for Darren Jones","Darren Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168186","168186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947672","2018-09-04","Treasury","2018-07-24","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the most recent guidance on the use of PFI and PF2 issued by his Department is; and when that guidance was last updated.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167878","167878"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947673","2018-09-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the Lugansk People's Republic law #211-II on the freedom of conscience and religious association.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168064","168064"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947674","2018-09-04","Treasury","2018-07-24","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what representations his Department has made to the Office for National Statistics on their work on considering alternative treatments for student loans in the national accounts.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167879","167879"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947675","2018-09-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the international community is taking to ensure that the freedom of religion or belief is protected in the Lugansk region of eastern Ukraine.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168065","168065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947676","2018-09-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether his Department has any plans to privatise the British Business Bank.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167880","167880"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947677","2018-09-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has had discussions with his Pakistani counterpart on strengthening the legal procedures relating to religious blasphemy charges in that country to protect against frivolous accusations.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168066","168066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947678","2018-09-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the implications for his polices of the submissions on proposed procedural amendments to check the misuse of blasphemy law in Pakistan authored by the Pakistani National Commission for Human Rights.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168067","168067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947679","2018-09-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps are being taken to support the Nigerian Government in alleviating the conflict between Fulani herders and farming communities.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168068","168068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947680","2018-09-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what information he holds on the means by which Fulani herders in Nigeria come into possession of sophisticated weaponry.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168069","168069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947681","2018-09-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether British Embassy staff in Nepal receive training on local religions, patterns of discrimination and conflict between religious groups and the interaction of religion with society.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168070","168070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947682","2018-09-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has plans to support the creation of an international and independent review of the issue of organ harvesting in China.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168071","168071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947683","2018-09-04","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to Prison Service Instruction 44 of 2010, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of nutritional standards in prisons and correctional facilities.","Biography information for Nick Smith","Nick Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168072","168072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947684","2018-09-04","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to Rule 29 of the Prison Rules 1999, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of prisoners' (a) access to and (b) engagement in physical education.","Biography information for Nick Smith","Nick Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168073","168073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947685","2018-09-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment her Department has made of the merits of not requiring people with degenerative conditions who were in receipt of employment and support allowance before September 2017 to attend a further face-to-face work capability assessment.","Biography information for Gillian Keegan","Gillian Keegan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168187","168187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947686","2018-09-05","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what plans he has for the future relationship between the EU and the UK broadcasting industry.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167849","167849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947687","2018-09-05","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether he now plans to negotiate mutual recognition of broadcasting regulation standards with the European Union; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167850","167850"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947688","2018-09-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate she has made of how much lower spending from the public purse on universal credit would have been in 2018-19 in the event that the waiting time for payment of benefit had not been reduced from six weeks to five.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167881","167881"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947689","2018-09-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate her Department has made of what the spend from the public purse on Universal Credit benefit payments will be in 2018-19.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167882","167882"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/964005","2018-09-05","Cabinet Office","2018-07-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what discussions officials in his Department's Europe Unit had with representatives of EU member states and EU institutions prior to 12 July 2018 on the content of the White Paper on the future relationship between the UK and the EU.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 169344","169344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/964725","2018-09-05","Department for International Trade","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what recent assessment he has made of the size of the UK trade deficit in respect of (a) manufactured goods, (b) food and (c) energy; and what recent comparison he has made of each deficit with the size of such deficits and surpluses registered by other major economies.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 169065","169065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/964726","2018-09-05","Department for International Trade","2018-07-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps he is taking to change the balance of trade in manufactured goods.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 169066","169066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944696","2018-07-23","Home Office","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what funding his Department spends from the proceeds of crime to support people affected by drug related harm.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166219","166219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946740","2018-07-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he has taken to ensure support for ambulance trusts during winter 2018-19.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 906626","906626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946757","2018-09-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what amount of revenue funding allocated to the East Cheshire NHS Trust for 2017-2018 under the Cheshire and Merseyside sustainability and transformation partnership process has been paid.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167138","167138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946758","2018-09-04","Department for Education","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what information his Department holds on trends in the number of people being home-schooled in Stockton South constituency.","Biography information for Dr Paul Williams","Dr Paul Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167402","167402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946759","2018-09-04","Treasury","2018-07-23","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will revise upwards the level of compensation paid to people who experienced financial loses as a result of the mismanagement of Equitable Life.","Biography information for Jared O'Mara","Jared O'Mara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167397","167397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946760","2018-09-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the effect of care home providers exiting local authority contracts on the provision of those services in Coventry.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167115","167115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946761","2018-09-04","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what plans the Department has to ensure financial sustainability of Coventry City Council.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167116","167116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946762","2018-09-04","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of Government funding for local authorities including Coventry City Council.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167117","167117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946763","2018-09-04","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that new student accommodation buildings in Coventry are energy efficient.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167118","167118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946764","2018-09-04","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what estimate his Department has made of the number of (a) new towns, (b) garden cities and (c) garden villages that will have started construction  by the end of the 2017 Parliament.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167119","167119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946765","2018-09-04","Treasury","2018-07-23","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he is taking steps in relation to (a) the BBC and (b) the employees of the BBC who previously used (i) personal service companies and (ii) other remuneration schemes and as a result are now liable for increased tax bills; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167220","167220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946766","2018-09-04","Department for Transport","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate his Department has made of the average decline in battery efficiency in each year of a passenger vehicle's life.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167120","167120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946767","2018-09-04","Department for Education","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of levels of government funding for the 30-hours free childcare policy.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167228","167228"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946768","2018-09-04","Department for Education","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children are eligible for 30 hours free childcare in the Salford local authority area.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167229","167229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946769","2018-09-04","Department for Transport","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the cost to his Department has been of the compensation payments to customers made by Govia Thameslink Railway in relation to its rail franchises in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167104","167104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946770","2018-09-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he has made a recent assessment of the effect on the environment of reducing meat consumption nationally.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167387","167387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946771","2018-09-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of the provisions of the Abortion Act 1967.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167388","167388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946772","2018-09-04","Treasury","2018-07-23","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he has issued guidance to consumers without mobile phones on alternatives to the one-time password code banking system; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167389","167389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946773","2018-09-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he has made an assessment of the potential merits of the goals of the Real Bread Campaign; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167390","167390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946774","2018-09-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he plans to bring forward legislative proposals in relation to the appropriate labelling and marketing of bread products; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167391","167391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946775","2018-09-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what his policy is on Israel’s immigration policy which restricts the access of international passport holders to the Occupied Palestinian Territories.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167392","167392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946776","2018-09-04","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether he has any role in oversight or approval of the regeneration of Silvertown Quays; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167237","167237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946777","2018-09-04","Women and Equalities","2018-07-23","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to amend the Equalities Act 2010 so that the provisions of that Act on the public sector equality duty apply to Parliament and to hon. Members.","Biography information for Jared O'Mara","Jared O'Mara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167398","167398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946778","2018-09-04","Home Office","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to Answer of 16 July 2018 to Question 162516 on Gemalto, whether his Department has received reports of criminality from Gremalto in providing passports for those countries.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167221","167221"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946779","2018-09-04","Department for International Trade","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what the percentage increase in trade is for UK exports to the Association of South East Asian Nations since 2010; and what comparative assessment he has made of this figure and UK exports to other regions.","Biography information for Richard Graham","Richard Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167241","167241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946780","2018-09-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps are being taken to (a) make the HMRC Gateway service more accessible and (b) enable improved access to Government services for people with no online or digital access.","Biography information for Dr Paul Williams","Dr Paul Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167403","167403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946781","2018-09-04","Treasury","2018-07-23","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate his Department has made of the cost to the public purse on not collecting VAT at UK ports after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167298","167298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946782","2018-09-04","Treasury","2018-07-23","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much VAT was raised from goods coming through the Port of Dover in 2017.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167299","167299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946783","2018-09-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to page 82 of the Industrial Strategy, when he plans to agree long-term funding for the Catapult Network.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167295","167295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946784","2018-09-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to page 89 of the Industrial Strategy, whether his Department has launched the new international research and innovation strategy.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167296","167296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946785","2018-09-04","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to page 154 of the Industrial Strategy, when he plans to publish the review of the telecoms market.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167297","167297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946786","2018-09-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of the introduction on an independent fuel price monitoring body.","Biography information for Kirstene Hair","Kirstene Hair","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167410","167410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946787","2018-09-04","Department for Education","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Written Ministerial Statement of 19 July 2018 on on Relationships and Sex Education, HCWS 892 , what additional funding he plans to allocate to schools to support training and investment required to deliver (a) Relationships Education, (b) Relationships and Sex Education and (c) Health Education.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167367","167367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946788","2018-09-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the use of the amending procedure of the Rome Statute, Article 121(5), to withdraw from the jurisdiction of the International Criminal Court over the crime of aggression, is consistent with the UK's ratification of articles 12-15, which commits the UK to accepting the Court's jurisdiction over this crime.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167218","167218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946789","2018-09-04","Department for Education","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what progress his Department has made on meeting the target of three million apprenticeship starts by 2020.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167335","167335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946790","2018-09-04","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the timetable is for his Department to respond to the Tribunal Procedure Committee consultation on Tribunal Procedure (First-Tier Tribunal) (Health, Education and Social Care Chamber) Rules 2008, published on 22 March 2018.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167250","167250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946791","2018-09-04","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the timetable is for the opening of the five new residential women’s centres announced on 27 June 2018.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167251","167251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946792","2018-09-04","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what average number of cases each probation officer has worked on in (a) the National Probation Service and (b) private Community Rehabilitation Companies in each year since 2014.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167252","167252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946793","2018-09-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 18 June 2018 to Question 153210 on UNUM, which organisations are authorised to award local contracts under the low value procurement process.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167163","167163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946794","2018-09-04","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners supervised by private Community Rehabilitation Companies were classified as (a) high-risk, (b) medium-risk and (c) low-risk offenders in each year since 2014.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167253","167253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946795","2018-09-04","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners supervised by the National Probation Service were classified as (a) high-risk, (b) medium-risk and (c) low-risk offenders in each year since 2014.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167254","167254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946796","2018-09-04","Department for Transport","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the role of the high temperature incinerator at the Lakeside Energy from Waste facility in the disposal of waste from the Salisbury novichok incident demonstrates that that facility is of national strategic significance in the context of the Airports National Policy Statement; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167222","167222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946797","2018-09-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Adjournment debate of 17 July 2018 on Access to Orkambi, Official Report, cols 377-386, what steps he is taking to (a) facilitate and (b) participate as appropriate in a meeting between the chief executives of NHS England and of Vertex to discuss patient access to lumacaftor-ivacaftor and other medicines for cystic fibrosis.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167137","167137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946798","2018-09-04","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the Government's procurement of Type 26 Destroyers will include a requirement for manufacture (a) of components sourced from manufacturing facilities in Rugby and (b) in the UK.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167268","167268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946799","2018-09-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Defence on the future of GE engineering in Rugby.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167269","167269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946800","2018-09-04","Department for Transport","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he plans to announce his decision on the preferred corridor for the Oxford-Cambridge expressway.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167368","167368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946801","2018-09-04","Department for Transport","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 18 January 2018 to Question 903381 on Road Links: Kent and the South-east, when the hon. Member for Hereford and South Herefordshire plans to visit Botley.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167369","167369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946802","2018-09-04","Department for Transport","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with train operating companies on the compensation payable to people when trains are cancelled but do not cause a delay of over an hour.","Biography information for Tonia Antoniazzi","Tonia Antoniazzi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167358","167358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946803","2018-09-04","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Written Statement of 12 July 2018, on Justice update, HCWS853, whether the reinstatement of legal aid will apply to children located outside of the UK whose cases may fall under (a) the Dublin regulation and (b) section 67 of the Immigration Act 2016.","Biography information for Heidi Allen","Heidi Allen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167336","167336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946804","2018-09-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what types of Government support are being made available to food producers to help improve their productivity.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167111","167111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946805","2018-09-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to enable technological innovation and productivity to enhance British food production.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167112","167112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946806","2018-09-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he is taking steps to help the poultry meat sector scale up production to support increased self-sufficiency after the UK leaves the EU; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167113","167113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946807","2018-09-04","Home Office","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the recommendation of the Advisory Council on the Misuse of Drugs that medicinal cannabis products be moved out of Schedule 1 and into Schedule 2 of the Misuse of Drugs Regulations, how long it will take to reclassify the medicinal cannabis oil used by Alfie Dingley and Billy Caldwell; and whether he plans to ensure that all patients who might benefit from such treatment will be able to access medicinal cannabis by the time the House returns from its summer recess.","Biography information for Tonia Antoniazzi","Tonia Antoniazzi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167359","167359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946808","2018-09-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the EU suspension of invitations to senior military officers from Burma to visit the EU remains in place.","Biography information for Bambos Charalambous","Bambos Charalambous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167354","167354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946809","2018-09-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the UK Permanent Representative to the United Nations Security Council raised the detention of political prisoners with Aung San Suu Kyi when they met during the visit of the Security Council delegation to Burma.","Biography information for Bambos Charalambous","Bambos Charalambous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167355","167355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946810","2018-09-04","Home Office","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what progress has been made on his review of his Department's policies on (a) immigration and (b) refugee family reunion.","Biography information for Bambos Charalambous","Bambos Charalambous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167356","167356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946811","2018-09-04","Treasury","2018-07-23","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment he has made of trends in the level of public sector pay in the last five years.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167219","167219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946812","2018-09-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether Government procurement policies permit for non-stun meat to be procured by government departments for consumption on government premises.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167361","167361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946813","2018-09-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether the UK imports any non-stun (a) meat and (b) meat products.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167362","167362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946814","2018-09-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether the Government will be permitting the export of non-stun meat as part of its recently announced trade deal with Saudi Arabia.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167363","167363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946815","2018-09-04","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, when he plans to publish the  Withdrawal and Implementation Bill White Paper.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167161","167161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946816","2018-09-04","Department for Education","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department has taken to support small providers of apprenticeship training.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167223","167223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946817","2018-09-04","Department for Education","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department has taken to encourage new entrants into the apprenticeship training market.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167224","167224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946818","2018-09-04","Department for Education","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of contracts awarded through the apprenticeship levy were valued at less than £500,000.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167225","167225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946819","2018-09-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the guidelines issued by the National Institute for Clinical Excellence’s on the treatment of depression.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167226","167226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946820","2018-09-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of recent trends in the number of dedicated mental health specialists.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167227","167227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946821","2018-09-04","Department for Education","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many teaching assistants were employed in primary schools in each parliamentary constituency in Cumbria in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167234","167234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946822","2018-09-04","Department for Education","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many teachers were employed in primary schools in each parliamentary constituency in Cumbria in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167235","167235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946823","2018-09-04","Treasury","2018-07-23","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he has made an assessment of the potential contribution of the London Stock Exchange to the UK economy after the UK leaves the EU; and if he will make statement.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167164","167164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946824","2018-09-04","Treasury","2018-07-23","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions has he had with the London Stock Exchange on the qualification criteria for the FTSE 100 (a) before and (b) after Unilever's announcement that it would seek to unify its headquarters outside of the UK.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167165","167165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946825","2018-09-04","Treasury","2018-07-23","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what representations he has received from representatives of the investment management industry in London on (a) Unilever unifying its dual headed corporate structure to the Netherlands and (b) the effect of that unification on the company remaining a constituent of the FTSE 100 index.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167166","167166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946826","2018-09-04","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Autumn Statement 2016, what progress his Department has made on implementing a ban on tenants' fees.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167332","167332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946827","2018-09-04","Treasury","2018-07-23","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he has had discussions with representatives of the financial services industry on the potential (a) unification by Unilever of its dual-headed corporate structure to the Netherlands and (b) implications of that unification for Unilever's remaining a constituent of the FTSE 100 index; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167167","167167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946828","2018-09-04","Treasury","2018-07-23","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he has had discussions with the Financial Conduct Authority on the potential (a) unification by Unilever of its dual-headed corporate structure to the Netherlands and (b) implications of that unification for Unilever's remaining a constituent of the FTSE 100 index; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167168","167168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946829","2018-09-04","Treasury","2018-07-23","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he has had discussions with Unilever on its proposal to unify its dual-headed corporate structure to the Netherlands; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167169","167169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946830","2018-09-04","Treasury","2018-07-23","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he has made representations to the London Stock Exchange on (a) the proposed unification by Unilever of its dual-headed corporate structure to the Netherlands and (b) Unilever's potentially no longer being a constituent of the FTSE 100; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167170","167170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946832","2018-09-04","Treasury","2018-07-23","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he has made an assessment of the level of discretion that the London Stock Exchange subsidiary FTSE-Russell will have over a decision on whether to continue to include Unilever in the FTSE 100 index; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167171","167171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946833","2018-09-04","Treasury","2018-07-23","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he has discussed with the London Stock Exchange the amount of discretion that its subsidiary FTSE-Russell has over decisions on constituents of the FTSE 100; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167172","167172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946834","2018-09-04","Treasury","2018-07-23","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he is aware of the role of the policy advisory board of the London Stock Exchange subsidiary FTSE-Russell in advising which companies are assigned UK nationality and therefore qualify for inclusion in the FTSE 100; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167173","167173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946835","2018-09-04","Treasury","2018-07-23","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he has asked the London Stock Exchange for the names of the members of the policy advisory board of FTSE-Russell.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167174","167174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946836","2018-09-04","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what is the last date on which a decision can be made that no deal has been struck with the EU before the UK leaves the EU on 29 March 2019.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167183","167183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946837","2018-09-04","Treasury","2018-07-23","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he has discussed with the London Stock Exchange the potential implications for the reputation of the UK investment management industry of Unilever unifying its headquarters in the Netherlands and no longer being a constituent of the FTSE 100 index.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167175","167175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946838","2018-09-04","Treasury","2018-07-23","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the London Stock Exchange divulged to him details of its discussions with Unilever on (a) the potential effect on its ability to remain a constituent of the FTSE 100 index and (b) other potential effects of its proposal to unify its dual-headed corporate structure; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167176","167176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946839","2018-09-04","Treasury","2018-07-23","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he plans to write to the London Stock Exchange on the level of flexibility of its FTSE-Russell subsidiary in relation to granting FTSE 100 index membership to Unilever; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167177","167177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946840","2018-09-04","Treasury","2018-07-23","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the London Stock Exchange has informed him of the steps it will take in relation to Unilever (a) remaining and (b) leaving as a constituent member of the FTSE 100 index; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167178","167178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946841","2018-09-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the Department of Health and Social Care Annual Report and Accounts 2017-18, if he will place in the Library the total value of healthcare purchased from Community Interest Companies in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167285","167285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946842","2018-09-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will list the tender board members involved in NHS England's national tender for (a) factor VIII and (b) factor IX haemophilia products; whether any of those board members represent (i) the Northern Ireland Executive and (ii) organisations involved in Northern Ireland; and whether that tender board has ever met in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167275","167275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946843","2018-09-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the Department of Health and Social Care Annual Report and Accounts 2017-18, if he will place in the Library the names of the five Community Interest Companies who received the the largest sums of money from NHS organisations in 2017-18.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167286","167286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946844","2018-09-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 26 June 2018 to Question 154637 on Haemophilia: Medical Treatments, what the value is of savings which have been made since 2004-05 for (a) factor VIII and (b) factor IX products; how those savings have been reinvested in haemophilia services; and whether those savings have accrued to the (i) the UK Government and (ii) the Northern Ireland Government.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167276","167276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946845","2018-09-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people who were previously regularly receiving (a) factor VIII and (b) factor IX extended half life (EHLs) products at any point in 2017-18 have since been taken off them; and if he will take steps to ensure that patients are taken off EHLs only when it is clinically necessary.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167277","167277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946846","2018-09-04","Treasury","2018-07-23","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the White Paper, The Future Relationship Between the United Kingdom and the European Union, published in July 2018, what assessment he has made of the effect of the policies set out in that White Paper on transactions in euro-denominated assets for the UK financial sector.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167337","167337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946847","2018-09-04","Treasury","2018-07-23","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the White Paper, The Future Relationship Between the United Kingdom and the European Union, published in July 2018, what assessment he has made of the effect of policies set out in that White Paper on derivatives clearing for the UK financial sector.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167338","167338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946848","2018-09-04","Treasury","2018-07-23","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what advice his Department has issued to the financial sector on contract continuity (a) during the implementation period and (b) after 31 December 2020.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167339","167339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946849","2018-09-04","Treasury","2018-07-23","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what progress he has made on replicating the insurance agreements that the EU has with third countries that enable reciprocal arrangements for insurers to open agencies and branches in third countries after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167340","167340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946850","2018-09-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to ensure compatibility of smart meters with different energy suppliers to encourage customers to switch to cheaper tariffs.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167288","167288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946851","2018-09-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether his Department has (a) lost or (b) destroyed (i) files and (ii) information it held on the AEA Technology Pension Scheme.","Biography information for Mohammad Yasin","Mohammad Yasin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167343","167343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946852","2018-09-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the performance of the Members Correspondence Unit in his Department.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167121","167121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946853","2018-09-04","Treasury","2018-07-23","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many contractors employed in (a) the Government Actuary's Department, (b) HM Revenue and Customs,(c) HM Treasury Group, (d) National Savings & Investments, (e) Office for National Statistics, (f) Royal Mint, and (g) Valuation Office Agency are paid £1,000 or more per day.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167300","167300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946854","2018-09-04","Treasury","2018-07-23","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many contractors employed in(a) the Government Actuary's Department, (b) HM Revenue and Customs, (c) HM Treasury Group, (d) National Savings & Investments, (e) Office for National Statistics, (f) Royal Mint and (g) Valuation Office Agency are paid £650 or more per day.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167301","167301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946855","2018-09-04","Treasury","2018-07-23","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many staff are employed by HMRC in each region; and how many staff will be employed in each HMRC regional hub when those hubs become fully operational.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167302","167302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946856","2018-09-04","Treasury","2018-07-23","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the Valuation Office Agency (VOA) Annual Report and Accounts 2017-18, HC 1282, what assessment he has made of the effect of the implementation of VOA's Target Organisational Model on delays in Billing Authorities receiving the New Homes Bonus.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167303","167303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946857","2018-09-04","Department for Transport","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to ensure the realisation of the economic potential of drones for the UK economy in the forthcoming draft Drones Bill.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167242","167242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946858","2018-09-04","Treasury","2018-07-23","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to page 22 of the Valuation Office Agency (VOA) Business Plan 2017-19, what estimate he has made of the  reduction in the number of full-time equivalent staff employed by the VOA over the spending review period.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167304","167304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946859","2018-09-04","Department for Transport","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he plans to publish the draft Drones Bill.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167243","167243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946860","2018-09-04","Department for Transport","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussion he has had with representatives of industry on the development of (a) changes to the Air Navigation Order 2016 and (b) proposals for the draft Drones Bill in regulating the use of drones over the last two years.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167244","167244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946861","2018-09-04","Treasury","2018-07-23","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to page 46 of the HMRC Annual Report and Accounts 2017-18, what recent assessment he has made of the effectiveness of Operation Swiftarrow; when that operation is planned to conclude; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167305","167305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946862","2018-09-04","Department for Transport","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the draft Drones Bill will include proposals for the creation of (a) U-space and (b) unmanned traffic management.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167245","167245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946863","2018-09-04","Department for Transport","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps the Government are taking to ensure that UK regulations will be sufficiently aligned to EU rules to support (a) the export of drones to Europe and (b) the operation of drones with UK approval in Europe after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167246","167246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946864","2018-09-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether his Department holds pre-privatisation information on the AEA Technology pension scheme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mohammad Yasin","Mohammad Yasin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167344","167344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946865","2018-09-04","Department for Transport","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of the resources available to (a) police forces and (b) the Civil Aviation Authority to enforce the recent changes to the Air Navigation Order 2016.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167247","167247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946866","2018-09-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 26 June 2018 to Question 154639 on Haemophilia: Medical Treatments, if he will take steps to carry out such a comparative assessment of the uptake of  treatment in (a) Ireland, (b) Canada and (c) the EU.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167278","167278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946867","2018-09-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to Trigger 1 of Specialised Commissioning Drugs Briefing: Spring 2018, published by NHS England, what assessment he has made of the effect of the faster adoption of best value medicines requirement on the procurement of Extended Half Life factor VIII products; and what factor VIII blood products will be covered by that CQUIN.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167279","167279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946868","2018-09-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans he has for how the (a) Pet Travel Scheme and (b) Balai Directive will operate between Great Britain and the Republic of Ireland after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167280","167280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946869","2018-09-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the average number of (a) available and (b) occupied consultant-led mental health beds in Yorkshire and the Humber in each year since 2009.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167393","167393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946870","2018-09-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the number of out-of-area placements made for inpatients in each year since 2009.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167394","167394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946871","2018-09-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the number of detentions under the Mental Health Act 2007 in (a) Yorkshire and the Humber and (b) England in each year since 2009.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167395","167395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946872","2018-09-04","Home Office","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether he has plans to provide additional resources to support border operations at UK airports during the summer period.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167248","167248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946873","2018-09-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with representatives of the Organisation for the Prohibition of Chemical Weaopns on the interim report of the Fact-Finding Mission on Chemical Weapons Use Allegations in Douma, Syria in 2018.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167370","167370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946874","2018-09-04","Home Office","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate the Government has made of the effect of delays at border controls on the UK economy.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167249","167249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946875","2018-09-04","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 30 October 2017 to Question 901471 on Assessment of Housing Need, if the hon. Member for North West Hampshire will meet with the hon. Member for Oxford West and Abingdon to discuss planning in Oxfordshire.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167371","167371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946876","2018-09-04","Home Office","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what extra support he is providing to the Liverpool City Council for the Syrian Resettlement Programme.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167139","167139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946877","2018-09-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many times a monitor from Natural England is required to visit a proposed badger culling site to assess whether the weather conditions are suitable for a cull.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167114","167114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946878","2018-09-04","Home Office","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many Syrian refugees have been resettled in the Liverpool City Region since 2016.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167140","167140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946879","2018-09-04","Home Office","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many family links applications to the UNHCR have been successful in reuniting relatives of Syrian families settled in the Liverpool City Council area.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167141","167141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946880","2018-09-04","Department for International Development","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much funding her Department has allocated to the UNHCR to support the processing of family links applications for each year since 2010.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167142","167142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946881","2018-09-04","Department for International Development","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will increase funding from her Department to the UNHCR to support the processing of family links applications in the Liverpool City Council area in each year for which information is available.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167143","167143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946882","2018-09-04","Home Office","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much funding has been allocated from his Department to the UNHCR to support the processing of family links applications for each year since 2010.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167144","167144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946883","2018-09-04","Home Office","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will take steps to increase the funding from his Department to the UNHCR to support the processing of family links applications in the Liverpool City Council area.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167145","167145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946884","2018-09-04","Department for Transport","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the trends in the (a) quantity and (b) frequency of bus services in Garston and Halewood constituency since 2010.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167146","167146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946885","2018-09-04","Department for Transport","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much funding his Department has allocated to Merseytravel for supported bus services in each year since 2010; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167147","167147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946886","2018-09-04","Department for Transport","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many supported bus services currently run in the Garston and Halewood constituency; and how that figure has changed in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167148","167148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946887","2018-09-04","Department for Transport","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will take steps to ensure the continued provision of existing supported bus services in the Garston and Halewood constituency.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167149","167149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946888","2018-09-04","Department for Transport","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the trends in the frequency of (a) commercial bus services and (b) supported bus services in Garston and Halewood constituency since 2010.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167150","167150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946889","2018-09-04","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to reduce the amount of time that families of child claimants of disability living allowance have to wait between appealing a decision and their tribunal hearing date.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167151","167151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946890","2018-09-04","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average time is that families of child claimants of disability living allowance in Garston and Halewood constituency have to wait for a tribunal hearing when appealing the outcome of a mandatory reconsideration.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167152","167152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946891","2018-09-04","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much funding his Department planned to allocate to the Community Prisons for Women; how much savings have been accrued as a result of the cancellation of those prisons; to which programmes those savings have been allocated; and how much of those savings have been allocated to the rehabilitation and support of female offenders.","Biography information for Michael Tomlinson","Michael Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167334","167334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946892","2018-09-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average number of days is that claimants for universal credit in Garston and Halewood constituency have been sanctioned in the last twelve months for missing appointments.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167153","167153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946893","2018-09-04","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many claimants of personal independence payment have (a) applied to a tribunal to appeal the decision in their case, (b) had their appeal heard at tribunal and (c) been successful on appeal at the Tribunal in Garston and Halewood constituency in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167154","167154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946894","2018-09-04","Department for Education","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, for what reasons the Regional School Commissioner for North West London and the South Central Region has not issued any warning notices to any schools about poor performance since the end of 2016.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167372","167372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946895","2018-09-04","Department for Education","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what information his Department holds on the number of schools letting out premises in order to raise money to supplement their budgets; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167373","167373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946896","2018-09-04","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, which statutes govern the use by hon. Members of the personal data of their constituents.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167239","167239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946897","2018-09-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the timetable is for issuing the guidance on influenza vaccines for front line staff.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167287","167287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946898","2018-09-04","Department for International Trade","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what international trade missions his Department has scheduled for the next 12 months.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167156","167156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946899","2018-09-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many prosecutions or other proceedings on illegally imported puppies taken in by Dogs Trust under its puppy pilot quarantine scheme have begun since 2017.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167312","167312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946900","2018-09-04","Department for International Trade","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many overseas trade missions planned for the next 12 months will include agri-food firms from Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167157","167157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946901","2018-09-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the implications for (a) consumers and (b) producers of the frozen vegetable food scare.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167158","167158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946902","2018-09-04","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what steps he has taken in negotiations on the UK leaving the EU to promote mutual access to medicines and drugs.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167159","167159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946903","2018-09-04","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what schemes his Department has allocated funding to for the purchase or hire of (a) uniforms and (b) instruments by (i) musical and (ii) marching bands in the last five years.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167160","167160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946904","2018-09-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what progress his Department has made on the implementation of the Cancer Strategy in relation to breast cancer.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167281","167281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946905","2018-09-04","Home Office","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether specialist tools for the purpose of DIY are exempted from Article 17 of the Offensive Weapons Bill in relation to online purchase.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167282","167282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946906","2018-09-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, for what reason self-employed individuals are not eligible for injuries disablement benefit.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167283","167283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946907","2018-09-04","Treasury","2018-07-23","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much tax revenue accrued to the public purse from small and medium-sized enterprises in (a) 2013-14, (b) 2014-15, (c) 2015-16, (d) 2016-17 and (e) 2017-18.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167284","167284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946908","2018-09-04","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the effect of changes in the level of business rates on the number retail businesses closing.","Biography information for Ged Killen","Ged Killen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167405","167405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946909","2018-09-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his Colombian counterpart on the killing of nine Colombian human rights defenders in the first week of June 2018.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167184","167184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946910","2018-09-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will take steps to encourage the Government in Colombia to invite the UN Special Rapporteur on Human Rights Defenders to visit that country.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167185","167185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946911","2018-09-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the Government of Colombia on the escalation of the humanitarian crisis in Chocó.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167186","167186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946912","2018-09-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what diplomatic (a) assistance and (b) support the Government has provided to the Government of Colombia to (a) tackle sexual violence being used by armed actors against the population in Chocó and (b) comply with the safeguards and commitments set out in the Ethnic Chapter in the Peace Accord.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167187","167187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946913","2018-09-04","Department for Transport","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much funding from the public purse has been allocated to Nottinghamshire for the (a) repair of and (b) prevention of potholes.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167400","167400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946914","2018-09-04","Department for Education","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of early intervention programmes in reducing levels of pupil exclusions.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167401","167401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946915","2018-09-04","Home Office","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when he plans to respond to the letter from the hon. Member for Glasgow North, of 9 May 2018, reference PG6427, on behalf of a constituent seeking family reunion advice and support.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167308","167308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946916","2018-09-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what diplomatic support the UK Government has provided to the (a) Sisma Mujer and (b) Somos Defensores organisations in Colombia; and what recent discussions his Department has had with representatives of those organisations on the (i) military and (ii) security threats made against those organisations.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167309","167309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946917","2018-09-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions (a) he and (b) officials of his Department have had with counterparts at the 38th session of the UN Human Rights Council on the situation of internally displaced people in Colombia.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167310","167310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946918","2018-09-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what support the Government provides for projects and programmes in the Orinoquia region of Colombia.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167311","167311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946919","2018-09-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 4 June 2018 to Question 146980 on State Retirement Pensions: Females, what the average length of time taken was for a complaint in relation to the equalisation of the state pension age to be (a) received and referred to be Independent Case Examiners Office, (b) allocated to a case manager and (c) investigated by the case manager and a response issued to the complainant.","Biography information for Ged Killen","Ged Killen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167406","167406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946920","2018-09-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent estimate has she made of the number of women who have seen an increase in the age threshold at which they can claim their state pension as a result of the Government's reforms to the equalisation of the state pension age.","Biography information for Ged Killen","Ged Killen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167407","167407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946921","2018-09-04","Treasury","2018-07-23","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he plans to bring forward legislative proposals to include (a) claims management companies and (b) law firms undertaking claims activities in the remit of the Financial Conduct Authority's jurisdiction and supervision under the supervision of the Solicitors Regulatory Authority.","Biography information for Lee Rowley","Lee Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167364","167364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946922","2018-09-04","Treasury","2018-07-23","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether (a) his Department or (b) the Financial Conduct Authority has made an assessment of trends in the level of costs for financial services as a result of (i) spurious and (ii) fraudulent claims by claims management companies.","Biography information for Lee Rowley","Lee Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167365","167365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946923","2018-09-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether arrangements have been made for the right hon. Member for Uxbridge to pay rent on grace and favour apartments after 9 July 2018; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167213","167213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946924","2018-09-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will develop a national obesity strategy for adults and children.","Biography information for Eleanor Smith","Eleanor Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167352","167352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946925","2018-09-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make it his policy to mandate that obesity and weight management training is included in the curriculum for the education of every healthcare professional.","Biography information for Eleanor Smith","Eleanor Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167353","167353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946926","2018-09-04","Treasury","2018-07-23","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent estimate he has made of the (a) average level and (b) total value of personal debt in the UK.","Biography information for Ged Killen","Ged Killen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167408","167408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946927","2018-09-04","Home Office","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether his Department has undertaken a recent review of international best practice in relation to the criminalisation of prostitution; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ged Killen","Ged Killen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167409","167409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946928","2018-09-04","Home Office","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 26 March 2018 to Question 133797 on Asylum: Housing, what criteria (a) his Department and (b) accommodation providers use to assess the particular circumstances and vulnerability of those in dispersed asylum accommodation.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167270","167270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946929","2018-09-04","Home Office","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 26 March 2018 to Question 133797 on Asylum: Housing, what information his Department holds on the number of incidences of forced room sharing of asylum seekers in dispersed accommodation in each (a) local authority and (b) region.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167271","167271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946930","2018-09-04","Home Office","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 26 March 2018 to Question 133797 on Asylum: Housing, which regions have not secured compliant bids under the tendering process for the new asylum accommodation contracts.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167272","167272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946931","2018-09-04","Home Office","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 26 March 2018 to Question 133797 on Asylum: Housing, how many asylum seekers have been placed into forced bedroom sharing in dispersed asylum accommodation in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167273","167273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946932","2018-09-04","Cabinet Office","2018-07-23","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will make it his policy to launch a public consultation on civil service pay guidance.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167216","167216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946933","2018-09-04","Cabinet Office","2018-07-23","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what recent discussions he has had with trades unions on the civil service pay guidance.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167217","167217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946934","2018-09-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what (a) guidance and (b) support on (i) diet, (ii) exercise and (iii) other means of recovery is offered to patients who have suffered kidney failure.","Biography information for Andrea Jenkyns","Andrea Jenkyns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167329","167329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946935","2018-09-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what plans the Government has to secure payments to subcontractors and suppliers owed money for work undertaken for Carillion prior to its liquidation; and whether he has made an assessment of the potential merits of amending the Insolvency Act 1986 to protect small and medium-sized enterprises.","Biography information for Andrea Jenkyns","Andrea Jenkyns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167330","167330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946936","2018-09-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, for what reasons it was decided (a) to include razorbills and (b) not  to include common guillemots as an additional feature of the Cumbria Coast Marine Conservation Zone in the Government's June 2018 consultation on sites proposed for designation in the third tranche of Marine Conservation Zones.","Biography information for Trudy Harrison","Trudy Harrison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167342","167342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946937","2018-09-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, for what reason the level of compensation for victims of the contaminated blood scandal in England is less than that in Scotland; and whether an assessment was made of the implications for the level of compensation of the status of healthcare as a non-devolved policy area when British haemophiliacs were treated with contaminated products.","Biography information for Andrea Jenkyns","Andrea Jenkyns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167331","167331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946938","2018-09-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has made representations to the Indian Government on reports of abuse and neglect in equine serum facilities in India; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Wayne David","Wayne David","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167162","167162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946939","2018-09-04","Home Office","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will make it his policy to allow people who are affected by paragraph 322(5) of the Immigration Rules to work during the course of any appeals and judicial reviews.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167306","167306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946940","2018-09-04","Department for Education","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 23 July 2018 to Question 165696, for what reasons he did not publish his response to the recommendations in the 2018 report of the School Teachers' Review Body before the summer adjournment.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167374","167374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946941","2018-09-04","Department for Education","2018-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 23 July 2018 to Question 165696, when his Department received the 2018 report of the School Teachers' Review Body.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167375","167375"
