"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/684081","2017-02-07","Ministry of Justice","2017-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what training is available for (a) police, (b) probation staff and (c) Crown Prosecution Service staff on the nature of and compliance with the Victims' Code.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63051","63051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/684082","2017-02-07","Leader of the House","2017-02-03","To ask the Leader of the House, what the total pay bill was for (a) male and (b) female employees in his Office in 2015-16; and what the per capita spend from that pay bill for each man and woman was in that year.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63077","63077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/684083","2017-02-07","Northern Ireland Office","2017-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what the total pay bill was for (a) male and (b) female employees in his Department in 2015-16; and what the per capita spend from that pay bill for each man and woman was in that year.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63078","63078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/684084","2017-02-08","Cabinet Office","2017-02-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the total pay bill was for (a) male and (b) female employees in 10 Downing Street in 2015-16; and what the per capita spend from that pay bill for each man and woman was in that year.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63082","63082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/684085","2017-02-07","Public Accounts Commission","2017-02-03","To ask the Chairman of the Public Accounts Commission, what the total pay bill for (a) male and (b) female employees in his Department was in 2015-16; and what the per capita spend from that pay bill for each man and woman was in that year.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63087","63087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/684086","2017-02-07","Scotland Office","2017-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what the total pay bill was for (a) male and (b) female employees in his Department in 2015-16; and what the per capita spend from that pay bill for each man and woman was in that year.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63080","63080"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/684087","2017-02-08","Department for Transport","2017-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to support the connectivity of regional airports to High Speed 2.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63040","63040"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/684088","2017-02-08","Department for Transport","2017-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect of halogen bulbs in recently manufactured cars on a driver's eyesight when driving at night.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63056","63056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/684089","2017-02-08","Department for Transport","2017-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 20 January 2017 to Question 60278, what his Department's timescale is for a decision on future improvements for the strategic road network, including the M4, as part of the long-term planning process for road investment programmes; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63060","63060"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/684090","2017-02-08","Department for Transport","2017-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to his Department's consultation on Draft Airports National Policy Statement: new runway capacity and infrastructure at airports in the South East of England, published in February 2017, how capacity on the M4 will be assessed as part of future planning in relation to the road network; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63061","63061"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/684091","2017-02-08","Department for Transport","2017-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to ensure that airports continue to meet the requirements of the Birds and Habitats Directives and the Strategic Environmental Assessment Directive during airspace change decision-making processes.","Biography information for Tommy Sheppard","Tommy Sheppard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63013","63013"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/684092","2017-02-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if his Department will bring forward funding proposals to support the growth of regional airports as part of the industrial strategy.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63041","63041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/684093","2017-02-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate his Department has made of (a) savings to UK consumers and (b) reductions in greenhouse gas emissions from the implementation of the Eco Design and Energy Product Directives in (i) each of the last three years and (ii) in each year up to 2030.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63048","63048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/684094","2017-02-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 18 January 2017 to Question 59477, how differences in the age and gender profiles of members of the final salary pension scheme across the Nuclear Decommissioning Authority estate and public sector pension schemes have been accounted for in the equalities analysis referred to in that Answer.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63052","63052"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/684095","2017-02-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 18 January 2017 to Question 59477, what equalities assessment has been carried out on the cap on pensionable pay for final salary pension scheme members across the Nuclear Decommissioning Authority estate.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63053","63053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/684096","2017-02-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how much Ashfield constituency has received from the Regional Growth Fund since that fund's inception; and what the average funding per parliamentary constituency has been over that period.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63045","63045"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/684097","2017-02-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 2 February 2017 to Question 62005, when his Department plans to publish the revised Better Regulation Framework Manual following consultation on the final agreement of efficiency changes.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63047","63047"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/684098","2017-02-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate he has made of how much the Government will receive from the Mineworkers' Pension Scheme in (a) 2016-17, (b) 2017-18 and (c) 2018-19.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63016","63016"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/684099","2017-02-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what information was supplied to each bidder who expressed an interest in purchasing UK Green Investment Bank on the assets, structures and investments of that bank; and whether that information was supplied in the same form to each bidder.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63023","63023"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/684100","2017-02-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the total pay bill was for (a) male and (b) female employees in his Department in 2015-16; and what the per capita spend from that pay bill for each man and woman was in that year.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63062","63062"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/684101","2017-02-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what comparative assessment he has made of the profitability of the solar panel industry in the UK in (a) 2016 and (b) 2015; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63092","63092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/684102","2017-02-07","Department for International Trade","2017-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what the total pay bill was for (a) male and (b) female employees in his Department in 2015-16; and what the per capita spend from that pay bill for each man and woman was in that year.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63075","63075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/684103","2017-02-07","Department for International Trade","2017-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, if he will make it his policy to prioritise negotiating free trade agreements with (a) China, (b) Vietnam and (c) Indonesia when the UK leaves the EU; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63008","63008"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/684104","2017-02-07","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what the total pay bill was for (a) male and (b) female employees in his Department in 2015-16; and what the per capita spend from that pay bill for each man and woman was in that year.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63071","63071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/684105","2017-02-07","Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster","2017-02-03","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster, what the total pay bill for (a) male and (b) female employees in his Department was in 2015-16; and what the per capita spend from that pay bill for each man and woman was in that year.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63088","63088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683282","2017-02-06","Attorney General","2017-02-02","To ask the Attorney General, what the (a) ethnicity, (b) gender, (c) disability status, (d) educational background and (e) socio-economic status is of the three most senior officials of the Law Officers' Departments.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62875","62875"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683283","2017-02-06","Attorney General","2017-02-02","To ask the Attorney General, how many former prisoners have been employed by the Law Officers' Departments in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62949","62949"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683284","2017-02-06","Cabinet Office","2017-02-02","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many former prisoners have been employed by his Department in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62950","62950"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683285","2017-02-06","Cabinet Office","2017-02-02","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many staff of his Department at what grade were employed in the Cabinet Office youth policy team in July (a) 2014, (b) 2015 and (c) 2016.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62994","62994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683286","2017-02-06","Cabinet Office","2017-02-02","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the (a) ethnicity, (b) gender, (c) disability status, (d) educational background and (e) socio-economic status is of the three most senior officials of his Department.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62876","62876"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683287","2017-02-07","Cabinet Office","2017-02-02","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many civil servants have been recruited to his Department who previously worked at (a) PwC, (b) Deloitte, (c) Accenture, (d) KPMG, (e) McKinsey & Co, (f) Ernst & Young and (g) Bain & Company in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62916","62916"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683288","2017-02-07","Cabinet Office","2017-02-02","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what Government contracts have been awarded to (a) PwC, (b) Accenture, (c) Deloitte, (d) KPMG, (e) McKinsey & Co, (f) Ernst & Young and (g) Bain & Company; how much those contracts are worth; and how many of those contracts were pro bono in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62923","62923"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683289","2017-02-07","Cabinet Office","2017-02-02","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many deaths have been registered for people between the ages of (a) 50 and 64 and (b) 65 and over since 24 June 2016.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62841","62841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683290","2017-02-07","Cabinet Office","2017-02-02","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the Government's policy is on ministerial attendance at events at which the Irish national anthem is played in (a) the UK, (b) Ireland and (c) the rest of the world.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62843","62843"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683291","2017-02-07","HM Treasury","2017-02-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the consultation on Simplification of the Tax and National Insurance treatment of termination payments: government response and consultation on draft legislation, which closed for comments on 5 October 2016, what assessment he has made of the responses to that consultation; what changes he plans to make to the tax and national insurance treatment of redundancy payments in lieu of notice; and whether he still plans to introduce those changes in April 2018.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62921","62921"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683292","2017-02-06","HM Treasury","2017-02-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether his Department has any further funds from Libor fines to allocate in the March 2017 Budget.","Biography information for Ms Gisela Stuart","Ms Gisela Stuart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62902","62902"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683293","2017-02-07","HM Treasury","2017-02-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment his Department has made of the value of the UK wine and spirits industry to the economy.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62912","62912"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683294","2017-02-07","HM Treasury","2017-02-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, by how much rates of duty for (a) wine and (b) spirits have risen in percentage terms since 2007.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62913","62913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683295","2017-02-07","HM Treasury","2017-02-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect of a two per cent reduction in duty on UK wine and spirits to the economy.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62914","62914"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683296","2017-02-07","HM Treasury","2017-02-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what tax liabilities would result from a 3.2 per cent increase in duty on UK wine and spirits for (a) UK consumers and (b) businesses.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62915","62915"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683297","2017-02-06","HM Treasury","2017-02-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the (a) ethnicity, (b) gender, (c) disability status, (d) educational background and (e) socio-economic status is of the three most senior officials of his Department.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62897","62897"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683298","2017-02-07","HM Treasury","2017-02-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport on the potential effect on tax receipts of proposals that are being considered under the Triennial Review of gaming machine stakes and prizes.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62853","62853"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683299","2017-02-06","HM Treasury","2017-02-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many former prisoners have been employed by his Department in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62969","62969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683300","2017-02-06","Church Commissioners","2017-02-02","To ask the right hon. Member for Meriden, representing the Church Commissioners, what the (a) ethnicity, (b) gender, (c) disability status, (d) educational background and (e) socio-economic status is of the three most senior officials of the Church Commissioners.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62877","62877"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683301","2017-02-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the (a) ethnicity, (b) gender, (c) disability status, (d) educational background and (e) socio-economic status is of the three most senior officials of his Department.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62878","62878"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683302","2017-02-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what measures his Department has put in place to tackle fraud and abuse related to the Right to Buy scheme.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Howarth","Sir Gerald Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62931","62931"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683303","2017-02-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what additional safeguards the Government's Right to Buy working group has identified to tackle fraud and abuse of that scheme.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Howarth","Sir Gerald Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62932","62932"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683304","2017-02-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 25 January 2017 to Question 60366, if he will publish his Department's unpublished impact assessment on the changes to the affordable housing programme announced in the Autumn Statement 2016.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62983","62983"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683305","2017-02-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 30 January 2017 to Question 60963, if he will place in the Library unpublished research on the effect of immigration on housing commissioned or produced by his Department.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62984","62984"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683306","2017-02-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 2 February 2017 to Question 61611, on housing construction, how many Home and Committees Agency customers who have received funding from the Home Building Fund have had customer identification and verification checks which have identified possible red flags for tax avoidance or evasion.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62986","62986"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683307","2017-02-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 2 February 2017 to Question 61611, on housing construction, how many organisations that have received funding from the Home Building Fund are registered for tax purposes in (a) one of the Channel Islands and (b) the Isle of Man.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62987","62987"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683308","2017-02-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many former prisoners have been employed by his Department in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62951","62951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683309","2017-02-06","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many former prisoners have been employed by her Department in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62952","62952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683310","2017-02-06","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many staff of her Department at what grades are employed in the youth policy team.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62990","62990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683311","2017-02-06","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions she has had with Cabinet colleagues on England hosting the Commonwealth Games in 2026; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62833","62833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683312","2017-02-06","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what the (a) ethnicity, (b) gender, (c) disability status, (d) educational background and (e) socio-economic status is of the three most senior officials of her Department.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62879","62879"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683314","2017-02-06","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to her Department's press release of 22 December 2016, whether the £440 million made available for superfast rural broadband only includes costs for traditional and fibre-optic cables; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62906","62906"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683316","2017-02-06","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to her Department's press release of 22 December 2016, whether the £440 million made available for superfast rural broadband will include funding to cover difficult installations or provide access to isolated neighbourhoods.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62907","62907"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683318","2017-02-07","Ministry of Defence","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether there will be compulsory redundancies as a result of his Department's site closures.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62946","62946"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683321","2017-02-06","Ministry of Defence","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the (a) ethnicity, (b) gender, (c) disability status, (d) educational background and (e) socio-economic status is of the three most senior officials of his Department.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62880","62880"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683323","2017-02-06","Ministry of Defence","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the provision of any military supplies agreed by the Government as suitable for the Kurdistan Regional Government has not been allowed by the federal Government of Iraq since June 2014; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62865","62865"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683326","2017-02-07","Ministry of Defence","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what discussions he has had with (a) Kent County Council and (b) Maidstone Borough Council on the proposed closure of Invicta Park Barracks.","Biography information for Mrs Helen Grant","Mrs Helen Grant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62855","62855"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683328","2017-02-07","Ministry of Defence","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether an Equality Impact Assessment will be published on the proposal to close Invicta Park Barracks.","Biography information for Mrs Helen Grant","Mrs Helen Grant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62856","62856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683331","2017-02-07","Ministry of Defence","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will publish his Department's cost-benefit analysis on the sale of the Invicta Park Barracks site prior to that site's selection for closure as part of his Department's Better defence estate strategy.","Biography information for Mrs Helen Grant","Mrs Helen Grant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62847","62847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683333","2017-02-07","Ministry of Defence","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what safety assessment his Department has carried out on the Invicta Park Barracks site to determine whether the land is suitable for house building; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Helen Grant","Mrs Helen Grant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62848","62848"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683335","2017-02-07","Ministry of Defence","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) Royal Navy, (b) Army and (c) Royal Air Force personnel have been deployed overseas on UN, EU and NATO operations and missions in each of the last five years; and how many such personnel are currently deployed on such operations and missions.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62859","62859"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683337","2017-02-07","Ministry of Defence","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) Royal Navy, (b) Army and (c) Royal Air Force personnel have been deployed overseas on UN, EU and NATO operations and missions on tours exceeding a duration of (i) three, (ii) six and (iii) nine months in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62860","62860"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683340","2017-02-07","Ministry of Defence","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Royal Navy personnel have been deployed aboard warships for a  duration exceeding (a) three, (b) six and (c) nine months in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62861","62861"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683342","2017-02-07","Ministry of Defence","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 1 February 2017 to Question 61395, what the shortfall was for the recruitment of soldiers and officers in (a) The Rifles, (b) Royal Gurkha Rifles, (c) Parachute Regiment, (d) Royal Irish Regiment, (e) Royal Welsh, (f) Mercian Regiment, (g) Yorkshire Regiment, (h) Royal Anglian Regiment, (i) Royal Regiment of Fusiliers, (j) Duke of Lancaster's Regiment, (k) Princess of Wales' Royal Regiment, (l) Royal Regiment of Scotland, (m) Welsh Guards, (n) Irish Guards, (o) Scots Guards, (p) Coldstream Guards, (q) Grenadier Guards and (r) Royal Military Academy Sandhurst in each financial year between 2011-12 and 2015-16.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62862","62862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683345","2017-02-07","Ministry of Defence","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the locations are of UN, EU and NATO operations and missions that personnel from each of the UK armed forces are deployed to.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62863","62863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683354","2017-02-06","Ministry of Defence","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many former prisoners have been employed by his Department in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62953","62953"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683355","2017-02-06","Department for Education","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many former prisoners have been employed by her Department in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62954","62954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683356","2017-02-06","Department for Education","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many staff of her Department at what grade were employed in the youth policy team in July 2014.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62991","62991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683357","2017-02-06","Department for Education","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when her Department plans to announce further character award grants.","Biography information for Oliver Dowden","Oliver Dowden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62992","62992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683358","2017-02-07","Department for Education","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she plans for the statutory guidance prescribed in Clause 37 of the Children and Social Work Bill to set out minimum standards for monitoring and evaluation.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62834","62834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683359","2017-02-07","Department for Education","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to Chapter 3 of the Children and Social Work Bill and her Department's responsibility to monitor and evaluate pilot periods, whether there is a defined threshold at which trials are to be deemed no longer to be working in the best interests of children.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62835","62835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683360","2017-02-07","Department for Education","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to Chapter 3 of the Children and Social Work Bill and her Department's responsibility to monitor and evaluate pilot periods, whether there is a defined trigger that will prompt her to revoke the regulations and immediately stop any trial deemed to be no longer working in the best interests of children.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62836","62836"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683361","2017-02-07","Department for Education","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to her reference to adverse impacts on children during committee stage of the Children and Social Work Bill on 10 January 2017, what such impacts are in the context of Chapter 3 of the Children and Social Work Bill.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62837","62837"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683362","2017-02-06","Department for Education","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will make it her policy for first aid and CPR to be taught in all schools.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62828","62828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683363","2017-02-06","Department for Education","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the (a) ethnicity, (b) gender, (c) disability status, (d) educational background and (e) socio-economic status is of the three most senior officials of her Department.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62881","62881"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683364","2017-02-07","Department for Education","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the change in the level of funding for maintained nursery schools in (a) England and (b) Coventry in the last three years; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62947","62947"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683365","2017-02-06","Department for Education","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children her Department has received information on from the 2016-17 autumn school census; and of those responses how many and what proportions response was (a) refused, (b) not yet obtained and (c) not known to questions on (i) country of birth and (ii) nationality; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62925","62925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683366","2017-02-06","Department for Education","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether the money pledged by the Government in January 2017 for institutes of technology and schools will in part be allocated for aerospace and aviation engineering.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62905","62905"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683367","2017-02-06","Department for Education","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how she plans to ensure that girls and women benefit from the money pledged by the Government in January 2017 for institutes of technology and schools.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62904","62904"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683368","2017-02-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the (a) ethnicity, (b) gender, (c) disability status, (d) educational background and (e) socio-economic status is of the three most senior officials of her Department.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62882","62882"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683369","2017-02-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if the Government will take steps to encourage more consumers to buy Fairtrade produce.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62827","62827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683370","2017-02-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what her Department's policy is on introducing a total ban on the sale of ivory in the UK; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sarah Olney","Sarah Olney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62854","62854"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683371","2017-02-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many former prisoners have been employed by her Department in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62955","62955"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683372","2017-02-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many former prisoners have been employed by his Department in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62957","62957"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683373","2017-02-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the effectiveness of the transition of power resulting from planned presidential elections in the Democratic Republic of Congo in 2017.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62824","62824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683374","2017-02-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the (a) ethnicity, (b) gender, (c) disability status, (d) educational background and (e) socio-economic status is of the three most senior officials of his Department.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62884","62884"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683375","2017-02-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received on the sentence given to Reverend Hassan Abduraheem, Petr Jasek and Abdumonem Abdumawla in Sudan; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mark Durkan","Mark Durkan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62866","62866"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683376","2017-02-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the effect on freedom of religion or belief in Sudan as a result of the verdict in the recent case related to Reverend Hassan Abduraheem, Petr Jasek and Abdumonem Abdumawla in that country.","Biography information for Mark Durkan","Mark Durkan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62867","62867"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683377","2017-02-06","Department of Health","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of the sustainability of the GP network.","Biography information for Oliver Colvile","Oliver Colvile","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62832","62832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683378","2017-02-06","Department of Health","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the (a) ethnicity, (b) gender, (c) disability status, (d) educational background and (e) socio-economic status is of the three most senior officials of his Department.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62886","62886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683379","2017-02-06","Department of Health","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 13 January 2017 to Question 58887, on nutrition, if he will publish on the gov.uk website the proposed timescale for the review of the nutrient profiling model.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62903","62903"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683380","2017-02-07","Department of Health","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the cost was of prescribing paracetamol on the NHS in each of the last five years; and if he will make statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62918","62918"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683381","2017-02-06","Department of Health","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what redundancy costs were incurred by his Department in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62928","62928"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683382","2017-02-06","Department of Health","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 26 January 2017 to Question 60527, what priority recommendation level was assigned by the NHS England Clinical Priority Advisory Group to each of the policy proposals (a) recommended for routine commissioning and (b) not recommended for routine commissioning.","Biography information for Crispin Blunt","Crispin Blunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62930","62930"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683383","2017-02-06","Department of Health","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many civil servants his Department plans to recruit in the next 12 months; and what the cost to the public purse of that recruitment will be.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62929","62929"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683384","2017-02-07","Department of Health","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many times an ambulance has been called to a prison for an inmate who has attempted suicide in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62838","62838"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683385","2017-02-07","Department of Health","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many prisoners have waited for more than 14 days for a transfer to hospital under the Mental Health Act 1983 in each month since April 2015.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62839","62839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683386","2017-02-06","Department of Health","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of recent trends in the level of availability of NHS beds.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62851","62851"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683388","2017-02-06","Department of Health","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many former prisoners have been employed by his Department in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62959","62959"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683389","2017-02-06","Department of Health","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make it his policy to restructure the most junior Agenda for Change pay bands to (a) pay the living wage and (b) maintain pay differentials.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62938","62938"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683390","2017-02-06","Department of Health","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether it is his Department's policy that the mandation of health visiting services will continue after March 2017.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62939","62939"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683391","2017-02-06","Department of Health","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make it his policy to implement a pay award for nursing staff in line with the retail price index.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62940","62940"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683392","2017-02-06","Department of Health","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will publish Public Health England's review of the mandated health visiting service.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62941","62941"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683393","2017-02-06","Department of Health","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department plans to allow registered birth certificates for children born from 20 weeks gestation.","Biography information for Maria Caulfield","Maria Caulfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62995","62995"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683394","2017-02-07","Department of Health","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) of his Department's and (b) NHS England staff are employed in media relations and communications roles; and how much was spent on the salaries of those staff members in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62974","62974"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683395","2017-02-07","Department of Health","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether NHS England has met the Prisons and Probation Ombudsman to discuss avoidable deaths in custody since 9 January 2017.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62972","62972"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683396","2017-02-07","Department of Health","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he plans to place the governance arrangements for sustainability and transformation plans on a statutory footing.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62973","62973"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683397","2017-02-07","Department of Health","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will publish information his Department holds from UCAS on the number of applications for undergraduate (a) nursing, (b) midwifery and (c) allied health degrees on 15 January 2017 in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62975","62975"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683398","2017-02-06","Department of Health","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his policy is on increasing the number of nursing graduates.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62998","62998"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683399","2017-02-06","Department of Health","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions NHS England has with clinical commissioning groups on commissioning policies and the requirements of the NHS constitution, NICE guidance and the Health and Social Care Act 2012.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62989","62989"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683400","2017-02-06","Home Office","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many staff of her Department will support Stephen Shaw in producing the review of his report on immigration detention.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62997","62997"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683401","2017-02-07","Home Office","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of Question 58064, on overseas students, what definition her Department uses to define (a) top universities and (b) best students.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62976","62976"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683402","2017-02-07","Home Office","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the Government's policy is on (a) reducing the level of migration to the UK and (b) caps related to international student recruitment.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62977","62977"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683403","2017-02-07","Cabinet Office","2017-02-02","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people from other EU countries are resident in (a) Camberwell and Peckham constituency and (b) the London Borough of Southwark.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62978","62978"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683404","2017-02-06","Home Office","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she expects Stephen Shaw to (a) begin, (b) complete and (c) publish the findings of his review of his report on immigration detention.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62993","62993"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683405","2017-02-06","Home Office","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many former prisoners have been employed by her Department in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62960","62960"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683406","2017-02-06","Home Office","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 19 January 2017 to Question 59369, on immigrant detainees, what the terms of reference are for Stephen Shaw's review.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62981","62981"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683407","2017-02-06","Home Office","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 19 January 2017 to Question 59369, on immigrant detainees, what the key actions are from Stephen Shaw's previous report.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62982","62982"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683408","2017-02-06","Home Office","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the (a) ethnicity, (b) gender, (c) disability status, (d) educational background and (e) socio-economic status is of the three most senior officials of her Department.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62887","62887"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683409","2017-02-06","Home Office","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 1 February 2017 to Question 61835, on immigration: appeals, how long follow-on actions are expected to take if the Home Office decides not to contest a successful appeal.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62868","62868"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683410","2017-02-06","House of Commons Commission","2017-02-02","To ask the right hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington, representing the House of Commons Commission, what the (a) ethnicity, (b) gender, (c) disability status, (d) educational background and (e) socio-economic status is of the three most senior officials of the House of Commons Commission.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62888","62888"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683411","2017-02-06","Department for International Development","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what the (a) ethnicity, (b) gender, (c) disability status, (d) educational background and (e) socio-economic status is of the three most senior officials of her Department.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62889","62889"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683412","2017-02-06","Department for International Development","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much and what proportion of the aid that her Department gives to Paraguay is for cultural projects in that country; and what those projects so funded are.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62908","62908"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683413","2017-02-06","Department for International Development","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that adequate port infrastructure is in place at Al Hudaydah port and other ports in Yemen for the transmission of international aid to the Yemeni people.","Biography information for Nick Smith","Nick Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62668","62668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683414","2017-02-07","Department for International Development","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether she raised the case of Andrew Tsege during her recent visit to Ethiopia.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62864","62864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683415","2017-02-06","Department for International Development","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many former prisoners have been employed by her Department in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62961","62961"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683416","2017-02-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners were given extra days in prison for assaulting a prison officer in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62942","62942"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683417","2017-02-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment she has made of trends in the number of prisoners temporarily released on resettlement overnight release licences in each of the last five years; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62943","62943"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683418","2017-02-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether victims of crime will be invited to submit details of their experiences as part of the review of the victims code.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62944","62944"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683419","2017-02-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many former prisoners have been employed by her Department in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62963","62963"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683420","2017-02-07","Department of Health","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 31 January 2017 to Question 61891, on the Healthy Start Scheme, how many people have received support through that scheme since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62842","62842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683421","2017-02-07","Ministry of Justice","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much the Prisons and Probation Ombudsman has spent on investigations into self-inflicted deaths in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62840","62840"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683422","2017-02-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many probation staff employed by the Community Rehabilitation Company in Wales have (a) been offered and (b) accepted the enhanced voluntary redundancy scheme since the start of financial year 2015-16.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62849","62849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683423","2017-02-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what competitive tendering process was followed prior to Aurelius taking control of the Community Rehabilitation Company from Working Links in Wales and the West Country.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62821","62821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683424","2017-02-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what experience Aurelius, which manages the Community Rehabilitation Company in Wales and the West Country, has in the direct supervision of offenders.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62822","62822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683425","2017-02-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what criteria bidders had to satisfy earlier in 2017 prior to being awarded the contract to manage the Community Rehabilitation Company in Wales.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62823","62823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683426","2017-02-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when the Government plans to commence its review of the victims code; and what the terms of reference of that review will be.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62934","62934"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683427","2017-02-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much government funding was given to Sharia councils in the UK in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62935","62935"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683428","2017-02-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many Sharia Councils are based in the UK.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62936","62936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683429","2017-02-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many former prisoners have been employed as prison officers in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62937","62937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683430","2017-02-07","Ministry of Justice","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate she has made of the number of prisoners who have been imprisoned over 100 miles from their home in England in the last 12 months; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62919","62919"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683431","2017-02-07","Ministry of Justice","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that familial relationships are maintained for prisoners that are transferred to prisons more than 100 miles away from their home; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62920","62920"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683432","2017-02-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the (a) ethnicity, (b) gender, (c) disability status, (d) educational background and (e) socio-economic status is of the three most senior officials of her Department.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62891","62891"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683433","2017-02-06","Leader of the House","2017-02-02","To ask the Leader of the House, what the (a) ethnicity, (b) gender, (c) disability status, (d) educational background and (e) socio-economic status is of the three most senior officials of his Office.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62892","62892"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683434","2017-02-06","Leader of the House","2017-02-02","To ask the Leader of the House, how many former prisoners have been employed by his Office in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62964","62964"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683435","2017-02-06","Northern Ireland Office","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many former prisoners have been employed by his Department in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62965","62965"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683436","2017-02-06","Northern Ireland Office","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what the (a) ethnicity, (b) gender, (c) disability status, (d) educational background and (e) socio-economic status is of the three most senior officials of his Department.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62893","62893"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683437","2017-02-07","Northern Ireland Office","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what his Department's policy is on ministerial attendance at events at which the national anthem of Ireland is played.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62844","62844"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683438","2017-02-06","Cabinet Office","2017-02-02","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the (a) ethnicity, (b) gender, (c) disability status, (d) educational background and (e) socio-economic status is of the three most senior officials of 10 Downing Street.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62894","62894"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683439","2017-02-07","Cabinet Office","2017-02-02","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether the Prime Minister's predecessor met Lord Rothermere in February or March 2016.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62917","62917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683440","2017-02-06","Cabinet Office","2017-02-02","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many former prisoners have been employed by 10 Downing Street in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62966","62966"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683441","2017-02-06","Public Accounts Commission","2017-02-02","To ask the Chairman of the Public Accounts Commission, what the (a) ethnicity, (b) gender, (c) disability status, (d) educational background and (e) socio-economic status is of the three most senior officials in the National Audit Office.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62871","62871"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683442","2017-02-06","Scotland Office","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what the (a) ethnicity, (b) gender, (c) disability status, (d) educational background and (e) socio-economic status is of the three most senior officials of his Department.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62895","62895"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683443","2017-02-06","Scotland Office","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how many former prisoners have been employed by his Department in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62967","62967"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683444","2017-02-06","Speaker's Committee for the Independent Parliamentary Standards Authority","2017-02-02","To ask the hon. Member for Broxbourne, representing the Speaker's Committee for the Independent Parliamentary Standards Authority, (IPSA) what the (a) ethnicity, (b) gender, (c) disability status, (d) educational background and (e) socio-economic status is of the three most senior officials employed by IPSA.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62872","62872"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683445","2017-02-06","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2017-02-02","To ask the hon. Member for Houghton and Sunderland South, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what the (a) ethnicity, (b) gender, (c) disability status, (d) educational background and (e) socio-economic status is of the three most senior officials employed by the Electoral Commission.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62873","62873"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683446","2017-02-06","Department for Transport","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the (a) ethnicity, (b) gender, (c) disability status, (d) educational background and (e) socio-economic status is of the three most senior officials of his Department.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62896","62896"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683447","2017-02-06","Department for Transport","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what requirements there are for train operating companies to consult with disabled passengers and groups representing disabled people on the provision of signage and information as part of the development of those companies' Disabled People's Protection Policy; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62926","62926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683448","2017-02-07","Department for Transport","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment his Department has made of the options available to increase the provision of audio-visual information on buses.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62857","62857"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683449","2017-02-07","Department for Transport","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to improve access to bus services for people who are visually impaired.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62858","62858"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683450","2017-02-06","Department for Transport","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what progress has been made towards making the M60 a smart motorway; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62850","62850"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683451","2017-02-06","Department for Transport","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many former prisoners have been employed by his Department in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62968","62968"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683452","2017-02-06","Wales Office","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how many former prisoners have been employed by his Department in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62970","62970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683453","2017-02-06","Wales Office","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what the (a) ethnicity, (b) gender, (c) disability status, (d) educational background and (e) socio-economic status is of the three most senior officials of his Department.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62898","62898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683454","2017-02-06","Women and Equalities","2017-02-02","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, when the Government plans to launch a public consultation on caste and the Equality Act 2010.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62869","62869"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683455","2017-02-06","Women and Equalities","2017-02-02","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what the (a) ethnicity, (b) gender, (c) disability status, (d) educational background and (e) socio-economic status is of the three most senior officials of the Government Equalities Office.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62885","62885"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683456","2017-02-06","Women and Equalities","2017-02-02","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, how many former prisoners have been employed by the Government Equalities Office in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62958","62958"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683457","2017-02-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 24 January 2017 to Question 60655, on universal credit and housing benefit, if he will place in the Library the assumptions by which those estimates were calculated.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62985","62985"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683458","2017-02-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many former prisoners have been employed by his Department in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62971","62971"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683459","2017-02-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what his policy is on removing the automatic entitlement to the housing element of universal credit only for 18 to 21 year olds who are out of work.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62996","62996"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683460","2017-02-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 2 February 2017 to Question 62388, on social security benefits, what information his Department holds on the number of claimants who have applied for (a) jobseekers' allowance and (b) universal credit (i) by post and (ii) during a home visit.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62980","62980"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683461","2017-02-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent representations he has received on assaults on betting shop staff.","Biography information for Holly Lynch","Holly Lynch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62829","62829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683462","2017-02-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether an assessment has been made by the Health and Safety Executive of the safety of lone staff working in betting shops; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Holly Lynch","Holly Lynch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62830","62830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683463","2017-02-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the UK leaving the EU on UK pensioners living elsewhere in the EU.","Biography information for Ian Blackford","Ian Blackford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62831","62831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683464","2017-02-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the findings of Age UK's report entitled Working Later, Waiting Longer, published in November 2016, what assessment he has made of the merits of reviewing the effect on groups that are most reliant on their state pension of the existing state pension age timetable to April 2028.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62870","62870"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683465","2017-02-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the (a) ethnicity, (b) gender, (c) disability status, (d) educational background and (e) socio-economic status is of the three most senior officials of his Department.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62899","62899"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683466","2017-02-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the pension status is of women who were widowed but later remarried; and how much state pension they are entitled to relative to the level of their late husband's national insurance contributions.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62911","62911"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683467","2017-02-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, which credit unions have received funding under the Credit Union Expansion Project; and how much each such union has received.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62924","62924"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683468","2017-02-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what representations he has received on trends in the number of inaccurate state pension forecasts sent to people nearing retirement age; and whether he plans to take steps to assist those affected by errors in such forecasts.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62909","62909"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683469","2017-02-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether a widow who later remarries is eligible to claim pension credit to top up her income; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62910","62910"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683470","2017-02-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many staff (a) were employed by and (b) left the UK Green Investment Bank in each year since its creation; and how many staff have left that bank in 2017 to date.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62846","62846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683471","2017-02-06","HM Treasury","2017-02-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much has been raised by the apprenticeship levy since it was established; and how much of that sum has been subsequently re-invested in apprenticeships.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62927","62927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683472","2017-02-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the (a) ethnicity, (b) gender, (c) disability status, (d) educational background and (e) socio-economic status is of the three most senior officials of his Department.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62874","62874"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683473","2017-02-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what consultation took place with non-management level staff at the Green Investment Bank on its privatisation.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62852","62852"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683474","2017-02-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how much funding has been paid to ACAS; and how many full-time equivalent staff were employed by that organisation in (a) 2015-16 and (b) 2016-17 to date.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62979","62979"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683475","2017-02-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what plans his Department has to respond to the recommendations of the Competition and Market Authority report on the energy sector, published in December 2016.","Biography information for Chris Elmore","Chris Elmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62988","62988"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683476","2017-02-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many former prisoners have been employed by his Department in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62948","62948"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683477","2017-02-06","Department for International Trade","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many former prisoners have been employed by his Department in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62962","62962"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683478","2017-02-06","Department for International Trade","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether UK Export Finance staff ask for advice from diplomatic missions on agents when special handling arrangements apply.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62933","62933"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683479","2017-02-06","Department for International Trade","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, pursuant to the Answer of 27 January 2017 to Question 60711, with which other countries or groups of countries the Government is planning to enter trade negotiations after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62826","62826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683480","2017-02-06","Department for International Trade","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what the (a) ethnicity, (b) gender, (c) disability status, (d) educational background and (e) socio-economic status is of the three most senior officials of his Department.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62890","62890"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683481","2017-02-07","Department for International Trade","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, by whom the decision was made to have a European Committee debate on the EU-Canada Comprehensive Economic and Trade Agreement on 6 February 2017 rather than a debate on the floor of the House; when that decision was made; for what reason that decision was made; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62945","62945"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683482","2017-02-07","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for the Home Department on the cost of replacing passports to remove reference to the EU; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62922","62922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683483","2017-02-06","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what the (a) ethnicity, (b) gender, (c) disability status, (d) educational background and (e) socio-economic status is of the three most senior officials of his Department.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62883","62883"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683484","2017-02-06","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether the Government has taken legal advice on the possibility of reversing a trigger of Article 50.","Biography information for Geraint Davies","Geraint Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62901","62901"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683485","2017-02-06","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of changes to UK rules on movement on the UK's negotiations relating to securing a trade agreement on energy with the EU after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62825","62825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683486","2017-02-07","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what his policy is on retaining Article 3 of the European Convention on Human Rights in UK law after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62845","62845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683487","2017-02-06","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many former prisoners have been employed by his Department in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62956","62956"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683488","2017-02-06","Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster","2017-02-02","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster, what the (a) ethnicity, (b) gender, (c) disability status, (d) educational background and (e) socio-economic status is of the three most senior officials of his Department.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62900","62900"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686576","2017-02-08","Cabinet Office","2017-02-02","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what discussions he has had with the Chancellor of the Exchequer on when the Government plans to end the public sector pay freeze.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 908675","908675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686577","2017-02-08","Cabinet Office","2017-02-02","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps he has taken to ensure that the civil service has the number of people it needs in each Department to deal with the implications of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 908674","908674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686578","2017-02-08","Cabinet Office","2017-02-02","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the UK's decision to leave the EU on the size of the civil service workforce.","Biography information for Hannah Bardell","Hannah Bardell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 908671","908671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686579","2017-02-08","Cabinet Office","2017-02-02","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps his  Department has taken to improve transparency in government.","Biography information for Michelle Donelan","Michelle Donelan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 908673","908673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682931","2017-02-06","Cabinet Office","2017-02-01","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many officials in which Government Departments receive a level of pay greater than that of the Prime Minister; what the roles of such officials are; and when such officials were appointed to their current roles.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62672","62672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682932","2017-02-06","Cabinet Office","2017-02-01","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many staff have been seconded to Government Departments from (a) PwC, (b) Deloitte, (c) Accenture, (d) KPMG, (e) McKinsey & Co, (f) Ernst and Young and (g) Bain & Company since July 2016.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62723","62723"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682933","2017-02-06","Cabinet Office","2017-02-01","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many meetings Government Ministers or senior civil servants have had with representatives of (a) PwC, (b) Deloitte, (c) Accenture, (d) KPMG, (e) McKinsey & Co, (f) Ernst and Young and (g) Bain & Company since July 2016.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62724","62724"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682934","2017-02-03","Cabinet Office","2017-02-01","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps the Government takes to consult professional bodies in the IT industry on ensuring value for money before embarking on large-scale IT projects.","Biography information for Alex Chalk","Alex Chalk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62786","62786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682935","2017-02-06","HM Treasury","2017-02-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate his Department has made of the reduction in monies coming in to the public purse which result from each increase in one per cent in excise duty charged on tobacco products.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62819","62819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682936","2017-02-03","HM Treasury","2017-02-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of increased inflation on low-income households.","Biography information for Ian Blackford","Ian Blackford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62780","62780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682937","2017-02-03","HM Treasury","2017-02-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he plans to publish the next edition of The Green Book: Appraisal and Evaluation in Central Government.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62777","62777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682938","2017-02-06","HM Treasury","2017-02-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he expects the Government's stake in Lloyds Bank to be returned to the private sector.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62796","62796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682939","2017-02-06","HM Treasury","2017-02-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the total value of revenue forgone was of tax relief for personal pension contributions for (a) basic and (b) higher rate taxpayers in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62797","62797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682940","2017-02-06","HM Treasury","2017-02-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the revenue to the Exchequer from insurance premium tax on (a) individual health insurance and (b) corporate health insurance was in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62806","62806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682941","2017-02-06","HM Treasury","2017-02-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the potential economic effect on the (a) pharmaceuticals, (b) aerospace, (c) vehicle manufacturing, (d) financial services, (e) agriculture and (f) creative industries of reverting to trade on World Trade Organisation terms as a result of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62718","62718"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682942","2017-02-03","HM Treasury","2017-02-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether there are Government guidelines given to banks to ensure that consumers are protected when considering closing bank accounts that have not been in use for a number of years.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62680","62680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682943","2017-02-03","HM Treasury","2017-02-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether there are any penalties in place for banks that are found to retain customer's money without informing them after the account has been closed.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62681","62681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682944","2017-02-03","HM Treasury","2017-02-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 12 October 2016 to Question 47155, what progress has been made on (a) funding and (b) bringing forward legislative proposals on a breathing space mechanism for families in debt.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62653","62653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682945","2017-02-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many local authorities in England provide or commission an oral health improvement programme; and what estimate he has made of the funds committed to such programmes by local authorities in England in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62638","62638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682946","2017-02-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the wastage rate of local government employees in each job role over the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62652","62652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682947","2017-02-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the funding allocation to the Lancashire Enterprise Partnership has been in each year since its inception; and what that funding allocation is for 2016-17.","Biography information for David Morris","David Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62689","62689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682948","2017-02-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if his Department will provide transitional loss protection for local authorities affected by the new taper on New Homes Bonus.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62694","62694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682949","2017-02-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the new taper on New Homes Bonus on local authorities who approve and build a high volume of houses.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62695","62695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682950","2017-02-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much Lancashire County Council received from the Revenue Support Grant in each of the last three years.","Biography information for David Morris","David Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62748","62748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682951","2017-02-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, on what dates (a) Buckinghamshire County Council submitted a proposal for local government reorganisation in Buckinghamshire and (b) district councils in Buckinghamshire submitted their counter proposals; and what his timetable is for reaching a decision on those proposals.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62807","62807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682952","2017-02-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he plans to respond to the letters from the hon. Member for Christchurch of (a) 19 January 2017 on behalf of the Christchurch Citizens' Association and (b) 23 January 2017 on the application for a Dorset Combined Authority.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62808","62808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682953","2017-02-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will permit Poole Unitary Authority and Bournemouth Unitary Authority to merge voluntarily to form a new authority.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62809","62809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682954","2017-02-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will visit the Borough of Christchurch and the districts of East Dorset and Purbeck to discuss reasons for those authorities voting to retain their status as independent principal authorities; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62810","62810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682955","2017-02-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate his Department has made of the net value of the Government's spending on starter homes in the next (a) 10, (b) 20 and (c) 30 years.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62793","62793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682956","2017-02-06","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many young people are expected to benefit from the National Citizen Service between 2015 and 2020.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62737","62737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682957","2017-02-03","Department of Health","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to stop websites promoting suicide.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62759","62759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682958","2017-02-06","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if she will estimate the number of betting shops likely to close as a result of a potential future reduction in the maximum stakes on fixed-odds betting terminals.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62709","62709"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682959","2017-02-03","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps she is taking to ensure the museum sector contributes to her Department's tourism-related objectives.","Biography information for Michael Gove","Michael Gove","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62647","62647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682960","2017-02-03","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps her Department and its non-departmental public bodies are taking to support poetry, creative writing and community drama.","Biography information for Michael Gove","Michael Gove","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62648","62648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682961","2017-02-03","Ministry of Defence","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which state schools receive funds from his Department to support cadet forces; how much each school received in 2015-16; and how much each school will receive in 2016-17.","Biography information for Michael Gove","Michael Gove","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62641","62641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682962","2017-02-03","Ministry of Defence","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which independent schools receive funds from his Department to support cadet forces; how much each of those schools received in 2015-16; and how much each of those schools will received in 2016-17.","Biography information for Michael Gove","Michael Gove","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62642","62642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682963","2017-02-03","Ministry of Defence","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when the Defence Suppliers SME Forum (a) last met and (b) will next meet.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62651","62651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682964","2017-02-06","Ministry of Defence","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what his Department's policy is on publication of the results of the Royal Navy SSBN and Trident II D5 demonstration and shakedown operations.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62655","62655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682965","2017-02-06","Ministry of Defence","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 17 January 2017 to Question 59886, when he plans for the (a) 12th and (b) 20th Armoured Infantry Brigade to reach initial operational capacity with upgraded Warrior, upgraded Challenger 2 and Scout vehicles; and when he plans for the (i) 12th and (ii) 20th Armoured Infantry Brigade to reach full operational capacity with that new equipment.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62656","62656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682966","2017-02-06","Ministry of Defence","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when the Defence Suppliers Forum Mid-Tier Group will next meet.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62657","62657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682967","2017-02-06","Ministry of Defence","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many civilian staff were employed by his Department, by civil service grade, in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62658","62658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682968","2017-02-06","Ministry of Defence","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) operational ration packs and (b) tonnes of food that represents have been withdrawn from use and disposed of in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62725","62725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682969","2017-02-03","Ministry of Defence","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment his Department has made of the potential diminishment of US commitment to NATO after President Trump's reorganisation of the US National Security Council.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62692","62692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682970","2017-02-03","Ministry of Defence","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether (a) Lockheed Martin and (b) Draper Engineering have identified the fault to the Trident D5 missile that was test fired in June 2016.","Biography information for John Cryer","John Cryer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62686","62686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682971","2017-02-03","Ministry of Defence","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether there is a cost to the public purse if a Trident D5 missile is defective during a test launch; and whether the defective missile is replaced at the manufacturers expense.","Biography information for John Cryer","John Cryer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62687","62687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682972","2017-02-03","Ministry of Defence","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the UK's other Trident missiles have been checked for faults after the failed Trident II D5 missile test in June 2016.","Biography information for John Cryer","John Cryer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62688","62688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682973","2017-02-06","Ministry of Defence","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which NATO appointments are held by British officers by (a) rank, (b) responsibility and (c) location.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62675","62675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682974","2017-02-03","Ministry of Defence","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans he has for ensuring close co-operation with EU countries on defence policy after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Robert Courts","Robert Courts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62767","62767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682975","2017-02-06","Ministry of Defence","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, on how many occasions explosive ordnance disposal personnel were deployed in Northern Ireland between 1 August and 31 December 2016.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62798","62798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682976","2017-02-03","Ministry of Defence","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many service personnel who have left the (a) Royal Navy, (b) Army and (c) Royal Air Force have left for the reason of (i) voluntary outflow, (ii) time expiry, (iii) redundancy and (iv) other wastage in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62790","62790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682977","2017-02-03","Ministry of Defence","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many personnel in the (a) infantry, (b) Royal Artillery, (c) Royal Corps of Signals, (d) Army Medical Services, (e) Adjutant General's Corps, (f) Royal Armoured Corps, (g) Army Air Corps, (h) Royal Engineers, (i) Royal Logistics Corps, (j) Royal Electrical and Mechanical Engineers and (k) Intelligence Corps, (l) Royal Navy and (m) RAF have breached harmony guideline targets in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62781","62781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682978","2017-02-03","Ministry of Defence","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many personnel in the (a) infantry, (b) Royal Artillery, (c) Royal Corps of Signals, (d) Army Medical Services, (e) Adjutant General's Corps, (f) Royal Armoured Corps, (g) Army Air Corps, (h) Royal Engineers, (i) Royal Logistics Corps, (j) Royal Electrical and Mechanical Engineers and (k) Intelligence Corps, (l) Royal Navy and (m) RAF have breached harmony guideline targets in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62782","62782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682979","2017-02-03","Ministry of Defence","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the harmony guideline target is for the (a) Royal Navy, (b) Army and (c) Royal Air Force.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62783","62783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682980","2017-02-03","Ministry of Defence","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the outflow target was for reserve and regular soldiers and officers leaving the (a) infantry, (b) Royal Artillery, (c) Royal Corps of Signals, (d) Army Medical Services, (e) Adjutant General's Corps, (f) Royal Armoured Corps, (g) Army Air Corps, (h) Royal Engineers, (i) Royal Logistics Corps, (j) Royal Electrical and Mechanical Engineers and (k) Intelligence Corps in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62784","62784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682981","2017-02-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Oral Answer of 30 January 2017, Official Report, column 653, whether the action of the coalition in Yemen is supported by UN Security Council resolution 2216 (2015); and which of the provisions of that resolution authorises the level of force used by the coalition.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62795","62795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682982","2017-02-03","Ministry of Defence","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether equality impact assessments have been carried out on the proposed closure of his Department's sites (a) in Scotland and (b) elsewhere in the UK.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62787","62787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682983","2017-02-06","Department for Education","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what account her Department took during preparation of its Green Paper, Schools that Work for Everyone, published in September 2016, of the work of the Integrated Education Fund; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Hugo Swire","Sir Hugo Swire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62804","62804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682984","2017-02-06","Department for Education","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department takes to ensure that commercial organisations which sell access to school websites and teachers' emails do so securely and responsibly.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62669","62669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682985","2017-02-03","Department for Education","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which academies have been transferred between which academy trusts since May 2015; and what the cost of each such transfer was.","Biography information for John Pugh","John Pugh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62705","62705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682986","2017-02-03","Department for Education","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with which university vice-chancellors she has discussed opening new free schools; and what progress has been made on opening such schools.","Biography information for Michael Gove","Michael Gove","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62708","62708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682987","2017-02-06","Department for Education","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many UK students have studied in higher education facilities in EU member states in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62716","62716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682988","2017-02-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many UK students have participated in the Erasmus Scheme in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62717","62717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682989","2017-02-06","Cabinet Office","2017-02-01","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many UK nationals under the age of 25 (a) live, (b) work and (c) study in EU member states.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62722","62722"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682990","2017-02-06","HM Treasury","2017-02-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the sums to be accrued from the apprenticeship levy in each region of the UK in (a) 2017-18, (b) 2018-19 and (c) 2019-20.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62730","62730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682991","2017-02-06","Department for Education","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department has taken to reduce the number of children who are returned to care after adoption in the last 12 months; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62741","62741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682992","2017-02-06","Department for Education","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of the number of children who have been returned to care after adoption in England and Wales in each of the last five years; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62743","62743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682993","2017-02-03","Department for Education","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will meet representatives of the charity Protecting Children and Uniting Families Across Borders to discuss how to provide specialist children's inter-country social work services.","Biography information for Michael Gove","Michael Gove","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62639","62639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682994","2017-02-03","Department for Education","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, for what reason her Department ceased funding for the charity Protecting Children and Uniting Families Across Borders; and what provision she has made for ensuring that charity's work is sustained.","Biography information for Michael Gove","Michael Gove","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62640","62640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682995","2017-02-03","Home Office","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when the Government plans to ratify the Lanzarote Convention.","Biography information for Michael Gove","Michael Gove","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62643","62643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682996","2017-02-03","Department for Education","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which initiatives the Education Endowment Foundation has funded since its establishment; and what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of each such initiative.","Biography information for Michael Gove","Michael Gove","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62649","62649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682997","2017-02-03","Department for Education","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how she has assessed the effectiveness of Regional School Commissioners.","Biography information for Michael Gove","Michael Gove","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62650","62650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682998","2017-02-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to page 16 of the UK Climate Change Risk Assessment 2017, published in January 2017, how many staff at her Department are working on the review of the UK's environmental policy framework.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62733","62733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682999","2017-02-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to page 16 of the UK Climate Change Risk Assessment 2017, when her Department expects to complete its review of the UK's environmental policy framework.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62744","62744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683000","2017-02-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what progress has been made on each of the eight work streams within her Department's EU exit programme.","Biography information for Calum Kerr","Calum Kerr","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62710","62710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683001","2017-02-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the eight work streams within her Department's EU exit programme are; and what the purpose of each of those work streams is.","Biography information for Calum Kerr","Calum Kerr","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62711","62711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683002","2017-02-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the role of devolved administrations will be in her Department's EU exit programme.","Biography information for Calum Kerr","Calum Kerr","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62712","62712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683003","2017-02-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when her consultation with farmers on her Department's EU exit programme will commence.","Biography information for Calum Kerr","Calum Kerr","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62713","62713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683004","2017-02-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to encourage recycling of plastic cartons.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62766","62766"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683005","2017-02-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to page 16 of the UK Climate Change Risk Assessment 2017, published in January 2017, if she will publish the fundamental review of the UK's whole environmental policy framework.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62776","62776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683006","2017-02-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to the Government of Sudan on recent convictions of Christians in that country for spying and the sentences those people have received.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62800","62800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683007","2017-02-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of (a) the extent of and (b) who is responsible for growth in the level of violence in the Donbas region of Ukraine; and whether such violence constitutes a breach of the ceasefire agreement.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62742","62742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683008","2017-02-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his international counterparts on progress in the campaign against Daesh.","Biography information for Robert Courts","Robert Courts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62701","62701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683009","2017-02-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the strength of relations between India and the UK.","Biography information for Robert Courts","Robert Courts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62693","62693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683010","2017-02-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to Kenyan authorities on the safety and whereabouts of Dong Samuel Luak and Aggrey Idri, who have been missing from Nairobi since 23 and 24 January 2017 respectively.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62684","62684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683011","2017-02-06","Department of Health","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidance his Department issues to clinical commissioning groups on implementation of quality statements made by NICE published in Quality Standards.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62654","62654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683012","2017-02-03","Department of Health","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information his Department holds on when the UK Health Forum project into the costs to the NHS and to social care from air pollution will (a) conclude and (b) publish its findings.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62660","62660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683013","2017-02-03","Department of Health","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the current level of treatment for people diagnosed with cerebral palsy.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62663","62663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683014","2017-02-03","Department of Health","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent steps his Department has taken to improve recruitment of nurses to the NHS.","Biography information for Oliver Colvile","Oliver Colvile","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62676","62676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683015","2017-02-03","Department of Health","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect of better use of pharmacies on the healthcare provision to local communities.","Biography information for Oliver Colvile","Oliver Colvile","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62677","62677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683016","2017-02-03","Department of Health","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much of the funding that has been allocated to the GP Development Programme remains unspent.","Biography information for Oliver Colvile","Oliver Colvile","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62678","62678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683017","2017-02-03","Department of Health","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people over the age of 60 have been diagnosed with an eating disorder in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62760","62760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683018","2017-02-03","Department of Health","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when Sqalamine will be available for the treatment of Parkinson's disease on the NHS.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62761","62761"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683019","2017-02-06","Department of Health","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the performance of Capita in administrating the National Dental Performers' List; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62714","62714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683020","2017-02-06","Department of Health","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government on changes to the business rates system.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62719","62719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683021","2017-02-06","Department of Health","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will provide the NHS with extra funding to cover any additional costs arising from proposed changes to the business rates system.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62720","62720"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683022","2017-02-06","Department of Health","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that people with muscle-wasting conditions in (a) Coventry and (b) the UK have access to neuromuscular care advice close to their home; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62729","62729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683023","2017-02-06","Department of Health","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of proposed changes to business rates on NHS hospital and GP practice services in England.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62721","62721"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683024","2017-02-06","Department of Health","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to increase organ donation.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62726","62726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683025","2017-02-06","Department of Health","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people died while on waiting lists for organ donation in each year since 2011.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62727","62727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683026","2017-02-06","Department of Health","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to reduce the number of people who die while on the waiting list for organ donation.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62728","62728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683027","2017-02-03","Department of Health","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he expects NICE to conclude its deliberations on the use of Vismodegib; what the cost is of providing Vismodegib for a 12 month period; and what estimate he has made of the number of people who could benefit from Vismodegib being approved by NICE.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62758","62758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683028","2017-02-03","Department of Health","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he expects NICE to conclude its deliberations on the use of Regorafenib; what the cost is of providing Regorafenib for a 12 month period; and what estimate he has made of the number of people who could benefit from Regorafenib being approved by NICE.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62757","62757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683029","2017-02-03","Department of Health","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he expects NICE to conclude its deliberations on the use of Clofarabine; what the cost is of providing Clofarabine for a 12 month period; and what estimate he has made of the number of people who could benefit from Clofarabine being approved by NICE.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62755","62755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683030","2017-02-03","Department of Health","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he expects NICE to conclude its deliberations on the use of Nelarabine; what the cost is of providing Nelarabine for a 12 month period; and what estimate he has made of the number of people who could benefit from Nelarabine being approved by NICE.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62756","62756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683031","2017-02-06","Department of Health","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on access to care of any requirement for two forms of identification to be provided before NHS treatment is given to a patient.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62740","62740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683032","2017-02-03","Department of Health","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he expects NICE to conclude its deliberations on the use of Vandetanib; what the cost is of providing Vandetanib for a 12 month period; and what estimate he has made of the number of people who could benefit from Vandetanib being approved by NICE.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62751","62751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683033","2017-02-03","Department of Health","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he expects NICE to conclude its deliberations on the use of Sunitinib; what the cost is of providing Sunitinib for a 12 month period; and what estimate he has made of the number of people who could benefit from Sunitinib being approved by NICE.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62752","62752"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683034","2017-02-03","Department of Health","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he expects NICE to conclude its deliberations on the use of Eribulin; what the cost is of providing Eribulin for a 12 month period; and what estimate he has made of the number of people who could benefit from Eribulin being approved by NICE.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62753","62753"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683035","2017-02-03","Department of Health","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he expects NICE to conclude its deliberations on the use of Pertuzumab; what the cost is of providing Pertuzumab for a 12 month period; and what estimate he has made of the number of people who could benefit from Pertuzumab being approved by NICE.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62754","62754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683036","2017-02-03","Department of Health","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that new medicines introduced on the NHS are (a) medically and (b) cost effective.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62765","62765"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683037","2017-02-03","Department of Health","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many meetings his Department has had with (a) NHS England, (b) professional bodies and (c) stakeholder bodies to discuss the creation of a benchmark price for IVF.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62750","62750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683038","2017-02-03","Department of Health","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people have been living with a diagnosis of epilepsy in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62762","62762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683039","2017-02-03","Cabinet Office","2017-02-01","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people have died as a result of symptoms relating to epilepsy in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62763","62763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683040","2017-02-03","Department of Health","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the cost to the NHS has been of treating people with a diagnosis of epilepsy in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62764","62764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683041","2017-02-03","Department of Health","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the timescale is for deciding and publishing the benchmark price for IVF.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62749","62749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683042","2017-02-03","Department of Health","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he was first told that NHS England proposed to close the congenital heart disease units operating in (a) Manchester, (b) Leicester and (c) at the Royal Brompton Hospital.","Biography information for Maria Caulfield","Maria Caulfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62794","62794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683043","2017-02-06","Department of Health","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many NHS staff are on the highest point of the Agenda for Change (AfC) payscale in (a) total and (b) each AfC pay band.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr   Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62812","62812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683044","2017-02-06","Department of Health","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the expenditure of NHS Property Services was in each financial year since 2013-14.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr   Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62813","62813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683045","2017-02-06","Department of Health","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the real terms change in salary has been, cumulatively by financial year up to and including 2015-16, for a member of NHS staff who was at the top of their payscale in 2009-10 measured by (a) retail price index and (b) consumer price index.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr   Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62814","62814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683046","2017-02-06","Department of Health","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the income of NHS Property Services was in each financial year since 2013-14.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr   Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62815","62815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683047","2017-02-03","Home Office","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make an assessment of the effectiveness of the Safe Bet Alliance in reducing crime relating to betting shops in Yorkshire.","Biography information for Holly Lynch","Holly Lynch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62774","62774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683048","2017-02-03","Home Office","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the effect of new betting shops on crime rates in their local areas.","Biography information for Holly Lynch","Holly Lynch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62775","62775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683049","2017-02-06","Home Office","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many designated road traffic officers there have been in each police force in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62769","62769"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683050","2017-02-03","Home Office","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans the Government has to review controls on the online sale of crossbows.","Biography information for Alex Chalk","Alex Chalk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62820","62820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683051","2017-02-06","Home Office","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to ensure that asylum seekers have access to decent housing in all areas of the UK.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62738","62738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683052","2017-02-06","Home Office","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 31 January 2017 to Question 61888, when the current lease arrangement for the site of Dungavel Immigration Removal Centre with the Crown is due to be reviewed.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62801","62801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683053","2017-02-06","Home Office","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many fixed penalty notices have been issued by each police force for road traffic offences in each quarter since 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62805","62805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683054","2017-02-06","Home Office","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of trends in the number of independent domestic violence advisers in England and Wales in each of the last 12 months; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62731","62731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683055","2017-02-06","Home Office","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to ensure the police represent the communities they serve in (a) rural and (b) other areas.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr   Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62715","62715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683056","2017-02-06","Home Office","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Answer of 18 February 2016 to Question 26302, how many people from the Kurdistan Region in Iraq (a) applied for and (b) were refused entry clearance to the UK from 1 October 2015 to 30 April 2016.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62732","62732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683057","2017-02-06","Home Office","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will respond to the report from Freedom From Torture, Proving Torture, on its findings on the level of certainty required by her Department for asylum seekers to prove that they have experienced torture.","Biography information for Dr Alasdair McDonnell","Dr Alasdair McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62671","62671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683058","2017-02-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many G4S electronic tags used in England and Wales to monitor curfews have been (a) lost, (b) broken and (c) removed in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62674","62674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683059","2017-02-03","Home Office","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Twelfth Report of the Home Affairs Committee, Asylum Accommodation, HC 637, what plans the Government has to include the number of asylum seekers in temporary accommodation in its future quarterly statistical releases.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62690","62690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683060","2017-02-03","Home Office","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Twelfth Report of the Home Affairs Committee, Asylum Accommodation, HC 637, whether the Government plans to publish the outcome of its assessment of the equality impacts of the Compass contracts.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62691","62691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683061","2017-02-03","Home Office","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 12 January 2017 to Question 58925, on G4S, whether her Department knew of plans to introduce body-worn cameras for welfare officers prior to that plan being implemented.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62704","62704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683062","2017-02-03","Home Office","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will hold a consultation on deciding the commissioning of asylum accommodation to regional strategic partnerships; and what steps she is taking to ensure that devolved governments have a role in deciding on arrangements for decentralising commissioning and ensuring a fair distribution of accommodation.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62661","62661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683063","2017-02-03","Home Office","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she has considered the potential merits of extending to people who are objecting to decisions to grant a sexual entertainment licence the same rights of appeal as people have who are objecting to alcohol and gambling licences.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62659","62659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683064","2017-02-03","Department for International Development","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to monitor and report on the effect of its nutrition investment programmes in low and middle income countries.","Biography information for Oliver Colvile","Oliver Colvile","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62702","62702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683065","2017-02-03","Department for International Development","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department has taken to encourage other donors to scale up nutrition investment programmes to tackle malnutrition in high-burden countries.","Biography information for Oliver Colvile","Oliver Colvile","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62703","62703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683066","2017-02-03","Department for International Development","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, who aid partner reference GB-1-205059 is whom her Department funds to provide food and winter items in Syria.","Biography information for John Glen","John Glen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62697","62697"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683067","2017-02-03","Department for International Development","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the effect of withdrawing aid to middle-income countries on achieving the sustainable development goal to end AIDS as a public health threat by 2030.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62679","62679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683068","2017-02-06","Department for International Development","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether her Department plans to contribute to the fund set up by the Government of the Netherlands in response to the changes to foreign aid for family planning announced by the new US Administration.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62673","62673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683069","2017-02-06","Department for International Development","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps the Government is taking to support the rebuilding of cranes in Hodeidah port in Yemen in order to ensure that food supplies can be imported into that country.","Biography information for Yvonne Fovargue","Yvonne Fovargue","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62802","62802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683070","2017-02-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the oral contribution of 24 January 2017, Official Report, column 144, on prison staff, if she will assess the effect of the reduction in accommodation fabric checks on (a) the incidence of self-harm and (b) maintaining order and security in prisons; and whether the outcomes set out in Prison Service Instruction 28/2011 and Prison Service Instruction 09/2016 have been achieved.","Biography information for Mr David Burrowes","Mr David Burrowes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62803","62803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683071","2017-02-03","Ministry of Justice","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners took their own lives by using an upended unsecured bedframe as a ligature point in each of the last five years in (a) HMP Northumberland, (b) private prisons, (c) public sector prisons; if she will take steps to ensure that all bedframes in prisons are securely fixed; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62785","62785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683072","2017-02-06","Cabinet Office","2017-02-01","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the Sixth Special Report (HC911), Tackling corruption overseas: Government Response to the Fourth Report from the International Development Committee, Session 2016-17, whether it remains the Government's policy to persuade the UK's Crown Dependencies to adopt public registers of beneficial ownership.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62682","62682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683073","2017-02-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the Sixth Special Report HC911, Tackling corruption overseas: Government Response to the Fourth Report from the International Development Committee, Session 2016-17, whether it remains the Government's policy to persuade the UK's Crown Dependencies to adopt public registers of beneficial ownership.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62683","62683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683074","2017-02-03","Ministry of Justice","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps she is taking to implement the recommendation in paragraph 87 of the Review of the Youth Justice system in England and Wales, published in December 2016, on reducing the period before which childhood convictions become spent.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Mrs Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62696","62696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683076","2017-02-06","Northern Ireland Office","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Education during preparation of the Government's Green Paper, Schools That Work For Everyone, published on 12 September 2016, on the work of the Integrated Education Fund; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Hugo Swire","Sir Hugo Swire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62746","62746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683077","2017-02-03","Department for Transport","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what guidance on the duration and timing of works Highways England gives to its contractors operating on the M3 between junctions 2 and 4a.","Biography information for Michael Gove","Michael Gove","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62644","62644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683078","2017-02-03","Department for Transport","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions he has had with the Mayor of London on roadworks in London; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Michael Gove","Michael Gove","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62645","62645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683079","2017-02-03","Department for Transport","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what limitations government guidance places on the duration and timing of roadworks in urban areas; and if he will introduce lane rental or other means of shortening the length of time required for such work.","Biography information for Michael Gove","Michael Gove","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62646","62646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683080","2017-02-03","Department for Transport","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of advanced quality partnership schemes between 2010 and 2016.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62664","62664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683081","2017-02-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, for what reason he has not yet published his Department's response to the consultation Parking reform: tackling unfair practices.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62666","62666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683082","2017-02-03","Department for Transport","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if it is his policy to ensure all car manufacturing companies provide consumers with appropriately detailed technical information when informing the owner of the vehicle they need to be serviced.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62667","62667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683083","2017-02-06","Department for Transport","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 31 January 2017 to Question 61887, on railways: industrial disputes, what steps he has taken to ensure that the dates of submission and conclusion of Southern Govia Thameslink Railway's existing force majeure claims are centrally recorded.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62734","62734"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683084","2017-02-06","Department for Transport","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what further steps the Government is taking to situate additional lighting and street furniture on the M6 Heysham link road to enhance road safety.","Biography information for David Morris","David Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62747","62747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683085","2017-02-06","Department for Transport","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 31 January 2017 to Question 61886, on railways: industrial disputes, what steps he has taken to record the amount of staff hours spent on Southern Southern Govia Thameslink Railway's current force majeure claims; and how many staff have worked on those claims to date.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62735","62735"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683086","2017-02-06","Department for Transport","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he expects the review of Southern Rail's performance to be completed; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62745","62745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683087","2017-02-06","Department for Transport","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 31 January 2017 to Question 61884, on railways: industrial disputes, what the value of each agreed claim was to the train-operating company in each instance.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62736","62736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683088","2017-02-08","Department for Transport","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what representations has he received from the motorsport industry on the scope of the Motor Insurance Directive (2009/13/EC) since the European Court of Justice ruling of September 2014, Damijan Vnuk v Zavarovalnica Triglav C-162/13, on insurance for motorised vehicles used off-road.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62816","62816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683089","2017-02-03","Department for Transport","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what power he has to intervene in respect of car park charges set by the rail franchise where the franchisee controls car parks adjacent to railway stations within their franchise area; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for James Cartlidge","James Cartlidge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62699","62699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683090","2017-02-03","Department for Transport","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect on passengers of recent changes to car park charges at franchisee controlled railway station car park on the Greater Anglia franchise route.","Biography information for James Cartlidge","James Cartlidge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62700","62700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683091","2017-02-03","Department for Transport","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what progress has been made in improving rail links to Stansted Airport; and what timescale he has set to ensure that those links are improved.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62706","62706"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683092","2017-02-03","Department for Transport","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he expects to receive the initial industry advice from the Rail Delivery Group; and if he will publish that advice.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62707","62707"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683093","2017-02-06","Department for Transport","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether Peter Wilkinson, when engaged in any capacity by his Department, has been involved in assessing franchise bids by Govia Thameslink Railway while (a) providing consultancy advice for Govia Thameslink Railway and (b) holding shares in any company providing consultancy advice for Govia Thameslink Railway.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62685","62685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683094","2017-02-03","HM Treasury","2017-02-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will respond to EDM 572, Frequent Flyer Levy campaign.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62791","62791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683095","2017-02-03","Department for Transport","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department's aviation strategy will set out how the Government plans to support the development of airports with spare capacity to their maximum potential up to 2030 or before Heathrow expansion is complete.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62792","62792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683096","2017-02-03","Department for Transport","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what funds the Government has provided to local authorities for the maintenance of Home Zones.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62772","62772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683097","2017-02-03","Department for Transport","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many Home Zones have been established in England since 2000; and where those zones are located.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62773","62773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683098","2017-02-03","Department for Transport","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what his policy is on the establishment of new Home Zones.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62770","62770"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683099","2017-02-03","Department for Transport","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of establishing more Home Zones.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62771","62771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683100","2017-02-08","Department for Transport","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the European Court of Justice ruling of September 2014, Damijan Vnuk v Zavarovalnica Triglav C-162/13 on insurance for motorised vehicles used off-road, if he will make an assessment of ways in which the effect of the scope of the Motor Insurance Directive (2009/13/EC) could be limited to the use of vehicles in the context of traffic as defined in the Road Traffic Act 1998.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62817","62817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683101","2017-02-08","Department for Transport","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the potential change in the level of motor insurance premiums as a result of the European Court of Justice ruling of September 2014, Damijan Vnuk v Zavarovalnica Triglav C-162/13, on insurance for motorised vehicles used off-road.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62818","62818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683103","2017-02-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effect of recent trends in inflation on low income families with children; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62698","62698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683104","2017-02-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answers of 17 January 2017 to Question 59783 and 59784, on personal independence payment: motability, what the (a) estimated cost was to his Department of answering those Questions, (b) maximum amount his Department will spend on an Answer, (c) average cost to his Department per Answer and (d) maximum and minimum amount spent on answering a Question was in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62739","62739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683105","2017-02-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Answer of 28 July 2015 to Question 7097, whether his Department holds information on the proportion of Association of British Bookmakers member betting shops which have been deemed unsafe for single manning.","Biography information for Holly Lynch","Holly Lynch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62811","62811"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683106","2017-02-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what his most recent estimate is of the number of workers who will automatic enrolment in pension schemes by 2018.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62799","62799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683107","2017-02-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what discussions he has had with the Chancellor of the Exchequer on uprating the state pension for UK pensioners living in the EU after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Ian Blackford","Ian Blackford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62778","62778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683108","2017-02-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what his policy is on maintaining the triple lock on the state pension.","Biography information for Ian Blackford","Ian Blackford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62779","62779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683109","2017-02-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on nuclear safety and existing nuclear safety regimes in the UK of the UK leaving Euratom.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62670","62670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683110","2017-02-03","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment the Government has made of the effectiveness of the work of the Global Innovation Lab for Climate Finance in driving investment in developing countries.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62662","62662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683111","2017-02-03","Department for International Trade","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what assessment he has made of the level of interest among small and medium-sized enterprises in the Great.gov.uk digital platform.","Biography information for Robert Courts","Robert Courts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62768","62768"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683112","2017-02-03","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what recent discussions he has had with the main opposition parties in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62788","62788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683113","2017-02-03","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what steps is he taking to ensure that each of the four main political parties in Northern Ireland continue to be consulted on his Department's work while the Assembly is dissolved.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62789","62789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683114","2017-02-03","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what assessment he has made of the cost to the public purse of the European Medicines Agency physically leaving its current location in the UK.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62665","62665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/683387","2017-02-07","Department of Health","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will permit tobacco products that are proven to be less harmful to health than cigarettes to be advertised.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 908629","908629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685527","2017-02-07","Department of Health","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that every hospital that has a maternity unit has a bereavement suite.","Biography information for Will Quince","Will Quince","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 908638","908638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685678","2017-02-07","Department of Health","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure safe staffing levels in the NHS.","Biography information for Steven Paterson","Steven Paterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 908637","908637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685679","2017-02-07","Department of Health","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department has taken to reduce the number of patients with lung disease admitted to accident and emergency departments.","Biography information for Mrs Flick Drummond","Mrs Flick Drummond","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 908641","908641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/685680","2017-02-07","Department of Health","2017-02-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that NHS bodies make timely payments to small business providers.","Biography information for Mr Steve Baker","Steve Baker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 908645","908645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682228","2017-02-02","Attorney General","2017-01-31","To ask the Attorney General, which persons not employed by the Law Officers' Departments hold security passes entitling them to enter the Law Officers' Departments premises.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62528","62528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682229","2017-02-02","Cabinet Office","2017-01-31","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, which persons not employed by his Department and its agencies hold security passes entitling them to enter his Department's premises.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62529","62529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682231","2017-02-03","HM Treasury","2017-01-31","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he plans to publish the results of the HM Revenue and Customs consultation on sanctions for tobacco duty fraud, which closed on 28 August 2015.","Biography information for Dr James Davies","Dr James Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62443","62443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682232","2017-02-03","HM Treasury","2017-01-31","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what criteria he is using to determine which soft drinks will be subject to the soft drinks industry levy announced in the Budget 2016.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62470","62470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682233","2017-02-03","HM Treasury","2017-01-31","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the potential revenue to the Exchequer from the proposed soft drinks industry levy.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62471","62471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682234","2017-02-03","HM Treasury","2017-01-31","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment he has made of the possible negative effect on businesses of the proposed soft drinks industry levy.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62472","62472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682235","2017-02-03","HM Treasury","2017-01-31","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what distributional analysis his Department has undertaken of the impact of tax-free childcare.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62469","62469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682236","2017-02-03","HM Treasury","2017-01-31","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the point of revenue maximisation on tobacco excise.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62474","62474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682237","2017-02-03","HM Treasury","2017-01-31","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect on the UK economy of the freeze in duty on spirits announced in the Budget 2016.","Biography information for Anne-Marie Trevelyan","Mrs Anne-Marie Trevelyan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62488","62488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682238","2017-02-02","HM Treasury","2017-01-31","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, which persons not employed by his Department hold security passes entitling them to enter his Department's premises.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62545","62545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682239","2017-02-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the reported agreement between the Libyan Central Bank and the Government of National Accord and its effect on sanctions; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62595","62595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682240","2017-02-02","HM Treasury","2017-01-31","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the total amount of Gaddafi family assets frozen in the UK.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62598","62598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682241","2017-02-03","HM Treasury","2017-01-31","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate his Department has made of the cost to the public purse of tax-free childcare in each year of this Parliament.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62615","62615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682242","2017-02-03","HM Treasury","2017-01-31","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the value is of the assets of the Gaddafi family that are frozen in the UK.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62636","62636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682243","2017-02-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what information his Department holds on whether receipts and revenue flows accruing from Libya's renewed oil production have been deposited or held in UK banking and financial institutions; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62631","62631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682244","2017-02-02","Church Commissioners","2017-01-31","To ask the right hon. Member for Meriden, representing the Church Commissioners, which persons not employed by the Church Commissioners hold security passes entitling them to enter the Church Commissioners premises.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62530","62530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682245","2017-02-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, which persons not employed by his Department and its agencies hold security passes entitling them to enter his Department's premises.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62531","62531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682246","2017-02-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what guidance his Department has issued to local authorities on engaging with groups with particular protected characteristics covered by the Public Sector Equality Duty when drawing up proposals for a combined authority.","Biography information for Mrs Flick Drummond","Mrs Flick Drummond","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62583","62583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682247","2017-02-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what guidance his Department has issued to local authorities on their engagement with local communities when drawing up proposals for a combined authority.","Biography information for Mrs Flick Drummond","Mrs Flick Drummond","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62584","62584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682248","2017-02-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what progress he has made on building one million new homes by 2020 since the announcement by the Prime Minister on 12 October 2015.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62610","62610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682249","2017-02-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will estimate the proportion of land designated as greenbelt in each local authority area in the North West.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62480","62480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682250","2017-02-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of exempting local community energy projects from business rates.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62444","62444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682251","2017-02-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answers of 9 January 2017 to Question 58515 and of 18 January 2017 to Question 59298, what plans he has to equalise the payment ratio of new homes bonuses in two-tier local authority areas to help fund social care; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen McPartland","Stephen McPartland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62435","62435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682252","2017-02-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will allow authorities to apply discretionary measures with regard to business rates levied on hospitals and GP surgeries.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62419","62419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682253","2017-02-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, for what reason the proposed new business rates system does not include local authority discretion on business rates levied on hospitals and GP surgeries.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62420","62420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682254","2017-02-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the potential change to the costs of NHS operations in (a) Birmingham, Selly Oak constituency, (b) Birmingham and (c) the West Midlands as a result of proposed changes to the business rates system.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62421","62421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682255","2017-02-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Health on changes to the business rates system.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62422","62422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682256","2017-02-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the proposed increase in business rates for NHS hospitals, GP surgeries and other NHS services on the provision of adult social care.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62423","62423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682257","2017-02-02","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate she has made of the number of digitally excluded people resident in Hemsworth constituency; and what assessment she has made of the effects of digital exclusion on their capacity to bank online safely and effectively.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62464","62464"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682258","2017-02-02","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps her Department is taking to promote interest in fencing.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62635","62635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682259","2017-02-02","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, which persons not employed by her Department and its agencies hold security passes entitling them to enter her Department's premises.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62532","62532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682260","2017-02-02","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to her Department's news story of 22 December 2016, how the £440 million made available for superfast rural broadband will be (a) allocated between and (b) managed by local authorities.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62521","62521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682261","2017-02-02","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate her Department has made of how many premises in Coventry South constituency do not have access to superfast broadband.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62498","62498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682262","2017-02-02","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 12 December 2016 to Question 56187, what the budget is for the Iraq Historic Allegations Team in (a) 2017-18 and (b) 2018-19.","Biography information for Sir Henry Bellingham","Sir Henry Bellingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62501","62501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682263","2017-02-02","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what criteria underpinned the decision not to make public the fact that the 2016 Demonstration and Shakedown Operation exercise had not been completed as planned and that the Trident D5 II missile launched by HMS Vanguard had not completed its test as planned.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62565","62565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682264","2017-02-02","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how soon after he took office was the Prime Minister informed by his Department that the Trident D5 II missile launched as part of the 2016 Demonstration and Shakedown Operation exercise had not completed its test as planned.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62561","62561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682265","2017-02-02","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what information his Department holds on the (a) nature and (b) incidence of faults in the navigation controls on the Trident D5 II missiles.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62563","62563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682266","2017-02-02","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the Inertial Guidance System on board the Trident D5 II missile was tested during the 2016 Demonstration and Shakedown exercise.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62564","62564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682267","2017-02-02","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when after the 2016 Demonstration and Shakedown Operation exercise did he advise the former Prime Minister that the Trident D5 II missile launched by HMS Vanguard had not completed its test as planned.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62559","62559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682268","2017-02-02","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when after the 2016 Demonstration and Shakedown Operation exercise was he advised that the Trident D5 II missile launched by HMS Vanguard had not completed its test as planned.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62560","62560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682269","2017-02-02","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the age was of the Trident D5 II missile that was launched but unable to complete the testing as part of the 2016 Demonstration and Shakedown Operation exercise.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62556","62556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682270","2017-02-02","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the issue that led to the Trident D5 II missile not being able to complete its testing after being launched as part of the 2016 Demonstration and Shakedown Operation exercise has now been identified.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62557","62557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682271","2017-02-02","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, who briefed the Prime Minister that a Trident D5 II missile launched as part of the 2016 Demonstration and Shakedown Operation exercise had not completed its test as planned.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62558","62558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682272","2017-02-03","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to support the liberation of East Mosul; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62637","62637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682273","2017-02-03","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which persons not employed by his Department and its agencies hold security passes entitling them to enter his Department's premises.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62604","62604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682274","2017-02-03","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 26 January 2017 to Question 61198, on armed forces, when his Department's policy was changed not to release that information.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62605","62605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682275","2017-02-03","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many full-time, non-reservist (a) doctors and (b) nurses are employed by (i) the Army and (ii) his Department.","Biography information for Will Quince","Will Quince","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62599","62599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682276","2017-02-02","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to paragraph 2.9 of the National Security Strategy and Strategic Defence and Security Review 2015 - First Annual Report 2016, published in December 2016, and his oral evidence to the Defence Select Committee of 31 January 2017, for what reason the expected start date of sea trials by HMS Queen Elizabeth has changed.","Biography information for Mrs Flick Drummond","Mrs Flick Drummond","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62620","62620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682277","2017-02-02","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will publish the terms of reference for the Army's Junior Entry Review; when he expects that review to report; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62585","62585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682278","2017-02-02","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he was part of the discussion in which it was decided not to inform Parliament that the Trident D5 II missile launched as part of the 2016 Demonstration and Shakedown Operation exercise had not completed its test as planned.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62562","62562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682279","2017-02-03","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 19 January 2017 to Question 59855, what mechanisms his Department has put in place to monitor how many of the jobs announced by Boeing at the Farnborough Air Show are created.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62606","62606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682280","2017-02-02","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to ensure that members of the armed forces and their families are not accommodated in hotels.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62550","62550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682281","2017-02-02","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, during which month he expects HMS Queen Elizabeth to depart Rosyth for her first sea trials.","Biography information for Mrs Flick Drummond","Mrs Flick Drummond","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62463","62463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682282","2017-02-02","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which British officers have been appointed to NATO by (a) rank, (b) responsibility and (c) location in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62437","62437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682283","2017-02-02","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much his Department has spent on identifying and repairing the fault that led to the Trident D5 II missile not being able to complete its test after being launched as part of the 2016 Demonstration and Shakedown Operation exercise.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62522","62522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682284","2017-02-02","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what work has been carried out by the manufacturers of other Trident D5 II missiles to prevent reoccurrence since the missile was unable to complete its test after being launched as part of the 2016 Demonstration and Shakedown Operation exercise.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62523","62523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682285","2017-02-03","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which British Officers were attached to the UN by appointments and ranks in the last two years.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62468","62468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682286","2017-02-03","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which contractors are contracted by his Department to manufacture boots for the armed forces.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62484","62484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682287","2017-02-03","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which prime contractors are contracted by his Department to manufacture Personal Clothing System garments.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62485","62485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682288","2017-02-03","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, for what reasons his Department does not restrict the geographical location of manufacture for Personal Clothing System garments.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62483","62483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682289","2017-02-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions the Government has had with Iraqi and Kurdish authorities on the withdrawal of Kurdish forces from lands they have captured in northern Iraq; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62402","62402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682290","2017-02-02","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what mechanisms are in place to support (a) female service personnel and (b) female veterans with mental wellbeing (i) during and (ii) after military service.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62430","62430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682291","2017-02-02","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many women serving in the tri-service regular and reserve forces have accessed medical services in relation to concerns about their own mental health in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62431","62431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682292","2017-02-02","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the establishment is of the HQ Royal Air Force by rank and responsibility.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62405","62405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682293","2017-02-02","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the establishment is of the HQ Royal Navy by rank and responsibility.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62406","62406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682294","2017-02-03","Department for Education","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to ensure that children who are eligible for free school meals are registered to receive them.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62424","62424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682295","2017-02-03","Department for Education","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate her Department has made of the number of children in receipt of 15 hours free childcare who will be ineligible for receipt of the further 30 hours free childcare.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62482","62482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682296","2017-02-20","Department for Education","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent discussions she has had with (a) the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland and (b) her other cabinet colleagues on the principles of integrated education.","Biography information for Sir Hugo Swire","Sir Hugo Swire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62527","62527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682297","2017-02-03","Department for Education","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she plans to expand the International Teacher Recruitment Strategy; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62489","62489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682298","2017-02-03","Department for Education","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the trends of expected literacy levels for seven year olds in England and Wales in each of the last five years; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62477","62477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682299","2017-02-03","Department for Education","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 11 May 2016 to Question HL8119, how much of the £300 million (a) set aside to support schools to convert and support sponsors to turn around failing schools and (b) to support strong and effective multi-academy trusts to grow and improve has been (i) spent by her Department and (ii) returned to the public purse.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62481","62481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682300","2017-02-02","Department for Education","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when her Department plans to provide approval for the proposed amalgamation of College House Junior School and Meadow Lane Infant School.","Biography information for Anna Soubry","Anna Soubry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62459","62459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682301","2017-02-03","Department for Education","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 30 January 2017 to Question 61767, on social services: children, if she will set out how much funding each organisation or person listed has received from the public purse in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62441","62441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682302","2017-02-03","Department for Education","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of where in her Department's table of 151 local authority funding positions West Sussex will rank in each of the next three years.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62442","62442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682303","2017-02-03","Department for Education","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the trends of the difference in attainment of phonics standards between boys and girls aged seven in England and Wales in each of the last five years; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62475","62475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682304","2017-02-03","Department for Education","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the total spend on literacy programmes for children under seven in  in England and Wales in each of the last five years; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62476","62476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682305","2017-02-02","Department for Education","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will take steps to include a module on safeguarding mental health in the national curriculum.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62512","62512"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682306","2017-02-02","Department for Education","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when she plans to publish the consultation on flexible admission to schools for summer-born children.","Biography information for Mr Edward Vaizey","Mr Edward Vaizey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62515","62515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682307","2017-02-02","Department for Education","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which persons not employed by her Department and its agencies hold security passes entitling them to enter her Department's premises.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62533","62533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682308","2017-02-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, which persons not employed by her Department and its agencies hold security passes entitling them to enter her Department's premises.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62534","62534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682309","2017-02-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to control bird flu since the recent outbreak of that virus.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62549","62549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682310","2017-02-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to encourage firms to (a) recycle packaging and (b) make unsold food available to charities for distribution.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62465","62465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682311","2017-02-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, which Ministers in her Department are responsible for the corporate governance and regulation of the Forestry Commission.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62436","62436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682312","2017-02-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she plans to take to prevent the use of gin traps; if she will review the penalties available for those who use or possess such traps; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62524","62524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682313","2017-02-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when she plans to publish the 25-year plan for the environment.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62428","62428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682314","2017-02-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when she plans to publish the 25-year plan for food and farming.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62429","62429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682315","2017-02-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many times he has met the Chief Minister of Gibraltar since 23 June 2016.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62494","62494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682317","2017-02-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to tackle the situation in Umm al-Hiran, South Israel.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62456","62456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682318","2017-02-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representation he has made to the Israeli Government on the protection of homes of villagers in Umm al-Hiran.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62452","62452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682319","2017-02-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions her Department has had with her counterparts in African and South American countries on the preservation of monkeys and apes.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62553","62553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682320","2017-02-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had on the cost of refurbishing the Commonwealth Secretary-General's residence; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62572","62572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682321","2017-02-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department takes to provide accountability and oversight of public money spent by the Commonwealth Secretariat.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62573","62573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682322","2017-02-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, which persons not employed by his Department and its agencies hold security passes entitling them to enter his Department's premises.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62602","62602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682323","2017-02-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Written Statement of 21 July 2016, HCWS125, whether his Department has undertaken an assessment of whether the Saudi-led coalition in Yemen has committed any breaches of international humanitarian law.","Biography information for Dr Alasdair McDonnell","Dr Alasdair McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62626","62626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682324","2017-02-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what information he holds on how the EU is monitoring the resumption of Libyan oil exports from the ports of Ras Lanuf, Zuwetina, Es Sidra and Brega.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62633","62633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682325","2017-02-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions his Department has had with the Libyan Deputy Prime Minister on the formation of a committee to assess the case of victims of IRA terrorism; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62634","62634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682326","2017-02-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will place in the Library a list of public consultations, White Papers and other documents his Department plans to publish to assist the UK in making effective the Government's plans for the UK to leave the EU within the two year timetable from the triggering of Article 50 of the Lisbon Treaty.","Biography information for Michael Gove","Michael Gove","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62504","62504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682327","2017-02-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the Israeli Government on protecting the human rights of Bedouin villagers living in Israel; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62587","62587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682328","2017-02-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions his Department has had with Libyan Deputy Prime Minister, Ahmed Maiteeq, regarding the formation of a committee to study the case of victims of IRA terrorism; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62597","62597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682329","2017-02-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what information he holds on how the EU monitors the resumption of Libyan oil exports from the ports of Ras Lanuf, Zuwetina, Es Sidra and Brega; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62596","62596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682330","2017-02-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to support the cessation of the demolition of the village of Umm al-Hiran in southern Israel.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62588","62588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682331","2017-02-02","Department of Health","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to raise awareness of the signs and symptoms of heart valve disease among people aged over 65 to ensure early diagnosis of that disease.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62589","62589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682332","2017-02-02","Department of Health","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of rolling out routine stethoscope checks by a trained primary care healthcare professional for peopled aged over 65 to ensure the effective diagnosis of heart valve disease.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62590","62590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682333","2017-02-02","Department of Health","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 23 December 2016 to Question 59052, for what reasons the decision was taken by his Department in 2015 to begin funding Overseas Development Assistance; from which Departmental budget such funding was taken; and how much has been so spent to date.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62591","62591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/682334","2017-02-02","Department of Health","2017-01-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that superbugs do not make cancer untreatable.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 62546","62546"
