"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758039","2017-09-11","Cabinet Office","2017-09-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much his Department paid to the Behavioural Insights Team in each year since 2014.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9181","9181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758040","2017-09-11","Cabinet Office","2017-09-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will make an assessment of the merits of including housing associations in the list of bodies subject to freedom of information requests in response to the Grenfell Tower tragedy.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9122","9122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758041","2017-09-11","Cabinet Office","2017-09-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what model the Boundary Commission will employ in its new review of constituency boundaries.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9109","9109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758042","2017-09-11","Cabinet Office","2017-09-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what model the Boundary Commission will employ in its new review of constituency boundaries in Wales.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9111","9111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758043","2017-09-11","Cabinet Office","2017-09-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to his oral contribution of 5 September 2016, Official Report, column 65, when the Joint Ministerial Committee will next meet.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9054","9054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758044","2017-09-11","Cabinet Office","2017-09-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to his oral contribution of 5 September 2016, Official Report, column 65, what mechanisms are being considered as an alternative to the Joint Ministerial Committee; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9055","9055"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758045","2017-09-11","Cabinet Office","2017-09-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the total cost was of the privatisation of the Behavioural Insights Team.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9199","9199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758046","2017-09-11","Cabinet Office","2017-09-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the total cost to his Department was of (a) legal advice and (b) consultants with regard the privatisation of the Behavioural Insights Team.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9200","9200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758047","2017-09-11","Cabinet Office","2017-09-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many staff external to the Civil Service have been seconded into the Behavioural Insights Team and from which firms in each year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9201","9201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758048","2017-09-11","Cabinet Office","2017-09-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many hours civil servants of his Department spent on the privatisation of the Behavioural Insights Team; and what the estimated cost was of staff time spent on that privatisation.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9202","9202"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758049","2017-09-11","Cabinet Office","2017-09-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether (a) he or (b) officials of his Department were aware that after privatisation the Behavioural Insights Team planned to (a) open an office in Singapore and (b) operate in any other tax haven.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9204","9204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758050","2017-09-11","Cabinet Office","2017-09-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much each Government department is charged for using the Government's Verify scheme.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9192","9192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758051","2017-09-11","Cabinet Office","2017-09-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what oversight his Department has over the work of the Behavioural Insights Team relating to its (a) remit and (b) clients.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9193","9193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758052","2017-09-11","Cabinet Office","2017-09-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when his Department plans to publish its annual report and accounts for 2016-17.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9194","9194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758053","2017-09-11","HM Treasury","2017-09-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many staff of HM Revenue and Customs are employed in monitoring whether undertakings in respect of public access to heritage assets that have been exempted from inheritance tax and capital gains tax are adhered to.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9294","9294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758054","2017-09-11","HM Treasury","2017-09-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when the Government plans to ratify the World Health Organisation Framework Convention on Tobacco Control Protocol to Eliminate Illicit Trade in Tobacco Products.","Biography information for Bob Blackman","Bob Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9241","9241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758055","2017-09-11","HM Treasury","2017-09-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 18 July 2017 to Question 3921, by what process he plans to assess the balance of pay referred to in that Answer for pay awards for public sector workers who are not covered by a pay review body.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9206","9206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758056","2017-09-11","HM Treasury","2017-09-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 24 July 2017 to HL1074, whether the estimates for average employer pension contributions used in the table given in that Answer were based on (a) all public sector and private sector employees or (b) public sector and private sector employees who are enrolled in a pension scheme.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9207","9207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758057","2017-09-11","HM Treasury","2017-09-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to section 8 of his Department's Civil Service Pay Guidance 2017-18, published on 27 April 2017, what recruitment and retention-related pay flexibilities have been granted since 2012 for (a) non-consolidated performance related pay pot adjustments and (b) targeted consolidated increases; and to which core departments and non-departmental public bodies those flexibilities have been granted.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9209","9209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758058","2017-09-11","HM Treasury","2017-09-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment he has made of the effect of stamp duty levels on the housing market; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9056","9056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758059","2017-09-11","HM Treasury","2017-09-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of abolishing the Class 2 National Insurance category on the living standards of people earning under £6,000 a year.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9080","9080"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758060","2017-09-11","HM Treasury","2017-09-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people in (a) Dwyfor Meirionnydd constituency, (b) Wales and (c) the UK earn under £6,000 a year and make voluntary national insurance contributions through Class 2.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9081","9081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758061","2017-09-11","HM Treasury","2017-09-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department takes to provide (a) information on its services in British Sign Language (BSL) and (b) correspondence in BSL to people whose principal language is BSL.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9012","9012"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758062","2017-09-11","HM Treasury","2017-09-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department has taken to ensure that the terms and conditions of insurance policies are drafted in plan English to facilitate consumer understanding.","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9036","9036"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758063","2017-09-11","HM Treasury","2017-09-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, by what date the free software promised by HM Revenue and Customs for smaller companies to comply with Making Tax Digital will be made available.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9026","9026"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758064","2017-09-12","HM Treasury","2017-09-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many (a) buildings, (b) estates, (c) parklands and (d) objects with national (i) scientific and (ii) historic interest have been granted exemption from inheritance tax and capital gains tax in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9174","9174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758065","2017-09-11","Department for Transport","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the total economic benefit to each region from expansion at Heathrow Airport.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9106","9106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758066","2017-09-11","HM Treasury","2017-09-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of inheritance tax and capital gains tax exemptions for heritage assets.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9162","9162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758067","2017-09-11","HM Treasury","2017-09-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of granting people earning less than £6,000 a year the same pension rights that come with Class 4 contributions after the abolition of the Class 2 bracket.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9097","9097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758068","2017-09-11","HM Treasury","2017-09-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of retaining the Class 2 category of national insurance contributions.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9098","9098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758069","2017-09-11","HM Treasury","2017-09-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make it his policy to issue remit letters to the chairs of the pay review bodies for the 2018-19 pay round before the 2017 Autumn Budget.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9141","9141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758070","2017-09-11","HM Treasury","2017-09-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many exemptions from inheritance tax and capital gains tax have been withdrawn as a result of a failure to meet undertakings to (a) look after the item, (b) make the item available to the public and (c) keep the item in the UK in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9165","9165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758071","2017-09-11","HM Treasury","2017-09-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when the Government plans to bring forward legislative proposals to implement the requirement in the Illicit Trade Protocol to license tobacco manufacturing machinery.","Biography information for Bob Blackman","Bob Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9195","9195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758072","2017-09-11","HM Treasury","2017-09-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will remove the pay cap for public sector workers and ensure that the Barnett formula for the devolved institutions is reflected in that decision.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9255","9255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758073","2017-09-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will (a) publish communications he has had with the British Board of Agrément on the failure of cladding systems in high winds and (b) set out his Department's plans to deal with problems described in such communications.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9246","9246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758074","2017-09-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much his Department paid to the Behavioural Insights Team in each year since 2014.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9182","9182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758075","2017-09-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many new (a) local authority social lettings and (b) registered social landlord lettings in England were taken up by (i) UK nationals, (ii) EU nationals and (iii) non-EU nationals in (A) 2015-16 and (B) 2016-17.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9151","9151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758076","2017-09-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to improve the building standards of older council stock properties.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9152","9152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758077","2017-09-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he plans to publish the responses to the Government's consultation exercise on the implementation of a ban on letting agency fees paid by tenants.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9118","9118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758078","2017-09-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what discussions he has had with local authorities on the effect of the UK leaving the EU on (a) the delivery of child social services, (b) the delivery of adult social services and (c) local authority workforce levels.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9147","9147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758079","2017-09-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the number of tower blocks over 30 metres high which are (a) fire safe and (b) unsafe.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9167","9167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758080","2017-09-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what total amount of funding has been requested from central government by local authorities, housing associations and other organisations responsible for the management of high-rise residential accommodation for remedial work since the Grenfell Tower fire.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9225","9225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758081","2017-09-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many councils have made inquiries to the Government about financial assistance for remedial work on high-rise residential buildings in their area since the Grenfell Tower fire.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9226","9226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758082","2017-09-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many residential units were granted planning permission in each financial year since 2000-01.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9228","9228"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758083","2017-09-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, which Ministers of his Department have requested funds from the public purse for improvements to their Ministerial offices.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9149","9149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758084","2017-09-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will publish a breakdown of all office improvement costs at his Department's offices at 2 Marsham Street in each year since 2015.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9150","9150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758085","2017-09-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether it remains his policy to phase out the revenue support grant by 2020.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9116","9116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758086","2017-09-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the planned timetable is for bringing forward proposals to ban letting agency fees paid by tenants.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9117","9117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758087","2017-09-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many affordable residential pitches have been (a) started and (b) completed in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9129","9129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758088","2017-09-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many (a) starts and (b) completions have occurred for Gypsy and Traveller sites under the Affordable Homes Programme 2015-18 in each local authority area.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9130","9130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758089","2017-09-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment of need for Traveller sites has been made for each minimum geography area for each of the next five years.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9131","9131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758090","2017-09-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what plans he has for new council housing deals with local authorities to provide more social housing.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9142","9142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758091","2017-09-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what plans he has put in place to encourage local councils to build new fixed-term social houses with an automatic right-to-buy.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9143","9143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758092","2017-09-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what plans he has to conduct a full review of the business rates system.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9030","9030"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758093","2017-09-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he makes of the adequacy of the number of transit pitches made available to Travellers in (a) England and (b) South Gloucestershire.","Biography information for Jack Lopresti","Jack Lopresti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8996","8996"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758094","2017-09-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many and what proportion of businesses eligible for business rates transitional relief have received that relief in the last 12 months for which figures are available.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9016","9016"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758095","2017-09-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department takes to provide (a) information on its services in British Sign Language (BSL) and (b) correspondence in BSL to people whose principal language is BSL.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9000","9000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758096","2017-09-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much has been received by the London Borough of Barnet from the Housing Infrastructure Fund; and which projects have been so funded.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9210","9210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758097","2017-09-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much each local authority was allocated in Discretionary Housing Payment funding in each of the last three years; and how much each authority has spent from that funding in each such year.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9287","9287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758098","2017-09-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that Discretionary Housing Payments are being spent for the intended purpose by local authorities.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9288","9288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758099","2017-09-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Prime Minister's letter relating to the Grenfell Tower Inquiry of 15 August 2017 to the right hon. Sir Martin Moore-Bick, how much time has been allocated for the Housing Minister to meet and hear from as many social housing tenants as possible; how long that exercise will last for; and how findings from that exercise will be reported.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9205","9205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758100","2017-09-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what recent progress has been made on rehousing survivors of the Grenfell Tower fire.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9297","9297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758101","2017-09-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to his Department's August 2015 Planning Policy for Traveller Sites (PPTS), how many local planning authorities have set pitch targets for Gypsies and Travellers using the revised definition as set out in Annex 1 of the PPTS 2015.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9187","9187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758102","2017-09-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many Travellers who conform to the revised definition of Gypsy Travellers as set out in the Planning Policy for Traveller Sites 2015 have been successful in obtaining a pitch in the last year for which data is available.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9188","9188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758103","2017-09-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many and which local authorities have met the requirement (a) in the Planning Policy for Traveller Sites 2015 to identify and maintain a supply of specific deliverable sites, sufficient to provide five years' worth of sites, against their locally set target and (b) to include the same outcome for each of the next five, six and 10 years as set down in the Planning Policy for Travellers Sites document.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9189","9189"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758104","2017-09-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to the announcement made by him and the Prime Minister on 21 December 2016, on tackling homelessness, when he expects the trials of the Housing First model to begin.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9291","9291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758105","2017-09-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that people who want to access Discretionary Housing Payments are not blocked by overly strict criteria set by local authorities.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9286","9286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758106","2017-09-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he plans to publish the Draft Tenants Fees Bill.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9280","9280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758107","2017-09-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the number of private high-rise residential blocks that have one of the four types of cladding and insulation combinations assessed as non-compliant with building regulations guidance BR135 by local authority area.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9281","9281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758108","2017-09-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what plans he has to ensure that high-rise residential accommodation with external cladding that is not composed of aluminium composite material is tested to ensure that it is fire safe.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9235","9235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758109","2017-09-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, by what date he plans that all the households eligible for rehousing as a result of the Grenfell Tower fire will receive an offer of permanent housing.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9236","9236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758110","2017-09-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many social housing blocks have failed the recent fire safety tests co-ordinated by his Department in each local authority area.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9237","9237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758111","2017-09-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much funding his Department has set aside for remedial work in response to the Grenfell Tower fire; and whether such funding is additional to existing departmental allocations.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9295","9295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758112","2017-09-11","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps her Department takes to provide (a) information on its services in British Sign Language (BSL) and (b) correspondence in BSL to people whose principal language is BSL.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9001","9001"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758113","2017-09-11","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether she has had recent discussions with the (a) English Football League or (b) Football Association on Coventry City Football Club's search for a long-term stadium solution within Coventry.","Biography information for Colleen Fletcher","Colleen Fletcher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9077","9077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758114","2017-09-11","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions she has had with the charity sector on the practice of posting plastic bags through people's letterboxes.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9110","9110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758115","2017-09-11","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how much her Department paid to the Behavioural Insights Team in each year since 2014.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9183","9183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758116","2017-09-11","Ministry of Defence","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much his Department paid to the Behavioural Insights Team in each year since 2014.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9184","9184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758117","2017-09-11","Ministry of Defence","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much UK (a) funding, (b) personnel and (c) other resources have been used for civilian harm tracking as part of Operation Inherent Resolve.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9247","9247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758118","2017-09-11","Ministry of Defence","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the UK's rules of engagement are for Operation Inherent Resolve (a) overall and (b) in relation to planned and reactive strikes as part of combat air patrols.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9248","9248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758119","2017-09-11","Ministry of Defence","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what proportion of UK Steel will be used to produce the five new frigates announced in the National Shipbuilding Strategy.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9092","9092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758120","2017-09-11","Ministry of Defence","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department has taken to ensure that the behaviour of the Iraqi armed forces trained by UK armed forces is compliant with international (a) humanitarian and (b) human rights law.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9071","9071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758121","2017-09-11","Ministry of Defence","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department takes to provide (a) information on its services in British Sign Language (BSL) and (b) correspondence in BSL to people whose principal language is BSL.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9002","9002"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758122","2017-09-11","Ministry of Defence","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the reason was for cancelling the Maritime Conference at Chatham House on 7 July 2017.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9042","9042"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758123","2017-09-11","Ministry of Defence","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he plans to publish (a) his Department's response to the Better Combat Compensation consultation and (b) the submissions made to that consultation; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9046","9046"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758124","2017-09-11","Department for Education","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department takes to provide (a) information on its services in British Sign Language (BSL) and (b) correspondence in BSL to people whose principal language is BSL.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9003","9003"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758125","2017-09-11","Department for Education","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will encourage exam boards to offer GCSEs in British Sign Language.","Biography information for Dawn Butler","Dawn Butler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9014","9014"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758126","2017-09-11","Department for Education","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will extend the number of courses covered by the exemption to the Equivalent Level Qualification rules to include full-time undergraduate STEM courses.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9025","9025"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758127","2017-09-11","Department for Education","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to increase the intake of students on university nursing courses.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9074","9074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758128","2017-09-11","Department for Education","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of children in (a) Newcastle upon Tyne, (b) the North East and (c) England were entitled to receive free school meals in each of the last seven years.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9049","9049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758129","2017-09-11","Department for Education","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the proportion of infant pupils in (a) Newcastle upon Tyne, (b) the North East and (c) England who would currently be entitled to receive free school meals under the pre-universal free school meals system.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9050","9050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758130","2017-09-11","Department for Education","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what information her Department holds on (a) primary schools, (b) secondary schools and (c) further education colleges which are clad in flammable substances.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9052","9052"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758131","2017-09-11","Department for Education","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether her Department has made an estimate of how many families in Stockton North constituency would be entitled to free school meals under the pre-universal free school meals system; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9099","9099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758132","2017-09-11","Department for Education","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment her Department has made of the work of the Careers and Enterprise Company to help young people into work; and whether her Department plans to provide support to that company in future.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9250","9250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758133","2017-09-11","Department for Education","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many (a) women and (b) men (i) work as childminders or (ii) are employed by childcare providers which are set to deliver the 30 hours of free childcare for three and four year olds.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9197","9197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758134","2017-09-11","Department for Education","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans she has to ensure the ongoing high quality of childcare; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9198","9198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758135","2017-09-11","Department for Education","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what guidance her Department provides to schools and examination boards on whether English language and English literature should be (a) taught, (b) examined and (c) reflected in school tables separately; and what the practice is of state schools.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9252","9252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758136","2017-09-11","Department for Education","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 25 July 2017 to Question 5173, how many school children at Kensington Aldridge Academy have been unable to begin the academic school year 2017-18.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9155","9155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758137","2017-09-11","Department for Education","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 25 July 2017 to Question 5173, how many children attending St Francis of Assisi Primary School were relocated to an alternative school.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9156","9156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758138","2017-09-11","Department for Education","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 25 July 2017 to Question 5173, what estimate she has made of the length of time that Kensington Aldridge Academy will remain closed.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9157","9157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758139","2017-09-11","Department for Education","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what comparative assessment she has made of the levels of educational attainment in (a) Northamptonshire and (b) England.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9274","9274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758141","2017-09-11","Department for Education","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many teachers have been trained to teach the computing curriculum; and what the average length and cost was of such training.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9271","9271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758142","2017-09-11","Department for Education","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many people and what proportion of eligible families in each local authority area registered for the 30 hours of free childcare for three and four-year olds by 1 September 2017.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9259","9259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758143","2017-09-11","Department for Education","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many providers registered to deliver the 30 hours of free childcare for three and four-year olds by 1 September 2017; and what assessment she has made of whether the number of registered providers is sufficient to meet demand.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9260","9260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758144","2017-09-11","Department for Education","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to page 17 of the Early Years Workforce Strategy, published in March 2017, what progress her Department has made on conducting a feasibility study into growing the graduate early years workforce in disadvantaged areas.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9263","9263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758145","2017-09-11","Department for Education","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions she and her officials had with learndirect Ltd on the withdrawal of its submitted bid for the Adult Education budget procurement for 2017-18.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9273","9273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758146","2017-09-11","Department for Education","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the number of childcare providers and childminders in each local authority area who cannot cover their costs in delivering the 30 hours of free childcare for three and four-year olds.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9261","9261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758147","2017-09-11","Department for Education","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many secondary schools in Scunthorpe constituency have been allocated a careers and enterprise company adviser.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9278","9278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758148","2017-09-11","Department for Education","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of the number of childcare and early years education settings that (a) are charging supplements, (b) are charging for items that they did not previously charge for in order to make up a shortfall in funding they receive and (c) have raised costs for two-year olds to cross-subsidise for three and four-year olds in order to deliver the 30 hours of free childcare for three and four-year olds.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9262","9262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758149","2017-09-11","Department for Education","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions she has had with the Careers and Enterprise Company on providing careers education to more schools than the 1,700 that have signed up for the scheme to date.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9285","9285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758150","2017-09-11","Department for Education","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many secure children's homes are registered in England; how many places are available in such homes; and how many such facilities have closed since 2010.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9265","9265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758151","2017-09-11","Department for Education","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department has taken to ensure that childcare providers are not charging parents for extra services in order to access the 30 hours of free childcare.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9266","9266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758152","2017-09-11","Department for Education","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent discussions she has had with (a) HM Revenue and Customs and (b) the Student Loans Company on graduate student loan overpayments.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9298","9298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758153","2017-09-11","Department for Education","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when she expects to appoint a permanent chief executive of the Institute for Apprenticeships and Technical Education.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9299","9299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758154","2017-09-11","Department for Education","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent discussions she has had with the Home Secretary on the removal of international students from net migration statistics.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9300","9300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758155","2017-09-11","Department for Education","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the recent report by the Social Market Foundation, On course for success? student retention at university, if she will make an assessment of the finding that black students are 50 per cent more likely to drop out of university than white students.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9301","9301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758156","2017-09-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether his Department plans to employ additional staff in response to demands placed on his Department by the EU exit process.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9276","9276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758157","2017-09-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he has had discussions with the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport on steps to reduce the number of plastic bags posted unsolicited into letterboxes by charities.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9239","9239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758158","2017-09-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many civil servants in his Department made use of a cycle-to-work scheme in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9275","9275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758159","2017-09-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what proportion of the UK allocation from the European Maritime and Fisheries Fund has been (a) allocated and (b) spent.","Biography information for Holly Lynch","Holly Lynch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9222","9222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758160","2017-09-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate he has made of the level of ivory imports to and exports from the UK in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9234","9234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758161","2017-09-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, in how many cases his Department has made offers of financial support which were subsequently withdrawn because it was found to be in breach of EU state aid rules; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Holly Lynch","Holly Lynch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9227","9227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758162","2017-09-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, which local authorities breached legal air quality limits in the last year.","Biography information for Neil Parish","Neil Parish","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9115","9115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758163","2017-09-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to tackle the smuggling of dogs into the UK.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9107","9107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758164","2017-09-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate he has made of the number of unused plastic bags that end up in landfill that have been posted through letterboxes by the charity sector.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9072","9072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758165","2017-09-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department takes to provide (a) information on its services in British Sign Language (BSL) and (b) correspondence in BSL to people whose principal language is BSL.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9004","9004"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758166","2017-09-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department takes to provide (a) information on its services in British Sign Language (BSL) and (b) correspondence in BSL to people whose principal language is BSL.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9006","9006"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758167","2017-09-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the implications are for the Government's policies on North Korea of the C4ADS Report Risky Business, published in June 2017.","Biography information for Paul Masterton","Paul Masterton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9070","9070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758168","2017-09-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions (a) he and (b) Ministers of his Department have had with representatives from the UK's Sikh community on the UK's military role in the 1984 raid on the Golden Temple in Amritsar; and if he will commission a public inquiry into UK involvement in that event.","Biography information for Colleen Fletcher","Colleen Fletcher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9079","9079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758169","2017-09-11","Ministry of Defence","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will make it his policy for the UK not to participate in any further military exercises in the region of the Korean peninsula without prior parliamentary approval; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8993","8993"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758170","2017-09-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with the representatives of the Nigerian Government on the political situation in Northern Nigeria; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9160","9160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758171","2017-09-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of taking up promoting the Six Party Talks with North Korea which were broken off in 2009.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9093","9093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758172","2017-09-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how much funding from the public purse has been paid by his Department to Adam Smith International since March 2017; how much of that funding is classified as Official Development Assistance; and whether his Department has (a) signed any new contracts or (b) extended existing contracts with Adam Smith International since March 2017.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9083","9083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758173","2017-10-09","Department of Health","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many cases of (a) chlamydia, (b) gonorrhea, (c) genital herpes, (d) HIV/AIDS, (e) human papillomavirus, (f) Syphilis, (g) Bacterial Vaginosis and (h) trichomoniasis were treated by (i) Lancashire Teaching Hospitals, (ii) University Hospitals of Morecambe Bay, (iii) Blackpool Teaching Hospitals, (iv) Bolton NHS, (v) East Lancashire Hospital and (vi) Southport and Ormskirk Hospitals Trust s in each quarter since 1 January 2014 for people aged 50 years and over.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9088","9088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758174","2017-10-09","Department of Health","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many cases of female genital mutilation were reported to police forces by (a) Lancashire Teaching Hospitals, (b) University Hospitals of Morecambe Bay, (c) Blackpool Teaching Hospitals, (d) Bolton NHS, (e) East Lancashire Hospital, (f) Southport and Ormskirk Hospitals, (g) Warrington and Halton Hospitals, (h) St Helens and Knowsley Teaching Hospitals and (i) Liverpool Women's NHS Foundation Trust in each each quarter between 1 January 2016 and 30 June 2017.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9089","9089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758175","2017-10-09","Department of Health","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many vacancies there were for (a) consultants, (b) other doctors, (c) registered nurses, (d) physiotherapists, (e) X-ray technicians and (f) pharmacists at (i) Lancashire Teaching Hospitals, (ii) University Hospitals of Morecambe Bay, (iii) Blackpool Teaching Hospitals, (iv) Bolton NHS, (v) East Lancashire Hospital, (vi) Southport and Ormskirk Hospitals Trust, (vii) Warrington and Halton Hospitals and (viii) St Helens and Knowsley Teaching Hospitals as at 31 August 2017.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9090","9090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758176","2017-10-09","Department of Health","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps Public Health England has taken to support the commissioning of condom delivery, open access sexual health services and STI screening, focusing on groups at highest risk, as part of the implementation of the Health Promotion for Sexual Health and HIV Strategic Action Plan 2016 to 2019.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9102","9102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758177","2017-09-11","Department of Health","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many and which GP practices (a) closed and (b) opened in the London Borough of Enfield in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9140","9140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758178","2017-09-11","Department of Health","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much the NHS has spent on wheelchair provision in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9108","9108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758179","2017-09-11","Department of Health","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what (a) restrictions and (b) guidance are in place on charges made by GP surgeries to patients for copies of test results or correspondence with hospitals.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9163","9163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758180","2017-09-11","Department of Health","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that NHS staff are representative of the population in respect of ethnicity.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9132","9132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758181","2017-09-11","Department of Health","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the cost per child to his Department is of treating under 18 year olds for total dental clearances.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9171","9171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758182","2017-09-11","Department of Health","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to increase the number of neuromuscular care advisors for people with muscle-wasting conditions.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9105","9105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758183","2017-09-11","Department of Health","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the cost to his Department was of treating under 18 year olds for total dental clearances in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9172","9172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758184","2017-09-11","Department of Health","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many hospitals have diabetic out-patient support and care programmes.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9173","9173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758185","2017-09-11","Department of Health","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what emergency support is in place for pregnant women affected by temporary closures of NHS maternity units.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9230","9230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758186","2017-09-11","Department of Health","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he expects (a) Barts NHS Health Trust, (b) Gloucestershire Hospitals NHS Foundation Trust and (c) St George's University Hospitals NHS Foundation Trust to submit data to NHS England on the number of incomplete referral to treatment pathways.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9231","9231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758187","2017-09-11","Department of Health","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the level of business rates to be paid by NHS hospitals in (a) 2016-17, (b) 2017-18, (c) 2018-19 and (d) 2019-20.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9232","9232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758188","2017-09-11","Department of Health","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether NHS England has made an assessment of the level of financial resource required for the NHS to meet the 18 week referral to treatment target.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9233","9233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758189","2017-09-11","Department of Health","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether it is the Government's policy for the NHS to provide a wheelchair to everyone who needs one.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9120","9120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758190","2017-09-11","Department of Health","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidance NHS England publishes on minimising GP appointment drop-outs and did-not-attends.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9125","9125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758191","2017-09-11","Department of Health","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many did-not-attends and drop-outs from appointments occurred in GP practices in (a) Barnsley and (b) England in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9124","9124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758192","2017-09-11","Department of Health","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients have visited specialist diabetic clinics in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9168","9168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758193","2017-09-11","Department of Health","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many NHS-funded wheelchairs have been provided in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9119","9119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758194","2017-09-11","Department of Health","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) pre-school, (b) primary school and (c) secondary school children have undergone total dental clearances in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9166","9166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758195","2017-09-11","Department of Health","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will implement the recommendations of the National Childbirth Trust's report, The Hidden Half - bringing postnatal mental illness out of hiding, published in June 2017.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9121","9121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758196","2017-09-11","Department of Health","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department takes to provide (a) information on its services in British Sign Language (BSL) and (b) correspondence in BSL to people whose principal language is BSL; and what steps he has taken to encourage GPs and other practitioners to provide (i) prescriptions, (ii) details of medical appointments and (iii) other essential personal medical documents in BSL to people whose principal language is BSL.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8998","8998"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758197","2017-09-11","Department of Health","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to increase awareness of eating disorders.","Biography information for Colleen Fletcher","Colleen Fletcher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8987","8987"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758198","2017-09-11","Department of Health","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure equal access to IVF treatment across the UK.","Biography information for Colleen Fletcher","Colleen Fletcher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8988","8988"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758199","2017-09-11","Department of Health","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to reduce regional variations in the availability of free-of-charge IVF treatment.","Biography information for Colleen Fletcher","Colleen Fletcher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8989","8989"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758200","2017-09-11","Department of Health","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress he has made on reviewing the operation of the internal market in the NHS.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8990","8990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758201","2017-09-11","Department of Health","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to improve the early identification of eating disorders in order to ensure that sufferers can access early intervention.","Biography information for Colleen Fletcher","Colleen Fletcher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9069","9069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758202","2017-09-11","Department of Health","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information his Department holds on (a) hospitals, (b) GP surgeries and (c) walk in centres which are (i) clad in flammable substances and (ii) fitted with sprinklers.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9053","9053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758203","2017-09-11","Department of Health","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much has been spent by the NHS on unplanned admissions associated with urinary tract infections in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9062","9062"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758204","2017-09-11","Department of Health","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to prevent the incidence of Candida auris in NHS hospitals.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9063","9063"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758205","2017-09-11","Department of Health","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what additional funding from the public purse is available to NHS trusts that experience an outbreak of Candida auris.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9064","9064"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758206","2017-09-11","Department of Health","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many NHS patients have been infected with Candida auris in each of the last 12 months for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9065","9065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758207","2017-09-11","Department of Health","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many NHS patients have developed bloodstream infections as a result of Candida auris in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9066","9066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758208","2017-09-11","Department of Health","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will list each NHS trust which has experienced an outbreak of Candida auris in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9067","9067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758209","2017-09-11","Department of Health","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much funding from the public purse that was allocated to capital accounts in the NHS has been transferred to revenue accounts in each of the last 10 years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9057","9057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758210","2017-09-11","Department of Health","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of private sector referral management schemes.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9059","9059"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758211","2017-09-11","Department of Health","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the recent trends in the NHS high-risk maintenance backlog; and what steps he is taking to tackle that backlog.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9058","9058"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758212","2017-09-11","Department of Health","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether individual clinical commissioning groups are required to comply with the majority decision of a sustainability and transformation plan board.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9060","9060"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758213","2017-09-11","Department of Health","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many and what proportion of IT exemplar trusts use IT systems supplied by Cerner.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9061","9061"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758214","2017-09-11","Department of Health","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect of the provision of bedside television and bedside telephones in NHS hospitals on the installation of broadband services for NHS patients.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9034","9034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758215","2017-09-11","Department of Health","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the NICE process for reviewing new treatments for rare diseases.","Biography information for Michelle Donelan","Michelle Donelan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9043","9043"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758216","2017-09-11","Department of Health","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many clinical commissioning groups in England follow in full the guidance provided to them by NICE on the provision of IVF treatment.","Biography information for Colleen Fletcher","Colleen Fletcher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9017","9017"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758217","2017-09-11","Department of Health","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of Allied Health Professionals in leadership roles in the NHS; and if he will meet representatives of the Allied Health Professions Federation to discuss this matter.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9019","9019"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758218","2017-09-11","Department of Health","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what representations he has received from the Allied Health Professions Federation in response to his consultation on leadership in the NHS; and what his response was to these representations.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9020","9020"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758219","2017-09-11","Department of Health","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients with urinary tract infections went on to contract sepsis in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9037","9037"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758220","2017-09-11","Department of Health","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure adequate levels of cellular pathology staff in the NHS.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9038","9038"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758221","2017-09-11","Department of Health","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the recommended antibiotic treatment for urinary tract infections.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9039","9039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758222","2017-09-11","Department of Health","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department has taken to improve the security of NHS passwords since the WannaCry cyber attack in May 2017.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9272","9272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758223","2017-09-11","Department of Health","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the Government's policy is on the fortification of flour with folic acid.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9208","9208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758224","2017-09-11","Department of Health","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many walk-in clinics are in operation; and how many such clinics offer specialist diabetic care.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9296","9296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758225","2017-09-11","Home Office","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the effect of the Scrap Metal Dealers Act 2013 on sole traders.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9185","9185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758226","2017-09-11","Home Office","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how and when she plans to report on the findings of the review of the Scrap Metal Dealers Act 2013.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9186","9186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758227","2017-09-11","Home Office","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many EU citizens applied for leave to remain in the UK in the last five years.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9292","9292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758228","2017-09-11","Home Office","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average processing time was for immigration applications that fell outside service standards because they raised human rights issues between 1 September 2016 and 31 August 2017.","Biography information for Meg Hillier","Meg Hillier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9268","9268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758229","2017-09-11","Home Office","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of applications for settlement visas paid for under her Department's Priority Service Scheme were processed within 60 working days in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9242","9242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758230","2017-09-11","Home Office","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many of the refugee family reunion visas granted on the basis of exceptional compelling compassionate circumstances outside the immigration rules were under 18, for each of the last five years.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9040","9040"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758231","2017-09-11","Home Office","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many refugee family reunion visas were granted to children, by country of origin, for each year for which records are available.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9041","9041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758232","2017-09-11","Home Office","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have been classified as having no recourse to public funds in (a) Camberwell and Peckham constituency and (b) the London Borough of Southwark in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9018","9018"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758233","2017-09-11","Home Office","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people with dependents have been classified as having no recourse to public funds in (a) Camberwell and Peckham constituency and (b) the London Borough of Southwark in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9022","9022"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758234","2017-09-11","Home Office","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate her Department has made of the cost to West Yorkshire Police of providing support to people with mental health needs.","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9035","9035"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758235","2017-09-11","Home Office","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department takes to provide (a) information on its services in British Sign Language (BSL) and (b) correspondence in BSL to people whose principal language is BSL.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9007","9007"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758236","2017-09-11","Home Office","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, of applicants who were refused leave to remain as a stateless person since April 2013, how many were recognised as stateless persons but not considered eligible for leave to remain.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9031","9031"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758237","2017-09-11","Home Office","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications for leave to remain as a stateless person have been received each year from April 2013 to present; and how many such applications were (a) granted, (b) refused, (c) declared invalid, (d) withdrawn, (e) still pending after six months, (f) still pending after 12 months and (g) still pending after 18 months.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9032","9032"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758238","2017-09-11","Home Office","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications for British citizenship for people recognised as stateless the naturalisation or registration fee has been waived or reduced in the last five years; and of these how many were (a) for applicants under 18 years, (b) for applicants under 22 years at the time of application and applying under Paragraph 3, Schedule 2 of the British Nationality Act 1981 and (c) adult naturalisation applications under section 6 of the British Nationality Act 1981.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9033","9033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758239","2017-09-11","Home Office","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will extend the proscription of the military wing of Hezbollah under the provisions of the Terrorism Act 2000 to include its political wing.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8994","8994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758240","2017-09-11","Home Office","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to ensure that police forces and chief constables enforce Section 61 of the Criminal Justice and Public Order Act 1994 in relation to the combatting of illegal Travellers' sites.","Biography information for Jack Lopresti","Jack Lopresti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8997","8997"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758241","2017-09-11","Home Office","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average length of time taken to process an application for a priority settlement visa in New Delhi was in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9224","9224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758242","2017-09-11","Home Office","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of applications for non-settlement visas paid for under her Department's Priority Service scheme were processed within 15 working days in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9123","9123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758243","2017-09-11","Home Office","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether it remains her policy to reform the police funding formula.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9229","9229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758244","2017-09-11","Home Office","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 20 July 2017 to Question 5241, what her Department's definition is of an exceptional circumstance that would validate a refund to people who have submitted a visa application under her Department's Priority Service scheme.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9158","9158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758245","2017-09-11","Home Office","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will publish the advice given by her Department's representative on the Police Staff Council on the one per cent public sector pay cap at meetings of that Council since the 2011 Autumn Statement.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9159","9159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758246","2017-09-11","Home Office","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of (a) settlement, (b) non-settlement and (c) total visa applications are submitted under her Department's Priority Service scheme.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9196","9196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758247","2017-09-11","Home Office","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many firms have been prosecuted on more than one separate occasion in Northern Ireland for employing staff who did not have a legal right to be in the UK in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9251","9251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758248","2017-09-11","Home Office","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many reports of online child grooming have been received by the police in each of the last five years; and how many convictions for online child grooming have been made in each such year.","Biography information for Kit Malthouse","Kit Malthouse","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9249","9249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758249","2017-09-11","Home Office","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many EU nationals of each nationality have been prevented from entering the UK since 2010; and what the reasons were for their entry being refused.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9127","9127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758250","2017-09-11","Home Office","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many EU nationals of each ethnic group have been prevented from entering the UK since 2010; and what the reasons were for their entry being refused.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9128","9128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758251","2017-09-11","Home Office","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of stop and searches involved (a) foreign and (b) British nationals; and what proportion of each such category resulted in an arrest in the last year for which information is available.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9138","9138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758252","2017-09-11","Home Office","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of arrests of (a) foreign and (b) British nationals resulted in a prosecution in the last year for which information is available.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9139","9139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758253","2017-09-11","Home Office","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans she has to allow visitors from Australia to use e-passport gates as a matter of routine; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9100","9100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758254","2017-09-11","Home Office","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the number of non-UK seasonal workers from the EU that are required for the (a) agricultural, (b) construction and (c) hospitality industries after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Anna Soubry","Anna Soubry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9095","9095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758255","2017-09-11","Home Office","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make it her policy to include within published immigration statistics data relating to applications for leave to remain as a stateless person under Part 14 of the Immigration Rules.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9087","9087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758256","2017-09-11","Home Office","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make it her policy to record and publish data in relation to the number and outcome of applications received from stateless persons each year under paragraph 3, schedule 2 to the British Nationality Act 1981.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9086","9086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758257","2017-09-11","Department for International Development","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what (a) plans her Department has and (b) funding it has allocated to implement its Youth Agenda, published in April 2016; and how her Department plans to ensure that it works alongside and consults young people as advocates and agents for change.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9085","9085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758258","2017-09-11","Department for International Development","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether her Department plans to (a) publish and (b) implement its new Strategic Vision for Gender Equality.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9084","9084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758259","2017-09-11","Department for International Development","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what contingency planning her Department has undertaken to support Iraqi Kurds in the event of a vote for independence in the forthcoming referendum.","Biography information for Jack Lopresti","Jack Lopresti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9103","9103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758260","2017-09-11","Department for International Development","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what estimate she has made of the cost to the public purse in cash terms of meeting the target to spend 0.7 per cent of gross national income as development assistance in 2018.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9253","9253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758261","2017-09-11","Department for International Development","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what support her Department is providing to Syrian refugees in Lebanon.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9028","9028"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758262","2017-09-11","Department for International Development","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the effect of church-based initiatives in Lebanon in supporting Syrian refugees.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9029","9029"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758263","2017-09-11","Department for International Development","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what estimate she has made of the number of Syrian refugees in Lebanon.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9027","9027"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758264","2017-09-11","Department for International Development","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department takes to provide (a) information on its services in British Sign Language (BSL) and (b) correspondence in BSL to people whose principal language is BSL.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9008","9008"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758265","2017-09-11","Department for International Development","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what plans exist for the repatriation or reallocation of the proportion of the overseas aid budget currently contributing towards EU development funds; and whether the Government intends to bring these plans before Parliament.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9021","9021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758266","2017-09-11","Department for International Development","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that sufficient food and medical assistance is being provided to the displaced civilians of Rakine State.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9048","9048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758267","2017-09-11","Department for International Development","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much funding from the public purse has been paid by her Department to Adam Smith International since March 2017; how much of that funding is classified as Official Development Assistance; and whether her Department has (a) signed any new contracts or (b) extended any existing contracts with Adam Smith International since March 2017.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9082","9082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758268","2017-09-11","Department for International Development","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much overseas development aid the Government has provided to Yemen since 2015.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9282","9282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758269","2017-09-11","Department for International Development","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will ensure that two-thirds of UK support for energy access in developing countries is allocated to centralised, renewable electricity and clean cooking solutions.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9279","9279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758270","2017-09-11","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many cases have been brought before employment tribunals in (a) Jarrow constituency, (b) South Tyneside, (c) the North East and (d) the UK in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9290","9290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758271","2017-09-11","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many court orders for children to be held securely have been made in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9267","9267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758272","2017-09-11","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of reimbursing people who have paid employment tribunal fees.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9269","9269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758273","2017-09-11","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) staff and (b) vacancies there were in each community rehabilitation company in each quarter since those companies were established.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9270","9270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758274","2017-09-11","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the prison incarceration rates per capita are for (a) England and Wales and (b) other EU countries; and what the average cost of jailing a person per year is in (i) England and Wales and (ii) other EU countries.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9073","9073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758275","2017-09-11","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many cases brought before the family courts have been found to be based on false allegations in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Sir Hugo Swire","Sir Hugo Swire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9051","9051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758276","2017-09-11","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department takes to provide (a) information on its services in British Sign Language (BSL) and (b) correspondence in BSL to people whose principal language is BSL.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9010","9010"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758277","2017-09-11","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will place the documents relating to the contract signed in 2017 between the Government and G4S for the electronic tagging of offenders in the Library.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9216","9216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758278","2017-09-11","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have chosen to represent themselves in Crown Court since the implementation of the Legal Aid, Sentencing and Punishment of Offenders Act 2012.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9217","9217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758279","2017-09-11","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of (a) foreign and (b) British national defendants of each (i) sex and (ii) ethnic group were sentenced to immediate custody for each offence type in the last year for which information is available.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9137","9137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758280","2017-09-11","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, on what date the Government plans to publish its review into legal aid reform.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9112","9112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758281","2017-09-11","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will list (a) the organisations and (b) people who have given evidence to the Government's review into legal aid reform; and if he will publish that evidence.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9113","9113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758282","2017-09-11","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what power a court has to require a person to hand over a device if that device has been seen to have been used or is thought to have been used to take a photograph or recording in court.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9133","9133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758283","2017-09-11","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what power a court has to search a person for a device if that device has been seen to have been used or is thought to have been used to take a photograph or recording in court.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9134","9134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758284","2017-09-11","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of offenders who re-offended or breached their licence and who were liable to be recalled were not recalled in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9135","9135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758285","2017-09-11","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of (a) foreign and (b) British national defendants of each (i) sex and (ii) ethnic group were refused bail for each offence type in the last year for which information is available.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9136","9136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758286","2017-09-11","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to implement the recommendations of the report by Lord Farmer, The importance of strengthening prisoners' family ties to prevent reoffending and reduce intergenerational crime, published in August 2017.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9144","9144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758287","2017-09-11","Department for International Trade","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what plans he has to ensure that each nation and region can take advantage of the opportunities for trade and inward investment after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9254","9254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758288","2017-09-11","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2017-09-06","To ask the hon. Member for Houghton and Sunderland South, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, how many voters were wrongly excluded from the electoral list at the 2017 General Election; and in which constituencies those exclusions took place.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9114","9114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758289","2017-09-13","Department for Transport","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of introducing heating apparatus in certain road surfaces similar to that installed on the M4 at Chiswick in the 1960s to improve safety in winter and reduce the need for gritting; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9101","9101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758290","2017-09-14","Department for Transport","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which (a) parliamentary constituencies he visited and (b) hon. Members he met with in their constituencies during the 2017 summer recess; what the dates were of those visits; and which proposed or current transport schemes he visited in that period.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9096","9096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758291","2017-09-11","Department for Transport","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans he has to increase passenger capacity on trains between Bradford and (a) Manchester and (b) Leeds.","Biography information for Judith Cummins","Judith Cummins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9170","9170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758292","2017-09-11","Department for Transport","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect of the decision not to electrify the Midland Mainline on the ability of High Speed 2 to integrate with the existing rail network.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9091","9091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758293","2017-09-11","Department for Transport","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether HS2 Limited has worked with the Behavioural Insights Team.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9219","9219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758294","2017-09-11","Department for Transport","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department has received services from the Behavioural Insights Team on High Speed 2.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9220","9220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758295","2017-09-11","Department for Transport","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether High Speed 2 has received services from the Behavioural Insights Team.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9221","9221"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758296","2017-09-11","Department for Transport","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department has worked with the Behavioural Insights Team on High Speed 2.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9218","9218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758297","2017-09-11","Department for Transport","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the projected cost was of the cancelled electrification of the (a) Great Western Mainline, (b) Midland Mainline and (c) the line between Windermere and Oxenholme.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9214","9214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758298","2017-09-11","Department for Transport","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much has been spent to date on the planned electrification of the (a) Midland Mainline, north of Kettering to Sheffield and Nottingham, (b) Great Western route, west of Cardiff, (c) line between Windermere and Oxenholme and (d) Transpennine route between Manchester and Leeds.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9215","9215"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758299","2017-09-11","Department for Transport","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what proportion of Network Rail's work by value was outsourced to external firms in the 2016-17 financial year; and what estimate his Department has made of (a) the total value of that work, split according to maintenance, renewals and enhancements, (b) the total profit to external firms from those contracts, split according to maintenance, renewals and enhancements and (c) the total additional cost resulting from multiple tiers of external contractors duplicating project management functions, split according to maintenance, renewals and enhancements.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9213","9213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758300","2017-09-11","Department for Transport","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much has been spent to date on the electification of the Midland Mainline (a) in total, (b) London to Corby and (c) north of Kettering.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9223","9223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758301","2017-09-11","Department for Transport","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much has been spent on (a) all, (b) standard train and (c) first class train travel by staff of HS2 Ltd in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9164","9164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758302","2017-09-11","Department for Transport","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans he has to reduce train journey times between Bradford and (a) Manchester and (b) Leeds.","Biography information for Judith Cummins","Judith Cummins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9169","9169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758303","2017-09-11","Department for Transport","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department takes to provide (a) information on its services in British Sign Language (BSL) and (b) correspondence in BSL to people whose principal language is BSL.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9011","9011"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758304","2017-09-11","Department for Transport","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the cost to the public purse has been of electrification of the railway line (a) in the Severn Tunnel, (b) between the Severn Tunnel and Cardiff Central station, (c) between Cardiff Central Station and Bridgend, (d) between Bridgend and Port Talbot Parkway, (e) between Port Talbot Parkway and Neath and (f) between Neath and Swansea; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9045","9045"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758305","2017-09-11","Department for Transport","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to prevent the deliberate use of drones to disrupt transport.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9075","9075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758306","2017-09-11","Department for Transport","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, by what date it is planned that the Government Car Service no longer uses diesel vehicles.","Biography information for Andrew Selous","Andrew Selous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9264","9264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758307","2017-09-11","Department for Transport","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he has received an application to the Access for All programme for funding for platform nine at Stirling station; and if he will meet the hon. Member for Ochil and South Perthshire the effect of lack of accessibility at that station on residents of Ochil and South Perthshire constituency.","Biography information for Luke Graham","Luke Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9212","9212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758308","2017-09-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claims for personal independence payment in the London Borough of Southwark have been due to a mental health illness in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9024","9024"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758309","2017-09-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will meet the hon. Member for Coventry North East and a delegation from WASPI Coventry to discuss changes to the state pension age for women born in the 1950s.","Biography information for Colleen Fletcher","Colleen Fletcher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9078","9078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758310","2017-09-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in the London Borough of Southwark have appealed against his Department's decision not to grant them personal independence payment in each of the last five years; and how many of those appeals have been successful in those years.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9023","9023"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758311","2017-09-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department takes to provide (a) information on its services in British Sign Language (BSL) and (b) correspondence in BSL to people whose principal language is BSL.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9013","9013"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758312","2017-09-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make it his policy to report annually to Parliament on progress in tackling the disability employment gap as part of the annual report on full employment.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9126","9126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758313","2017-09-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans his Department has to reduce the disability employment gap.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9245","9245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758314","2017-09-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much is owned to resident parents by non-resident parents in child support arrears in each local authority in Scotland in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Kirsty Blackman","Kirsty Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9076","9076"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758315","2017-09-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the universal credit minimum income floor on self-employed creative workers whose incomes are unpredictable.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9283","9283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758316","2017-09-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will commission an independent review of the universal credit minimum income floor to improve its responsiveness to the conditions of people in self-employment; and if he will suspend the introduction of that floor for self-employed claimants until such a review has been completed.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9284","9284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758317","2017-09-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average time is after an application is submitted for universal credit before the first payment is received for claimants in (a) Jarrow constituency, (b) South Tyneside, (c) the North East and (d) the UK.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9190","9190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758318","2017-09-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of universal credit applicants wait more than (a) six and (b) 10 weeks after making their claim before they receive any income in (i) Jarrow constituency, (ii) South Tyneside, (iii) the North East and (iv) the UK.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9191","9191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758319","2017-09-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he plans to extend the Access to Work scheme to (a) internships and (b) apprenticeships.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9243","9243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758320","2017-09-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether his Department has regional strategies for reducing the disability employment gap.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9244","9244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758321","2017-09-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what transitional arrangements are in place for claimants whose health deteriorates when in receipt of jobseeker's allowance if their claim is stopped and they are advised to claim employment support allowance.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9203","9203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758322","2017-09-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when the list of departmental chief scientific advisers was last updated.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9258","9258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758323","2017-09-11","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what the gender balance is at Tech City and Tech North (a) overall and (b) among STEM staff.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9257","9257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758324","2017-09-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether any installations made under the non-domestic Renewable Heat Incentive scheme have been found to have been used for over 12 hours a day, seven days a week.","Biography information for Graham Stringer","Graham Stringer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9240","9240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758325","2017-09-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many small businesses are registered in Northamptonshire; how many such businesses were registered in Northamptonshire in 2010; and what assessment he has made of the health of the local business environment in that county.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9277","9277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758326","2017-09-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the average cost per kilowatt of capacity has been of installations made under the non-domestic Renewable Heat Incentive scheme.","Biography information for Graham Stringer","Graham Stringer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9303","9303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758327","2017-09-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the announcement made by his Department on 3 April 2016, New public sector boost for UK steel, when he plans to announce the list of approved steel suppliers; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9289","9289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758328","2017-09-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the Government's press release of 30 August 2017, UK Government committed to maximising economic opportunity in North Sea, what plans he has to maximise the economic opportunity in the North Sea.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9094","9094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758329","2017-09-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the extent to which the profit margins of distribution network operators affect the cost of energy.","Biography information for Mr Simon Clarke","Mr Simon Clarke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9104","9104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758330","2017-09-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many single applicants received subsidies for multiple installations under the non-domestic Renewable Heat Incentive scheme since its inception.","Biography information for Graham Stringer","Graham Stringer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9145","9145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758331","2017-09-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many installations made under the non-domestic Renewable Heat Incentive scheme have been found to be non-compliant.","Biography information for Graham Stringer","Graham Stringer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9176","9176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758332","2017-09-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many businesses have had boilers installed under the non-domestic Renewable Heat Incentive scheme; and how many of those boilers will be inspected as part of the National Audit Office's study into that scheme.","Biography information for Graham Stringer","Graham Stringer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9175","9175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758333","2017-09-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many cases of fraud have been brought by Ofgem under the (a) non-domestic and (b) domestic Renewable Heat Incentive schemes.","Biography information for Graham Stringer","Graham Stringer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9177","9177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758334","2017-09-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 6 July 2017 to Question 1697, what provisions and safeguards he has made to ensure that where a disused shale gas well needs decommissioning or maintenance and the company responsible is insolvent that the costs incurred do not fall to the taxpayer either locally or nationally.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9178","9178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758335","2017-09-11","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what representations she has received on the implementation processes for age verification for online pornography; and how that data is stored and shared.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9256","9256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758336","2017-09-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how much his Department paid to the Behavioural Insights Team in each year since 2014.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9179","9179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758337","2017-09-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many and what proportion of the civil servants and advisors working on the industrial strategy are women.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9015","9015"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758338","2017-09-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what information his Department holds on the number of university premises, including student accommodation, which are clad in flammable substances.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9044","9044"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758339","2017-09-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what checks are in place to ensure the safe installation of smart meters.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9047","9047"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758340","2017-09-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, in which month in 2017 he plans to reintroduce the Renewable Heat Incentive Scheme Regulations 2017.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9068","9068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758341","2017-09-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what his policy is on circumstances in which the special share in the Green Investment Bank (GIB) held by the Green Purposes Company Ltd can be used to approve or reject changes to GIB's green purposes as set out in the objects of its Articles of Association.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8995","8995"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758342","2017-09-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department takes to provide (a) information on its services in British Sign Language (BSL) and (b) correspondence in BSL to people whose principal language is BSL.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8999","8999"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758343","2017-09-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what progress he has made on addressing concerns relating to tumble dryer safety; and what recent discussions he has had with manufacturers on that matter.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8991","8991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758344","2017-09-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether the Government has a target date by which all homes in England and Wales should attain a particular energy performance standard.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8992","8992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758345","2017-09-11","Department for International Trade","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps his Department takes to provide (a) information on its services in British Sign Language (BSL) and (b) correspondence in BSL to people whose principal language is BSL.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9009","9009"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758346","2017-09-11","Department for International Trade","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, if he will publish a list of future meetings with (a) US Administration staff, (b) business representatives and (c) others who he plans to hold discussions with in each of the next six months.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9153","9153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758347","2017-09-11","Department for International Trade","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, if he will publish details of (a) US Administration staff, (b) business representatives and (c) others who (i) he and (ii) Departmental staff had meetings with during his visit to the US in July 2017.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9154","9154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758348","2017-09-11","Department for International Trade","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, which agencies his Department has used to recruit staff to that Department.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9148","9148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758349","2017-09-11","Department for International Trade","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what estimate he has made of the number of staff required to assist in trade negotiations; how many such staff have been hired; and what the budget is for the employment of such staff.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9146","9146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758350","2017-09-11","Department for International Trade","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what proportion and value of UK exports to the EU were destined for markets outside the EU in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Kit Malthouse","Kit Malthouse","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9211","9211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758351","2017-09-11","Department for International Trade","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, if he will list all the (a) US Administration staff, (b) business representatives and (c) others he met during his visit to the US in July 2017.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9238","9238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758352","2017-09-11","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to paragraph 3.16 of the Review of the Balance of Competences between the UK and the EU: The Single Market, published in July 2013, whether the impact assessments relating to the effect of EU exit on 50 sectors of the economy conducted by his Department have reached conclusions different to those of the studies cited in the 2013 review about the effect of the Single Market on the UK's GDP.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9293","9293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758353","2017-09-11","Department for International Trade","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, if he will seek to retain current EU countervailing duties on biodiesel imported from the US after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9161","9161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758354","2017-09-11","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what steps his Department takes to provide (a) information on its services in British Sign Language (BSL) and (b) correspondence in BSL to people whose principal language is BSL.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9005","9005"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759503","2017-09-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether the Government plans for the UK to remain in the internal energy market after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 900803","900803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759504","2017-09-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, to ask the Secretary of State what steps he is taking to improve productivity as part of the Industrial Strategy","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 900804","900804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759505","2017-09-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he has taken to develop skills and technical education to encourage productivity growth.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 900801","900801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759506","2017-09-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, to ask the Secretary of State what assessment he has made of the UK's ability to meet its carbon reduction targets.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 900807","900807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759507","2017-09-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, to ask the Seceretary of State what the reasons are for the time taken to publish the carbon reduction plan.","Biography information for Ms Karen Buck","Ms Karen Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 900805","900805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/759508","2017-09-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, to ask the Secretary of State what assessment he has made of the UK's ability to meet its carbon reduction targets.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 900808","900808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757379","2017-09-07","Cabinet Office","2017-09-05","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many times the Government Property Unit has applied conditions to its agreements for Departments to extend or renew their lets in each year since 2012.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8508","8508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757380","2017-09-07","Cabinet Office","2017-09-05","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the success rate is of verified user identities from the Government Verify system being accepted by the departmental service being accessed by that person.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8509","8509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757381","2017-09-07","Cabinet Office","2017-09-05","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many civil servants have been trained by the Government Digital Service in their digital academy since September 2016.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8518","8518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757382","2017-09-07","Cabinet Office","2017-09-05","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many members of staff of the Government Digital Service have come from the civil service fast stream.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8512","8512"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757383","2017-09-07","Cabinet Office","2017-09-05","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether the Government is on track to meet the target of 25 million people using the Verify service by April 2020.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8513","8513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757384","2017-09-07","Cabinet Office","2017-09-05","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, which departmental services have connected to the Government Verify service.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8514","8514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757385","2017-09-07","Cabinet Office","2017-09-05","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the value is of savings from the Governmental Digital Service's spending controls in each year since 2011.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8515","8515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757386","2017-09-07","Cabinet Office","2017-09-05","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether he plans to make any changes to the spending controls issued by the Government Digital Service.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8516","8516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757387","2017-09-07","Cabinet Office","2017-09-05","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether the Government Digital Service will publish the findings of its central monitoring of email vulnerability levels for departments since April 2017.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8517","8517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757388","2017-09-07","Cabinet Office","2017-09-05","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when he expects to provide an updated list of ministerial responsibilities, including for executive agencies and non-ministerial departments; and if copies will be made available in the Vote Office of the House of Commons.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8525","8525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757389","2017-09-07","Cabinet Office","2017-09-05","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many letters have been published on the ACOBA website more than one month after the letter being sent in (a) the last 12 months and (b) each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8510","8510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757390","2017-09-07","HM Treasury","2017-09-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if his Department will respond to the recommendations of the Citizens Advice Bureau report, Stuck in Debt, on forcing lenders to scrap unarranged overdraft fees, prohibiting lenders from increasing a credit limit without a customer's permission, offering financial advice and making debt plans legally enforceable.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8519","8519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757391","2017-09-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans he has to introduce provisions relating to Class 3 national insurance credits in the National Insurance Contributions Bill.","Biography information for Michael Tomlinson","Michael Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8487","8487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757392","2017-09-07","HM Treasury","2017-09-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department is taking to reduce levels of unsecured debt.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8523","8523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757393","2017-09-11","Department of Health","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the statement from the Royal College of Nursing of 4 March 2017 on the number of nurses and healthcare assistants who applied for hardship grants in 2016; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8589","8589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757394","2017-09-07","HM Treasury","2017-09-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make it his policy to end public sector pay restraint in the Autumn Budget 2017.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8567","8567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757395","2017-09-11","Department for Education","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Answer of 29 March 2017 to Question 69018, for what reasons the Government consultation on the case for introducing an adoption allowance similar to maternity allowance for self-employed adopters is no longer being brought forward; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8590","8590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757396","2017-09-07","HM Treasury","2017-09-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of increasing Barnett formula funding for Wales in line with the recent increase in funding for Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8645","8645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757397","2017-09-07","HM Treasury","2017-09-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the number of jobs at risk of being lost in the UK economy as a result of no deal being reached on the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8581","8581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757398","2017-09-07","HM Treasury","2017-09-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what research his Department has conducted into the readability of the terms and conditions set out in life insurance policies.","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8661","8661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757399","2017-09-07","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what penalties his Department has imposed on businesses not complying with the Construction Products Regulations 2013 since those regulations were introduced.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8584","8584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757400","2017-09-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what progress has been made on identifying and addressing issues in social housing referred to in the Prime Minister's statement on the Grenfell Tower inquiry terms of reference of 15 August 2017; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8585","8585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757401","2017-09-11","Department of Health","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of provision of mental health support, trauma counselling and bereavement counselling for the survivors of Grenfell Tower and their families; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8586","8586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757402","2017-09-07","Department for Transport","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what guidance his Department has published on local authorities adopting new private roads.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8548","8548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757403","2017-09-07","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department takes to ensure that the sale and installation of narrow-cavity, low-sightline glass-sealed units into heritage windows is compliant with the Construction Products Regulations 2013.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8493","8493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757404","2017-09-07","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what progress he has made on introducing flexible ticketing for part-time commuters.","Biography information for James Cartlidge","James Cartlidge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8494","8494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757405","2017-09-07","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department takes to ensure that trading standards departments enforce the Construction Products Regulations 2013.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8495","8495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757406","2017-09-07","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps her Department is taking to help reduce the gender pay gap at the BBC.","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8662","8662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757407","2017-09-07","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to the Answer of 12 September 2016 to Question 45539 from the right hon. Member for East Ham, on gaming machines, when the Triennial Review of Stakes and Prizes will be published.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8643","8643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757408","2017-09-07","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate her Department has made of the proportion of funds staked on fixed-odds betting terminals that is staked by (a) problem gamblers and (b) people who are in receipt of benefits.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8553","8553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757409","2017-09-07","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate her Department has made of the total number of people in receipt of benefits who regularly use fixed-odds betting terminals.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8554","8554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757410","2017-09-07","Ministry of Defence","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what contingency planning has been conducted by his Department in the event that no deal is reached on the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8580","8580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757411","2017-09-07","Ministry of Defence","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will adopt a no first use policy in relation to the UK's nuclear weapons capability; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8502","8502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757412","2017-09-07","Ministry of Defence","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department takes to ensure that weapons sold to or gifted to Iraq reach their designated destination and end user.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8470","8470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757413","2017-09-07","Department for Education","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her policy is on the removal of the cap on faith admissions; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Pound","Stephen Pound","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8497","8497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757414","2017-09-07","Department for Education","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of the number of schools in (a) England and (b) each local authority in England projecting that they will run an in-year deficit in the next three years.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8530","8530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757415","2017-09-07","Department for Education","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many teachers who are nationals of other EU member states were working in schools in the UK in the 2016-17 academic year.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8531","8531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757416","2017-09-07","Department for Education","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many teachers who are nationals of other EU member states are employed in schools in the UK in the 2017-18 academic year.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8532","8532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757417","2017-09-07","Department for Education","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many language teachers in UK schools are nationals from other EU countries in the 2017-18 academic year.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8533","8533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757418","2017-09-07","Department for Education","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of the number of sites to be purchased by LocatED by 2019; and how many and what proportion of those sites will be intentionally temporary.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8486","8486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757419","2017-09-07","Department for Education","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of children were eligible for free school meals in (a) Kirklees and (b) England in each of the last seven years.","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8653","8653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757420","2017-09-07","Department for Education","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the average class size was for (a) primary and (b) secondary schools in (i) Colne Valley constituency, (ii) Kirklees, (iii) West Yorkshire and (iv) England in each of the last seven years.","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8654","8654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757421","2017-09-07","Department for Education","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans she has to increase the number of apprentices undertaking apprenticeships at level 3 or above.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8555","8555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757422","2017-09-07","Department for Education","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to increase access to Russell Group universities for students from disadvantaged and under-represented backgrounds.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8556","8556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757423","2017-09-07","Department for Education","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the effect of the E-Bacc on (a) pupils from disadvantaged backgrounds studying the arts and creative subjects and (b) access to careers in the arts and creative industries for people from disadvantaged backgrounds.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8557","8557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757424","2017-09-07","Department for Education","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what (a) discussions she has had with and (b) representations she has received from the Vice Chancellors of Russell Group universities on improving access for students from disadvantaged and under-represented groups.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8562","8562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757425","2017-09-07","Department for Education","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what guidance her Department provides to Russell Group universities on improving access for students from disadvantaged and under-represented backgrounds.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8558","8558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757426","2017-09-07","Department for Education","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of the level of teacher shortages in (a) the London Borough of Haringey and (b) London.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8559","8559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757427","2017-09-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the effect on the UK farming industry in the event that no deal is reached on the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8578","8578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757428","2017-09-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what contingency planning his Department has carried out for the possibility that there is no deal reached on the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8577","8577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757429","2017-09-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many people have been employed in shooting sports in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8482","8482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757430","2017-09-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will consider controls on the number of raptor birds in the countryside.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8483","8483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757431","2017-09-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many licences have been issued to control ravens in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8479","8479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757432","2017-09-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate he has made of the value of shooting sports to the UK in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8480","8480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757433","2017-09-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his counterpart in Qatar on the funding of the Muslim Brotherhood.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8471","8471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757434","2017-09-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his Turkish counterpart on human rights abuses in that country.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8472","8472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757435","2017-09-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Egyptian counterpart on allegations of corruption in that country.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8473","8473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757436","2017-09-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his US counterpart on recent missile tests in North Korea; whether he has made any (a) political and (b) military commitments to the US relating to North Korea; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8499","8499"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757437","2017-09-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the Government is taking steps to promote (a) bilateral dialogue between North Korea and the US and (b) six party dialogue with North Korea; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8501","8501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757438","2017-09-07","Ministry of Defence","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what information his Department holds on illegal killing of wild birds on the sovereign bases on Akrotiri and Dhekelia.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8526","8526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757439","2017-09-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, on how many occasions the UK Ambassador to Iran has had discussions with the Iranian Government on Kamal Foroughi since his appointment; and what recent progress has been made on securing his release.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8576","8576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757440","2017-09-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the Answer of 21 March 2017 to Question HL5901, on Bahrain: capital punishment, when his Department expects the findings of the Ombudsman and Special Investigations Unit investigation into the allegations of torture of Mohammed Ramadan and Hussein Ali Mousa to be published.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8591","8591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757441","2017-09-07","Department of Health","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he plans to bring forward legislative proposals to create an independent healthcare safety investigations body in the NHS.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8572","8572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757442","2017-09-07","Department of Health","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to make non-legislative changes to remove barriers to the integration of care; and if he will make statement.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8573","8573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757443","2017-09-07","Department of Health","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will publish all documentation relating to the capped expenditure process.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8574","8574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757444","2017-09-07","Department of Health","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will estimate the cost to the NHS of follow-up surgery for patients who have been given an Essure implant.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8568","8568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757445","2017-09-07","Department of Health","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many women have reported problems to the Medicines and Healthcare Products Regulatory Agency about the Essure implant in the last five years.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8569","8569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757446","2017-09-07","Department of Health","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 29 June 2017 to Question 822, on accident and emergency departments, what progress is being made on introducing front-door clinical streaming in accident and emergency departments by October 2017.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8570","8570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757447","2017-09-07","Department of Health","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 29 June 2017 to Question 690, on NHS: reorganisation, how many online visitors the NHS England Sustainability and Transformation Partnerships website has received in each week since it was made available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8571","8571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757448","2017-09-07","Department of Health","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many walk-in centres will close as a consequence of the decision to introduce front-door clinical streaming.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8575","8575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757449","2017-09-07","Department of Health","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when the Government plans to respond to the Final Report of the Accelerated Access Review; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Crispin Blunt","Crispin Blunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8644","8644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757450","2017-09-07","Department of Health","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many online visitors the sustainability and transformation partnerships dashboard has received in each week since it was published.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8565","8565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757451","2017-09-07","Department of Health","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of patients who were given an Essure implant were readmitted for follow-up surgery.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8564","8564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757452","2017-09-07","Department of Health","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people with mental health issues were admitted to accident and emergency departments in (a) Kirklees, (b) West Yorkshire and (c) England in each of the last seven years.","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8655","8655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757453","2017-09-07","Department of Health","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the key milestones are of the Neonatal Transformation Review; and when that review plans to (a) announce its plans, (b) consult and (c) report its findings.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8583","8583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757454","2017-09-07","Department of Health","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients were admitted to the Huddersfield Royal Infirmary Accident and Emergency Department in each of the last seven years.","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8656","8656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757455","2017-09-07","Department of Health","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his policy is on the use of private financial investment companies to fund the building of new hospitals.","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8657","8657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757456","2017-09-07","Department of Health","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many times items belonging to patients using ambulance services in England and Wales were lost in the most recent annual data period.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8652","8652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757457","2017-09-07","Department of Health","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will proscribe the practice of conversion therapy in England.","Biography information for Christian Matheson","Christian Matheson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8646","8646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757458","2017-09-07","Department of Health","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information his Department holds on ongoing or long-term delays for women seeking to have vaginal meshes removed.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8527","8527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757459","2017-09-07","Department of Health","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with hospital trusts on the use of vaginal meshes to treat urinary tract infections.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8528","8528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757460","2017-09-07","Department of Health","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people have been given a diagnosis of Lyme disease in the UK in the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8478","8478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757461","2017-09-07","Department of Health","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) NHS and (b) private care homes have been sanctioned for cases of neglect in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8481","8481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757462","2017-09-07","Department of Health","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to reduce deaths due to obesity.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8484","8484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757463","2017-09-07","Department of Health","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make Zytiga available on the NHS.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8469","8469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757464","2017-09-07","Department of Health","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to address nurse shortages and pay gaps between English regions.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8488","8488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757465","2017-09-07","Department of Health","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people in the UK have been diagnosed with chronic stomach pains in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8489","8489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757466","2017-09-07","Department of Health","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many women have been diagnosed with menometrorrhagia in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8490","8490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757467","2017-09-07","Cabinet Office","2017-09-05","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people in UK have been diagnosed with thyroid cancer in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8491","8491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757468","2017-09-07","Department of Health","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to increase the availability of treatments to reduce heart and kidney disease.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8492","8492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757469","2017-09-07","Department of Health","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to make Kadcyla available to patients in the UK.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8474","8474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757470","2017-09-07","Department of Health","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport on steps to reduce illegal drug-taking in sports.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8475","8475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757472","2017-09-07","Home Office","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many dogs have been reported stolen in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8485","8485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757473","2017-09-07","Cabinet Office","2017-09-05","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether it is his policy to change the electoral system for police and crime commissioner elections.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8503","8503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757474","2017-09-07","Home Office","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many armed response vehicles each police force had in each year from 2010 to date.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8504","8504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757475","2017-09-07","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what plans he has to bring forward legislation on victims' rights to make clear what level of service they should expect from the police.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8505","8505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757476","2017-09-07","Department of Health","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to ensure police and crime commissioners sit on local health and wellbeing boards.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8506","8506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757477","2017-09-07","Home Office","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she plans to devolve budget responsibility to local police and crime commissioners.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8507","8507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757478","2017-09-07","Home Office","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many reports of anti-social behaviour in connection with mopeds were made in Hornsey and Wood Green constituency in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8529","8529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757479","2017-09-07","Home Office","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent discussions she has had with (a) the Mayor of London and (b) Mayor Sophie Linden on the current and future operation of Hornsey police station.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8524","8524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757480","2017-09-07","Home Office","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what impact assessment her Department has made of plans to close half of London's police stations.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8520","8520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757481","2017-09-07","Home Office","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the rate of conviction for anti-social behaviour related to moped use was in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8521","8521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757482","2017-09-07","Home Office","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent representations she has received from the Metropolitan Police on proposed closures of police stations.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8522","8522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757483","2017-09-07","Home Office","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what contingency planning has been conducted by her Department in the event that no deal is reached on the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8582","8582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757484","2017-09-07","Home Office","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the effect on small online businesses of proposed changes to the online sale of knives.","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8658","8658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757485","2017-09-07","Home Office","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many police forces have made representations for additional funding to support people affected with mental health issues.","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8659","8659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757486","2017-09-07","Home Office","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average number of police responses to calls from people with a mental health issue was in (a) England and (b) West Yorkshire in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8660","8660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757487","2017-09-07","Home Office","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have been (a) detained and (b) deported in each year since 2010 as a result of information received from hon. Members via her Department's immigration enforcement hotlines and webpages.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8563","8563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757488","2017-09-07","Home Office","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many communications were received from hon. Members to her Department on immigration enforcement hotlines and webpages in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8566","8566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757489","2017-09-07","Home Office","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if her Department will introduce a time limit for holding immigration and asylum applicants.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8537","8537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757490","2017-09-07","Home Office","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether immigration enforcement information passed to her Department by hon. Members contravenes the Data Protection Act 1998.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8552","8552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757491","2017-09-07","Home Office","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what contingency planning has been conducted by her Department on matters of national security in the event that no deal is reached on the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8579","8579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757492","2017-09-11","Home Office","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many unaccompanied children are supported by each local authority; how many children each local authority has offered to support; and what support has been offered to local authorities to increase their capacity to provide appropriate psychological support for unaccompanied child refugees.","Biography information for Tommy Sheppard","Tommy Sheppard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8593","8593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757493","2017-09-11","Home Office","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking together with the French Government to reduce the level of unnecessary force used by the police in that country against child refugees and to ensure the protection of unaccompanied child refugees seeking a place of safety in the UK.","Biography information for Tommy Sheppard","Tommy Sheppard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8592","8592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757494","2017-09-07","Department for International Development","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what plans she has for the future of the Global Learning programme.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8649","8649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757495","2017-09-07","Department for International Development","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether it is her policy that the UK should continue to participate in the Europe Aid Development Awareness programme after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8650","8650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757496","2017-09-07","Department for International Development","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what plans she has for the future of development awareness education.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8651","8651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757497","2017-09-07","Department for International Development","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to support the victims of human trafficking and exploitation in Libya.","Biography information for Paul Masterton","Paul Masterton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8549","8549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757498","2017-09-07","Department for International Development","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much development funding was provided by her Department to the Palestinian Authority in each of the last five financial years; what organisations were so funded; and what the objectives of that funding were.","Biography information for Paul Masterton","Paul Masterton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8550","8550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757499","2017-09-07","Department for International Development","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what safeguards her Department has in place to ensure that international development funding to the Palestinian Authority is not used for the payment of terror salaries or associated purposes.","Biography information for Paul Masterton","Paul Masterton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8551","8551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757500","2017-09-07","Department for Transport","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if his Department will bring forward legislative proposals to amend the Road Traffic Act 1988 to ensure that cyclists are bound by that legislation.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8535","8535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757501","2017-09-07","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department has taken to increase the levels of literacy and numeracy in the prison population.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8538","8538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757502","2017-09-07","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department has taken to reduce the incidence of self-harming of people held in the Prison Estate.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8539","8539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757503","2017-09-07","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how many people have been found guilty of illegal drug-taking in sport in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8476","8476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757504","2017-09-07","Prime Minister","2017-09-05","To ask the Prime Minister, if she will make it her policy to urge the President of the US to engage in high-level dialogue without pre-conditions with North Korea on preserving peace and security; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8500","8500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757505","2017-09-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what benefits he anticipates will accrue to the British public from President Trump's forthcoming official visit to the UK.","Biography information for Christian Matheson","Christian Matheson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8647","8647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757506","2017-09-11","Department for Transport","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether VAT is levied on Mersey (a) tunnel and (b) bridge charges.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8595","8595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757507","2017-09-11","Department for Transport","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect on the (a) local economy and (b) economy of the North West region of new Mersey crossing tolls.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8594","8594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757508","2017-09-07","Department for Transport","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the timetable is for season tickets for part-time workers to be introduced on the Govia Thameslink Railway franchise; and what the reasons are for the time taken to implement such tickets.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8498","8498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757509","2017-09-07","Department for Transport","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what progress has been made on the trans-Pennine upgrade programme; and what the timetable is for completion.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8496","8496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757510","2017-09-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what safeguards his Department has introduced to ensure that when housing benefit is paid to tenants it is paid to the landlord.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8536","8536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757511","2017-09-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, for what reasons people receiving Access to Work grants do not receive a monthly statement setting out the amount of their remaining allowance.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8477","8477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757512","2017-09-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many complaints the Child Maintenance Service received in the first six months of 2017 on the 25 per cent threshold for payment reassessment.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8587","8587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757513","2017-09-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the total sum of housing benefit payable to households living in the private rented sector in 2017-18.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8560","8560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757514","2017-09-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether the Government's Clean Growth Plan will include measures to reduce carbon emissions from homes.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8648","8648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757515","2017-09-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department takes to regulate and monitor courier companies in the UK.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8468","8468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757516","2017-09-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what progress has been made on increasing the representation of women on company boards.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8534","8534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757517","2017-09-07","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many civil servants have been sent to Brussels at any point to engage in the detail of the Brexit negotiation talks; and how many of these have been seconded from outside the Government.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8511","8511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757518","2017-09-07","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what plans his Department has to publish studies into the effect of the UK leaving the EU on different sectors of the UK economy.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8561","8561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757519","2017-09-11","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many times his Department raised the issue of the co-ordination of social security entitlements for people moving within the EU during the negotiations on the UK leaving the EU; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8588","8588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757520","2017-09-07","Attorney General","2017-09-05","To ask the Attorney General, what cost has been incurred by the Crown Prosecution Service in each of the last 11 years of extradition proceedings in relation to suspected Rwandan genocide by Dr Vincent Bajinya, Charles Munyaneza, Emmanuel Nteziryayo, Celestin Ugirashebuja and Celestin Mutabaruka.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Mitchell","Mr Andrew Mitchell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8675","8675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757521","2017-09-07","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what progress the Government has made on plans to strengthen sentencing powers for acid attacks.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8876","8876"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757522","2017-09-07","Attorney General","2017-09-05","To ask the Attorney General, what recent discussions he has had with social media providers on user postings and the provisions of the Contempt of Court Act 1981.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8839","8839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757523","2017-09-07","Attorney General","2017-09-05","To ask the Attorney General, what steps he is taking to improve public legal education.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8850","8850"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757524","2017-09-07","Attorney General","2017-09-05","To ask the Attorney General, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the work of the Serious Fraud Office in investigating and securing convictions for fraud offences.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8851","8851"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757525","2017-09-07","Attorney General","2017-09-05","To ask the Attorney General, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of extending the Unduly Lenient Sentences scheme to offences beyond those which are already covered by that scheme.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8852","8852"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757526","2017-09-07","Cabinet Office","2017-09-05","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, (a) how many and (b) what proportion of working-age people in Hemsworth constituency worked in the public sector in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8817","8817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757527","2017-09-07","Cabinet Office","2017-09-05","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many agency staff have been employed in the Government Property Unit; and how many secondments there have been to that unit from (a) inside and (b) outside government in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8714","8714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757528","2017-09-07","Cabinet Office","2017-09-05","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether the Government has plans to charge recipients for work done by civil servants working for the Government Communications Service abroad.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8715","8715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757529","2017-09-07","Cabinet Office","2017-09-05","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many civil servants in the Government Communications Service have been assigned to work on issues relating to the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8717","8717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757530","2017-09-07","Cabinet Office","2017-09-05","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many projects the (a) Government Communications Service and (b) Government Communications Service International have completed since inception.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8718","8718"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757531","2017-09-07","Cabinet Office","2017-09-05","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what progress has been made on making the Government Communications Service a new function that helps deliver the annual Government Communications Plan by filling in essential roles for priority communications campaigns.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8719","8719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757532","2017-09-07","Department for Transport","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many civil servants in the Government Communications Service have been assigned to work on issues relating to High Speed 2.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8716","8716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757533","2017-09-11","Cabinet Office","2017-09-05","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the total value of investment is by the (a) Parliamentary Contributory Pensions Fund and (b) Civil Service Pension Scheme in funds linked to freehold ground rents.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8596","8596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757534","2017-09-11","Cabinet Office","2017-09-05","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when the Government's race audit findings will be published.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8638","8638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757535","2017-09-11","HM Treasury","2017-09-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many new projects in the UK have been (a) signed-off and (b) financed by the European Investment Bank in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8669","8669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757536","2017-09-11","HM Treasury","2017-09-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans his Department has to update the 1993 Reinsurance Act and the process of certifying terror attacks.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8601","8601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757537","2017-09-11","HM Treasury","2017-09-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he plans to publish the post-implementation review of PAYE Real Time Information.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8609","8609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757538","2017-09-07","HM Treasury","2017-09-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many procurements undertaken by his Department have taken more than (a) three months, (b) six months, (c) one year and (d) two years.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8766","8766"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757539","2017-09-11","HM Treasury","2017-09-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much his Department has paid from the public purse in compensation for errors relating to (a) tax-free and (b) 30 hours of free childcare; and what estimate he has made of how much will be paid out in total for such errors.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8693","8693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757540","2017-09-11","HM Treasury","2017-09-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of Heritage Maintenance Funds; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8700","8700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757541","2017-09-11","HM Treasury","2017-09-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many potentially eligible parents were unable to access their eligibility codes for their 30 hours of free childcare due to technical issues with the site administered by HM Revenue and Customs.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8694","8694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757542","2017-09-07","HM Treasury","2017-09-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much his Department has received from sub-lets on its estate in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8747","8747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757543","2017-09-11","HM Treasury","2017-09-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what progress the Government has made on its consultation report on the effect of VAT on tourism in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8880","8880"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757544","2017-09-07","HM Treasury","2017-09-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make it his policy to exempt automated external defibrillators from VAT.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8849","8849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757545","2017-09-07","HM Treasury","2017-09-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 17 July 2017 to Question 4658, whether the Government carried out any research or assessment before deciding to levy business rates on cash machines; and for what reasons and by whom that decision was taken to levy those rates.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8846","8846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757546","2017-09-07","HM Treasury","2017-09-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what potential effect treating payments to employees derived from image rights as earnings subject to taxation would have on the public purse.","Biography information for Charlie Elphicke","Charlie Elphicke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8823","8823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757547","2017-09-07","HM Treasury","2017-09-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on the economy of a reduction in UK fuel duty to (a) the EU average, (b) an equivalent rate to that used in France and (c) an equivalent rate to that used in Luxembourg; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Charlie Elphicke","Charlie Elphicke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8824","8824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757548","2017-09-07","HM Treasury","2017-09-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the fuel duty differential between the UK and each of the other 27 member states of the EU has been for each of the last five years for which data is available.","Biography information for Charlie Elphicke","Charlie Elphicke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8825","8825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757549","2017-09-07","HM Treasury","2017-09-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much his Department has paid in letting fees for its estate in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8785","8785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757550","2017-09-07","HM Treasury","2017-09-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the cost has been to the public purse of the Help to Buy ISA policy since the introduction of that scheme.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8945","8945"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757551","2017-09-07","HM Treasury","2017-09-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the cost has been to the public purse of the Help to Buy policy since the introduction of that scheme.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8946","8946"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757552","2017-09-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the effect of the national living wage on the number of low skilled jobs since the introduction of that wage.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8948","8948"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757553","2017-09-07","HM Treasury","2017-09-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many homebuyers have been exempt from stamp duty in the last five years.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8949","8949"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757554","2017-09-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 5 September 2017 to Question 5844, if he will commission an update of the 2012 estimate of the Audit Commission on the extent of tenancy fraud in the social housing sector and whether it is higher or lower as a result of Government initiatives.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8970","8970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757555","2017-09-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 5 September 2017 to Question 5844, what benefits resulted from the provision of £19 million to local authorities tackle tenancy fraud.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8971","8971"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757556","2017-09-07","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he plans to respond to the representations made by the Salvation Army on the effect of universal credit on the Salvation Army's provision of supported housing.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8954","8954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757557","2017-09-07","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to ensure the increase in provision of refuges in Gloucestershire.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8955","8955"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757558","2017-09-07","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether he plans to reassess the level of funding to be reclaimed from Stroud District Council as a result of changes to council tax and rent support arrangements.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8956","8956"
