"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600765","2016-10-17","Department for Transport","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he expects flights to recommence from the UK to Sharm-el-Sheikh.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48422","48422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600766","2016-10-17","Department for Transport","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans his Department has for the next public consultation on Crossrail 2.","Biography information for Stephen Hammond","Stephen Hammond","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48420","48420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600767","2016-10-17","Department for Transport","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans his Department has for further evaluation of the possibility of establishing direct flights from the UK to Erbil International Airport in Iraqi Kurdistan; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48356","48356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600768","2016-10-17","Department for Transport","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many British Transport Police officers there have been in each territorial division in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48347","48347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600769","2016-10-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment his Department has made of the likelihood of aeroplane manufacturing moving from the UK to other EU countries in the event of the UK leaving the European Aviation Safety Agency.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48374","48374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600770","2016-10-17","Department for Transport","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the UK leaving the EU on funding for the Civil Aviation Authority from its international activities.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48373","48373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600771","2016-10-17","Department for Transport","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he intends to negotiate continued UK participation in the European Open Skies aviation arrangement.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48372","48372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600772","2016-10-17","Department for Transport","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many minibuses have been delivered under his Department's Community Transport Minibus scheme; and how many such buses are still on order under that scheme.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48311","48311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600773","2016-10-17","Department for Transport","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many reports have been made to the British Transport Police using the 61016 text service in each territorial division in each quarter since its introduction.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48349","48349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600774","2016-10-17","Department for Transport","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much has been spent from the public purse on promoting and publicising the British Transport Police's 61016 text service in each quarter since its introduction.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48348","48348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600775","2016-10-17","Department for Transport","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what meetings have been held by (a) Ministers and (b) officials of his Department with the Rail Accident Investigation Branch (RAIB) on the investigation by the RAIB into train driver fatigue.","Biography information for Dr Andrew Murrison","Dr Andrew Murrison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48237","48237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600776","2016-10-17","Department for Transport","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans he has to certify UK aircraft, their engines and other related products for safety if the United Kingdom departs the European Air Safety Agency after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48300","48300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600777","2016-10-17","Department for Transport","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent steps he has taken to improve access to public transport for disabled people.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48222","48222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600778","2016-10-17","Department for Transport","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to increase the number of accessible taxis in the UK.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48223","48223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600779","2016-10-17","Department for Transport","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, on which dates (a) Ministers and (b) officials of his Department met representatives of (i) George Best Airport and (ii) the Northern Ireland Assembly to discuss the potential effect on jobs in Northern Ireland of airport expansion in South East England.","Biography information for Dr Andrew Murrison","Dr Andrew Murrison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48467","48467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600780","2016-10-17","Department for Transport","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many appeals against charges for use of the Dartford Crossing have been passed to the Traffic Penalty Tribunal in each of the last three years; and how many of those cases have subsequently been conceded by Highways England before being heard by the Tribunal.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48468","48468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600781","2016-10-17","Department for Transport","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that the outcomes of its proposed Accessibility Action Plan will improve the accessibility of public transport for autistic people.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48470","48470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600782","2016-10-17","Department for Transport","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the High Speed Rail Committee's recommendations on ecology in its report of March 2016, Government overview of the case for High Speed 2 Phase One and its environmental impacts, what the reasons are for the time taken for Natural England to publish its report into the net loss of biodiversity measurements; and when he expects that report to be published.","Biography information for Michael Fabricant","Michael Fabricant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48489","48489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600783","2016-10-17","Department for Transport","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when his Department plans to publish its Accessibility Action Plan.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48490","48490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600784","2016-10-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 7 September 2016 to Question 44365, whether the Health and Safety Executive holds any data on changes to work patterns in the mining industry in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48471","48471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600785","2016-10-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether his Department has made a decision not to provide any support for the British Steel Pension Scheme which would require new secondary legislation in the way proposed in the British Steel Pension Scheme: Public Consultation; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48455","48455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600786","2016-10-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies on benefit sanctions of the report by the Children's Society, The cost of being care free, published in June 2016.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48280","48280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600787","2016-10-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 8 September 2016 to Question 44899, if he will make readily available the number of people who applied for attendance allowance under the special rules for people with terminal illness in each of the last five years (a) before and (b) during the consultation on the devolution of attendance allowance.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48239","48239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600788","2016-10-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people have opted out of workplace pensions in each month since the inception of that scheme.","Biography information for Dr Andrew Murrison","Dr Andrew Murrison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48345","48345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600789","2016-10-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many officials employed by the Child Maintenance Service are responsible for (a) identifying and (b) supporting victims of (i) domestic and (ii) financial abuse.","Biography information for Dr Andrew Murrison","Dr Andrew Murrison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48346","48346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600790","2016-10-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what discussions he has had with the Pensions Ombudsman on how that body investigates instances of suspected fraudulent documents being received from pension trustees.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48381","48381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600791","2016-10-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what information his Department  holds on the number of fraudulent documents received by the Pensions Ombudsman in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48380","48380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600792","2016-10-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 5 September 2016 to Question 43519, what assessment he has made of the potential financial effect of proposed changes to the administration of attendance allowance on local authorities with the highest proportions of attendance allowance cases in payment.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48440","48440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600793","2016-10-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 9 September 2016 to Question 44858, if he will meet the hon. Member for Copeland and representatives of the Civil Nuclear Police Federation before Christmas 2016 to discuss the Civil Nuclear Constabulary Police Officers' retirement age.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48438","48438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600794","2016-10-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what meetings Ministers or officials of (a) his Department and (b) the Department for Business, Innovation and Skills had with Sir Richard Paniguian in the last 12 months; and on what dates those meeting took place.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48387","48387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600795","2016-10-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent discussions he has had with the CEOs of the Big Six energy companies on the availability of the cheapest energy tariff for existing customers.","Biography information for Callum McCaig","Callum McCaig","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48427","48427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600796","2016-10-17","Department for Education","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what (a) financial and (b) childcare support is offered to young women who work as apprentices in the (i) engineering, (ii) manufacturing, (iii) hospitality, (iv) IT, (v) transport and (vi) science sectors.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48284","48284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600797","2016-10-17","Department for Education","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she plans to encourage public sector employers to set gender targets when recruiting apprentices.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48285","48285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600798","2016-10-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the future role of open source software in industrial strategy (a) for the digital economy and (b) as an enabling platform; and what steps he is taking to support that software in relation to public sector procurement.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48304","48304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600799","2016-10-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent meetings he has had with Ministers of the Department for Culture, Media and Sport on rural superfast broadband.","Biography information for Dr Andrew Murrison","Dr Andrew Murrison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48217","48217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600800","2016-10-17","Department for Education","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when she plans to respond to the letter from the hon. Member for Blaydon of 19 August 2016 on the application of the Apprenticeship Levy in Scotland.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48469","48469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600801","2016-10-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect of proposed increases to electricity network costs on manufacturers.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48454","48454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600802","2016-10-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether there has been a recent change to the policy that the Government would take a 25 per cent equity stake in Tata Steel's UK assets if a sale was necessary to secure the future of UK steel.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48453","48453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600803","2016-10-17","Department for International Trade","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what discussions he has had with his counterparts in (a) Argentina, (b) Indonesia, (c) Saudi Arabia and (d) Turkey on negotiating trade deals with the UK.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48476","48476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600804","2016-10-17","Department for International Trade","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what recent meetings he has had with representatives from (a) Iceland, (b) Liechtenstein, (c) Norway and (d) Switzerland on trade with EFTA countries.","Biography information for Dr Andrew Murrison","Dr Andrew Murrison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48214","48214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600805","2016-10-17","Department for International Trade","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many civil servants who work for his Department work in each EU member state other than the United Kingdom; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48301","48301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600806","2016-10-17","Department for International Trade","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, pursuant to the Answer of 10 October 2016 to Question 46317, whether he plans to review the terms of those trade deals.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48275","48275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600807","2016-10-17","Department for International Trade","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many applicants his Department has received for trade negotiator positions; how many such applicants have been invited for interview; to how many such applicants job offers have been made; and how many such applicants have started work in his Department.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48262","48262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600808","2016-10-17","Department for International Trade","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many civil servants work for his Department in EU member states excluding the United Kingdom; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48340","48340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600809","2016-10-17","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many civil servants working in his Department have been seconded from other government departments; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48339","48339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600810","2016-10-17","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many civil servants are employed by his Department; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48338","48338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600811","2016-10-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will make it his policy to ensure that the UK intellectual property practitioners will continue to have the right to file European Trade Mark and design applications and appear on behalf of clients at the EU Intellectual Property Office after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Alex Chalk","Alex Chalk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48358","48358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600812","2016-10-17","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, for what reasons the Government plans to activate Article 50 of the Treaty on European Union by the end of March 2017.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48388","48388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600813","2016-10-17","Home Office","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to her oral contribution of 10 October 2016, Official Report, column 62, how an EU citizen demonstrates their having lived in the UK for five or more years; how citizenship is claimed after six years; which Department will be responsible for confirming the right to (a) remain and (b) citizenship; what certification of these rights will be provided; what estimate she has made of the cost to the applicant of that process; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48382","48382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600814","2016-10-17","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many civil servants who work for his Department work in each EU member state other than the UK; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48302","48302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600815","2016-10-17","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what recent meetings he has had with representatives from (a) Iceland, Liechtenstein, (c) Norway and (d) Switzerland on the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Dr Andrew Murrison","Dr Andrew Murrison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48225","48225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/604067","2016-10-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the potential implications for Zimbabwe's political and economic future in the event of the death of President Mugabe.","Biography information for Oliver Colvile","Oliver Colvile","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 906661","906661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/604257","2016-10-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the implications for his Department's policy on Yemen of the airstrike in Sanaa on 8 October 2016.","Biography information for Chris White","Chris White","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 906655","906655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/604258","2016-10-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he plans to have with Ministers of the Scottish Government on the role of that Government in negotiations on the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Roger Mullin","Roger Mullin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 906660","906660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/604259","2016-10-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will review the UK's support for the Saudi-led coalition forces operating in Yemen.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 906654","906654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/604260","2016-10-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what role his Department has taken in discussions with the EU on UK membership of the single market after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 906653","906653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599322","2016-10-17","Attorney General","2016-10-11","To ask the Attorney General, how many allegations of bribery of overseas parties by UK companies the Serious Fraud Office has received in each year since August 2012.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48054","48054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599323","2016-10-13","Attorney General","2016-10-11","To ask the Attorney General, which agreed EU directives have not yet been transposed directly into UK law; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48170","48170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599324","2016-10-13","Cabinet Office","2016-10-11","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, which agreed EU directives have not yet been transposed directly into UK law; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48171","48171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599326","2016-10-17","Home Office","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the total cost to the public purse has been of all (a) salaries, (b) transport, (c) hotel stays, (d) redundancy payments, (e) pension entitlements and (f) all other associated costs since the announcement of the Independent Inquiry into Child Sexual Abuse.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48064","48064"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599328","2016-10-13","Cabinet Office","2016-10-11","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of using blockchain and distributed ledger technologies in the public sector.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47976","47976"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599329","2016-10-17","Cabinet Office","2016-10-11","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether the Government plans to introduce restrictions on the posts that EU nationals are able to (a) work in and (b) apply for within the Civil Service; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47995","47995"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599330","2016-10-13","HM Treasury","2016-10-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with financial services industry bodies on tariffs for customers who do not access services online.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47964","47964"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599332","2016-10-17","HM Treasury","2016-10-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with the Irish government on the potential implications for economic growth (a) on the island of Ireland and (b) in Northern Ireland of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48006","48006"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599333","2016-10-17","HM Treasury","2016-10-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland on the potential effect of a change in the rate of VAT for tourism on employment creation in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48009","48009"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599334","2016-10-17","HM Treasury","2016-10-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate his Department has made of the number of full-time equivalent officials in his Department employed on cases of mandatory reconsideration; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48037","48037"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599335","2016-10-17","HM Treasury","2016-10-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate his Department has made of the number of full-time equivalent officials in his Department who are employed on cases where tax credits have been stopped by Concentrix; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48038","48038"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599336","2016-10-17","HM Treasury","2016-10-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 15 September 2016 to Question 45730, what estimate he has made of the current value of his Department's share in local partnerships.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48030","48030"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599338","2016-10-17","HM Treasury","2016-10-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many loans from the European Investment Bank were approved in the UK by (a) constituent region and nation and (b) local authority area in each of the last 10 years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48031","48031"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599339","2016-10-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what comparative assessment he has made of the effect of the increase in business rates on (a) state and (b) privately funded schools with roof-top solar photovoltaic panels.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47944","47944"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599341","2016-10-17","HM Treasury","2016-10-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 10 October 2016 to Question 46494, whether his Department keeps a record of the number of people who have had their tax credits stopped and subsequently reinstated by Concentrix in each of the last 12 months; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48079","48079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599342","2016-10-17","HM Treasury","2016-10-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many applications his Department has received for the Widening Access Tax Rebate Scheme for trainee psychologists in each year since the rebate scheme has been in operation.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48080","48080"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599343","2016-10-13","HM Treasury","2016-10-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, which agreed EU directives have not yet been transposed directly into UK law; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48187","48187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599345","2016-10-13","HM Treasury","2016-10-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the potential benefits of replacing the Bank of England's two per cent inflation target with a two to three per cent inflation target averaged over the business cycle","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48115","48115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599346","2016-10-17","HM Treasury","2016-10-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will estimate the potential change in (a) the number of jobs in the UK and (b) tax revenue collected by HM Treasury in the event of euro-denominated clearing being no longer permitted once the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48202","48202"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599347","2016-10-17","HM Treasury","2016-10-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will estimate the annual (a) percentage change and (b) change to the nearest million pounds in tax revenue to HM Treasury in the event of the UK leaving the EU without securing any preferential trade agreements and reverting to standard World Trade Organisation rules from current trading relationships.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48203","48203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599348","2016-10-17","HM Treasury","2016-10-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will estimate the percentage change in (a) trade, (b) foreign direct investment and (c) the level of productivity in the UK in the event of the UK leaving the EU without securing any preferential trade agreements and reverting to standard World Trade Organisation rules from current trading relationships.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48205","48205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599350","2016-10-17","HM Treasury","2016-10-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will estimate the (a) percentage change in GDP and (b) change in the number of jobs in the UK in the event of the UK leaving the EU without securing any preferential trade agreements and reverting to standard World Trade Organisation rules from current trading relationships.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48204","48204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599351","2016-10-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will publish the amount of business rate income generated in each local authority area in England for each of the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48168","48168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599352","2016-10-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will publish a review of the effectiveness of Local Economic Partnerships; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48167","48167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599354","2016-10-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what loans have been issued for what purposes to Business Improvement Districts in each (a) region of the UK and (b) local authority area in each of the last two years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48211","48211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599355","2016-10-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how much funding the UK received from the European Regional Development Agency in (a) total, (b) each action region of the UK and (c) each local authority area in each of the last 10 years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48165","48165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599358","2016-10-13","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2016-10-11","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, which local authorities have asked the Local Government Boundary Commission to consider changes to their boundaries; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48166","48166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599359","2016-10-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate his Department has (a) made and (b) received from outside sources of the increase in demand for social care services from local councils over the last three years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48138","48138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599361","2016-10-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many local authorities in England have held council tax referendums in each of the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48158","48158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599363","2016-10-13","Department for Education","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what criteria are used to require local authorities to contract out the statutory children's social work services; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48157","48157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599364","2016-10-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many enterprise zones there are in each (a) region and (b) local authority area in England; how long each zone has been in existence; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48159","48159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599365","2016-10-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he expects to publish the Local Government Settlement; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48160","48160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599366","2016-10-13","Department for Education","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which local authorities' children's social work services have been rated inadequate; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48156","48156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599367","2016-10-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he expects to publish a response to the consultation his Department launched in March 2015 on the future of Business Improvement Districts; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48162","48162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599368","2016-10-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will bring forward proposals for a further round of Regional Growth Funding; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48163","48163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599370","2016-10-13","Department for Transport","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions his Department has had with local authorities on the possible expansion of Heathrow and Gatwick airports; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48164","48164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599371","2016-10-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, which agreed EU directives have not yet been transposed directly into UK law; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48172","48172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599372","2016-10-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will make it his policy to devolve further fiscal powers to local authorities; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48161","48161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599373","2016-10-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what discussions with local authorities he is having on possible devolution deals; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48077","48077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599374","2016-10-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many representations he has received from business groups on the reform of business rates in the last six months; if he will publish such representations; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48073","48073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599375","2016-10-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what further steps he plans to take to give councils greater flexibility and control over budgets; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48074","48074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599377","2016-10-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what data his Department holds on the proportion of households without working smoke alarms in (a) England, (b) the North East, (c) Redcar and Cleveland and (d) Middlesbrough in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48061","48061"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599378","2016-10-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what further steps he plans to take to allow local authorities to use capital receipts from the sale of its assets to fund local authority services; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48075","48075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599379","2016-10-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, which devolution deals have been agreed between his Department and local authorities; when each such deal will come into force; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48076","48076"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599380","2016-10-18","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will review the operation of the scheme requiring letting agents to publicise their fees to consumers.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48049","48049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599382","2016-10-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, who has responsibility for delivering the Northern Powerhouse.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47977","47977"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599383","2016-10-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many responses his Department has received to the consultation on local government retention of business rates.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48015","48015"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599384","2016-10-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what his policy is on requiring areas which are bidding for devolved powers to introduce directly elected mayors.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47993","47993"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599385","2016-10-13","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent assessment she has made of the effectiveness of Part 10 of the Gambling Act 2005.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47992","47992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599387","2016-10-18","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what measures her Department is taking to ensure that all mobile phone operators have sufficient spectrum to meet future demands for mobile data; and what steps her Department is taking to prevent a dominant company controlling the market on spectrum availability.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48050","48050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599389","2016-10-17","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions she has had on the future of regional programming as part of the BBC Charter renewal process.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48067","48067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599390","2016-10-17","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent meetings she has had with the National Cyber Security Center on cyber resilience among small businesses.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48082","48082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599391","2016-10-17","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps she is taking to (a) support the development of an effective market in cyber insurance products for small businesses and (b) encourage the establishment of standards within that insurance industry.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48083","48083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599392","2016-10-17","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 12 September 2016 to Question 45219, on small businesses: cybercrime, how many certificates have been issued in each category.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48089","48089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599394","2016-10-13","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, which agreed EU directives have not yet been transposed directly into UK law; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48173","48173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599395","2016-10-18","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of the potential effect of establishment of the Fundraising Preference Service on charitable donations.","Biography information for Susan Elan Jones","Susan Elan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48210","48210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599396","2016-10-13","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps she is taking to encourage children not to access indecent images on social media.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48151","48151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599397","2016-10-13","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, in how many instances his Department's procurement section sought further information from a company with regard to potential corruption, bribery or fraud in the last two years.","Biography information for Lord Davies of Gower","Byron Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48114","48114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599399","2016-10-13","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to improve the quality of dental treatment available to armed forces personnel.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48153","48153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599400","2016-10-13","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which agreed EU directives have not yet been transposed directly into UK law; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48174","48174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599401","2016-10-17","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many times explosive ordinance officers were deployed to deal with incidents in Northern Ireland between 1 January 2016 and 1 July 2016.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48068","48068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599402","2016-10-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the statement by Ned Price, US National Security Council Spokesman, of 8 October 2016, on reviewing the US support provided to the Saudi-led coalition in the Yemen, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of the UK Government carrying out such a review of UK support.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48070","48070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599403","2016-10-13","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 2 September 2016 to Question 44352, for what contracts the largest three total payments were made to (a) PwC, (b) Deloitte, (c) Ernst and Young and (d) KPMG in the last three years.","Biography information for Dame Margaret Hodge","Margaret Hodge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48094","48094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599405","2016-10-17","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when his Department plans to respond to the letter from the hon. Member for Walsall North, dated 13 September 2016, on behalf of a constituent concerning HM2 helicopters.","Biography information for Mr David Winnick","Mr David Winnick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48041","48041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599406","2016-10-17","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department is investigating allegations that the Saudi-led coalition deployed UK manufactured cluster munitions; and whether UK military personnel or UK aircraft were involved in the deployment of such munitions.","Biography information for Dr Rupa Huq","Dr Rupa Huq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48045","48045"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599408","2016-10-17","Department for Education","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many colleges which were not recognised or listed have been shut down in each of the last three years; and how many such colleges are currently under investigation.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48032","48032"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599409","2016-10-17","Department for Education","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will estimate the cost to the public purse of the Educational Excellence Everywhere White Paper consultation document.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48033","48033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599410","2016-10-17","Department for Education","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many level 2 apprenticeships have been available in her Department in each year since 2010; how many such apprenticeships were completed in full; and how many such apprentices subsequently progressed to level 3 or above.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48034","48034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599411","2016-10-18","Department for Education","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will estimate the proportion of funding for extended school activities in primary schools in 2015-16 which came from parental contributions in (a) England, (b) the North East and (c) Sunderland.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48047","48047"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599412","2016-10-17","Department for Education","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many level 3 apprenticeships have been available in her Department in each year since 2010; how many such apprenticeships were completed in full; and how many such apprentices subsequently progressed to level 4 or above.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48035","48035"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599414","2016-10-17","Department for Education","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many times her Department has used the services of Denford Associates in each of the last five financial years; what work was so undertaken; and what the cost to the public purse was on each such occasion.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48036","48036"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599415","2016-10-13","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the recent statement of the Secretary of State for Defence on increasing the number of cadet units in state schools across the UK, what steps he plans to help ensure that those units provide opportunities for young people from ethnic minority and vulnerable backgrounds.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48017","48017"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599416","2016-10-17","Department for Education","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment she has made of disparities in funding for early-years education across England; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47997","47997"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599417","2016-10-17","Department for Education","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the announcement made by the Department for Culture, Media and Sport on 10 October 2016 that the Government plans to provide training in basic digital skills for adults, what funding her Department has allocated for that purpose; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47994","47994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599420","2016-10-17","Department for Education","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much the Education Funding Agency has spent to date on refurbishing the former East Ham Police Station; and how much of that sum was spent on demolition of the former accommodation for police officers.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47979","47979"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599421","2016-10-13","Department for Education","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many pupils with special educational needs in schools in England (a) have an education, health and care plan and (b) are educated in a special school.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47943","47943"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599423","2016-10-18","Department for Education","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to improve participation rates in extended school activities of primary school pupils from disadvantaged backgrounds.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48048","48048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599424","2016-10-18","Department for Education","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the effect the availability of childcare provision of extended schools has had on reducing (a) the gender pay gap, (b) child poverty, and (c) workless households in England.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48051","48051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599425","2016-10-17","Department for Education","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what data her Department holds on the number of children who rely on public transport to get to school in (a) England and (b) the North East.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48062","48062"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599426","2016-10-13","Department for Education","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the effect of the level of parental contributions required to fund extended school activities on participation of pupils pupils from low-income families in such activities.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48102","48102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599428","2016-10-13","Department for Education","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which agreed EU directives have not yet been transposed directly into UK law; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48175","48175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599429","2016-10-13","Department for Education","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that sprinkler systems are installed in all schools.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48152","48152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599430","2016-10-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate her Department has made of the number of cattle which have died of disease or were put down on account of disease in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48140","48140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599431","2016-10-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to reduce levels of knotweed proliferation; and what assessment she has made of the potential merits of making house and land owners more responsible for uncontrolled weed growth.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48143","48143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599432","2016-10-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate her Department has made of the number of pigs which have died of disease or were put down on account of disease in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48141","48141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599434","2016-10-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to enforce the EU-wide ban on 37 invasive species.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48142","48142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599435","2016-10-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, which agreed EU directives have not yet been transposed directly into UK law; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48176","48176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599436","2016-10-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, which local authorities have breached legal air quality limits in the last year.","Biography information for Neil Parish","Neil Parish","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47949","47949"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599437","2016-10-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she has taken to encourage local authorities to implement a voluntary Clean Air Zone; and what estimate she has made of how many will do so within the next 12 months.","Biography information for Neil Parish","Neil Parish","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47950","47950"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599439","2016-10-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions she has had with water suppliers on tariffs for customers who do not elect to pay for services online.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47966","47966"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599440","2016-10-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the potential implications of UK withdrawal from the EU for the rice milling industry.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Mrs Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48046","48046"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599442","2016-10-17","Department for International Development","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is taking to support projects that encourage co-operation and co-existence between Israelis and Palestinians.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Mrs Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47983","47983"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599444","2016-10-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, which agreed EU directives have not yet been transposed directly into UK law; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48178","48178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599446","2016-10-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his UN counterparts on invoking UN Resolution 337A, Uniting for Peace, in order to convene an emergency Special Session of the General Assembly on Syria.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48201","48201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599447","2016-10-13","Department for International Development","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what diplomatic steps her Department is taking to assist Ethiopia with famine relief and support in dealing with drought.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48155","48155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599448","2016-10-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to the Uzbekistan government on reports of (a) recent sentencing of Christians for possession of religious literature and (b) the deduction of the salaries of people who have previously been found guilty of possessing religious literature.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48066","48066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599450","2016-10-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with (a) the Prime Minister, (b) the Attorney General and (c) the Secretary of State for Defence on the implications for Government policies of the Joint Declaration for the Export and Subsequent Use of Armed or Strike-Enabled unmanned Aerial Vehicles issued on 5 October 2016.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48069","48069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599451","2016-10-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will support the establishment of a UN Inquiry into alleged war crimes committed during the Yemen civil war.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48071","48071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599452","2016-10-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will raise with the Sudanese government reports of attacks on Christians and proposals by the Sudanese government to demolish church property in the Bahri region of Khartoum.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48065","48065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599454","2016-10-17","Department of Health","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of proposed changes in the level of community pharmacy funding on 100 hour pharmacies.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48091","48091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599455","2016-10-13","Department of Health","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many midwives from other EU countries work at hospitals in (a) Royal Liverpool and Broadgreen University Hospital NHS Trust, (b) St Helens and Knowsley Hospital Services NHS Trust, (c) Aintree University Hospitals NHS Foundation Trust, (d) Wirral University Teaching Hospital NHS Foundation Trust, (e) Southport and Ormskirk NHS Trust and (f) Warrington and Halton Hospitals NHS Foundation Trust.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48121","48121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599456","2016-10-17","Department of Health","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that GP surgeries have the (a) resources and (b) training to provide a patient-friendly service, including appointments with a preferred GP in advance and at a time convenient to patients; and what rights patients have if GP surgeries do not meet such standards.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48090","48090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599457","2016-10-13","Department of Health","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the average waiting times for treatment in the accident and emergency departments of the (a) Royal Liverpool and Broadgreen University Hospital NHS Trust, (b) St Helens and Knowsley Hospital Services NHS Trust, (c) Aintree University Hospitals NHS Foundation Trust, (d) Wirral University Teaching Hospital NHS Foundation Trust, (e) Southport and Ormskirk NHS Trust in the last six months.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48123","48123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599459","2016-10-17","Cabinet Office","2016-10-11","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people have been diagnosed with the rare cancer rhabdomyosarcoma in each of the last five years by (a) age group and (b) gender; and what proportion of those people died in each of those years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48088","48088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599460","2016-10-13","Department of Health","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the number of cancelled elective operations in the (a) Royal Liverpool and Broadgreen University Hospital NHS Trust, (b) St Helens and Knowsley Hospital Services NHS Trust, (c) Aintree University Hospitals NHS Foundation Trust, (d) Wirral University Teaching Hospital NHS Foundation Trust, (e) Southport and Ormskirk NHS Trust and (f) Warrington and Halton Hospitals NHS Foundation Trust in the last six months.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48124","48124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599461","2016-10-13","Department of Health","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he take steps to raise awareness among pregnant women of the (a) risks of alcohol consumption and (b) benefits of zero alcohol consumption.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48111","48111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599462","2016-10-13","Department of Health","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the budget deficits are at the (a) Royal Liverpool and Broadgreen University Hospital NHS Trust, (b) St Helens and Knowsley Hospital Services NHS Trust, (c) Aintree University Hospitals NHS Foundation Trust, (d) Wirral University Teaching Hospital NHS Foundation Trust, (e) Southport and Ormskirk NHS Trust and (f) Warrington and Halton Hospitals NHS Foundation Trust.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48125","48125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599464","2016-10-17","Department of Health","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions his Department has had with key health stakeholders on providing guidance for GPs on extending the length of appointment slots and increasing the number of appointments bookable for each GP each day.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48085","48085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599465","2016-10-13","Department of Health","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to reduce the number of (a) obese and (b) overweight children under the age of 11; and if he will take steps to cooperate with (a) his counterparts in the devolved administrations, (b) GPs, (c) teachers and (d) parents to help reduce that number.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48108","48108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599466","2016-10-13","Department of Health","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many doctors from other EU countries work at hospitals in (a) Royal Liverpool and Broadgreen University Hospital NHS Trust, (b) St Helens and Knowsley Hospital Services NHS Trust, (c) Aintree University Hospitals NHS Foundation Trust, (d) Wirral University Teaching Hospital NHS Foundation Trust, (e) Southport and Ormskirk NHS Trust and (f) Warrington and Halton Hospitals NHS Foundation Trust.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48120","48120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599467","2016-10-17","Department of Health","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if his Department will take steps to encourage people not to eat too soon before they plan to sleep in order to avoid increased risk of heart attacks.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48086","48086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599469","2016-10-17","Department of Health","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to help prevent the Zika virus from entering the UK.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48087","48087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599470","2016-10-13","Department of Health","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much (a) Royal Liverpool and Broadgreen University Hospital NHS Trust, (b) St Helens and Knowsley Hospital Services NHS Trust, (c) Aintree University Hospitals NHS Foundation Trust, (d) Wirral University Teaching Hospital NHS Foundation Trust, (e) Southport and Ormskirk NHS Trust and (f) Warrington and Halton Hospitals NHS Foundation Trust spent on agency medical staff in (i) 2014-15 and (ii) 2015-16.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48122","48122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599471","2016-10-13","Department of Health","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to improve early diagnosis of childhood cancers; and if he will make available additional funding to improve such early diagnosis.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48110","48110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599472","2016-10-17","Department of Health","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the report by Cancer Research UK on the barriers to people making GP appointments, published in the Public Health Journal in October 2016.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48081","48081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599473","2016-10-13","Department of Health","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions the Chemotherapy Clinical Reference Group has had on the use of bisphosphonates for the indication of preventing secondary breast cancer since July 2015.","Biography information for Dame Caroline Spelman","Dame Caroline Spelman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48107","48107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599475","2016-10-13","Department of Health","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many NICE highly specialised technology evaluations are expected to take place over the next two years.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48117","48117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599476","2016-10-17","Department of Health","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to his announcement of 27 September 2016 on extra funding for mental health, what steps he is taking to ensure that funding reaches children who have experienced abuse, neglect or live in poverty.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48078","48078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599477","2016-10-17","Department of Health","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to enable more radiologists to be trained and approved to carry out breast cancer mammogram imagery.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48084","48084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599479","2016-10-13","Department of Health","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 19 September 2016 to Question 46209, what the relationship will be between the clinical expert groups and the recently established cross-Clinical Reference Group working parties.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48106","48106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599480","2016-10-13","Department of Health","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 19 September 2016 to Question 46209, when he expects terms of reference to be published for (a) the clinical expert groups and (b) the clinical steering group.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48105","48105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599481","2016-10-13","Department of Health","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 19 September 2016 to Question 46209, when NHS England plans to publish the service guidance documents produced by the clinical reference groups.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48104","48104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599482","2016-10-17","Department of Health","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of particle pollutants on children's health and development in the UK.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48056","48056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599483","2016-10-17","Department of Health","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment has been made of the potential effect of proposed changes to pharmacy funding on the ability of local authorities to deliver local public health improvement.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48055","48055"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599485","2016-10-13","Department of Health","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 2 September 2016 to Question 44352, for what contracts the largest three total payments were made to (a) PwC, (b) Deloitte, (c) Ernst and Young and (d) KPMG in the last three years.","Biography information for Dame Margaret Hodge","Margaret Hodge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48095","48095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599486","2016-10-13","Department of Health","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy on the sale of ex-emergency service vehicles.","Biography information for Gerald Jones","Gerald Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48099","48099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599487","2016-10-13","Department of Health","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many children are born each year in England with Duchenne muscular dystrophy; how many people are living with this condition; and how many such people do receive Translarna.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48136","48136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599488","2016-10-13","Department of Health","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to support women suffering side-effects from hormone replacement therapy.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48145","48145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599490","2016-10-13","Department of Health","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will publish the names of chair and members of the Specialised Ophthalmology Services Reference Group.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48135","48135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599491","2016-10-13","Department of Health","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether NHS England is looking at treatments for Leber's Hereditary Optic Neuropathy.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48134","48134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599492","2016-10-13","Department of Health","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what new treatments for Duchenne muscular dystrophy have been notified to the Horizon Scanning Research and Intelligence Centre in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48137","48137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599493","2016-10-17","Department of Health","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the total number of supplementary hours worked by pharmacists beyond the hours mandated in the standard NHS contract.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48093","48093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599495","2016-10-13","Department of Health","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what responsibilities the Government has for delivering services to teenagers and young adults with cancer.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48113","48113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599496","2016-10-17","Department of Health","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many pregnant women received treatment from alcohol services in each region of England in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48200","48200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599497","2016-10-17","Department of Health","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many pregnant women in (a) Liverpool Wavertree constituency, (b) Liverpool, (c) the Liverpool City Region and (d) England received treatment from alcohol services in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48199","48199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599499","2016-10-13","Department of Health","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to increase the availability of epithalial suspension for people with ulcers.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48148","48148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599501","2016-10-13","Department of Health","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to increase the number of organ donors from ethnic minorities.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48147","48147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599502","2016-10-13","Department of Health","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many abortions have been performed on the grounds of possible abnormalities detected in the womb in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48144","48144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599504","2016-10-17","Department of Health","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of training for midwives on foetal alcohol syndrome.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48197","48197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599505","2016-10-13","Department of Health","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which agreed EU directives have not yet been transposed directly into UK law; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48179","48179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599506","2016-10-17","Department of Health","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of the cost to the NHS of (a) foetal alcohol syndrome and (b) foetal alcohol syndrome disorders.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48198","48198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599507","2016-10-13","Department of Health","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he plans for new implants for people diagnosed with damaged shoulder tendons to be available on the NHS.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48146","48146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599508","2016-10-13","Department of Health","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department has made an estimate of the effect on smoker mortality levels as a result of people giving up smoking by using electronic vaping devices in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47958","47958"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599510","2016-10-17","Department of Health","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of the number of patients who have been denied a second allogeneic stem cell transplant following an individual funding request in each of the last three years; and what estimate his Department has made of the associated cost saving to the health service.","Biography information for Colleen Fletcher","Colleen Fletcher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47980","47980"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599511","2016-10-17","Department of Health","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to review the outcomes of NHS England's clinical policy prioritisation process for specialised services; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Colleen Fletcher","Colleen Fletcher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47981","47981"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599512","2016-10-17","Department of Health","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 10 October 2016 to Question 46088, on childbirth: roads, if his Department will collect information on the number of babies born by the side of the road in England in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47982","47982"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599513","2016-10-13","Department of Health","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 10 October 2016 to Question 46089, if his Department will collect information on the number of babies born in transit between Stafford and Stoke Royal University Hospital.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47963","47963"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599514","2016-10-13","Cabinet Office","2016-10-11","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many deaths from the abuse of nitrous oxide were recorded for each region of England and Wales for each (a) age and (b) gender in 2015.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47932","47932"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599516","2016-10-13","Cabinet Office","2016-10-11","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many deaths from volatile substance abuse were recorded in each region of England and Wales for each (a) substance, (b) age and (c) gender in 2015.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47933","47933"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599517","2016-10-13","Department of Health","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans (a) NICE and (b) NHS England has to issue a consultation on changes to the highly specialised technologies evaluation programme.","Biography information for John Glen","John Glen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47935","47935"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599520","2016-10-13","Department of Health","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential for community pharmacies to (a) deliver early identification of medical complaints and ongoing patient monitoring and (b) help reduce hospital admission rates.","Biography information for Nigel Adams","Nigel Adams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47927","47927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599521","2016-10-17","Department of Health","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the cost to local NHS consortium formed of Lewisham and Greenwich Healthcare Trust, Local Care Networks and Oxleas Trust was of preparing their unsuccessful tender for the contract to provide musculoskeletal services in Greenwich; and if he will assess the effect of such spending on resources available for services to patients; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Clive Efford","Clive Efford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48024","48024"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599522","2016-10-17","Department of Health","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the implications are for patients who remain on the waiting list for orthopaedic surgery on 1 December 2016 of Circle Holdings PLC being awarded the contract for musculoskeletal services in Greenwich; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Clive Efford","Clive Efford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48025","48025"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599523","2016-10-17","Department of Health","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many NHS prescription charge penalty charge notices were issued in the last year for which figures are available; and how much was recovered in (a) prescription income and (b) penalty charges and surcharges in the last year for which information is available.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48026","48026"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599524","2016-10-17","Department of Health","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with Greenwich Clinical Commissioning Group on the capacity of local health providers meeting the Getting it Right First Time requirements in Greenwich since the contract to provide musculoskeletal services was awarded to Circle Holdings PLC; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Clive Efford","Clive Efford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48022","48022"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599526","2016-10-13","Department of Health","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress his Department has made on improving the performance of ambulance services which are in special measures.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48018","48018"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599527","2016-10-17","Department of Health","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many proceedings for debt recovery the NHS has issued in the county court for NHS prescription charges and penalties in the last year for which information is available; how many such proceedings resulted in recovery of the outstanding money.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48027","48027"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599528","2016-10-17","Department of Health","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with Greenwich Clinical Commissioning Group since the award of the contract to provide musculoskeletal services to Circle Holdings PLC on the Sustainability and Transformation Plans for elective orthopaedic surgery in Greenwich; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Clive Efford","Clive Efford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48023","48023"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599529","2016-10-13","Department of Health","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he has taken to improve public and patient involvement in the NHS.","Biography information for Mr Geoffrey Cox","Mr Geoffrey Cox","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47968","47968"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599531","2016-10-13","Department of Health","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he plans to appeal NICE's draft guidance on asfotase alfa for treating paediatric-onset hypophosphatasia, issued in September 2016.","Biography information for John Glen","John Glen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47969","47969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599532","2016-10-13","Department of Health","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that asfotase alfa is available on the NHS to all patients who may benefit from it.","Biography information for John Glen","John Glen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47970","47970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599533","2016-10-13","Department of Health","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many instances were recorded in which a young person was restrained physically by placing their face on the floor in a children's mental health ward in each year from 2012.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47971","47971"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599534","2016-10-13","Department of Health","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many instances were recorded in which a person was restrained physically by placing their face on the floor in a mental health ward in each year from 2012.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47972","47972"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599535","2016-10-17","Department of Health","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions he has had with representatives of the Gloucestershire Hospitals NHS Foundation Trust on the financial deficit of that Trust.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47996","47996"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599537","2016-10-17","Department of Health","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what support his Department makes available for young people diagnosed with Crohn's disease.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48000","48000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599538","2016-10-17","Department of Health","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with Ministers in the devolved administrations on fully funded NHS Continuing Healthcare.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48005","48005"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599539","2016-10-17","Department of Health","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect of decisions taken by Circle Holdings PLC in the delivery of musculoskeletal services in Greenwich on the financial capacity of the local healthcare trust to sustain accident and emergency services at University Hospital Lewisham and Queen Elizabeth Hospital Woolwich; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Clive Efford","Clive Efford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48002","48002"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599540","2016-10-13","Department of Health","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with Greenwich Clinical Commissioning Group on the future of the Fracture Clinic Service and physiotherapy service in Greenwich and whether that service is included in the contract awarded to Circle Holdings PLC to provide musculoskeletal services; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Clive Efford","Clive Efford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48011","48011"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599542","2016-10-13","Department of Health","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with Lewisham and Greenwich Healthcare Trust on progress towards meeting the Getting it Right First Time requirements since the contract for musculoskeletal services was awarded to Circle Holdings PLC; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Clive Efford","Clive Efford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48012","48012"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599543","2016-10-13","Department of Health","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to provide support for (a) junior doctors and (b) other medical staff employed in hospitals who are experiencing stress.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48109","48109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599544","2016-10-13","Department of Health","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions he has held on the devolution of health services in the Liverpool City Region.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48190","48190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599545","2016-10-13","Department of Health","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people in the Liverpool City Region are currently on a waiting list for elective surgery.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48191","48191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599547","2016-10-13","Department of Health","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people in the Liverpool City Region are currently on a waiting list for an outpatient hospital appointment.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48192","48192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599548","2016-10-13","Department of Health","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much was spent per head on GP services in (a) Knowsley Clinical Commissioning Group area, (b) comparator clinical commissioning groups and (c) England in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48193","48193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599549","2016-10-13","Department of Health","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to his Department's press release entitled, Department of Health's settlement at the Spending Review 2015, published on 25 November 2015, how the investment of up to 300 million per year on diagnostics will be spent in 2016-17.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48194","48194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599550","2016-10-13","Department of Health","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of changes in funding for pharmacies on patient safety.","Biography information for Derek Thomas","Derek Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48195","48195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599552","2016-10-17","Home Office","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the criteria for inclusion in the limited post-study work visa pilot were; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48003","48003"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599553","2016-10-17","Home Office","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 21 July 2016 to Question 42843, whether all necessary checks were completed on the departure of the ferry Barfleur from Cherbourg to Poole.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48028","48028"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599554","2016-10-17","Home Office","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many unaccompanied children the UK has accepted from the Jungle near Calais; and what estimate the Government has made of the number of such children the UK will take as a consequence of the Dubs amendment.","Biography information for Dr Rupa Huq","Dr Rupa Huq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48044","48044"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599556","2016-10-13","Home Office","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she plans to review the citizenship process for EU nationals married to British citizens.","Biography information for Drew Hendry","Drew Hendry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47941","47941"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599557","2016-10-13","Home Office","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many citizenship applications from EU nationals have been rejected as a result of changes to the rules on the evidence required to demonstrate permanent residence since those changes came into force.","Biography information for Drew Hendry","Drew Hendry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47942","47942"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599558","2016-10-13","Home Office","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which agreed EU directives have not yet been transposed directly into UK law; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48180","48180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599559","2016-10-17","Home Office","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which contractors have been sanctioned for breaching contractual obligations in relation to accommodation for asylum seekers in (a) Birmingham, (b) the West Midlands and (c) England in the last two years; when each such contractor was sanctioned; and what each sanction so applied was.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48040","48040"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599561","2016-10-13","Home Office","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to speed up family reunification in the UK for unaccompanied refugee children currently in Europe.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48101","48101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599562","2016-10-13","Home Office","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many police cars were sold by police forces in England and Wales in each year between 2010 and 2015.","Biography information for Gerald Jones","Gerald Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48098","48098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599563","2016-10-17","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment her Department has made of the levels of the use of (a) illegal drugs and (b) legal highs in prisons in the UK in each of the last 5 years.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48060","48060"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599564","2016-10-13","Department for International Development","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking in co-operation with UN agencies to tackle the increase in child brides in refugee camps and conflict areas.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48097","48097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599566","2016-10-13","Department for International Development","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 2 September 2016 to Question 44352, for what contracts the largest three total payments were made to (a) PwC, (b) Deloitte, (c) Ernst and Young and (d) KPMG in the last three years.","Biography information for Dame Margaret Hodge","Margaret Hodge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48096","48096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599567","2016-10-13","Department for International Development","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, which agreed EU directives have not yet been transposed directly into UK law; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48181","48181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599568","2016-10-13","Department for International Development","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to assist Ethiopia with famine relief and support in dealing with draught.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48149","48149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599569","2016-10-13","Department for International Development","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to increase investment in decentralised renewable energy to benefit the world's poorest people.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48116","48116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599570","2016-10-13","Department for International Development","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if the Government will take steps to ensure that UK aid to Malawi funds long-term transport infrastructure, irrigation, diversification of farming and food products projects.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47956","47956"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599572","2016-10-13","Department for International Development","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what her policy is on UK support for the global eradication of polio; and what discussions she has had with her counterparts in Pakistan, Afghanistan and Nigeria on eradication of that disease in those countries.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48019","48019"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599574","2016-10-13","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, on how many occasions a level 3 fine was issued under the provisions of section 168 of the Equality Act 2010, relating to assistance dogs in taxis, in each year since 2011.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47973","47973"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599575","2016-10-13","Department of Health","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of the number of young offenders residing within the justice system who have a diagnosed mental health disorder.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47974","47974"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599576","2016-10-13","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when the Government plans to bring forward legislation to reform the law relating to marital contracts.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Djanogly","Mr Jonathan Djanogly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47957","47957"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599577","2016-10-13","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many young offenders under the age of 18 have been admitted to a children's mental health ward in each month since January 2014.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47975","47975"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599579","2016-10-13","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many young offenders under the age of 18 have been admitted to an adult mental health ward in each month since January 2014.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47960","47960"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599581","2016-10-13","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the powers are of the Victims' Commissioner.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47928","47928"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599582","2016-10-13","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether any amendments will be made to the Victims' Code as a result of the (a) coming into force of the EU Directive on victims' rights and (b) result of the EU membership referendum.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47929","47929"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599583","2016-10-13","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether she plans to bring forward a green paper on the case for a victims' law during the current parliamentary session.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47930","47930"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599585","2016-10-13","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether the Victims' Commissioner has the authority to investigate complaints about breaches of the Victims' Code; and whether the Commissioner can make recommendations.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47931","47931"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599586","2016-10-17","Department of Health","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the proportion of the prison population affected by (a) foetal alcohol syndrome and (b) foetal alcohol spectrum disorder.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48196","48196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599588","2016-10-13","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which agreed EU directives have not yet been transposed directly into UK law; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48183","48183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599589","2016-10-13","Northern Ireland Office","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, which agreed EU directives have not yet been transposed directly into UK law; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48184","48184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599591","2016-10-17","Northern Ireland Office","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what steps he plans to take to retain the network of electoral offices in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48008","48008"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599593","2016-10-17","Northern Ireland Office","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what the Government's policy is on the nature of the border controls between the UK and the Republic of Ireland after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Dr Rupa Huq","Dr Rupa Huq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48042","48042"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599594","2016-10-17","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether he plans for any trade agreement between the UK and EU to come into force after the UK leaves the EU to be undertaken alongside negotiations on the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Dr Rupa Huq","Dr Rupa Huq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48043","48043"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599595","2016-10-13","Prime Minister","2016-10-11","To ask the Prime Minister, on what occasions she has met and conversed with members of the public in her official capacity since she became Prime Minister on 13 July 2016.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47985","47985"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599597","2016-10-13","Scotland Office","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what opportunities are available to households in Scotland with dynamically teleswitched meters to switch between electricity suppliers.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47988","47988"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599599","2016-10-13","Scotland Office","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what tariffs are available to households in Scotland with dynamically teleswitched meters that may want to switch between electricity suppliers.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47989","47989"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599600","2016-10-13","Scotland Office","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how many households in (a) Scotland and (b) the Highland area of Scotland have their electricity supplies controlled by dynamically teleswitched meters.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48013","48013"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599601","2016-10-13","Scotland Office","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, which agreed EU directives have not yet been transposed directly into UK law; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48185","48185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599603","2016-10-13","Department for Transport","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which agreed EU directives have not yet been transposed directly into UK law; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48186","48186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599604","2016-10-17","Department for Transport","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the total budget is of the team of writers being hired by his Department to help write the story of High Speed 2 from inception to present day.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48052","48052"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599605","2016-10-17","Department for Transport","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans he has to ensure that his Department's officials being recruited to help write the story of High Speed 2 from inception to the present day meet with all hon. Members representing parliamentary constituencies along the route.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48053","48053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599606","2016-10-13","Department for Transport","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions he has had with the Chancellor of the Exchequer on the introduction of tolls on the Mersey Gateway and Silver Jubilee bridges; and whether a decision has been taken on discounts for use of those bridges for local businesses and residents.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48119","48119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599608","2016-10-13","Department for Transport","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect of tolls on the Mersey Gateway and Silver Jubilee bridges on the (a) finances, (b) employment levels, (c) employment choices and (d) road travel habits of residents of Knowsley.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48118","48118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599609","2016-10-17","Department for Transport","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when the Government plans to respond to the recommendations of the Law Commission Report on taxi and private hire vehicle licensing, published in May 2014; and whether it plans to take steps to permit more local authority cross-border use of such vehicles.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48029","48029"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599610","2016-10-17","Department for Transport","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to reduce the number of people using mobile phones while driving; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48039","48039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599611","2016-10-18","Department for Transport","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, for what reasons his Department deploys speed cameras that photograph vehicles from the (a) front and (b) rear on (i) trunk roads and (ii) motorways; and for what reasons his Department does not have a consistent policy on the deployment and use of such speed cameras.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47984","47984"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599613","2016-10-17","Department for Transport","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the job vacancy notice DFT/649/16/DFTC, published by his Department in October 2016, how his Department expects the report and slide pack which form part of the project to write the story of High Speed 2 from inception to the present day to be used; and who his Department expects to use that report and slide pack.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48208","48208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599614","2016-10-17","Department for Transport","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the job vacancy notice DFT/649/16/DFTC, published by his Department in October 2016, who will be responsible for editing the report and slide pack which form part of the project to write the story of High Speed 2 from inception to the present day.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48209","48209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599615","2016-10-13","Wales Office","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, which agreed EU directives have not yet been transposed directly into UK law; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48188","48188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599616","2016-10-13","Women and Equalities","2016-10-11","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what steps she is taking to improve the representation of women at senior executive levels in (a) FTSE 100 and (b) all businesses.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48133","48133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599618","2016-10-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to address levels of discrimination in the work-place for women who are pregnant.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48150","48150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599619","2016-10-13","Department for Education","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will estimate the number of employers which publish targets for the ratio of male to female apprentices.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48128","48128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599620","2016-10-17","Cabinet Office","2016-10-11","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment he has made of the effect of proposed boundary changes on the potential number of female hon. Members in the next Parliament.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48001","48001"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599621","2016-10-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when his Department plans to publish its Life Changes Strategy.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47998","47998"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599623","2016-10-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 8 September 2016 to Question 44901, if he will make the advertising costs of attendance allowance readily available either (a) during or (b) after the consultation on the devolution of attendance allowance.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48010","48010"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599624","2016-10-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether his Department's staff performance monitoring includes key performance indicators on how many personal independence payment (PIP) claims are (a) accepted and (b) rejected by those staff who are PIP assessors.","Biography information for Philip Boswell","Phil Boswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47987","47987"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599625","2016-10-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether personal independence payment (PIP) assessors employed by (a) his Department, (b) Capita and (c) Atos Healthcare have targets of how many PIP claims they (i) reject and (ii) accept.","Biography information for Philip Boswell","Phil Boswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47986","47986"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599626","2016-10-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what qualifications are required of people who work as personal independence payment assessors.","Biography information for Philip Boswell","Phil Boswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48021","48021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599627","2016-10-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what measures his Department has put in place to ensure that terminally ill patients' needs are fully considered during personal independence payment assessments.","Biography information for Drew Hendry","Drew Hendry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47939","47939"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599629","2016-10-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, in a case where an applicant has been refused employment and support allowance (ESA), the disallowance has been confirmed following mandatory reconsideration and an appeal against the refusal has been submitted, in what circumstances ESA is payable pending the outcome of the appeal.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47978","47978"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599630","2016-10-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what criteria determine whether personal independence payment assessors receive financial bonuses in addition to their salary.","Biography information for Philip Boswell","Phil Boswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47959","47959"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599632","2016-10-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 8 September 2016 to Question 44898, if he will make it his policy to collect the total administrative costs related to attendance allowance in 2015-16 (a) during the consultation and (b) after the consultation on the devolution of attendance allowance.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48103","48103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599633","2016-10-13","Cabinet Office","2016-10-11","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate his Department has made of the net change in the number of jobs in the UK since 23 June 2016.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48154","48154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599634","2016-10-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to safeguard the jobs of EU nationals living in the UK after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48139","48139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599636","2016-10-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the report by the Children's Society, The cost of being care free, published in June 2016, if he will take steps to provide additional protection for care leavers to reduce the number of benefits sanctions being applied to such people.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48112","48112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599637","2016-10-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 8 September 2016 to Question 44900, if he will publish the number of people with cancer who applied for attendance allowance under the special rules for people with terminal illness in each of the last five years either (a) during or (b) after the consultation on the devolution of attendance allowance.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48092","48092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599638","2016-10-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department is taking to promote and enable partners to share parental leave.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48131","48131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599639","2016-10-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what research his Department has recently undertaken into the potential benefits of increasing paternity leave for men.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48132","48132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599640","2016-10-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, which agreed EU directives have not yet been transposed directly into UK law; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48189","48189"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599642","2016-10-13","Department for Education","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to prevent wage discrepancies between male and female apprentices.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48130","48130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599643","2016-10-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, which agreed EU directives have not yet been transposed directly into UK law; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48169","48169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599644","2016-10-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will regulate the sale of ex-emergency service vehicles.","Biography information for Gerald Jones","Gerald Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48100","48100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599645","2016-10-13","Department for Education","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what support is on offer to apprentices who need help covering childcare costs and if she will take steps to extend such support to match that available to other workers.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48129","48129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599646","2016-10-13","Department for Education","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to  increase diversity in apprenticeships.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48127","48127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599648","2016-10-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how much has been paid to social care workers by employers since HM Revenue and Customs introduced the self-correction process for recovering arrears for workers paid below the (a) national minimum wage and (b) national living wage.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47961","47961"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599650","2016-10-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what verification process is used by HM Revenue and Customs to ensure that the level of arrears paid to workers using the self-correction process by employers found to be non-compliant with the (a) national minimum wage and (b) national living wage is a true reflection of the amount the workforce is owed.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47962","47962"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599652","2016-10-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what discussions he has had with energy suppliers on tariffs for customers who do not elect to pay for services online.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47965","47965"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599653","2016-10-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps the Government is taking to tackle global climate change.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47955","47955"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599654","2016-10-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when his Department plans to publish the consultation on the Government's commitment to phase out coal-fired power stations.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47945","47945"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599655","2016-10-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate his Department has made of the number of households in (a) Feltham and Heston constituency, (b) all London boroughs and (c) the UK that are equipped with intelligent smart metering systems.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48016","48016"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599657","2016-10-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 29 September 2016 to Question 44820, whether any subsequent action is taken by HM Revenue and Customs against employers named and shamed for non-compliance with the national minimum wage and national living wage to check that they have changed their business practice and are continuing to pay their workforce legally.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47967","47967"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599658","2016-10-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many households in the Highland area of Scotland with dynamically teleswitched meters receive their electricity supply from Scottish Power.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47990","47990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599659","2016-10-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many households in the Highland area of Scotland with dynamically teleswitched meters receive their electricity supply under Scottish Power's Comfort Control tariff.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47991","47991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599660","2016-10-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many households in the UK have their electricity supplies controlled by dynamically teleswitched meters.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48014","48014"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599661","2016-10-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the UK leaving the EU on funding for dementia research.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47999","47999"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599663","2016-10-17","Department for International Trade","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what recent discussions he has had with his counterparts and officials in the Irish government and the Northern Ireland Executive on trade and export opportunities in (a) Northern Europe, (b) the US and (c) Asia Pacific countries.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48007","48007"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599664","2016-10-13","Department for International Trade","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what discussions he has had with (a) the government of Pakistan and (b) other key stakeholders on promoting UK trade with that country.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48020","48020"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599665","2016-10-17","Department for International Trade","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, pursuant to the Answer of 10 October 2016 to Question 46319, what overseas visits he has made as Secretary of State for International Trade since the establishment of his Department.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48072","48072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599666","2016-10-13","Department for International Trade","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, which agreed EU directives have not yet been transposed directly into UK law; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48182","48182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599668","2016-10-13","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, which agreed EU directives have not yet been transposed directly into UK law; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48177","48177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599669","2016-10-17","HM Treasury","2016-10-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, which projects in the UK are (a) currently funded and (b) due to be funded by the European Investment Bank.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48057","48057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599670","2016-10-17","HM Treasury","2016-10-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what his plans are for the UK's future relationship with the European Investment Bank.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48058","48058"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599671","2016-10-17","HM Treasury","2016-10-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent meetings he has had with representatives of the European Investment Bank.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48059","48059"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599673","2016-10-17","HM Treasury","2016-10-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much the UK received in funding from the European Investment Bank in the last three years.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48063","48063"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599674","2016-10-13","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, pursuant to the Answer of 10 October 2016 to Question 46424, if he will estimate the total cost of meetings held by his Department to date; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48126","48126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599675","2016-10-17","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many meetings the Government has had with Ministers of the Scottish Government on the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48004","48004"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599676","2016-10-13","Department of Health","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what preparations his Department has made for the likely relocation of the headquarters of the European Medicines Agency away from London after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47934","47934"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599678","2016-10-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment her Department has made of the potential effect of the UK leaving the EU on the export of meat from the UK to other EU member states.","Biography information for Susan Elan Jones","Susan Elan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48206","48206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599679","2016-10-17","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether his Department has made an assessment of whether tariff free trade between the UK and EU member states would be possible under World Trade Organisation rules.","Biography information for Susan Elan Jones","Susan Elan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48207","48207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/603863","2016-10-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the national living wage on unemployment levels.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 906599","906599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/603864","2016-10-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Justice on increasing the employment rate of ex-offenders.","Biography information for Andrew Selous","Andrew Selous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 906600","906600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/603865","2016-10-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps the Government is taking to help protect the pensions of long-serving employees.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 906582","906582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/603866","2016-10-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to reduce youth unemployment in areas with high levels of youth unemployment.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 906596","906596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/605548","2016-10-19","Wales Office","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what discussions he has had with the Welsh Government on its role in negotiations on the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Nick Thomas-Symonds","Nick Thomas-Symonds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 906622","906622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/605549","2016-10-19","Wales Office","2016-10-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what steps he is taking to ensure that Wales receives the maximum funding possible from the EU before the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 906620","906620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598160","2016-10-13","Attorney General","2016-10-10","To ask the Attorney General, how many people were (a) prosecuted for and (b) convicted of offences under the Hunting Act 2004 in 2015; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47654","47654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598161","2016-10-13","Attorney General","2016-10-10","To ask the Attorney General, how many people were (a) prosecuted for and (b) convicted of offences under the Wild Animals (Protection) Act 1996 in 2015; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47655","47655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598162","2016-10-13","Attorney General","2016-10-10","To ask the Attorney General, how many people were (a) prosecuted for and (b) convicted of offences under the Badgers Act 1991 in 2015; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47659","47659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598163","2016-10-13","Attorney General","2016-10-10","To ask the Attorney General, how many people were (a) prosecuted for and (b) convicted of offences under the Deer Act 1991 in 2015; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47660","47660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598164","2016-10-13","Cabinet Office","2016-10-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when he plans to update the List of Ministerial Responsibilities.","Biography information for Tommy Sheppard","Tommy Sheppard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47681","47681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598165","2016-10-13","Cabinet Office","2016-10-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what correspondence he has received from English Heritage on Duchy of Lancaster properties under the guardianship of English Heritage in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Tommy Sheppard","Tommy Sheppard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47682","47682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598166","2016-10-12","Cabinet Office","2016-10-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the remit is of the Gulf Strategy Unit; when the Unit was established; how many staff the Unit is intended to employ; and what the proposed budget for the Unit is.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47638","47638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598167","2016-10-12","Cabinet Office","2016-10-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what recent assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the Advisory Committee on Business Appointments in scrutinising the suitability of business appointments for former Ministers in government.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47620","47620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598168","2016-10-12","Cabinet Office","2016-10-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when he plans to publish an updated edition of Ministerial Responsibilities.","Biography information for Michael Fabricant","Michael Fabricant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47633","47633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598169","2016-10-13","Cabinet Office","2016-10-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will estimate the proportion of time Ministers in his Department spent on the management of matters relating to the Duchy of Lancaster in the last three months.","Biography information for Tommy Sheppard","Tommy Sheppard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47683","47683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598170","2016-10-12","HM Treasury","2016-10-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will meet FairFuelUK to discuss fiscal incentives for the use of cleaner fuels.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47707","47707"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598171","2016-10-13","HM Treasury","2016-10-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the effect on the employment of the introduction of tax on soft drinks.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47692","47692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598172","2016-10-13","HM Treasury","2016-10-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate his Department has made of the potential effect of leaving the EU Customs Union on UK GDP.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47695","47695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598173","2016-10-12","HM Treasury","2016-10-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people in (a) Ellesmere Port and Neston constituency and (b) Cheshire West and Chester have had a tax credit claim stopped by Concentrix; and how many such claims were subsequently reinstated by HM Revenue and Customs.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47712","47712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598174","2016-10-12","HM Treasury","2016-10-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many complaints HM Revenue and Customs has received about Concentrix from residents in the Rutherglen and Hamilton West constituency since that company has been under contract with his Department.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47731","47731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598175","2016-10-12","HM Treasury","2016-10-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many tax credits claims have been reinstated by HM Revenue and Customs as a result of (a) adjustments and (b) cancellations by Concentrix in the Rutherglen and Hamilton West constituency.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47730","47730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598176","2016-10-12","HM Treasury","2016-10-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department is taking to protect families paying debts over time from bailiff fees, court charges and interest rates; and if he will consider a statutory breathing space for families in debt.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47723","47723"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598177","2016-10-13","HM Treasury","2016-10-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to his announcement on EU regional funding dated 3 October 2016, what conditions will need to be passed by funding projects to ensure they are (i) good value for money and (ii) in line with domestic strategic priorities; and if he will guarantee that all regions will receive the full amount of funding they were allocated by the EU.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47657","47657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598178","2016-10-13","HM Treasury","2016-10-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he has received any reports that Concentrix has used postcode areas to target tax credit claimants with allegations that they have provided incorrect claim information.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47652","47652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598179","2016-10-12","HM Treasury","2016-10-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the implication for his Department's policies of the Children's Society's recent report, Damage of Debt; and if his Department will introduce a statutory breathing space scheme for families in debt.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47829","47829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598180","2016-10-13","Church Commissioners","2016-10-10","To ask the right hon. Member for Meriden, representing the Church Commissioners, what steps are being taken by the Church Commissioners to address the financial difficulties at Peterborough Cathedral; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stewart Jackson","Mr Stewart Jackson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47672","47672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598181","2016-10-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when the future high streets forum has met in the last two years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47834","47834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598182","2016-10-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many letters his Department received from the Mayor of London between May 2010 and April 2016; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47835","47835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598183","2016-10-12","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps she will take to ensure that people with audio or visual impairments benefit from the Digital Economy Bill; and if she will assess how on-demand services will meet such people's needs.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47847","47847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598184","2016-10-12","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if she will issue a response to the report Scientific and factual? A review of breastmilk substitute advertising to healthcare professionals, published by the First Steps Nutrition Trust.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47844","47844"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598185","2016-10-12","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of the effect of bringing into force the costs sanctions under section 40 of the Crime and Courts Act 2013 on individual press titles that have joined the Independent Press Standards Organisation.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47763","47763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598186","2016-10-13","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps her Department is taking to encourage female participation in sport.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47668","47668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598187","2016-10-12","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if she will make it her policy to restrict television advertising for unhealthy food on programming likely to be watched by children.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47703","47703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598188","2016-10-12","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what arrangements have been made to accommodate private aircraft at the Leuchars military base.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47635","47635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598189","2016-10-13","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to promote the welfare of members of the armed forces.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47669","47669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598190","2016-10-13","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what involvement the UK armed forces have had in training armed forces of Gulf states in each of the last 15 years.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47793","47793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598191","2016-10-13","Cabinet Office","2016-10-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much funding the Gulf Strategy Unit has received in each of the last 15 years.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47796","47796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598192","2016-10-12","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to ensure future interoperability of the Boeing Poseidon P-8 platform with the General Atomics MQ9 Reaper platforms.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47717","47717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598193","2016-10-12","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department is considering (a) radial gap electrical propulsion motors and (b) permanent magnet motors for the propulsion systems for the successor-class SSBNs.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47718","47718"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598194","2016-10-13","Cabinet Office","2016-10-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the Gulf Strategy Unit's remit is; and which Government Minister set that remit.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47797","47797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598195","2016-10-12","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the Government has access to radar data covering Aleppo on 17 August 2016 that might identify the type, origin and identity of aircraft present for the air attack on the Qaterji neighbourhood on that day.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47702","47702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598196","2016-10-12","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 20 September 2016 to Question 45999, how many of the 34 days in which all six Daring-class Type 45 Destroyers were berthed together at HMNB Portsmouth were consecutive.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47824","47824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598197","2016-10-12","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many times officials in his Department responsible for procurement checked whether a contractor employed by his Department was under investigation for corruption with law enforcement agencies in the last two years.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47726","47726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598198","2016-10-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how the UK is supporting the Iraqi government in its preparations to restore inclusive governance in Mosul after that city is removed from the control of IS.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47775","47775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598199","2016-10-12","Department for International Development","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps are being taken to attend to Iraqi civilians expected to be displaced as a result of a planned offensive on Mosul, Iraq.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47776","47776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598200","2016-10-12","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans the Government has for the decommissioning of (a) HMS Torbay, (b) HMS Trenchant, (c) HMS Talent and (d) HMS Triumph.","Biography information for Steven Paterson","Steven Paterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47777","47777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598201","2016-10-12","Cabinet Office","2016-10-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many (a) military and (b) civilian Government employees have been employed in the Gulf Strategy Unit in each of the last 15 years.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47725","47725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598202","2016-10-13","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the participation of assets of the Turkish armed forces in NATO Operation Joint Warrior 2016 had been planned.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47803","47803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598203","2016-10-13","Department for International Development","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps the UK will take to safeguard children and other civilians in any assault on IS in Mosul; what steps she will take to put in place safe routes out for children and families; and if she will ensure that screening procedures take care not to separate families.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47798","47798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598204","2016-10-12","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the in-service dates are for the River-Class Offshore Patrol Vessels currently under construction on the Clyde.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47719","47719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598205","2016-10-12","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that the insulation on coolant lines in the fuel tanks of UK F35B Lightning II fighters does not suffer decomposition.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47720","47720"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598206","2016-10-12","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether Royal Air Force F35B Lightning II jets have completed testing for shipborne rolling vertical landing in cooperation with US Air Force and US Navy assets.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47716","47716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598207","2016-10-13","Department for Education","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of children obtained five or more GCSEs at grade A* to C including English and mathematics in (a) selective, (b) partially selective and (c) comprehensive local authority areas in the last year for which data is available; and what that proportion was by ethnic group in each of those categories.","Biography information for Sir Graham Brady","Mr Graham Brady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47820","47820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598208","2016-10-13","Department for Education","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which (a) selective, (b) partially selective and (c) comprehensive local authority areas in England ranked by correlating guaranteed per pupil against the proportion of pupils attaining five or more grade A* to C GCSEs including English and mathematics in core subjects in the last year for which data is available.","Biography information for Sir Graham Brady","Mr Graham Brady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47821","47821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598209","2016-10-12","Department for Education","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when her Department's guidance on sex and relationships education will be revised.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47735","47735"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598210","2016-10-13","Department for Education","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of children achieved (a) five A* to C grade GCSEs including English and mathematics and (b) two or more A grades at A-level nationally; and what proportion of children achieved such grades in (i) selective, (ii) partially selective and (iii) comprehensive local education authority areas in the most recent year for which data is available.","Biography information for Sir Graham Brady","Mr Graham Brady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47822","47822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598211","2016-10-13","Department for Education","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of children in (a) England and (b) Northern Ireland achieved five A* to C grade GCSEs including English and mathematics in the last five years for which data is available.","Biography information for Sir Graham Brady","Mr Graham Brady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47823","47823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598212","2016-10-13","Department for Education","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of how effectively the new system for supporting children with special educational needs and disabilities is meeting the needs of children and young people on the autism spectrum; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Ms Marie Rimmer","Marie Rimmer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47691","47691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598213","2016-10-13","Department for Education","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she plans to include in the proposed Education for All Bill a contractual obligation on schools to provide sex and relationships education.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47785","47785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598214","2016-10-13","Department for Education","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions she has had with Ofsted on sex and relationships education.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47786","47786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598215","2016-10-13","Department for Education","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will make it her policy to make sex and relationships education compulsory in all schools.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47788","47788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598216","2016-10-13","Department for Education","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will make it her policy to provide additional resources to local authorities or schools for sex and relationships education.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47787","47787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598217","2016-10-12","Department for Education","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if the Government will ensure that the sex and relationships education curriculum includes (a) LGBT issues and (b) supporting young people's long-term physical health, mental health and general wellbeing.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47734","47734"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598218","2016-10-12","Department for Education","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the potential effect of the UK leaving the EU on UK universities' ability to attract high-quality students and researchers from across Europe.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47609","47609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598219","2016-10-12","Department for Education","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what research her Department has commissioned on the effect of selective education on the educational attainment of children in the last 12 months; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47648","47648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598220","2016-10-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will make it his policy to make available research funding at the same level as currently received after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47637","47637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598221","2016-10-13","Department for Education","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent research her Department has commissioned on the effect of academic selection at age 11 on the educational attainment of children from the poorest backgrounds; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47685","47685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598222","2016-10-13","Department for Education","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of the number of full-time equivalent officials based in her Department who are working on selective education policies; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47686","47686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598223","2016-10-12","Department for Education","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the effect of the selection processes used by faith schools on academic attainment in those schools.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47704","47704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598224","2016-10-13","Department for Education","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what representations she has received from existing grammar schools wishing to expand in each of the last 12 months; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47687","47687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598225","2016-10-13","Department for Education","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what advice her Department has received from experts on the reintroduction of grammar schools in the last 12 months; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47688","47688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598226","2016-10-13","Department for Education","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will review the implementation of new SEND system by local authorities; and what assessment she has made of how transitional funding is being used in each area to benefit children with (a) autism and (b) other special educational needs.","Biography information for Ms Marie Rimmer","Marie Rimmer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47690","47690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598227","2016-10-12","Department for Education","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans she has to support EU students at UK universities after 2020 if the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47636","47636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598228","2016-10-13","Department for Education","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what data is held by her Department on levels of parental debt owed to schools.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47868","47868"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598229","2016-10-13","Department for Education","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when the new National Funding Formula for schools will be introduced.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47866","47866"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598230","2016-10-13","Department for Education","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of schools are currently in debt; and to whom such schools are in debt.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47869","47869"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598231","2016-10-13","Department for Education","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment she has made of the current sources of financial pressure on schools; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47870","47870"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598232","2016-10-13","Department for Education","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent representations she has received on schools covering costs on behalf of parents and the ensuing parental debt.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47867","47867"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598233","2016-10-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if her Department will commission research into the economic, social and environmental contributions of small farms in England to inform policy and funding of this sector once the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47830","47830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598234","2016-10-13","HM Treasury","2016-10-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the announcement by HM Treasury on EU regional funding, dated 3 October 2016, whether his Department plans to (a) guarantee and (b) replace European Solidarity Funding for flood relief.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47656","47656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598235","2016-10-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans her Department has to reform management of the waters in the UK's Exclusive Economic Zone.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47674","47674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598236","2016-10-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will make it her policy to maintain or enhance the UK's environmental protection standards following an exit from the EU.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47784","47784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598237","2016-10-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if her Department will commission research into the economic, social and environmental contribution of the organic farming sector in England to assist in informing policy and funding of this sector once the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47778","47778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598238","2016-10-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent steps the Government has taken to tackle the threat from the Asian hornet to the honeybee population in the UK.","Biography information for Sammy Wilson","Sammy Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47767","47767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598239","2016-10-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment her Department has made of the threat from the Asian hornet to the honeybee population in the UK.","Biography information for Sammy Wilson","Sammy Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47768","47768"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598240","2016-10-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many schools in Birmingham are located in areas with pollution higher than World Health Organisation limits.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47724","47724"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598241","2016-10-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of enforcement of international humanitarian and human rights law in respect of children by the UN Human Rights Council in Yemen.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47782","47782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598242","2016-10-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answers of 12 September 2016 to Questions 45151 and 45154, on Iraq: Genocide, whether the character and scope of the campaign to hold Daesh to account for its crimes have been established; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47678","47678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598243","2016-10-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if the Government will (a) carry out its own assessment and (b) support an independent international inquiry into whether the airstrike on a community hall in Sana'a, where a funeral was taking place, on 8 October 2016, breached international humanitarian law.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47677","47677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598244","2016-10-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, which convictions of UK citizens in foreign countries the UK is currently challenging; and what guidance his Department follows in deciding which convictions of UK citizens in overseas courts to challenge.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47792","47792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598245","2016-10-13","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what account his Department took of the suspension by the Department for International Development of a security sector management programme in Ethiopia in deciding to oversee an executive MSc programme in such management.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47651","47651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598246","2016-10-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions his Department has had with officials from (a) the EU and (b) the UN on obtaining compensation for UK victims of Libyan-sponsored IRA terrorism.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47646","47646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598247","2016-10-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has received representations from the people of Norfolk Island on administrative and constitutional changes being implemented on that Island by the Australian government.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47623","47623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598248","2016-10-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations his Department has received on the compatibility with (a) Article 49 of the Fourth Geneva Convention and (b) other elements of international law of the Israeli Supreme Court's rejections of cases where demolition orders have been contested; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47625","47625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598249","2016-10-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the statement issued by his Department on 7 October 2016 on death sentences issued in Gaza, what discussions he has had with counterparts in the region on the subject of that statement.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47611","47611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598250","2016-10-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what account his Department took of the case of Andargachew Tsege in its decision to fund the executive MSc programme in security sector management in Ethiopia.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47618","47618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598251","2016-10-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent steps his Department has taken to persuade the Libyan government to issue compensation for UK victims of Libyan-sponsored IRA terrorism.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47645","47645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598252","2016-10-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether (a) Ministers and (b) officials of his Department have met the administrator of Norfolk Island since 1 July 2016.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47624","47624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598253","2016-10-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the possible diplomatic benefits of recommissioning HM Yacht Britannia.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47643","47643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598254","2016-10-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 9 September 2016 to Question 44301, United Nations: finance, how much his Department contributed voluntarily to the missions referred to in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47619","47619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598255","2016-10-17","Department of Health","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much has been spent in England on NHS Continuing Healthcare in each of the last five years.","Biography information for James Cartlidge","James Cartlidge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47699","47699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598256","2016-10-12","Department of Health","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Answer of 3 May 2016 to Question 35653, how much Public Health England plans to spend on campaigns promoting the cessation of smoking in 2016-17.","Biography information for Bob Blackman","Bob Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47621","47621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598257","2016-10-12","Department of Health","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps NHS England is taking to encourage local communities to input into individual sustainability and transformation plans; and if he will publish contact details for lead officers co-ordinating proposals on the way maternity services are delivered in each NHS area.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47649","47649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598258","2016-10-12","Department of Health","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of recently published research from Breast Cancer Now on the availability of bisphosphonates.","Biography information for Nick Thomas-Symonds","Nick Thomas-Symonds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47612","47612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598259","2016-10-12","Department of Health","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress his Department has made on ensuring that repurposed, off-patent drugs are consistently available to NHS patients where evidence supports their use.","Biography information for Nick Thomas-Symonds","Nick Thomas-Symonds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47613","47613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598260","2016-10-12","Department of Health","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions he has had with his Ministerial colleagues on encouraging young people in deprived communities to pursue a career in medicine.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47615","47615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598261","2016-10-12","Department of Health","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to analyse and expand health service capacity in areas of expected high population growth.","Biography information for Kelly Tolhurst","Kelly Tolhurst","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47608","47608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598262","2016-10-12","Department of Health","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent representations he has (a) received and (b) made on eye health services at Birmingham City Hospital.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47610","47610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598263","2016-10-13","Department of Health","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department plans to take to recruit and train more doctors.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47663","47663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598264","2016-10-12","Department of Health","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people have had stem cell transplantation procedures interrupted in England in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Gareth Johnson","Gareth Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47745","47745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598265","2016-10-12","Department of Health","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when his Department plans to publish a consultation on proposals to introduce fixed recoverable costs for clinical negligence cases.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47713","47713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598266","2016-10-12","Department of Health","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the cost per patient is of carrying out stem cell transplantation.","Biography information for Gareth Johnson","Gareth Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47744","47744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598267","2016-10-12","Department of Health","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his Department's policy is on the interruption of stem cell transplantation.","Biography information for Gareth Johnson","Gareth Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47743","47743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598268","2016-10-12","Department of Health","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he plans to publish sustainability and transformation plans.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47711","47711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598269","2016-10-12","Department of Health","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of the potential merits of reviewing the medical exemption criteria of prescription charges for people with long-term health conditions.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47781","47781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598270","2016-10-12","Department of Health","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the cost of the NHS Citizen scheme has been to date; and what assessment he has made of its success since its creation.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47728","47728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598271","2016-10-12","Department of Health","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the performance of the Cheshire Patient Transport Service in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47729","47729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598272","2016-10-12","Department of Health","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the likely effect on Category M of the Drug Tariff of the proposed changes to the pharmacy funding formula.","Biography information for Steve Double","Steve Double","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47779","47779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598273","2016-10-13","Department of Health","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of NHS treatment of craniosynostosis; and if he will take steps to increase training and awareness of craniosynostosis amongst NHS professionals.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47693","47693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598274","2016-10-12","Department of Health","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of NHS trusts have agreed financial control totals for the next two years.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47708","47708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598275","2016-10-12","Department of Health","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, who is responsible for approving sustainability and transformation plans.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47709","47709"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598276","2016-10-13","Department of Health","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of relative levels of productivity in community pharmacy and secondary care in each year since 2005.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47790","47790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598277","2016-10-12","Department of Health","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the sign-off process is for sustainability and transformation plans.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47710","47710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598278","2016-10-12","Department of Health","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) residents, (b) children and (c) adolescents from Lambeth and Southwark were admitted to a mental health facility outside the London boroughs of Lambeth, Lewisham, Southwark and Croydon served by South London and the Maudsley NHS Foundation Trust in the last year.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47736","47736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598279","2016-10-12","Department of Health","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect of changes to pharmacy funding on the availability of essential medicines.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47751","47751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598280","2016-10-12","Department of Health","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of changes in pharmacy funding on waiting times for NHS prescriptions.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47752","47752"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598281","2016-10-13","Department of Health","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with the British Medical Association and the Royal Colleges on proposals to make junior doctors repay training costs if they leave the profession within five years.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47804","47804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598282","2016-10-12","Department of Health","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect of proposed reductions in pharmacy funding on specific patient populations.","Biography information for Craig Mackinlay","Craig Mackinlay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47762","47762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598283","2016-10-12","Department of Health","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much time has been allocated for the public consultation on the sustainability and transformation plans for Birmingham and Solihull and the Black Country and West Birmingham; and if he will ensure that the feedback from this public consultation will be published.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47825","47825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598284","2016-10-12","Department of Health","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will issue a response to the report Scientific and factual? A review of breastmilk substitute advertising to healthcare professionals, published by the First Steps Nutrition Trust.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47845","47845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598285","2016-10-13","Department of Health","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the likely effect of proposed changes to pharmacy funding on the provision of supplementary hours beyond the core NHS contract.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47806","47806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598286","2016-10-12","Department of Health","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the likely effect on accident and emergency services of the proposed changes to the pharmacy funding formula.","Biography information for Steve Double","Steve Double","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47761","47761"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598287","2016-10-12","Home Office","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many incidents of gun crime have been recorded in (a) the UK, (b) London and (c) Hornsey and Wood Green constituency in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47764","47764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598288","2016-10-12","Home Office","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many instances of Islamophobic abuse have been recorded in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47765","47765"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598289","2016-10-12","Home Office","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many instances of Islamophobic abuse have been recorded in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47766","47766"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598290","2016-10-13","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment she has made of the relationship between the use of (a) illegal drugs and (b) legal high in prisons and incidents of violence against prison staff.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47805","47805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598291","2016-10-13","Home Office","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average Fire and Rescue response times were to incidents in (a) England, (b) the North East, (c) Redcar and Cleveland and (d) Middlesbrough in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47800","47800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598292","2016-10-13","Home Office","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the Government has carried out a (a) policy equality statement, (b) equality impact assessment or (c) any equality monitoring on its contracts with Compass to provide accommodation to asylum seekers since those contracts were signed in 2012.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47816","47816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598293","2016-10-12","Home Office","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate her has Department made of the number of UK nationals who have travelled overseas to engage in terrorist activity and have subsequently returned to this country.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47749","47749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598294","2016-10-12","Home Office","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate her Department has made of the number of UK nationals who have travelled overseas to engage in terrorist activity.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47748","47748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598295","2016-10-12","Home Office","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what evidence her Department holds on the effect of the creation of police and crime commissioners on police accountability.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47617","47617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598296","2016-10-12","Home Office","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate her Department has made of the total number of refugees who will attempt to cross the Mediterranean in 2017.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47640","47640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598297","2016-10-12","Home Office","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the (a) legal and (b) financial obstacles to immediately changing the colour of UK passports to blue.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47644","47644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598298","2016-10-12","Home Office","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what her policy is on the admission of Shaykh Hamza Sodagar into the UK; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47634","47634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598299","2016-10-12","Department of Health","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Modern Crime Prevention Strategy, published in March 2016, page 31, whether his Department has sought legal advice on its policies relating to heroin-assisted treatment; and what assessment he has made of the legal implications of those policies.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47629","47629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598300","2016-10-13","Home Office","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much compensation her Department paid for the unlawful detention of individuals under immigration powers in each of the last three financial years; for what categories of reason such compensation was paid; and how many such payments were made for each such category of reason.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47658","47658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598301","2016-10-12","Home Office","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that UK-based science research teams can employ foreign researchers without restriction.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47837","47837"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598302","2016-10-12","Department for International Development","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the effect of restrictions of water supplies on the humanitarian situation in the West Bank.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47626","47626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598303","2016-10-12","Department for International Development","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to assist with humanitarian action in the Lake Chad basin; and what funds have been allocated to programmes in (a) Cameroon, (b) Chad, (c) Niger and (d) Nigeria that assist with such action.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47740","47740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598304","2016-10-12","Department for International Development","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what discussions she has had with her counterparts in (a) Chad, (b) Cameroon, (c) Niger and (d) Nigeria on the humanitarian situation in the Lake Chad basin.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47739","47739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598305","2016-10-12","Department for International Development","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the humanitarian situation in the Lake Chad basin.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47738","47738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598306","2016-10-12","Home Office","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have been charged with terrorism offences committed overseas on their return to the UK in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47750","47750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598307","2016-10-12","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment her Department has made of proposals set out in January 2016 by Lord Justice Jackson to set fixed costs on all personal injury claims valued up to 250,000; and what steps the Government is taking to control costs and promote access to justice in this area.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47753","47753"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598308","2016-10-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when his Department will implement the recommendations of the Deane Review into Self-Employment, published in February 2016.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47807","47807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598309","2016-10-12","Northern Ireland Office","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many non-UK citizens are employed by his Department.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47758","47758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598310","2016-10-12","Scotland Office","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, whether he has made representations to the Department of Transport on negotiations on the bilateral agreement regulating direct flights between the UK and the People's Republic of China.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47722","47722"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598311","2016-10-12","Scotland Office","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how many non-UK citizens are employed by his Department.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47760","47760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598312","2016-10-12","Scotland Office","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what discussions he has had with the Scottish Government on the number of complaints Transport Scotland has received on over-staging on its dedicated hotline in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47783","47783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598313","2016-10-12","Scotland Office","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what incentives are provided by the Government to encourage electricity providers to create opportunities for households with dynamically teleswitched metres to switch between electricity suppliers.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47733","47733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598314","2016-10-12","Department for Transport","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will produce a cost impact assessment for users of the new Mersey Gateway.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47715","47715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598315","2016-10-13","Department for Transport","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the (a) status and (b) latest estimated or final cost is of each of the 19 road schemes announced in December 2014 for the Midlands.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47662","47662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598316","2016-10-12","Department for Transport","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much has been spent on road infrastructure per head of population in (a) Ellesmere Port and Neston constituency, (b) the North West, (c) the Northern Powerhouse area, (d) London and (e) England in (i) 2014-15 and (ii) 2015-16.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47727","47727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598317","2016-10-12","Department for Transport","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the (a) time and (b) cost of clearing all contaminated material on the grounds where Heathrow plans to build a third runway.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47772","47772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598318","2016-10-12","Department for Transport","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the timetable is for negotiations on the bilateral agreement regulating flights between the UK and the People's Republic of China.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47721","47721"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598319","2016-10-12","Department for Transport","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will hold discussions with manufacturers of satellite navigation devices on steps that could be taken to ensure that HGVs are not inappropriately directed into narrow residential streets.","Biography information for Alex Chalk","Alex Chalk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47701","47701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598320","2016-10-12","Department for Transport","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will undertake research on whether alternative pricing structures of the access charges set by Eurotunnel could incentivise greater passenger and freight traffic between the UK and mainland Europe.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47628","47628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598321","2016-10-12","Department for Transport","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if his Department will make an assessment of whether the Airports Commission considered the full potential for increased long distance rail passenger and rail freight movement between the UK and mainland Europe through using the full capacity of the Channel tunnel.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47627","47627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598322","2016-10-12","Department for Transport","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will hold discussions with Eurotunnel on providing incentives through its access charges for increased long distance transportation of passengers and freight by rail.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47622","47622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598323","2016-10-12","Department for Transport","2016-10-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what further devolution is being considered to the Mayor of London; and how his Department is working with the Mayor to tackle rail challenges facing the capital.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47846","47846"
