"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909012","2018-05-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent meetings he has had with scientists on bovine TB.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146081","146081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909013","2018-05-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many badgers are planned to be culled in each trial zone for the remainder of the cull period.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146082","146082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909014","2018-05-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment his Department is undertaking into the study of immunity against bovine TB among (a) badgers and (b) cattle.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146083","146083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909015","2018-05-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans he has to test for bovine TB (a) those badgers culled as part of the culling trial, (b) those badgers remaining in the high risk areas and (c) a sample of badgers in the low risk area.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146084","146084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909016","2018-05-23","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prosecutions for badger-baiting were (a) launched and (b) successful by police force in each year from 2010 to date.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146085","146085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909017","2018-05-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the membership is of the Local Energy Contact Group.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146086","146086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909018","2018-05-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will ensure that all agendas, minutes and papers of meetings of the Local Energy Contact Group are published online.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146087","146087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909019","2018-05-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when the Local Energy Contact Group was established; how many meetings of that group have taken place to date; and what the outcomes have been of those meetings.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146088","146088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909020","2018-05-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what his policy is on supporting the development of new community energy projects.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146089","146089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909021","2018-05-23","Attorney General","2018-05-21","To ask the Attorney General, what information he holds on the timetable for the Supreme Court hearing on the UK Withdrawal from the European Union (Legal Continuity) (Scotland) Bill.","Biography information for Lesley Laird","Lesley Laird","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146337","146337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909022","2018-05-24","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 25 April 2018 to Question 136859 on Small Claims: Electronic Government, where his Department has established a telephone helpline for claimants to contact to discuss those cases.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146229","146229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909023","2018-05-24","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 25 April 2018 to Question 136859, on Small Claims: Electronic Government, what steps he is taking to publicise the launch of the new online money claims service.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146230","146230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909024","2018-05-24","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 25 April 2018 to Question 136859 on Small Claims: Electronic Government, whether existing money claims online users will have access the new online money claims service.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146231","146231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909025","2018-05-24","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the efficacy of the telephone service accompanying the money claims online system; and whether that service is fully operational.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146232","146232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909026","2018-05-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will take steps to prevent GPs from charging for signing a patient’s letter.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146186","146186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909027","2018-05-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many children were being treated for psoriasis as of 1 May 2018.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146187","146187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909028","2018-05-23","Department for Education","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to support families in adopting children from overseas.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146188","146188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909029","2018-05-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent steps his Department has taken to encourage young people to work in agriculture.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146189","146189"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909030","2018-05-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many wind farms have been established in each of the last five years.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146190","146190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909031","2018-05-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department plans to take to increase the number of Blue Flag beaches in the UK.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146191","146191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909032","2018-05-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he has met representatives of the Ulster Farmers' Union since the referendum on the UK leaving the EU; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146192","146192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909033","2018-05-23","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of a 9.00pm watershed for TV advertisements for food and drinks that are high in fat, sugar and salt.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146161","146161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909034","2018-05-24","Home Office","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average wait time is for (a) appointments and (b) final decision for Windrush cases at each of the Home Office premium service location.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146253","146253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909035","2018-05-24","Home Office","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate he has made of the number of new biometric permits that have been issued to people from the Windrush generation to date.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146254","146254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909036","2018-05-24","Home Office","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate he has made of the average waiting time for the issuing a biometric permit by immigration status.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146255","146255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909037","2018-05-24","Home Office","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) phone calls and (b) other inquiries the Windrush taskforce has received from outside the UK, by country, to date.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146256","146256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909038","2018-05-24","Department for Education","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the average length of time has been for monthly salary deductions collected by HMRC to be reconciled with individual accounts held by the Student Loans Company in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146277","146277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909039","2018-05-24","Home Office","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the maximum compensation made to a person wrongly detained by the Home Office was in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146257","146257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909040","2018-05-24","Department for Education","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much debt interest accrued on student loans for which salary deductions have already been made by HMRC in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146278","146278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909041","2018-05-24","Department for Education","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the value is of student loan debt assets sold to the private sector since 2010.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146279","146279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909042","2018-05-24","Department for Education","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether debt interest is paid on portions of student loans for which salary deductions have already been made by HMRC.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146280","146280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909043","2018-05-24","Home Office","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many referrals has the National Crime Agency received from the Solicitors Regulation Authority in relation to potential criminal activity under (a) section 327-9 and (b) section 330 of the Proceeds of Crime Act 2017.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146240","146240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909044","2018-05-24","Home Office","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many investigations are being undertaking by the National Crime Agency into offences committed under (a) section 327-329 and (b) section 330 of the Proceeds of Crime Act 2017.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146241","146241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909045","2018-05-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 1 May 2018 to Question 136701, what the criteria will be by which his Department will assess the cost-effectiveness of the potential additional deployment of offshore wind.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146194","146194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909046","2018-05-24","Attorney General","2018-05-21","To ask the Attorney General, how many prosecutions have been initiated by the (a) Crown Prosecution Service and (b) Serious Fraud Office against corporate bodies for offences committed under (i) section 327-329 and (ii) section 330 of the Proceeds of Crime Act 2017.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146242","146242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909047","2018-05-24","Treasury","2018-05-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many investigations HMRC is undertaking into corporate bodies, in relation to offences under (a) section 327-329 and (b) section 330 of the Proceeds of Crime Act 2017.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146243","146243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909048","2018-05-24","Treasury","2018-05-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many prosecutions HMRC have initiated as a result of breaches of the (a) Proceeds of Crime Act 2017 and (b) Money Laundering Regulations 2007 and 2017 by Trust and Company Service providers.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146244","146244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909049","2018-05-24","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, if he will make an assessment of the implications for the Government's policies of the conclusions of the the paper, Northern Ireland and the UK’s Exit from the EU, What do people think, published by Queen’s University Belfast in May 2018.","Biography information for Ged Killen","Ged Killen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146350","146350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909050","2018-05-24","Department for Transport","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, If he will make an assessment of the potential merits of reintroducing road safety targets in the UK; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146092","146092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909051","2018-05-24","Department for Transport","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when the Hon Member for Hereford, the Transport Minister, plans to respond to the letter sent to him by the Batched on Site Association on 25 April 2018; and if he will place a copy of that response in the Library.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146159","146159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909052","2018-05-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has made representations to his Saudi Arabian counterpart on the recent detention of leading women’s rights activists in that country.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146093","146093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909053","2018-05-24","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps the Government is taking to implement the recommendations of the UK Labour Market Enforcement Strategy 2018-19.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146119","146119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909054","2018-05-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much funding from the public purse was allocated to biomedical research into myalgic encephalomyelitis in 2013-2014.","Biography information for Carol Monaghan","Carol Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146296","146296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909055","2018-05-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much funding from the public purse was allocated to biomedical research into myalgic encephalomyelitis in 2012-2013.","Biography information for Carol Monaghan","Carol Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146297","146297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909056","2018-05-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much funding from the public purse was allocated to biomedical research into myalgic encephalomyelitis in 2011-2012.","Biography information for Carol Monaghan","Carol Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146298","146298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909057","2018-05-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much funding from the public purse was allocated to biomedical research into myalgic encephalomyelitis in 2010-2011.","Biography information for Carol Monaghan","Carol Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146299","146299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909058","2018-05-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 16 May 2018 to Question 142751, on incinerators, what other sizes of particulates the term other particulates refers to.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146090","146090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909059","2018-05-24","Treasury","2018-05-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many staff have been employed by HM Revenue and Customs in each month since June 2016.","Biography information for Jenny Chapman","Jenny Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146206","146206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909060","2018-05-24","Home Office","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many staff have been employed by his Department in each month since June 2016.","Biography information for Jenny Chapman","Jenny Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146207","146207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909061","2018-05-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many staff have been employed by his Department in each month since June 2016.","Biography information for Jenny Chapman","Jenny Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146208","146208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909062","2018-05-24","Department for Transport","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent steps have been taken to improve passenger safety on trains for people with disabilities.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146094","146094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909063","2018-05-24","Home Office","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many incidents of race hate crime have been recorded in Coventry in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146095","146095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909064","2018-05-24","Home Office","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps his Department is taking to support refugees into education and employment upon their arrival in the UK.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146096","146096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909065","2018-05-23","Home Office","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps his Department is taking to improve processes for identifying children in UN-recognised refugee camps beyond Europe who have rights to family reunion in the UK.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146097","146097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909066","2018-05-23","Department for International Development","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to help improve healthcare facilities in Palestine.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146098","146098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909067","2018-05-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the effect on (a) patient safety and (b) the long term recovery of patients of the recent changes in service provision at the Adult Eating Disorder Service at South West London and St George's Mental Health NHS Trust.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146316","146316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909068","2018-05-23","Department for International Development","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much financial assistance her Department has given to projects in Palestine in each of the last ten years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146099","146099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909069","2018-05-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 15 May 2018 to Question 141381, what the longest time taken by the Independent Case Examiners Office has been (a) to allocate a case manager and (b) for a case manager to complete an investigation.","Biography information for Lesley Laird","Lesley Laird","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146338","146338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909070","2018-05-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many complaints from women affected by the changes in the state pension age have been investigated and closed by the Independent Case Examiners Office in (a) the UK and (b) Scotland.","Biography information for Lesley Laird","Lesley Laird","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146339","146339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909071","2018-05-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many complaints from women affected by the changes in the state pension age made to the Independent Case Examiners Office are outstanding in (a) the UK and (b) Scotland.","Biography information for Lesley Laird","Lesley Laird","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146340","146340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909072","2018-05-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 15 May 2018 to Question 141380, of the 13 complaints made by women in Kirkcaldy and Cowdenbeath constituency on changes to the state pension age, (a) what the date was of each complaint made, (b) how many complaints have been accepted for examination and (c) what the timetable is for each of those accepted complaints to be examined.","Biography information for Lesley Laird","Lesley Laird","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146341","146341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909073","2018-05-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many women in Scotland who have been affected by the changes in state pension age have lodged a complaint with the Independent Case Examiner’s office; how many of those complaints have been accepted for examination; and how many accepted complaints have been reviewed by the Independent Case Examiner’s office.","Biography information for Lesley Laird","Lesley Laird","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146342","146342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909074","2018-05-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of women affected by changes in the state pension age have made an official complaint to the Independent Case Examiner's Office.","Biography information for Lesley Laird","Lesley Laird","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146343","146343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909075","2018-05-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how her Department plans proactively to advise women affected by changes in the state pension age of the official complaints procedure to the Independent Case Examiner's Office.","Biography information for Lesley Laird","Lesley Laird","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146344","146344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909076","2018-05-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will ensure that the administration of mifepristone and misoprostol during a medical abortion will continue to be medically supervised in designated clinical settings.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146197","146197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909077","2018-05-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department plans to carry out research into the physical health risks associated with the ingestion of the abortion drug misoprostol; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146198","146198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909078","2018-05-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many complications resulting from medical abortions were reported in the UK in 2017.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146199","146199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909079","2018-05-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department has made a recent assessment of the relative frequency of complications arising from medical as opposed to surgical abortions; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146200","146200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909080","2018-05-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the article in Obstetrics and Gynaecology on Immediate complications after medical compared with surgical termination of pregnancy published in 2009, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policy of representations made by independent abortion providers to allow for abortion pills to be taken outside of a clinical setting.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146201","146201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909081","2018-05-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the number of women with complications following a (a) surgical and (b) medical abortion in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146202","146202"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909082","2018-05-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many women were diagnosed with complications following a (a) surgical and (b) medical abortion in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146203","146203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909083","2018-05-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the psychological impact of passing a foetus at home on a woman who has had an early medical abortion.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146204","146204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909084","2018-05-24","Home Office","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 15 May 2018 to Question 142892 on Prince Harry: Marriage, whether since that Answer (a) Thames Valley Police or (b) the Thames Valley Police and Crime Commissioner submitted an application to his Department for Special Grant funding for additional costs associated with policing the royal wedding.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146336","146336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909085","2018-05-24","Treasury","2018-05-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the cost to the public purse has been of the value added tax exemption for gold investment coins in (a) 2015-16 and (b) 2016-17.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146281","146281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909086","2018-05-23","Treasury","2018-05-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the cost to the public purse has been of the value added tax exemption for the sale and chartering of helicopters in (a) 2015-16 and (b) 2016-17.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146282","146282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909087","2018-05-23","Treasury","2018-05-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the cost to the public purse has been of the value added exemption for the sale or chartering of civil aeroplanes in (a) 2015-16 and (b) 2016-17.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146283","146283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909088","2018-05-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 21 May 2018 to Question 133903, what assessment her Department has made of the financial effect of the loss of equity caused by repaying the loan that has now replaced Support for Mortgage Interest at the point of sale of the home.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146263","146263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909089","2018-05-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 17 May 2018 to Question 143651 on State Retirement Pensions: Females, how much additional resource has been provided to the Independent Case Examiners Office for 2018/2019; what effect this additional resource is expected to have on waiting times for complaints to be completed; and what proportion of those who responded to the ICE customer survey whose complaint related to WASPI said that they were satisfied with the service they received.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146091","146091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909090","2018-05-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will seek legal advice on whether the UK can introduce a ban on the import of fur while the UK is a member of the EU.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146054","146054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909091","2018-05-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many FTE employees were based in Oldham Job Centre in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146310","146310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909092","2018-05-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether her Department has set a time limit for notifying claimants from the date of decision whether their (a) application and (b) mandatory reconsideration for Personal Independence Payment has been unsuccessful; and if she will take steps to ensure that unsuccessful claimants receive their decision in a timely manner.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146295","146295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909093","2018-05-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much money from the public purse was paid to work programme providers in Greater Manchester in each relevant year since 2010.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146311","146311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909094","2018-05-23","Department for Transport","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much money from the public purse was spent on subsidised bus routes in Greater Manchester in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146312","146312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909095","2018-05-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has had discussions with his US counterpart on appropriate (a) behaviour and (b language of the US president for his visit to the UK.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146313","146313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909096","2018-05-23","Home Office","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps his Department is taking to consult with EU citizens resident in the UK on the new IT system and process for applying for settled status.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146060","146060"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909097","2018-05-23","Home Office","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what representations his Department has received from EU citizens resident in the UK on the ease of use of the new IT system and process for applying for settled status.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146061","146061"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909098","2018-05-23","Home Office","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans he has to increase awareness among EU citizens resident in the UK of the new process for applying for settled status.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146062","146062"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909099","2018-05-23","Home Office","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that the new process for applying for settled status for EU citizens resident in the UK is user-friendly for applicants who have English as a second language.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146063","146063"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909100","2018-05-23","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what recent steps his Department has taken to help tackle illegal behaviour on social media platforms.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146345","146345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909101","2018-05-23","Home Office","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, by what means his Department will convey information to EU citizens resident in the UK on when they need to apply for settled status.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146064","146064"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909102","2018-05-23","Home Office","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what testing his Department has undertaken on the new IT system for applying for settled status to ensure that system is fit for purpose for EU citizens resident in the UK.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146065","146065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909103","2018-05-23","Home Office","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that (a) government departments, (b) organisations and (c) employers are sufficiently (i) prepared for the launch of the new IT system for applying for settled status and (ii) aware of the new process for verifying citizens’ documentation in relation to applications for settled status; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146066","146066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909104","2018-05-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the absence of a remission timeframe in the recommendation of NICE on the treatment of chronic lymphocytic leukaemia, for what reason NHS England does not prescribe ibrutinib to patients who have been in remission for more than three years.","Biography information for John Howell","John Howell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146193","146193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909105","2018-05-23","Home Office","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether his Department carried out any equality impact assessments prior to setting his Department's targets for the removal of illegal immigrants; and if he will publish any such assessments.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146067","146067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909106","2018-05-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he has taken to help ensure (a) refugees and (b) internally displaced people are included in the peace process in South Sudan.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146245","146245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909107","2018-05-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he has taken to help ensure (a) churches and (b) faith-based organisations are able to make an effective contribution to the peace process in South Sudan.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146246","146246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909108","2018-05-23","Department for International Development","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what funding will her Department plans to provide to UN agencies working in Sudan in 2018-19.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146247","146247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909109","2018-05-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what progress the Government is making on its strategy to tackle the spread of Japanese knotweed.","Biography information for Tonia Antoniazzi","Tonia Antoniazzi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146324","146324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909110","2018-05-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when he last met charities representing the interests of people living with duchenne muscular dystrophy.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146248","146248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909111","2018-05-24","Department for International Development","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the humanitarian situation of Palestinian refugees in Yarmouk camp in southern Damascus; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146195","146195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909112","2018-05-24","Department for International Development","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps he is taking to ensure protection and relief to Palestinian refugees affected by the conflict in Syria; and whether her Department has any plans to increase the UK's contribution to the United Nations Relief and Works Agency.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146196","146196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909113","2018-05-23","Department for International Development","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to support the people and Government of Somaliland in the aftermath of Cyclone Sagar.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146258","146258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909114","2018-05-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, for what reason the UK abstained during the recent UN Human Rights Council vote on an independent investigation into violence in Gaza.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146276","146276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909115","2018-05-23","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of people detained under the Mental Health Act 1983 who request a tribunal have received (a) absolute, (b) conditional or (c) deferred discharge in each of the last five years for which data is available.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146055","146055"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909116","2018-05-24","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy what assessment he has made of the potential effects on the small-scale renewables industry of introducing (a) tax incentives, (b) government-backed loans and (c) removal of EU tariffs on imported solar panels after April 2019.","Biography information for Mr Simon Clarke","Mr Simon Clarke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146332","146332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909117","2018-05-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the work undertaken to date by the Independent Review of the Mental Health Act 1983.","Biography information for Rosie Duffield","Rosie Duffield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146321","146321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909118","2018-05-24","Cabinet Office","2018-05-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many fixed penalty notices local authorities have issued to individuals who have failed to register to vote in each year for which data is available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146121","146121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909119","2018-05-24","Cabinet Office","2018-05-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many times the Electoral Commission has used its statutory power to make recommendations to central Government to require electoral registration officers to engage in door-to-door canvassing in each year since that power came into effect.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146122","146122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909120","2018-05-24","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when HM Courts and Tribunals Service plans to announce the results of the tender process on the provision of enforcement services for debt collecting companies.","Biography information for Rachel Maclean","Rachel Maclean","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146346","146346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909121","2018-05-24","Cabinet Office","2018-05-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much central Government funding has been allocated for the purpose of increasing individual electoral registration in each year for which data is available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146123","146123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909122","2018-05-23","Prime Minister","2018-05-21","To ask the Prime Minister, what recent discussions she has had with President Erdogan of Turkey on human rights in that country.","Biography information for Rosie Duffield","Rosie Duffield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146322","146322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909123","2018-05-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 21 May 2018 to Question 144202, how many universal credit claimants have had a disputed earnings referral in respect of their claim in each month since April 2017.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146120","146120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909124","2018-05-23","Treasury","2018-05-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether a first-time buyer purchasing a shared ownership resale property qualifies for the first-time buyer relief on Stamp Duty Land Tax if they elect to pay that tax on the full value of the property rather than on the share being purchased.","Biography information for Stephen Hammond","Stephen Hammond","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146185","146185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909125","2018-05-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had on reports of an attack by the Rapid Support Forces on areas controlled by the Sudan People's Liberation Movement-North at the UK-Sudan Strategic Dialogue in Khartoum; and what assessment he has made of the potential implications of that attack for the declaration of unilateral ceasefire by the Government of Sudan.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146259","146259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909126","2018-05-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received on recent attacks by the Government of Sudan in the Jebel Marra region of Darfur; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146260","146260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909127","2018-05-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what information his Department holds on the number of detainees who are imprisoned without charge in Darfur.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146261","146261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909128","2018-05-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many enforcement checks were carried out by the Animal and Plant Health Agency (a) during the loading of live animals and (b) at ports from which live animals were exported in 2017.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146056","146056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909129","2018-05-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received on the planned  closure of the Kalma refugee camp in Darfur; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146262","146262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909130","2018-05-23","Department for Transport","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much compensation has been disbursed from the public purse to home-owners who are affected by the High Speed Two project in Leicestershire to date.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146100","146100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909131","2018-05-23","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to create more affordable housing in London.","Biography information for Sir David Evennett","David Evennett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146125","146125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909132","2018-05-23","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what recent assessment his Department has made of the effect of housing costs and supply in London on the ability of employers to recruit staff.","Biography information for Sir David Evennett","David Evennett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146126","146126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909133","2018-05-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether the Government is planning to require mandatory environmental reporting by UK financial institutions in line with the framework developed by the Task Force on Climate-related Financial Disclosures; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Djanogly","Mr Jonathan Djanogly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146131","146131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909134","2018-05-24","Home Office","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department how many minors who entered the UK after January 2014 under the Dublin Regulation, or as part of the Calais camp clearance in 2016, were granted discretionary leave under rule 352ZC of the immigration rules and were subsequently denied further leave; and what the nationality of these minors was.","Biography information for Yvette Cooper","Yvette Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146111","146111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909135","2018-05-24","Ministry of Defence","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what progress is being made on plans to redevelop Weeton Barracks into HQ North West by 2022 as part of the 2016 Strategic Defence Estate Review; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146209","146209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909136","2018-05-24","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will ban the use of aluminium composite material cladding with fire retardant polyethylene filler.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146103","146103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909137","2018-05-23","Department for International Development","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what contribution her Department plans to make to the voluntary national review of progress towards the Sustainable Development Goals.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146233","146233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909138","2018-05-24","Ministry of Defence","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the timetable is for works to commence at Weeton Barracks as part of its transformation into HQ North West.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146210","146210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909139","2018-05-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether (a) NHS England's and (b) NICE's dietary advice is under review.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146301","146301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909140","2018-05-24","Home Office","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many children transferred to the UK under s67 of the Immigration Act 2016 (a) have been granted asylum, (b) have been granted discretionary leave, (c) have a pending asylum claim and (d) have been granted any other form of leave.","Biography information for Yvette Cooper","Yvette Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146112","146112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909141","2018-05-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department has any plans to review the effectiveness of the dietary advice provided by NHS England.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146302","146302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909142","2018-05-24","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government,  when his Department plans to (a) start and (b) conclude the proposed consultation on banning the use of combustible materials in cladding systems on high-rise residential buildings; and when he expects the recommendations from the consultation to be enacted.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146104","146104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909143","2018-05-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what representations he has received on dietary advice on the recommended level of fat in diet.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146303","146303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909144","2018-05-23","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what plans he has to improve Building Regulations relating to (a) desktop studies and (b) other aspects of fire safety.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146105","146105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909145","2018-05-23","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will place a temporary moratorium on the use of combustible cladding for the duration of his consultation of the potential merits of a permanent ban on such cladding.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146106","146106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909146","2018-05-24","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to his oral contribution of 17 May 2018, Official Report, column 465, whether it is his policy that developers should cover fire safety and cladding costs where unsafe cladding is found.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146107","146107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909147","2018-05-24","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will set out the assumptions on which he based the estimated cost of the removal and replacement of unsafe cladding by councils and housing associations.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146108","146108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909148","2018-05-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the Written Ministerial Statement of 17 May 2018, HCWS 690 on Energy Policy, which organisations were consulted prior to that statement being made.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146304","146304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909149","2018-05-24","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how much of the Homes England Home Building Fund has been spent in the North East since October 2016.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146134","146134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909150","2018-05-24","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what the average Homes England Home Building Fund loan amount has been since October 2016.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146135","146135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909151","2018-05-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the Written Ministerial Statement of 17 May 2018, HCWS 690 on Energy Policy, what representations he has received from (a) organisations, (b) businesses and (c) individuals on  fracking; which applications for exploratory fracking informed that statement; if he will publish the evidential basis for the statement that fracking will support jobs and the local economy; and what assessment he has made of the effect of fracking on the (i) insurance and (ii) tourism industry.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146305","146305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909152","2018-05-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the potential link between fracking and the manufacturing of non-degradable plastics.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146306","146306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909153","2018-05-24","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what the average length of time has been to process loans provided by the Homes England Home Building Fund since October 2016.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146136","146136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909154","2018-05-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what contribution her Department plans to make to the voluntary national review of progress towards the Sustainable Development Goals.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146234","146234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909155","2018-05-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans his Department has to contribute to the UK's Voluntary National Review of progress towards the Sustainable Development Goals to be presented in 2019 at the High Level Political Forum of the United Nations.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146235","146235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909156","2018-05-23","Treasury","2018-05-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he plans to publish the benefit-in-kind bands for after 2021.","Biography information for Neil Parish","Neil Parish","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146222","146222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909157","2018-05-23","Treasury","2018-05-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, for what reasons the benefit-in-kind surcharge for diesel has been increased from three per cent to four per cent; and what assessment he has made of the effect of this increase on leases which were agreed on the basis of a three per cent supplement.","Biography information for Neil Parish","Neil Parish","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146223","146223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909158","2018-05-23","Department for Transport","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the Government has carried out any assessment of the effect of emissions from older diesel locomotives on public health.","Biography information for Neil Parish","Neil Parish","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146224","146224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909159","2018-05-23","Department for Transport","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the Government has made an assessment of the potential effects on cleanliness of engines of retrofitting cleaner diesel engines into older trains and locomotives.","Biography information for Neil Parish","Neil Parish","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146225","146225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909160","2018-05-24","Department for Education","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when he first received information on the financial difficulties experienced by the University of Chester Academies Trust.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146284","146284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909161","2018-05-24","Department for Education","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, What steps his Department is taking to improve performance of University Church of England Academy.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146285","146285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909162","2018-05-24","Department for Education","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many academy schools have been removed from their sponsors and placed (a) in new trusts and (b) into local authority control in each of the last ten years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146286","146286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909163","2018-05-24","Department for Education","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which academy chains are banned from sponsoring any more schools.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146287","146287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909164","2018-05-23","Department for Education","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether there are any requirements that must be satisfied in order for bachelor’s degrees pursued at an institution of higher education in (a) England (b) Scotland (c) Wales and (d) Northern Ireland to be described by that institution as as a degree apprenticeship.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146110","146110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909165","2018-05-24","Department for Education","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will take steps to remove University Church of England Academy from its current sponsors.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146288","146288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909166","2018-05-24","Department for International Trade","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what representations he is making to (a) the EU and (b) his counterparts in EU member states on the UK's preferred options for when the exemption from US steel tariffs ends on 1 June 2018; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146315","146315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909167","2018-05-24","Department for International Trade","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, pursuant to the oral contribution of the Minister for Trade Policy of 17 May 2018, Official Report, column 410, if he will publish the Memorandum of Understanding between the UK and the Southern African Development Community EPA Group.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146047","146047"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909168","2018-05-24","Department for International Trade","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, pursuant to the oral contribution of the Minister for Trade Policy of 17 May 2018, Official Report, column 410, if he will publish the Memorandum of Understanding between the UK and the CARIFORUM states.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146048","146048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909169","2018-05-24","Department for International Trade","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, pursuant to his oral contribution by the Minister for Trade Policy of 17 May 2018, Official Report, column 410, if he will publish the Memorandum of Understanding between the UK and the Eastern and Southern Africa EPA Group.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146049","146049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909170","2018-05-24","Department for International Trade","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, if he will publish any documents pertaining to agreements reached by the Trade and Investment Working Groups.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146050","146050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909171","2018-05-23","Home Office","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment he has made of progress in tackling the production and distribution of illegal psychoactive substances.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146127","146127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909172","2018-05-23","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, which companies and organisations have been invited to attend the proposed roundtable discussion on the removal and replacement of cladding on privately owned tower blocks.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146109","146109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909173","2018-05-23","Department for International Trade","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what the (a) value and (b) volume of timber (i) imports from and (ii) exports to the Irish Republic was in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146128","146128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909174","2018-05-23","Treasury","2018-05-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the (a) checks and (b) controls placed on goods exiting the UK destined for markets outside the EU are.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146129","146129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909175","2018-05-23","Home Office","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when he expects the final Migration Advisory Committee report assessing the impact on the UK labour market of the UK's exit from the EU to be published.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146130","146130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909176","2018-05-24","Home Office","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department,how many bank account freezing orders have been (a) applied for by his Department under the powers contained in Schedule 7 of the Immigration Act 2016, (b) granted by a magistrates court and (c) granted and then revoked following an appeal since January 2018.","Biography information for Yvette Cooper","Yvette Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146113","146113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909177","2018-05-24","Home Office","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people who had held tier 1 (general) visas have been removed from the UK in the last 12 months as a result of a decision based on s322(5) of the Immigration Rules.","Biography information for Yvette Cooper","Yvette Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146114","146114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909178","2018-05-24","Home Office","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have received compensation from his Department as a result of their unlawful detention in an Immigration Removal Centre in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Yvette Cooper","Yvette Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146115","146115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909179","2018-05-24","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the findings of his Department's consultation on improving the home buying and selling process, when his Department plans to take steps to prevent incidents of gazumping in the process of house sales.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146156","146156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909180","2018-05-23","Department for International Development","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to tackle the stigma of, and discrimination towards people with, HIV Aids globally.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146116","146116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909181","2018-05-23","Department for International Development","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is taking to help ensure regional and global civil society networks have sufficient funds to respond to the HIV epidemic.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146117","146117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909182","2018-05-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, which clinical commissioning groups fund endoscopic thoracic sympathectomy operations.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146132","146132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909183","2018-05-24","Home Office","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what his Department's policy is on contesting an appeal against refusal of leave to remain in the UK once it has received legal advice that the appeal is (a) highly likely to succeed and (b) certain to succeed.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146057","146057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909184","2018-05-24","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department is taking to encourage the Independent Press Standards Organisation to apply for approval under the Press Recognition Panel.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146133","146133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909185","2018-05-24","Cabinet Office","2018-05-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 21 May 2018 to Question 144210 on Electoral Commission: Fines, on what date the last contact between the Electoral Commission and his Department took place.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146124","146124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909186","2018-05-24","Home Office","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the costs to the public purse were of defending the appeal in the case of Ahsan and others v SSHD [2017] EWCA Civ 2009.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146058","146058"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909187","2018-05-24","Home Office","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether his Department has made an estimate of the cost to the public purse of requiring people accused by ETS of cheating in Test of English for International Communication assessments to take another English language test.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146059","146059"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909188","2018-05-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether plans she has to exempt people with Motor Neurone Disease who are in receipt of the higher rate of Employment Support Allowance from being required to undertake a reassessment of their capability to work.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146228","146228"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909189","2018-05-24","Home Office","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps his Department is taking to (a) reduce and (b) tackle incidences of romance fraud.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146236","146236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909190","2018-05-23","Home Office","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate his Department has made of the number of incidences of romance fraud in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146237","146237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909191","2018-05-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many times (a) he and (b) Ministers of his Department have met with the Chief Dental Officer in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Judith Cummins","Judith Cummins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146264","146264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909192","2018-05-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the outcome of the pilot programmes on the new NHS dental contract.","Biography information for Judith Cummins","Judith Cummins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146265","146265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909193","2018-05-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what progress he has made on the development of a new NHS dental contract.","Biography information for Judith Cummins","Judith Cummins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146266","146266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909194","2018-05-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information his Department holds on the number of people who contacted NHS England's Customer Contact Centre after being unable to find a dentist accepting NHS patients in 2017.","Biography information for Judith Cummins","Judith Cummins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146267","146267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909195","2018-05-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he has taken to ensure that churches and other faith-based organisations can play an effective role in the peace process in South Sudan.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146249","146249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909196","2018-05-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people have contacted NHS 111 for (a) emergency and (b) non-emergency dental problems in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Judith Cummins","Judith Cummins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146268","146268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909197","2018-05-23","Department for Transport","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the (a) feasibility and (b) potential merits of completing work on the Northern Powerhouse Rail at the same time as High Speed Two.","Biography information for Judith Cummins","Judith Cummins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146269","146269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909198","2018-05-23","Department for Transport","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of routing Northern Powerhouse Rail through Bradford.","Biography information for Judith Cummins","Judith Cummins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146270","146270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909199","2018-05-23","Department for Transport","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with Transport for the North on the proposed route of Northern Powerhouse Rail.","Biography information for Judith Cummins","Judith Cummins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146271","146271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909200","2018-05-24","Department for International Trade","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what assessment he has made of the trends of UK inward and outward direct foreign investment between 2016 and 2017.","Biography information for Judith Cummins","Judith Cummins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146272","146272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909201","2018-05-24","Department for Transport","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the cost was of the Virgin East Coast re-branding of the East Coast line trains including (a) the repainting rolling stock and (b) changes staff uniforms; who is liable for the cost of that re-branding; and whether a further re-branding be necessary.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146238","146238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909202","2018-05-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he has taken to ensure refugees and internally displaced people take part in the peace process in South Sudan.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146250","146250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909203","2018-05-24","Department for International Trade","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the OECD Foreign Direct Investment Statistics which were published on 27 April 2018.","Biography information for Judith Cummins","Judith Cummins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146273","146273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909204","2018-05-23","Home Office","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of the level of funding for West Yorkshire Police.","Biography information for Judith Cummins","Judith Cummins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146274","146274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909205","2018-05-23","Department for International Development","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what funding her Department plans to allocate to UN agencies working in Sudan in the current financial year.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146251","146251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909206","2018-05-23","Home Office","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of the level of funding for West Yorkshire Fire and Rescue Service.","Biography information for Judith Cummins","Judith Cummins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146275","146275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909207","2018-05-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the report, Alcohol and Mental Health: Policy and Practice in England, published by the Institute of Alcohol Studies and Centre for Mental Health in April 2018, what plans he has to tackle the gaps in provision of treatment services for those with co-morbid alcohol use and mental health difficulties.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146211","146211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909208","2018-05-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he has plans to publish a second Five Year Forward View for Mental Health.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146212","146212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909209","2018-05-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the Childhood and Obesity action plan to tackle the link between social deprivation and childhood obesity.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146213","146213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909210","2018-05-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans he has to tackle the co-morbidity of alcohol use and mental health difficulties under the Government's alcohol strategy.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146214","146214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909211","2018-05-23","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment his Department has made of the consumption patterns of 5 to 15 year olds as a result of advertising aimed a children on (a) television, (b) Facebook, (c) YouTube and (d) Google.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146215","146215"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909212","2018-05-24","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what (a) rights and (b) protections are available to people to prevent data on them that is held by organisations being destroyed under the provisions of the the General Data Protection Regulation implementation process.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146239","146239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909213","2018-05-23","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport,what assessment his Department has made on the effect of Air Passenger Duty on tourism in (a) England, (b) Scotland and (c) Wales.","Biography information for Steve Double","Steve Double","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146300","146300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909214","2018-05-24","Ministry of Defence","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will make funds available to enable cadet adult instructors to attend Stonewall train-the-trainers courses to enable detachment commanders to identify a need to find assistance for cadets identifying to them as being LGBT.","Biography information for Crispin Blunt","Crispin Blunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146046","146046"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909215","2018-05-24","Treasury","2018-05-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what guidance his Department has issued to childcare voucher providers on changes to data-handling as a result of the implementation of the General Data Protection Regulation.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146317","146317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909216","2018-05-24","Department for Education","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 21 May 2018 to Question 144965 on Pre-school Education: Teachers, if he will publish the names of the (a) unions and (b) bodies referred to.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146318","146318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909217","2018-05-24","Department for Education","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what guidance his Department has issued to local authorities on offering incentives to Early Years settings to provide 30 hours of free childcare places.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146319","146319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909218","2018-05-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to his Written Ministerial Statement of 3 November 2017, whether the Multi-Agency Flood Plan Review will be completed at the end of May 2018; and what the timetable is for the review to be published.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146184","146184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909219","2018-05-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if the Government will commission independent research to assess trends in the number of people (a) signposted and (b) referred to food banks in areas where full service universal credit has been rolled out.","Biography information for Ged Killen","Ged Killen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146351","146351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909220","2018-05-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what projection has been made of the proportion of the UK population to be diagnosed with type 2 diabetes in each of the next 10 years.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146149","146149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909221","2018-05-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate his Department has made of the number of people who developed type 2 diabetes in the last twelve months.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146150","146150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909222","2018-05-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much money the NHS spent on treating (a) type 1 diabetes and (b) type 2 diabetes in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146151","146151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909223","2018-05-23","Treasury","2018-05-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much revenue has been raised for the public in each of the last five years from Air Passenger Duty by (a) reduced rate, (b) standard rate and (c) higher rate in (i) band A and (ii) band B.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146352","146352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909224","2018-05-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate his Department has made of the cost to the NHS of treating (a) type 1 diabetes and (b) type 2 diabetes in each of the next 10 years.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146152","146152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909225","2018-05-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the average annual cost to the NHS is of treating a patient with (a) type 1 diabetes and (b) type 2 diabetes.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146153","146153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909226","2018-05-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate his Department has made of the average amount of sugar consumed by a person in the UK (a) in one week, (b) in one year and (c) over the course of their life.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146154","146154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909227","2018-05-24","Wales Office","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what estimate his Department has made of the funding from agricultural subsidies which would be required to maintain the current level of farming in Wales after the UK leaves the Common Agricultural Policy.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146289","146289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909228","2018-05-23","Treasury","2018-05-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether his Department plans to extend the sugar levy to (a) milk drinks containing sugar and (b) confectionery; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146155","146155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909229","2018-05-24","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether his Department has made an estimate of the number of workers working in the UK who are covered by the EU Posted Workers’ Directive.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146290","146290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909230","2018-05-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department has made an estimate of the number of children in England who have mental health issues.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146291","146291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909231","2018-05-24","Department for Transport","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department has made an estimate of the number of flights between non-UK EU airports that are run by UK airline operators.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146292","146292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909232","2018-05-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average (a) mode, (b) mean and (c) median time taken for personal independence payments to be made is, from the date on which the application is made.","Biography information for Sir Desmond Swayne","Sir Desmond Swayne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146045","146045"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909233","2018-05-23","Department for Education","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the powers available to teachers to maintain discipline in classrooms.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146137","146137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909234","2018-05-23","Department for Education","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many 16 to 18-year-olds are studying for BTEC qualifications at each level in (a) schools, (b) sixth form colleges and (c) further education colleges.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146138","146138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909235","2018-05-23","Department for Education","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the competitive tendering policy model for school uniforms in reducing costs for parents.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146139","146139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909236","2018-05-23","Department for Education","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that pupils learn about (a) local flags and heraldry and (b) the importance of (i) national, (ii) county and (iii) town symbols.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146140","146140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909237","2018-05-23","Department for Education","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to ensure that teachers have an adequate understanding of female genital mutilation to (a) report and (b) prevent it.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146141","146141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909238","2018-05-23","Department for Education","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to reduce teachers' (a) paperwork and (b) administrative tasks.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146142","146142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909239","2018-05-23","Department for Education","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children in primary schools in Havering have been excluded in each of the last five years for which information is available.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146143","146143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909240","2018-05-23","Department for Education","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to ensure that a balanced approach is taken to the teaching of British colonial history.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146144","146144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909241","2018-05-23","Department for Education","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of his policies to improve the retention rates of teachers.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146145","146145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909242","2018-05-23","Department for Education","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children at secondary schools in Havering have been excluded in each of the last five years for which information is available.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146146","146146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909243","2018-05-23","Department for Education","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of his policy to encourage more former military personnel into the teaching profession.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146147","146147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909244","2018-05-23","Department for Education","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that children at school learn local history in relation to their (a) county, (b) town and (c) village.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146148","146148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/913760","2018-06-04","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government,  assessment he has made of recent trends in anti-semitic hate crime.","Biography information for Tom Pursglove","Tom Pursglove","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 905660","905660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/907075","2018-05-22","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will bring forward proposals to reduce the potential risk of the judicial system being used to delay investigations by regulatory bodies where there is an ongoing risk to children.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145577","145577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/907076","2018-05-22","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of spending on the services and treatment for victims and survivors of child sexual abuse.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145578","145578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/907077","2018-05-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy, and Industrial Strategy, what representations he has received on the potential erosion of UK intellectual property resulting from potential UK trade partners introducing widening copyright exceptions.","Biography information for Andrew Lewer","Andrew Lewer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145612","145612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/907078","2018-05-22","Treasury","2018-05-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what financial incentives the Government makes available to (a) purchase a car that runs on LPG fuel and (b) convert a car to run on LPG fuel.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145589","145589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/907079","2018-05-22","Department for Transport","2018-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what information he holds on the number and proportion of petrol stations which sell LPG fuel.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145590","145590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/907080","2018-05-23","Home Office","2018-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment the Government has made of the adequacy of the protections against child grooming which have been put in place on Facebook, Twitter and YouTube by those who own and operate those social media platforms.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145586","145586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/907081","2018-05-22","Treasury","2018-05-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of reducing vehicle tax for motorists who drive LPG cars.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145591","145591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/907082","2018-05-22","Department for Education","2018-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what progress has been made on enabling the introduction of a GCSE in British Sign Language.","Biography information for Peter Aldous","Peter Aldous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145568","145568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/907083","2018-05-23","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the total value was of severance packages paid to prison officers who took voluntary early departure in 2014 and were subsequently re-recruited.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145592","145592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/907084","2018-05-22","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the total value was of severance packages paid to prison officers who took voluntary early departure in 2015 and were subsequently re-recruited.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145593","145593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/907085","2018-05-22","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the total value was of severance packages paid to prison officers who took voluntary early departure in 2016 and were subsequently re-recruited.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145594","145594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/907086","2018-05-22","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the total value was of severance packages paid to prison officers who took voluntary early departure in 2017 and were subsequently re-recruited.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145595","145595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/907087","2018-05-23","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the real terms change was in grant allocation from his Department to the Youth Justice Board between 2010-11 and 2018-19.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145596","145596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/907088","2018-05-23","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the real terms change was in grant allocation from his Department to the Youth Justice Board between 2017-18 and 2018-19.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145597","145597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/907089","2018-05-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people have claimed universal credit in each month of the last three years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145550","145550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/907090","2018-05-23","Department for International Development","2018-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much aid her Department is planning to allocate to (a) Commonwealth and (b) non-Commonwealth countries in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145551","145551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/907091","2018-05-23","Department for International Development","2018-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much funding that is currently allocated to the EU's development assistance budget her Department plans to re-allocate to Commonwealth countries after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145552","145552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/907092","2018-05-22","Department for International Development","2018-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, with reference to the Commonwealth Heads of Government Meeting in April 2018, what commitments her Department has made to increase aid and investment to (a) Commonwealth countries and (b) for sea defences to Commonwealth island states to counter the risk of rising sea levels posed by global warming.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145553","145553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/907093","2018-05-22","Department for International Development","2018-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much and what proportion of her Department's overseas aid budget allocated to Commonwealth countries is used to protect and enhance rainforests in those countries.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145554","145554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/907094","2018-05-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Draft revised National Planning Policy Framework, published on 5 March 2018, for what reason he proposes to amend the duty on local planning authorities to make decisions that are in line with the objectives and provisions of the Climate Change Act 2008 to decisions that are within the context provided by that Act; and if he will make it his policy to restore the direct link between the objectives and provisions of that Act and local planning in the National Planning Policy Framework.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145565","145565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/907095","2018-05-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claimants who have been sent an ESA50 form have not returned that form by the deadline and have subsequently ceased to be eligible for the assessment rate of employment and support allowance.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145555","145555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/907096","2018-05-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether she has assessed the potential merits of extending in-work progression services to all low-paid workers in receipt of means-tested benefits and not just universal credit.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145556","145556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/907097","2018-05-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what activities he has taken part in to highlight Mental Health Awareness Week.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145544","145544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/907098","2018-05-22","Department for Transport","2018-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many incidences of sexual assault have been recorded on public transport in Lancashire in the last five years.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145545","145545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/907099","2018-05-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether there are plans to allow males to be offered the Human Papilloma Virus vaccine.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145546","145546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/907100","2018-05-22","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps are being taken to reduce the number of assaults on staff and prisoners in Her Majesty’s Prison Service.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145547","145547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/907101","2018-05-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to his Department's policy release, Government announces it will fully fund unsafe cladding removal in social housing, published on 16 May 2018, whether that funding will cover buildings where such work has already been paid for.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145526","145526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/907102","2018-05-23","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to his Department's press release, Government announces it will fully fund unsafe cladding removal in social housing, published on 16 May 2018, whether that funding has been provided by HM Treasury as an addition to his Department's existing budget.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145527","145527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/907103","2018-05-23","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to his Department's press release, Government announces it will fully fund unsafe cladding removal in social housing, and whether there is a limit on the total amount of spending set aside for that work.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145528","145528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/907104","2018-05-22","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many successful prosecutions have been made under the Racial and Religious Hatred Act 2006 in each year since that Act was introduced.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145548","145548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/907105","2018-05-23","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to his Department's press release, Government announces it will fully fund unsafe cladding removal in social housing, published on 16 May 2018, what assessment he has made of the effect of that announcement on affordable house building by councils and housing associations in each financial year to 2020-21.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145529","145529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/907106","2018-05-23","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to his Department's policy release, Government announces it will fully fund unsafe cladding removal in social housing, published on 16 May 2018, what plans he has to ensure that buildings on which that work is carried out meet high energy efficiency standards and provide a reasonable degree of thermal comfort.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145530","145530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/907107","2018-05-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to his Department's press release, Government announces it will fully fund unsafe cladding removal in social housing, published on 16 May 2018, what the timescale is for that work to be completed.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145531","145531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/907108","2018-05-23","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference, with reference to his Department's press release, Government announces it will fully fund unsafe cladding removal in social housing, published on 16 May 2018, whether that funding will cover buildings where dangerous and flammable cladding is found that is not comprised of aluminium composite material.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145532","145532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/907109","2018-05-22","Home Office","2018-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many incidents of race hate crime were recorded in Lancashire in (a) 2015, (b) 2016 and (c) 2017.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145549","145549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/907110","2018-05-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to his Department's press release, Government announces it will fully fund unsafe cladding removal in social housing, published on 16 May 2018, what definition of unsafe cladding will be used for the purposes of that programme.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145533","145533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/907111","2018-05-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, which private hospitals (a) Ministers, (b) Special Advisers and (c) senior officials of his Department have visited in each of the last 18 months; and what the subject of those visits was.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145570","145570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/907112","2018-05-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions (a) Ministers, (b) special advisers and (c) senior officials of his Department have had with representatives of private health companies in each of the last 18 months; and what the subject of those meetings was.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145571","145571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/907113","2018-05-22","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people were convicted of offences involving racial or religious hatred by offence in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145562","145562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/907114","2018-05-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to his Department's press release, Government announces it will fully fund unsafe cladding removal in social housing, published on 18 May 2018, whether he will require that cladding fitted under that programme is entirely non-combustible.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145534","145534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/907115","2018-05-22","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 17 May 2018 to Questions 142391, 142392 and 142807 to 142816, on Reoffenders: Alternatives to Prison, what the sentence listed as other was in each case.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145563","145563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/907116","2018-05-22","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many men were sent to immediate custody from (a) Crown Courts and (b) magistrates' courts for sentences (i) below 6 months and (ii) 6 months or above in each police force area in England and Wales in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145564","145564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/907117","2018-05-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether all high-rise buildings with unsafe cladding have now been identified.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145535","145535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/907118","2018-05-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many privately-owned buildings identified with unsafe aluminium composite material cladding have (a) started and (b) finished replacing such cladding.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145536","145536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/907119","2018-05-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of councils' legal (a) powers and (b) duties to compel the testing of privately-owned high rise blocks with suspected unsafe cladding.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145537","145537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/907120","2018-05-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what options he is considering to ensure that all privately-owned tower blocks remove and replace unsafe cladding.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145538","145538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/907121","2018-05-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what plans he has to support the large-scale testing of unsafe cladding that is made of materials other than aluminium composite material.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145539","145539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/907122","2018-05-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what the timescale is for all the people who survived the Grenfell Tower fire to have moved into permanent new housing.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145540","145540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/907123","2018-05-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential implications for the effectiveness of the National Cancer Patient Experience Survey of moving data from NHS trusts to (a) a central point of collection within the NHS and (b) an external survey provider.","Biography information for Karen Lee","Karen Lee","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145614","145614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/907124","2018-05-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many households in (a) Barandon Walk, (b) Testerton Walk, (c) Hurstway Walk, (d) Treadgold House and (e) Bramley House have required rehousing as a result of the Grenfell Tower fire; and how many of those households have been rehoused in (i) emergency, (ii) temporary and (iii) permanent accommodation.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145541","145541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/907125","2018-05-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, by what date he expects households in (a) Barandon Walk, (b) Testerton Walk, (c) Hurstway Walk, (d) Treadgold House and (e) Bramley House which require rehousing as a result of the Grenfell Tower fire to be permanently rehoused.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145542","145542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/907126","2018-05-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how much local authorities have been required to pay back to HM Treasury in right to buy receipts in each financial year since 2012-13; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145543","145543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/907127","2018-05-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how much funding (a) has been invested since the 2017 General Election and (b) is planned to be invested through the Government's Industrial Strategy  in (i) Scotland, (ii) England, (iii) Wales, and (iv) Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145587","145587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/907128","2018-05-23","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what recent assessment he has made of trends in the level of participation in the National Citizen Service; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145521","145521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/907129","2018-05-23","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what recent assessment he has made of trends in the level of tourism in (a) the West Midlands and (b) Coventry.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145522","145522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/907130","2018-05-23","Scotland Office","2018-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what discussions he has had with Cabinet colleagues on the tendering process for the new solid support ships for the Royal Fleet Auxiliary.","Biography information for Lesley Laird","Lesley Laird","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145613","145613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/907131","2018-05-23","Department for Education","2018-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent discussions he has had with Cabinet colleagues on the effect of the public sector pay cap on the recruitment and retention of staff in schools.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145523","145523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/907132","2018-05-23","Home Office","2018-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment his Department has made of any correlation between trends in police response times and trends in the number of police officers.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145524","145524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/907133","2018-05-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent changes his Department and Public Health England have made to the system by which women are invited to breast screening; and whether his Department is planning further changes to that system.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145567","145567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/907134","2018-05-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the availability of mental health support for people with haemophilia; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145525","145525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/907135","2018-05-23","Cabinet Office","2018-05-18","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many investigations under s17 of the Welsh Language Act 1993 his Department had open as of 15 May 2018.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145611","145611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/907136","2018-05-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether his Department has plans to work with the English Housing Survey to gather information on private room renting in England.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145600","145600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/907137","2018-05-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether his Department plans to introduce a deposit protection scheme for lodgers.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145601","145601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/907138","2018-05-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether he has plans to simplify the settlement of disputes between landlords and tenants renting private rooms.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145602","145602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/907139","2018-05-22","Home Office","2018-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Home Department, what assessment his Department has made of the risk of sexual exploitation that lodgers and those renting private rooms are exposed to.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145603","145603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/907140","2018-05-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether his Department plans to support the establishment of a lodger landlords’ association to champion best practice in the sector.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145604","145604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/907141","2018-05-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent estimate he has made of non-compliance with the (a) national living wage and (b) national minimum wage in the (i) garment and (ii) social care industry.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145557","145557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/907142","2018-05-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the risk that independent room renting websites which are not part of an accreditation body expose potential tenants to.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145605","145605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/907143","2018-05-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of workplace assessments in Scotland for attention deficit hyperactivity disorder in each year since 2015.","Biography information for Martin Docherty-Hughes","Martin Docherty-Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145582","145582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/907144","2018-05-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether his Department plans to require landlords renting a private room in their home to register with the Residential Tenancies Board.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145606","145606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/907145","2018-05-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether his Department plans to include lodger landlords in the national database of rogue landlords and property agents.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145607","145607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/907146","2018-05-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate she has made of the number of requests for workplace assessments for attention deficit hyperactivity disorder in Scotland which were completed in each year since 2015.","Biography information for Martin Docherty-Hughes","Martin Docherty-Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145583","145583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/907147","2018-05-23","Home Office","2018-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many submissions his Department has received to the review into harassment and intimidation near abortion clinics; and when he expects to publish the outcome of that review.","Biography information for Dr Rupa Huq","Dr Rupa Huq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145608","145608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/907148","2018-05-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate she has made of the number of completed workplace assessments for attention deficit hyperactivity disorder in Scotland which were followed up with recommendations for work place changes and support in each year since 2015.","Biography information for Martin Docherty-Hughes","Martin Docherty-Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145584","145584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/907149","2018-05-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the number of delays to the recruitment of overseas doctors for reasons of visa restrictions in (a) Ealing hospital and (b) the North West London Trust area in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Dr Rupa Huq","Dr Rupa Huq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145609","145609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/907150","2018-05-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he has received representations from the hospice movement on the effect of the proposed increases in NHS pay on that sector; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145519","145519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/907151","2018-05-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the effect of the proposed NHS pay increase on voluntary sector hospices.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145520","145520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/907152","2018-05-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many households in (a) the North West, (b) Merseyside, (c) Wirral and (d) Wallasey constituency his Department has written to on the change in support for mortgage interest from a benefit to a loan.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145559","145559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/907153","2018-05-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many households in (a) the North West and (b) Wallasey constituency were in receipt of support for mortgage interest in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145560","145560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/907154","2018-05-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in receipt of support for mortgage interest resident in (a) the North West, (b) Merseyside, (c) Wirral and (d) Wallasey constituency have applied for a loan under the new scheme.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145561","145561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/907155","2018-05-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the merits of bringing forward legislative proposals to make leading brands jointly responsible for non-compliance with the national living wage within their supply chains.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145558","145558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/907156","2018-05-23","Home Office","2018-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many staff in his Department have been transferred to work on the Windrush task force by (a) team, (b) geographic workplace location and (c) grade.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145572","145572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/907157","2018-05-23","Home Office","2018-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate he has made of the overtime accrued by staff in his Department working on the Windrush task force in each of the last four weeks.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145573","145573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/907158","2018-05-23","Home Office","2018-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the limits for (a) overnight accommodation, (b) travel expenses and (c) per diem entitlements are for staff on the Windrush taskforce who have been redeployed from their normal place of work.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145574","145574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/907159","2018-05-23","Home Office","2018-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many staff from the Home Office in Liverpool have been transferred to work on the Windrush taskforce in another Home Office location; and what each of those locations is.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145575","145575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/907160","2018-05-23","Home Office","2018-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average compensation payment was to people wrongly detained by the Home Office in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145576","145576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/907161","2018-05-23","Home Office","2018-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Refugee Action report, Waiting in the dark, published on 16 May 2018, what steps he plans to take to improve the (a) quality and (b) speed of the asylum decision making process; and if he will provide independent support and information to asylum seekers about the asylum system when they apply for asylum.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145566","145566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/907162","2018-05-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the oral contribution of the Minister for Health of 9 May 2018, Official Report, column 844, whether the £9.1 million in golden hellos to postgraduate students in specific hard-to-recruit disciplines such mental health, learning and disability, and district nursing will be made available to applicants for the 2018-19 academic year.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145579","145579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/907163","2018-05-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the oral contribution of the Minister for Health of 9 May 2018, Official Report, column 844, how the £9.1 million in golden hellos will be divided between applicants for (a) mental health nursing, (b) learning and disability nursing and (c) district nursing.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145580","145580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/907164","2018-05-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the oral contribution of the Minister for Health of 9 May 2018, Official Report, column 844, what estimate his Department has made of the number of students who will study nursing as a result of the offer of golden hellos for certain disciplines.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145581","145581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/907165","2018-05-23","Department for Education","2018-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 17 May 2018 to Question 143877, when last his Department reviewed the adequacy of the current approach to pupils with hyperactivity.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145616","145616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/907166","2018-05-23","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 27 April 2018 to Question 136385, on Ministry of Justice: Contracts, what types of costs are included under the (a) ad hoc, (b) hard variable, (c) soft variable and (d) management variable categories.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145598","145598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/907167","2018-05-23","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, for what reasons reoffending rates for prison sentences and community sentences are not both counted from the time of sentencing.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145599","145599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/907168","2018-05-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when he plans to respond to the letter from the hon. Member for Glasgow North West dated 27 April 2018 on Serco Group PLC’s contract with Public Health England.","Biography information for Carol Monaghan","Carol Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145588","145588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/907169","2018-05-23","Department for Education","2018-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many directive academy orders have been issued to maintained schools that Ofsted has rated as inadequate pursuant to s4(A1) of the Academies Act 2010; and how many of those schools have subsequently opened as sponsored academies.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145610","145610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/907170","2018-05-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what information his Department holds on the proportion of animal rescue centres in England which are members of the Association of Dogs and Cats Homes.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145617","145617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/907171","2018-05-22","Department for Transport","2018-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the timescale is for the commencement of s15 of the Road Safety Act 2006.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145569","145569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/907172","2018-05-23","Treasury","2018-05-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 16 May 2018 to Question 143241, whether Shared Prosperity Fund will be operational on 30 March 2019.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145618","145618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/907173","2018-05-22","Department for Education","2018-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of expanding the list of non-EEA countries that are recognised for the purposes of awarding Qualified Teacher Status in England.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145585","145585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/907174","2018-05-23","Department for Education","2018-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what progress has been made on introducing compulsory Relationships and Sex Education in schools by September 2019.","Biography information for Ged Killen","Ged Killen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145615","145615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906288","2018-05-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions he has had on placing wildlife crime on sovereign base areas in Cyprus on the agenda for the Illegal Wildlife Trade Conference in October 2018.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145292","145292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906289","2018-05-21","Department for Transport","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what funding his Department plans to allocate to dedicated cycle networks similar to London's cycle superhighways in (a) cities and (b) towns throughout the UK.","Biography information for Paul Girvan","Paul Girvan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145394","145394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906290","2018-05-21","Home Office","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will take steps to ensure that the facial recognition software that law enforcement bodies use is accurate.","Biography information for Paul Girvan","Paul Girvan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145395","145395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906291","2018-05-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when he plans to respond to the letter from the hon. Member for Glasgow North West dated 25 April 2018 on myalgic encephalomyelitis.","Biography information for Carol Monaghan","Carol Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145353","145353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906292","2018-05-21","Department for Education","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 14 May 2018 to Question 142462, how many schools have refused to admit looked-after or previously looked after children and were subsequently directed by his Department to do so in the last three years.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145341","145341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906293","2018-05-21","Department for Education","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many looked-after children were refused a place at a free school in each of the last three years; and which free schools have refused to admit looked-after or previously looked after children and were subsequently directed by his Department to do so in each of those years.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145342","145342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906294","2018-05-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what role his Department plans to play in reviewing UK arms exports to Israel as a result of the events in Gaza of 14 May 2018.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145278","145278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906295","2018-05-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what role his Department has in ensuring that UK arms exports to Israel are not being used in contravention of UK National Arms Export Licensing Criteria.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145279","145279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906296","2018-05-21","Ministry of Defence","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether a role is planned for the Goliath crane at Rosyth for the recycling of decommissioned nuclear ballistic missile submarines laid up in Rosyth dockyard; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145287","145287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906297","2018-05-22","Cabinet Office","2018-05-17","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the news release entitled Thousands of voters turned away from polling stations in mandatory ID trials, published by the Electoral Reform Society on 4 May 2018, what assessment he has made of the accuracy of the estimate by the Electoral Reform Society that 3,981 people were turned away from polling stations across the five pilot areas; and if he will make an estimate of what that figure would be in the event that the scheme was rolled out nationally.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145358","145358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906298","2018-05-22","Treasury","2018-05-17","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, which company is contracted to resolve technical issues with the tax free childcare online application system; what targets are set in that contract; and how much money that is paid to that company under that contract.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145359","145359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906299","2018-05-21","Home Office","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average length of time is to process an immigration application for (a) a Visa and (b) leave to remain.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145330","145330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906300","2018-05-21","Ministry of Defence","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the report Submarine Delivery Agency Corporate Plan 2018-2019, published in April 2018, what assessment his Department has made of the implications for the Dreadnought programme of the lessons learned process.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145360","145360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906301","2018-05-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department plans to allocation additional funding to the Learning Disability Mortality Review Programme to ensure the completion of the outstanding reviews into avoidable deaths of people with learning disabilities.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145295","145295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906302","2018-05-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what criteria NHS England will use to monitor the quality of the remaining reviews into the early deaths of people with learning disabilities notified to the Learning Disability Mortality Review Programme.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145296","145296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906303","2018-05-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether NHS England plans to publish regular progress reports on the remaining reviews into the early deaths of people with learning disabilities notified to the Learning Disability Mortality Review Programme.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145297","145297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906304","2018-05-21","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice,  how many prisons have held events to observe (a) Holocaust Memorial Day, (b) National Black History Month and (c) Interfaith Awareness Week in each of the last five years; and what his policy is on prisons observing those events.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145276","145276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906305","2018-05-21","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment his Department has made of the (a) effectiveness and (b) potential merits of expansion to other prisons under his jurisdiction of the Empty Spaces project developed by prisoners at Magilligan Prison in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145277","145277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906306","2018-05-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he has taken to (a) improve air quality and (b) reduce air pollution in York.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145362","145362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906307","2018-05-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, where York is placed in the national rankings for air quality and pollution.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145363","145363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906308","2018-05-21","Department for Transport","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what additional funding his Department is providing to reduce congestion in York.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145364","145364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906309","2018-05-21","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many homes in York have been sold under the right to buy scheme in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145365","145365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906310","2018-05-21","Department for Education","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what funding from the public purse was allocated to York College in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145366","145366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906311","2018-05-21","Department for Education","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much per pupil funding for students was allocated to York College in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145367","145367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906312","2018-05-21","Department for Education","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much per pupil funding was allocated to each primary school in York in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145368","145368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906313","2018-05-21","Department for Education","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much pupil funding has been allocated to secondary schools in York in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145369","145369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906314","2018-05-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claimants of universal credit have waited for more than (a) 2 weeks, (b) 3 weeks, (c) 4 weeks, (d) 5 weeks, (e) 6 weeks, (f) 7 weeks, (g) 8 weeks, (h) 9 weeks, (I) 10 weeks, (j) 11 weeks and (k) 12 weeks for a payment in each month since July 2017.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145370","145370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906315","2018-05-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in York Central constituency claim universal credit.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145371","145371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906316","2018-05-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in York have had their entitlement to personal independence payments upheld as a result of (a) mandatory reconsideration and (b) an appeal hearing.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145372","145372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906317","2018-05-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many benefit claimants in York Central constituency have received sanctions in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145373","145373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906318","2018-05-21","Department for Education","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many people have made claims to the Adoption Support Fund in York; and what the average award has been for such claims from that fund in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145374","145374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906319","2018-05-21","Department for Transport","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many cyclists have (a) been injured and (b) died from cycling-related accidents in (i) York and (ii) the UK in each of the last eight years.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145375","145375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906320","2018-05-21","Treasury","2018-05-17","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to exempt further education colleges from paying VAT.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145376","145376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906321","2018-05-21","Department for Education","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many schools provide first aid training to all pupils in (a) York and (b) UK.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145377","145377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906322","2018-05-21","Ministry of Defence","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many businesses have signed up to the Armed Forces Covenant since its commencement.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145378","145378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906323","2018-05-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to his Department's press release, Government announces it will fully fund unsafe cladding removal in social housing, published on 16 May 2018, what assessment he has made of the effect on residents in mixed-use developments who are (a) leaseholders or (b) are in shared ownership.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145263","145263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906324","2018-05-21","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, when his Department plans to publish the full list of buildings identified as having cladding which requires removing and replacing.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145264","145264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906325","2018-05-21","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to his Department's press release, Government announces it will fully fund unsafe cladding removal in social housing, published on 16 May 2018, what plans his Department has for similar support for leaseholders in private blocks.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145265","145265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906326","2018-05-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with Cabinet colleagues on the recent violence at the Palestinian border.","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145397","145397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906327","2018-05-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the Government condemned the violence used by Israeli forces on protesters at the Gaza-Israel border at the recent UN Security Council meeting.","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145398","145398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906328","2018-05-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many cases have been submitted to the Office of the Pub Code Adjudicator; and how many such cases have been concluded since its inception.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145379","145379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906329","2018-05-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many mental health nursing commissions his Department plans to offer in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145380","145380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906330","2018-05-21","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment his Department has made of the potential economic benefits to the North West of relocating Channel 4 to Merseyside.","Biography information for Damien Moore","Damien Moore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145404","145404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906331","2018-05-22","Department for Transport","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment he has made of the level of compliance of franchised train operating companies with the terms of their franchise agreements.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145267","145267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906332","2018-05-22","Treasury","2018-05-17","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment his Department has made of trends in the level of consumer credit since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145268","145268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906333","2018-05-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what financial support the Government allocated to specialist services for BAME women who are victims of domestic violence in the West Midlands in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145269","145269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906334","2018-05-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what representations he has received from the hospice movement on the impact proposed increases in NHS pay; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Derek Thomas","Derek Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145389","145389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906335","2018-05-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions has he had with his Saudi Arabian counterpart on respect for human rights in that country.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145270","145270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906336","2018-05-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department has made an assessment of the effect of the proposed NHS pay increases on sustainability of voluntary sector hospices.","Biography information for Derek Thomas","Derek Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145390","145390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906337","2018-05-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether voluntary hospices will be entitled to receive a proportion of the additional Government funding for the proposed NHS pay increases.","Biography information for Derek Thomas","Derek Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145391","145391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906338","2018-05-22","Cabinet Office","2018-05-17","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the suicide rates were in (a) Easington Constituency, (b) County Durham, (c) North East of England and (d) the UK in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145305","145305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906339","2018-05-21","Department for Education","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of families in (a) Coventry and (b) Coventry South constituency are in receipt of 15-hours a week free childcare for three and four-year olds.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145271","145271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906340","2018-05-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he has plans to allocate additional funding from the NHS England suicide prevention and reduction scheme to (a) Easington Constituency and (b) County Durham.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145306","145306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906341","2018-05-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment he has made of the reasons for the higher than average rate of suicide in (a) Easington Constituency and (b) County Durham.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145307","145307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906342","2018-05-21","Department for Education","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much (a) revenue and (b) capital funding was provided per pupil in state (i) primary and (ii) secondary schools in the West Midlands in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145272","145272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906343","2018-05-21","Department for Education","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of primary school pupils were in receipt of free school meals in (a) Coventry and (b) Coventry South constituency in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145273","145273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906344","2018-05-21","Department for Education","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many places there are in children's homes in (a) the West Midlands and (b) Coventry.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145274","145274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906345","2018-05-22","Department for Transport","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the funding that will be allocated by Greater Manchester Combined Authority to the High Speed 2 railway station at Manchester Airport.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145409","145409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906346","2018-05-22","Department for International Development","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what funding her Department has allocated to the Government of the Democratic Republic of Congo to tackle the spread of Ebola in Mbandaka.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145392","145392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906347","2018-05-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether his Department made an assessment of the effect of the ban on disposable plastic straws on disabled people.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145280","145280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906348","2018-05-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much funding from the public purse was allocated to biomedical research into Myalgic Encephalomyelitis 2014-2015.","Biography information for Carol Monaghan","Carol Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145354","145354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906349","2018-05-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions he has had with representatives of disability charities on banning disposable plastic straws.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145281","145281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906350","2018-05-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much funding from the public purse was allocated to biomedical research into Myalgic Encephalomyelitis 2015-2016.","Biography information for Carol Monaghan","Carol Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145355","145355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906351","2018-05-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what impact assessments his Department undertook in relation to disabled people in advance of the decision to ban disposable plastic straws.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145282","145282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906352","2018-05-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much funding from the public purse was allocated to biomedical research into Myalgic Encephalomyelitis 2016-2017.","Biography information for Carol Monaghan","Carol Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145356","145356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906353","2018-05-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much funding from the public purse he plans to allocate to biomedical research into Myalgic Encephalomyelitis in the current financial year.","Biography information for Carol Monaghan","Carol Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145357","145357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906354","2018-05-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions he has had with the Welsh Government on the introduction of a ban on plastic disposable straws.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145283","145283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906355","2018-05-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if will make it his policy to suspend all UK arms export licenses to Israel in the light of ongoing investigations into human rights violations by that country.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145303","145303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906356","2018-05-22","Department for Education","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she is taking steps to implement recommendation 8 of the report Growing up North, published by the Children's Commissioner in March 2018.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145332","145332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906357","2018-05-22","Home Office","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 12 March 2018 to Question 131391, what assessment  he has made of the effect of the recommendations of the Spicer Review on his Department's programme of work.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145333","145333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906358","2018-05-21","Attorney General","2018-05-17","To ask the Attorney General, pursuant to the Answer of 12 March 2018 to Question 131392 on Sexual Offences: Newcastle upon Tyne, what assessment he has made of the effect of the Spicer Review on his Department's existing programme of work.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145334","145334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906359","2018-05-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what progress he has made on negotiations with Welsh Assembly Government on the Swansea Tidal Lagoon Project; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Damien Moore","Damien Moore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145405","145405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906360","2018-05-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will make an estimate of the amount of funding her Department has allocated to support workless households in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145403","145403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906361","2018-05-22","Home Office","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 14 May 2018 to Question 142442 on Deportation, what information his Department holds on the (a) number of deportation orders that have been in force for more than five years and (b) average length of time taken before a deportation order is executed.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145335","145335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906362","2018-05-22","House of Commons Commission","2018-05-17","To ask the right hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington, representing the House of Commons Commission, what steps are being taken to tackle everyday sexism, biased language and unconscious bias in Parliament.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145336","145336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906363","2018-05-22","Northern Ireland Office","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, with reference to the content of the contribution made by the Chief Constable of the Police Service of Northern Ireland on the threat posed by the IRA dissidents after the UK leaves the EU, broadcast on BBC Newsnight on 15 May 2018, what assessment her Department has made of the level and nature of the threat posed by those dissidents; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145284","145284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906364","2018-05-22","Northern Ireland Office","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, pursuant to the oral contribution of the Financial Secretary to the Treasury and Paymaster General of 16 May 2018, Official Report, column 390 for 16 May 2018, if she will place redacted copies of the security briefings on the threat posed by IRA dissidents as a result of the UK leaving the EU which were provided to Ministers by the Police Service of Northern Ireland (a) in the Library and (b) with the Committee on Exiting the European Union; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145285","145285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906365","2018-05-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of the availability of acupuncture on the NHS in each Clinical Commissioning Groups in England.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145325","145325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906366","2018-05-22","Northern Ireland Office","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what recent estimate she has made of the likely timescale for talks to begin between the main political parties on the restoration of devolved government in Northern Ireland; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145286","145286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906367","2018-05-22","Home Office","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when he plans to respond to the letter of 4 April 2018 from the hon. Member for Sefton Central on Hillsborough Law.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145321","145321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906368","2018-05-21","Home Office","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the Commonwealth Taskforce will have access the records of (a) HMRC and (b) police records to confirm the status of Windrush generation migrants.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145266","145266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906369","2018-05-22","Home Office","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when he plans to respond to the Named Day Question 129506, tabled on 23 February 2018, tabled by the hon. Member for Sefton Central.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145322","145322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906370","2018-05-21","Department for Transport","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect on the local economy in Clacton of dualling the A120.","Biography information for Giles Watling","Giles Watling","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145410","145410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906371","2018-05-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to (a) the government of Sudan and (b) other governments in that region on the case of Noura Hussein.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Mr Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145315","145315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906372","2018-05-21","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether his Department plans to bring forward legislative proposals to restrict advertising of in-play sports betting; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145348","145348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906373","2018-05-21","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether his Department plans to bring forward legislative proposals to restrict the advertising of online gambling viewable by children.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145349","145349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906374","2018-05-21","Ministry of Defence","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many armed forces personnel from Bangladesh received training at Sandhurst Military Academy in each year since 1997; and whether any of the four cases of Bangladeshi military and police personnel serving in UN field missions implicated in allegations of sexual exploitation and abuse received any training from the UK military at (a) Sandhurst and (b) elsewhere.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145304","145304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906375","2018-05-21","Department for Transport","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of LPG vehicles in reducing levels of air pollution.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145381","145381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906376","2018-05-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the underspend for NHS dentist services was in the (a) 2014-15, (b) 2015-16, (c) 2016-17 and (d)  2017-18 financial years.","Biography information for Mr Edward Vaizey","Mr Edward Vaizey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145294","145294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906377","2018-05-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether the Government has plans to charge European Economic Area NHS staff the NHS surcharge after the UK leaves the European Union.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145345","145345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906378","2018-05-22","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether his Department has made an assessment of the potential merits of the establishment of an independent Sports Ombudsman to improve the welfare of elite athletes.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145346","145346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906379","2018-05-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether his Department has made an assessment of the potential merits of the construction of further tidal lagoons.","Biography information for Damien Moore","Damien Moore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145406","145406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906380","2018-05-22","Department for Transport","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment the Department has made of the number of people who are reliant on not-for-profit community transport.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145347","145347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906381","2018-05-21","Department for International Development","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to help improve healthcare facilities in Montserrat.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145385","145385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906382","2018-05-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effect of the Animal Welfare (Licensing of Activities Involving Animals) (England) Regulations 2018 on the number of dogs left at home for long periods of time.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145262","145262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906383","2018-05-22","Treasury","2018-05-17","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he plans to deposit the instruments of ratification for the Protocol to Eliminate Illicit Trade in Tobacco Products.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145339","145339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906384","2018-05-22","Treasury","2018-05-17","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make it his policy to deposit the instruments of ratification for the Protocol to Eliminate Illicit Trade in Tobacco Products before the 2 July 2018 deadline to ensure that the UK can participate in the event that there is a first Meeting of the Parties this year.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145340","145340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906385","2018-05-22","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, if the Government will bring forward legislative proposals to make it a criminal offence to send an explicit unsolicited picture via electronic means.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145308","145308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906386","2018-05-21","Treasury","2018-05-17","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department is taking to tackle the sale of illegal tobacco.","Biography information for Damien Moore","Damien Moore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145407","145407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906387","2018-05-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether his Department is taking steps to seek the removal of plastics from supply chains; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145386","145386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906388","2018-05-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to improve the efficiency of plastic recycling schemes.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145387","145387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906389","2018-05-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to tackle fly-tipping in urban areas.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145388","145388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906390","2018-05-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the timetable is for the announcement of the treatments selected for the accelerated access pathway.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145338","145338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906391","2018-05-22","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will make it his policy that letters relating to enforcement court orders sent to residences are unnamed to ensure that in incidences where the offender (a) does not live and (b) has never lived at the residence the occupants of that residence have a right to reply to the court before enforcement action is taken.","Biography information for Mr Ranil Jayawardena","Mr Ranil Jayawardena","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145383","145383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906392","2018-05-22","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many court orders the High Court has issued to Enforcement Agents that relate to an address where an offender (a) does not currently reside and (b) has never resided in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Ranil Jayawardena","Mr Ranil Jayawardena","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145384","145384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906393","2018-05-22","Ministry of Defence","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will published the allowances available for military personnel travel between the barracks and home during leave; and if he will made an assessment of the adequacy of those allowances to cover the costs of travel to all parts of the UK.","Biography information for Gavin Robinson","Gavin Robinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145343","145343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906394","2018-05-22","Home Office","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the commissioning letter to the Migration Advisory Committee of 27 July 2017, whether it remains the Government's policy to wait for that Committee's advice before determining the future long-term immigration rules for EU citizens.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145331","145331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906395","2018-05-21","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how much and what proportion of the funding allocated from the public purse for recladding tower blocks that failed safety tests will be allocated to the three tower blocks in Mount Wise, Plymouth.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145411","145411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906396","2018-05-21","Department for Transport","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that the UK's regional airports have the ability to increase their capacity over the next decade.","Biography information for Damien Moore","Damien Moore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145408","145408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906397","2018-05-22","Home Office","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will make it his policy to add the political wing of Hamas to the list of proscribed organisations.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145293","145293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906398","2018-05-21","Department for Education","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to protect nurseries from closure as a result of the introduction of 30 hours of free childcare.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145298","145298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906399","2018-05-21","Department for Education","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many nurseries in each region of England have closed in each of the last 5 years.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145299","145299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906400","2018-05-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether financial support has been offered to Hitachi Ltd to build nuclear reactors in Wales; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145361","145361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906401","2018-05-22","Department for Transport","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he has made an assessment of the potential merits of ending the sale of new petrol and diesel vehicles in 2030 as opposed to 2040 in order to meet the Government's commitments under the Paris Agreement.","Biography information for Anna McMorrin","Anna McMorrin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145393","145393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906402","2018-05-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department is taking to support economic growth in the construction industry.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145337","145337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906403","2018-05-21","Department for Transport","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much compensation Northern Rail has paid to passengers for delays and cancellations since the start of the current franchise.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Sir David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145275","145275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906404","2018-05-21","Department for Transport","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the date on which the first UK trains will be converted to run on hydrogen.","Biography information for Andrew Selous","Andrew Selous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145289","145289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906405","2018-05-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether he plans to introduce an equivalent of the Faraday Challenge for hydrogen.","Biography information for Andrew Selous","Andrew Selous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145290","145290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906406","2018-05-21","Department for Transport","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the Government plans to introduce more hydrogen fuel cell vehicles to its service fleet.","Biography information for Andrew Selous","Andrew Selous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145291","145291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906407","2018-05-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to increase investment in research into rare conditions.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145326","145326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906408","2018-05-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate his Department has made of the (a) start up and (b) running costs of the proposed independent environmental watchdog to be established after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145288","145288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906409","2018-05-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to increase investment in research into trigeminal neuralgia.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145327","145327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906410","2018-05-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to increase awareness among (a) clinicians and (b) the public of trigeminal neuralgia.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145328","145328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906411","2018-05-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what his Department's policy is on commissioning research into trigeminal neuralgia.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145329","145329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906412","2018-05-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the viability of extending BRCA testing to all women over 30 on request.","Biography information for Edward Argar","Edward Argar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145344","145344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906413","2018-05-21","Department for Education","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to support teaching assistants to support children with special education needs and disabilities.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145399","145399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906414","2018-05-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many applications for funding through the Northern Powerhouse have been (a) received and (b) successfully awarded by local authority district in each month since January 2015.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145300","145300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906415","2018-05-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what interest rate for finance under the Northern Powerhouse was offered to successful bidders by local authority district in each month since January 2015.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145301","145301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906416","2018-05-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of extending the eligibility for the motability scheme to recipients of attendance allowance.","Biography information for Paul Girvan","Paul Girvan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145396","145396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906417","2018-05-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether his Department has undertaken an economic impact assessment of the effects of clean air zones and associated air quality measures on businesses in (a) Manchester and (b) Greater Manchester; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145401","145401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906418","2018-05-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions his Department has had with small and medium-sized businesses in (a) Manchester and (b) Greater Manchester on the financial effect on their businesses of proposed clean air zones and associated air quality measures.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145402","145402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906419","2018-05-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 11 May 2018 to Question 141873, what progress has been made on evaluating the potential impact to the sector of sleep-in back-pay liabilities; and which care sector representatives have been consulted with respect to that evaluation.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145323","145323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906420","2018-05-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 26 March 2018 to Question 133443, on Social Services: Minimum Wage, what timescale he has for discussions with the European Commission.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145324","145324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906421","2018-05-21","Department for Transport","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps the Government is taking to encourage the use of (a) recycled plastic materials and (b) other innovative and durable techniques for road repairs.","Biography information for Alex Chalk","Alex Chalk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145382","145382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906422","2018-05-21","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether a mechanism is in place to allow a football club that has introduced a safe standing area to retain that area if it is promoted to the top two tiers of English football.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145400","145400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906423","2018-05-21","Department for Education","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to encourage more SMEs to take on apprentices in (a) Kent, (b) Medway and (c) Gillingham and Rainham constituency.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145309","145309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906424","2018-05-22","Cabinet Office","2018-05-17","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much it cost to deliver the local government voter ID pilots in each of the five local authority areas where the scheme was introduced.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145350","145350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906425","2018-05-22","Cabinet Office","2018-05-17","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much it cost to deliver the local government election postal voting pilots in each local authority area where the scheme was introduced.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145351","145351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906426","2018-05-22","Cabinet Office","2018-05-17","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many additional polling station staff in each local authority area were required to deliver the local government election voter ID pilots; and what the average number was of additional staff at a single polling station who were required to carry out identity checks as a result of the pilot scheme.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145352","145352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906427","2018-05-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the oral contribution of the hon. Member for Thurrock on 10 January 2018, column 146WH, when his Department plans to publish its report on patient travel times.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145302","145302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906428","2018-05-22","Home Office","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether his Department is making special immigration provisions to enable the recruitment and movement of skilled non-UK European scientists working in (a) academia and (b) industry after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145316","145316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906429","2018-05-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether his Department plans to make a comprehensive assessment of the adequacy of the life sciences skills base for the purposes of identifying and planning for potential gaps in that base as the UK prepares to leave the EU.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145317","145317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906430","2018-05-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether he has made an economic assessment of the (a) value of early-phase research and (b) inward investment generated by early-phase trials.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145318","145318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906431","2018-05-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department plans to take to (a) protect and (b) promote early phase research in the UK after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145319","145319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906432","2018-05-21","Department for Education","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many universities are registered as apprenticeship providers in (a) the South East and (b) Kent.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145310","145310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906433","2018-05-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care,  pursuant to the Answer of 22 February 2018 to Question 128062 on social services: minimum wage, if he will provide funding to reimburse the historical capital costs of social care sector organisations.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145320","145320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906434","2018-05-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people there are with registered disabilities in each clinical commissioning group area in Kent.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145311","145311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906435","2018-05-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many young people under the age of 18 were referred to Child and Adolescent Mental Health Services in the South East of England in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145312","145312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906436","2018-05-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what funding has been allocated from the public purse for youth mental health services in (a) Kent and (b) Medway in 2018-19.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145313","145313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906437","2018-05-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department are taking to reduce waiting times for access to mental health services in (a) the South East, (b) Kent and (c) Medway.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145314","145314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905388","2018-05-16","Cabinet Office","2018-05-16","Whether he has made a recent assessment of the potential merits of reducing the voting age to 16 in local government elections; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 905322","905322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905389","2018-05-16","Cabinet Office","2018-05-16","What the Government's policy is on support for the Ban the Box initiative.","Biography information for Andrew Selous","Andrew Selous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 905324","905324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905390","2018-05-16","Cabinet Office","2018-05-16","What recent discussions he has had with the devolved administrations on their receiving additional powers as the UK leaves the EU; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Douglas Ross","Douglas Ross","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 905325","905325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905391","2018-05-16","Cabinet Office","2018-05-16","Whether he has made an assessment of the operation of recent voter ID pilots; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gavin Robinson","Gavin Robinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 905328","905328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905392","2018-05-16","Cabinet Office","2018-05-16","What recent assessment he has made of Capita’s ability to deliver its public service contract obligations.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 905329","905329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905439","2018-05-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the financial effect on people in receipt of Support for Mortgage Interest moving on to a Support for Mortgage Interest loan.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144940","144940"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905440","2018-05-21","Home Office","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have been evicted under the provisions of the Immigration Act 2016 or otherwise made homeless as a result of his Department's actions in each of the last eight years.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144780","144780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905441","2018-05-21","Department for Education","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to ensure the adequacy of training for teachers on child bereavement.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144913","144913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905442","2018-05-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to her Answer of 28 March 2018 to Question 133504 on Social Security Benefits: Medical Examinations, if she will list the key service levels her Department has agreed with the Centre for Health and Disability Assessments.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144884","144884"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905443","2018-05-21","Department for Education","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the means by which local authorities are funded for the statutory services they provide to children.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144888","144888"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905444","2018-05-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that UK exports of medical supplies to Iran are protected in light of US sanctions imposed on that country.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144970","144970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905445","2018-05-21","Home Office","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment he has made of the effect of the reduction in police numbers on levels of knife crime in England and Wales.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144914","144914"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905446","2018-05-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of whether Government funding for NHS England is sufficient to enable it to meet the targets it has been set; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144892","144892"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905447","2018-05-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of the support for drugs rehabilitation provided to prisoners on their release from prison.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144885","144885"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905448","2018-05-21","Cabinet Office","2018-05-16","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, which visits have been made by officials of the Prime Minister’s Office and Cabinet Office Communications to (a) Wales and (b) the rest of the UK since the 2017 General Election; and what was the purpose of each visit.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144858","144858"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905449","2018-05-21","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 11 September 2017 to Question 8402, what assessment he has made the reasons for the increase in the average waiting times for a personal independence payment appeal to be heard between 2013-14 and 2016-17.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144828","144828"
