"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18361","2013-10-30","Home Office","2013-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the Government plans to retain unchanged existing provisions of the UK-US extradition agreement required by the EU-US extradition agreement if the UK ceases to be bound by that latter agreement, pursuant to Article 10 of the Protocol on Transitional Provisions annexed to the EU treaties; and what assessment she has made of whether the US will agree to such retention or planned or changes to those provisions proposed by the Government in circumstances where such agreement is required.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173250","173250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18362","2013-10-30","Department for Transport","2013-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of changes in the number of A350 and Dreamliner aircraft flying into the UK's regional airports in the next 10 years.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173164","173164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18363","2013-10-31","HM Treasury","2013-10-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the cost of administering the national insurance contributions holiday has been in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173195","173195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18364","2013-10-31","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether, in exercising his advisory role to the Department for Energy and Climate Change on gas storage, he took account of the fact that Dr John Roberts, who chaired the report commissioned by the Council for Science and Technology into GB electricity capacity margin, is also, as the Chair of Halite Gas Storage, seeking government approval for gas storage in Wyre.","Biography information for Mr Ben Wallace","Mr Ben Wallace","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173267","173267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18365","2013-10-31","Department of Health","2013-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 17 October 2013, Official Report, column 810W, on ICT, what each of his Department's non-departmental public bodies has spent on (a) iPads and (b) iPhones since 2011.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173180","173180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18366","2013-10-31","Department for Transport","2013-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 2 September 2013, Official Report, column 149W, on cycling, what estimate the National Transport Model makes of (a) the number of trips made by bicycle and (b) the distance travelled by bicycle in each year until 2035.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173273","173273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18367","2013-10-31","Home Office","2013-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will take steps to ensure that the National Crime Agency makes tackling online child abuse images an operational priority.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173291","173291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18368","2013-10-31","Home Office","2013-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how decisions about the National Crime Agency's operational priorities will be made; and how such decisions will be communicated to the public.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173292","173292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18369","2013-10-30","Ministry of Defence","2013-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, for what reasons his Department decided against purchasing land next to its Cape Wrath training range; and what costs were incurred in making that decision.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173282","173282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18370","2013-10-30","Ministry of Defence","2013-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many people he plans to recruit to the new cyber defence unit; and over what period of time such recruitment will take place.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173287","173287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18371","2013-10-31","Home Office","2013-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which countries import the largest volume of legal highs to the UK; and what recent discussions she has had with law enforcement bodies of those nations on preventing such imports.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173307","173307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18372","2013-10-31","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 16 October 2013, Official Report, column 761W, on Colombia, if he will raise with the Colombian President the clauses in the trade agreement between the EU and Colombia relating to human rights, labour standards and environmental standards and the mechanisms for monitoring and enforcing those clauses.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173315","173315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18373","2013-10-31","HM Treasury","2013-10-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he had with the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs regarding (a) human rights in China and (b) the Government's Action Plan on Business and Human Rights before his recent visit to China.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173318","173318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18374","2013-10-31","Department of Health","2013-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether electronic access to patient records by 2015 will cover (a) pre-existing patient records or (b) new patient records after that date.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173369","173369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18375","2013-10-31","Department for Transport","2013-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many times the Channel Tunnel Rail Link has had to reduce its operating speeds below 100mph because of (a) power, (b) maintenance and (c) safety issues since it came into operation.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173329","173329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18376","2013-10-31","Prime Minister","2013-10-28","To ask the Prime Minister, pursuant to his contribution of 28 October 2013, Official Report, column 664, what information has appeared in The Guardian on intelligence matters which the Government objects to on security grounds.","Biography information for Mr David Winnick","Mr David Winnick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173330","173330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18377","2013-10-31","Ministry of Defence","2013-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the Government review of the MOD Police and Defence Fire and Rescue Service will take into account the physical implications of a higher retirement age for MDP and DFRS officers.","Biography information for Gemma Doyle","Gemma Doyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173372","173372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18378","2013-10-30","Ministry of Defence","2013-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent estimate he has made of the cost to completion of the Queen Elizabeth class aircraft carriers.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173341","173341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18379","2013-10-31","Ministry of Defence","2013-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the Government review of the MOD Police and Defence Fire and Rescue Service pensions will include analysis of the effect of bringing officers' pension age in line with Home Office officers on those joining the MDP in the future.","Biography information for Gemma Doyle","Gemma Doyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173373","173373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18380","2013-10-30","Cabinet Office","2013-10-28","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people were registered as self-employed for the first time in each (a) parliamentary constituency and (b) region of the UK in each month since January 2008.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173355","173355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18381","2013-10-30","Cabinet Office","2013-10-28","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many new businesses were registered in each (a) parliamentary constituency and (b) region of the UK in each month since January 2008.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173350","173350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18533","2013-10-31","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment she has made of the value of Silverstone Circuit to the UK economy.","Biography information for Andrea Leadsom","Andrea Leadsom","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 900817","900817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18534","2013-10-31","Women and Equalities","2013-10-28","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what steps she is taking to increase the number of women in senior positions in business.","Biography information for Andrea Leadsom","Andrea Leadsom","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 900835","900835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18535","2013-10-31","HM Treasury","2013-10-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he had regarding (a) freedom of expression, (b) freedom of association, (c) protection of human rights, (d) the rule of law and (e) Tibet during his recent visit to China.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173316","173316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17968","2013-10-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will (a) raise with the Moroccan ambassador and (b) instruct the UK ambassador in Rabat to investigate the injuries caused by police and security forces when breaking up demonstrations in El Aaiun, Western Sahara on 19 October 2013.","Biography information for Joan Walley","Joan Walley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172975","172975"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17969","2013-10-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will (a) raise with the Moroccan ambassador and (b) instruct the UK ambassador in Rabat to investigate allegations that Saharawi homes were broken into and ransacked by Moroccan security forces following demonstrations in El Aaiun, Western Sahara on 19 October 2013.","Biography information for Joan Walley","Joan Walley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172976","172976"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17970","2013-10-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what his policy is on establishing a UN mechanism to monitor the human rights situation in Western Sahara.","Biography information for Joan Walley","Joan Walley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172977","172977"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17971","2013-10-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when he intends to (a) publish and (b) respond to the findings of the independent evaluation of the Partnership Funding approach for flood funding commissioned by his Department.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172978","172978"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17972","2013-10-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what provisions are in place to cover financial liabilities arising from environmental damage and civil claims associated with shale gas exploration should a shale gas operator be declared bankrupt.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172980","172980"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17973","2013-10-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when he intends to publish a summary of responses to his Local Air Quality Monitoring consultation.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172982","172982"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17974","2013-10-29","Department for Education","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what his policy is on the use of Ofsted to inspect and report upon all arrangements for the teaching of deaf children in schools.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172983","172983"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17975","2013-10-29","Department for Education","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the potential damage to children as a result of attendance at boarding school from a young age.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172984","172984"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17976","2013-10-29","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what criteria relating to increasing the participation of (a) women, (b) people with physical or learning disabilities and (c) people from black, Asian and minority ethnic groups are included as part of the bidding process for Sport England funding.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172985","172985"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17977","2013-10-29","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps her Department is taking to promote participation in sport among (a) women, (b) people with physical or learning disabilities and (c) people from black, Asian and minority ethnic groups; and what assessment she has made of trends in such participation since 2010.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172986","172986"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17978","2013-10-29","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of the proportion of Sport England funding allocated to each funded sport which is spent on encouraging greater participation by women.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172987","172987"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17979","2013-10-29","Department for Education","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to improve collection of data on deaf children in England.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172988","172988"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17980","2013-10-29","Department for Education","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of data sets available to local authorities for accurately identifying children who are deaf.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172989","172989"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17981","2013-10-29","Department for Education","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what his policy is on establishing a lower limit on the age at which children can full board at boarding school.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172990","172990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17982","2013-10-29","Department for Education","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the risk of potential psychological damage to children as a result of attendance at boarding school from a young age.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172991","172991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17983","2013-10-29","Department for Education","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to ensure that vulnerable children are not harmed as a result of boarding at a young age.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172992","172992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17984","2013-10-29","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will publish the report shown to Benjamin Mire before his resignation from the Property Tribunal Panel; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Peter Bottomley","Sir Peter Bottomley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172993","172993"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17985","2013-10-30","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the average change in energy bills has been for households in  the (a) Borough of Stockton-on-Tees, (b) Tees Valley and (c) North East in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173004","173004"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17986","2013-10-30","Cabinet Office","2013-10-25","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what work his Department is co-ordinating across Government on deaf communication and language support.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173005","173005"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17987","2013-10-30","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what progress has been made on Ofgem's proposal for a secure and private operating licence condition.","Biography information for Stephen Barclay","Stephen Barclay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173006","173006"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17988","2013-10-30","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many financial penalties have been levied on the six largest energy suppliers for unfair trading with small suppliers in the last year.","Biography information for Stephen Barclay","Stephen Barclay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173007","173007"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17989","2013-10-30","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if he will review whether charges applying to early removal from a fixed-term energy contract are proportionate.","Biography information for Stephen Barclay","Stephen Barclay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173008","173008"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17990","2013-10-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many properties were judged to be at (a) significant and (b) very significant risk of flooding in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173009","173009"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17991","2013-10-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many properties moved from (a) very significant and (b) significant to a lower flood-risk category in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173010","173010"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17992","2013-10-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many sustainable urban drainage schemes were delivered in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173011","173011"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17993","2013-10-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent notifications he has received from the European Commission in respect of infraction actions for breaches of nitrogen dioxide limit values.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173013","173013"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17994","2013-10-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many construction sites were visited by a Health and Safety Executive safety inspector in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173014","173014"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17995","2013-10-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many construction sites (a) in total and (b) in London were issued with a prohibition notice by the Health and Safety Executive in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173015","173015"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17996","2013-10-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many construction sites in London were visited by a Health and Safety Executive safety inspector in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173016","173016"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17997","2013-10-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many safety inspectors worked full-time for the Health and Safety Executive in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173017","173017"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17998","2013-10-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many complaints of age discrimination or harassment have been lodged against employees of (a) his Department and (b) its executive agencies by (i) employees and (ii) other individuals in each of the last five years; and how many such complaints resulted in disciplinary action.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173028","173028"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17999","2013-10-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many complaints of disability discrimination or harassment have been lodged against employees of (a) his Department and (b) its executive agencies by (i) employees and (ii) other individuals in each of the last five years; and how many such complaints resulted in disciplinary action.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173029","173029"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18000","2013-10-29","Department for Transport","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the total investment in (a) infrastructure, (b) rolling stock and (c) stations on the Greater Anglia Line from 2009-10 to date has been.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173030","173030"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18001","2013-10-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many start up loans have been granted to businesses in (a) Gillingham and Rainham constituency, (b) Medway and (c) Kent to date.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173031","173031"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18002","2013-10-29","Home Office","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many and what proportion of police officers have received training in mental health in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173032","173032"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18003","2013-10-29","Home Office","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the number of children trafficked (a) into and (b) out of the UK annually.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173033","173033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18004","2013-10-29","Department for Transport","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the total investment in (a) infrastructure, (b) rolling stock and (c) stations on the Great Western Line from 2009-10 to date has been.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173034","173034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18005","2013-10-29","Department for Transport","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the total investment in (a) infrastructure, (b) rolling stock and (c) stations on the West Coast Main Line from 2009-10 to date has been.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173035","173035"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18006","2013-10-29","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what evaluation has been undertaken of the A4E's work using volunteers to work with complex cases in the troubled families programme.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173036","173036"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18007","2013-10-30","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average time taken is for each type of Class E criminal offence to reach court.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173055","173055"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18008","2013-10-29","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what evaluation his Department has undertaken of the work of private companies working as part of the troubled families programme.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173037","173037"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18009","2013-10-30","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average time taken is for each type of Class C criminal offence to reach court.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173056","173056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18010","2013-10-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much his Department spent on (a) gas and (b) electricity in (i) 2010-11 and (ii) 2011-12.","Biography information for Jason McCartney","Jason McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173063","173063"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18011","2013-10-29","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps his Department is taking to reduce its spending on (a) gas and (b) electricity.","Biography information for Jason McCartney","Jason McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173070","173070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18012","2013-10-30","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent comparative assessment he has made of options currently run by police forces to reduce reoffending rates.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173057","173057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18013","2013-10-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, which companies supplied (a) gas and (b) electricity to his Department in (i) 2010-11 and (ii) 2011-12.","Biography information for Jason McCartney","Jason McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173077","173077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18014","2013-10-30","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many young people in each prison have been identified as at risk of (a) suicide and (b) self-harm.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173097","173097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18015","2013-10-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how much his Department spent on (a) gas and (b) electricity in (i) 2010-11 and (ii) 2011-12.","Biography information for Jason McCartney","Jason McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173064","173064"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18016","2013-10-29","Department of Health","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much his Department spent on (a) gas and (b) electricity in (i) 2010-11 and (ii) 2011-12.","Biography information for Jason McCartney","Jason McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173065","173065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18017","2013-10-29","Home Office","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much her Department spent on (a) gas and (b) electricity in (i) 2010-11 and (ii) 2011-12.","Biography information for Jason McCartney","Jason McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173066","173066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18018","2013-10-29","Department for International Development","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much her Department spent on (a) gas and (b) electricity in (i) 2010-11 and (ii) 2011-12.","Biography information for Jason McCartney","Jason McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173067","173067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18019","2013-10-29","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much his Department spent on (a) gas and (b) electricity in (i) 2010-11 and (ii) 2011-12.","Biography information for Jason McCartney","Jason McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173068","173068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18020","2013-10-30","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the costs incurred by his Department to date are in pursuit of the appeal against the decision of the Employment Appeals Tribunals in relation to the case of Usdaw v. Woolworths.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173059","173059"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18021","2013-10-29","HM Treasury","2013-10-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much his Department spent on (a) gas and (b) electricity in (i) 2010-11 and (ii) 2011-12.","Biography information for Jason McCartney","Jason McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173069","173069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18022","2013-10-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to reduce its spending on (a) gas and (b) electricity.","Biography information for Jason McCartney","Jason McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173071","173071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18023","2013-10-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to reduce its spending on (a) gas and (b) electricity.","Biography information for Jason McCartney","Jason McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173072","173072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18024","2013-10-29","Department of Health","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to reduce its spending on (a) gas and (b) electricity.","Biography information for Jason McCartney","Jason McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173073","173073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18025","2013-10-30","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of the support available for businesses employing fewer than 10 people provided by his Department.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173060","173060"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18026","2013-10-29","Home Office","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to reduce its spending on (a) gas and (b) electricity.","Biography information for Jason McCartney","Jason McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173074","173074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18027","2013-10-29","Department for International Development","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to reduce its spending on (a) gas and (b) electricity.","Biography information for Jason McCartney","Jason McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173075","173075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18028","2013-10-29","HM Treasury","2013-10-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department is taking to reduce its spending on (a) gas and (b) electricity.","Biography information for Jason McCartney","Jason McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173076","173076"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18029","2013-10-30","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will assess the adequacy of the advice made available to businesses employing fewer than 10 people by their bank.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173061","173061"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18030","2013-10-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, which companies supplied (a) gas and (b) electricity to his Department in (i) 2010-11 and (ii) 2011-12.","Biography information for Jason McCartney","Jason McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173078","173078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18031","2013-10-29","Department of Health","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which companies supplied (a) gas and (b) electricity to his Department in (i) 2010-11 and (ii) 2011-12.","Biography information for Jason McCartney","Jason McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173079","173079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18032","2013-10-29","Home Office","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which companies supplied (a) gas and (b) electricity to her Department in (i) 2010-11 and (ii) 2011-12.","Biography information for Jason McCartney","Jason McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173080","173080"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18033","2013-10-29","Department for International Development","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, which companies supplied (a) gas and (b) electricity to her Department in (i) 2010-11 and (ii) 2011-12.","Biography information for Jason McCartney","Jason McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173081","173081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18034","2013-10-29","HM Treasury","2013-10-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, which companies supplied (a) gas and (b) electricity to his Department in (i) 2010-11 and (ii) 2011-12.","Biography information for Jason McCartney","Jason McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173082","173082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18035","2013-10-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether Israel's renewal of co-operation with the United Nations Council for Human Rights would require a commitment by the UK and other Western European states not to discuss Israel and the Occupied Palestinian Territories within article 7 discussions.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173062","173062"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18036","2013-10-29","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of savings to the public purse to date due to crime, health and social problems being avoided as a result of the troubled families programme; and how this figure is calculated.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173038","173038"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18037","2013-10-29","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate he has made of the number of people affected by price rises by (a) SSE, (b) Scottish Power, (c) Npower and (d) British Gas in (i) Paisley and Renfrewshire North constituency, (ii) Renfrewshire, (iii) Scotland and (iv) the UK.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173039","173039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18038","2013-10-29","HM Treasury","2013-10-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what procedures are in place for HM Revenue and Customs' employees who are alerted to loopholes in tax rules.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173040","173040"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18039","2013-10-29","Department for International Development","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what geographic telephone numbers her Department advertises for use by the general public.","Biography information for Mike Weatherley","Mike Weatherley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173041","173041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18040","2013-10-29","Ministry of Defence","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what geographic telephone numbers his Department advertises for use by the general public.","Biography information for Mike Weatherley","Mike Weatherley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173042","173042"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18041","2013-10-29","Home Office","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she intends that actions required of the UK by SCH/Com-ex (99)6 will continue to be carried out, in the same way, if the UK ceases to be bound by that measure pursuant to Article 10 of the Protocol on Transitional Provisions annexed to the EU treaties.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173048","173048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18042","2013-10-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to raise awareness of electrical fires in workplaces in (a) Paisley and Renfrewshire North constituency, (b) Renfrewshire, (c) Scotland and (d) the UK.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173043","173043"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18043","2013-10-29","Home Office","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of how co-operation with other EU member states will be affected if the UK ceases to be bound by SCH/Com-ex (99)6 on the Schengen acquis relating to telecommunications pursuant to Article 10 of the Protocol on Transitional Provisions annexed to the EU treaties.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173049","173049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18044","2013-10-29","Department for Transport","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what investment in (a) infrastructure, (b) rolling stock and (c) stations on the Cross Country Line there has been since 2009-10.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173018","173018"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18045","2013-10-29","HM Treasury","2013-10-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the number of people (a) who have been moved from a full-time contract to a part-time contract and (b) who have had their number of working hours reduced in (i) Paisley and Renfrewshire North constituency, (ii) Renfrewshire, (iii) Scotland and (iv) the UK since 2010.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173044","173044"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18046","2013-10-29","Home Office","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the cost to the public purse has been in each of the last five years of UK compliance with Council Decision 2008/852/JHA.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173050","173050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18047","2013-10-29","Department for Transport","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what investment in (a) on-board catering facilities, (b) WiFi and (c) recycling facilities has been made on the Great Western Line since 2009-10.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173019","173019"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18048","2013-10-29","Home Office","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what measures (a) the EU, (b) other EU member states and (c) the UK have taken to prevent and combat corruption in each of the last five years as a result of UK participation in Council Decision 2008/852/JHA; and what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of such measures in preventing and combating corruption.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173051","173051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18049","2013-10-29","Department for Transport","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the total value of the maintenance contract for the Inter City Express programme train fleet allocated for service on the Great Western Line.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173020","173020"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18050","2013-10-29","Home Office","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many times in the last five years, as a result of Article 3 of Council Decision 2008/852/JHA, representatives of UK authorities have met other members of the network established by that Council Decision; and what the outcome of each such meeting has been.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173052","173052"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18051","2013-10-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many complaints of racial discrimination or harassment have been lodged against employees of (a) his Department and (b) its executive agencies by (i) employees and (ii) other individuals in each of the last five years; and how many such complaints resulted in disciplinary action.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173021","173021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18052","2013-10-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 10 September 2013, Official Report, column 657W, on employment: disability, if he will commission an impact assessment into the effect on (a) sick leave and (b) health of staff who have returned to work as a consequence of changes to disability benefit.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173045","173045"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18053","2013-10-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many complaints of homophobic or transphobic discrimination or harassment have been lodged against employees of (a) his Department and (b) its executive agencies by (i) employees and (ii) other individuals in each of the last five years; and how many such complaints resulted in disciplinary action.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173022","173022"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18054","2013-10-29","Home Office","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the Government would seek to continue co-operation and information exchange with other EU member states and EU bodies that was the same in content as that which currently occurs as a result of Council Decision 2008/852/JHA if the UK ceases to be bound by that Decision pursuant to Article 10 of the Protocol on Transitional Provisions annexed to the EU treaties; how this co-operation and information exchange would then be conducted; and what assessment she has made of whether this would be at least as efficacious as UK participation in the Council Decision.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173053","173053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18055","2013-10-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many complaints of sexual discrimination or harassment have been lodged against employees of (a) his Department and (b) its executive agencies by (i) employees and (ii) other individuals in each of the last five years; and how many such complaints resulted in disciplinary action.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173023","173023"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18056","2013-10-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 5 September 2013, Official Report, column 455W, on credit: interest rates, if he will estimate the number of people with disabilities who have requested a payday loan in each of the last 60 months.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173046","173046"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18057","2013-10-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what proportion of employees within his Department on each Civil Service pay scale are (a) women and (b) men.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173024","173024"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18058","2013-10-29","Home Office","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the cost to UK public funds has been in each of the last five years of UK participation in SCH/Com-ex (99)6 on the Schengen acquis relating to telecommunications.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173047","173047"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18059","2013-10-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many complaints of discrimination related to pregnancy or maternity have been lodged against employees of (a) his Department and (b) its executive agencies by (i) current employees and (ii) prospective employees in each of the last five years; and how many such complaints resulted in disciplinary action.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173025","173025"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18060","2013-10-29","Department for International Development","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she intends to take to ensure that women's equality and empowerment are part of the post-2015 international development agenda.","Biography information for Mark Lazarowicz","Mark Lazarowicz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173026","173026"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18061","2013-10-29","Home Office","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she has put in place to identify victims of child trafficking at UK borders.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173098","173098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18062","2013-10-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, which government departments currently use NRCPD-registered communication professionals to support deaf people accessing their services.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173083","173083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18063","2013-10-30","House of Commons Commission","2013-10-25","To ask the hon. Member for Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross, representing the House of Commons Commission, whether the current review of PICT and Parliament's internet presence will explicitly include a process review of internal services covered by (a) the Hansard Reporting Suite 2 project and (b) the Procedural Business and Data Programmes.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173084","173084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18064","2013-10-30","House of Commons Commission","2013-10-25","To ask the hon. Member for Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross, representing the House of Commons Commission, how much of the failed Hansard Reporting Suite 2 programme was built using open-source software; and which commercial or open-source software was in use when that programme was halted.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173085","173085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18065","2013-10-30","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to prevent the grooming of young people in adult prisons.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173086","173086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18066","2013-10-30","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, in how many cases in each of the last four years UK authorities have conducted consultations with authorities of one or more other EU member state as a result of Article 10 of Council Framework Decision 2009/948/JHA; what the outcome of such consultations was in each case; and what his assessment is of how useful this co-operation has been to the UK.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173093","173093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18067","2013-10-30","Deputy Prime Minister","2013-10-25","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what steps he is taking to increase the number of young people registering to vote.","Biography information for Mr David Ward","Mr David Ward","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173089","173089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18068","2013-10-30","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which requirements of Council Framework Decision 2009/948/JHA have not been implemented by the UK; and what measures the UK would need to take to implement these requirements.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173094","173094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18069","2013-10-30","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the cost to the public purse has been in each of the last four years of UK compliance with Council Framework Decision 2009/948/JHA.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173095","173095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18070","2013-10-30","Department of Health","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of reports published by the Care Quality Commission into Alder Hey Children's Hospital in April 2013 and University Hospital Aintree in January 2013.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173090","173090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18071","2013-10-30","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many requests for confirmation the UK has (a) made and (b) received in each of the last four years as a result of Article 5 of Council Framework Decision 2009/948/JHA; whether each of these requests received a response which was compliant with Article 9 of the Framework Decision; and how quickly each such response was given.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173096","173096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18072","2013-10-30","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if the Government will seek to continue without change the information exchange and co-operation with other EU member states established by Council Framework Decision 2009/948/JHA if the UK ceases to be bound by that Framework Decision pursuant to Article 10 of the Protocol on Transitional Provisions annexed to the EU treaties; how such information exchange and co-operation will be maintained; and what assessment he has made of whether this information exchange and co-operation will be maintained.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173091","173091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18073","2013-10-30","Home Office","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 13 September 2013, Official Report, column 901W, on entry clearances, how many family visa applications have been put on hold since 5 July 2013.","Biography information for Mr David Ward","Mr David Ward","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173104","173104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18074","2013-10-30","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many (a) businessmen and (b) businesswomen he has met in the last month.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173092","173092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18075","2013-10-30","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many new Lord Justices of Appeal appointments in 2012 were (a) male, (b) female, (c) black, Asian and minority ethnic, (d) educated at the University of Oxford or University of Cambridge, (e) educated at other Russell Group universities, (f) educated at all other universities, (g) solicitors, (h) barristers and (i) Queen's Counsel.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173099","173099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18076","2013-10-30","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of justices of the peace were (a) male, (b) female, (c) black, Asian and minority ethnic, (d) educated at the University of Oxford or University of Cambridge, (e) educated at other Russell Group universities, (f) educated at all other universities, (g) solicitors, (h) barristers and (i) Queen's Counsel in each year since 2003.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173100","173100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18077","2013-10-30","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of deputy district judges working in magistrates' courts were (a) male, (b) female, (c) black, Asian and minority ethnic, (d) educated at the University of Oxford or University of Cambridge, (e) educated at other Russell Group universities, (f) educated at all other universities, (g) solicitors, (h) barristers and (i) Queen's Counsel in each year since 2003.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173101","173101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18078","2013-10-30","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of district judges working in magistrates' courts were (a) male, (b) female, (c) black, Asian and minority ethnic, (d) educated at the University of Oxford or University of Cambridge, (e) educated at other Russell Group universities, (f) educated at all other universities, (g) solicitors, (h) barristers and (i) Queen's Counsel in each year since 2003.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173102","173102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18079","2013-10-30","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of deputy district judges at a County court level were (a) male, (b) female, (c) black, Asian and minority ethnic, (d) educated at the University of Oxford or University of Cambridge, (e) educated at other Russell Group universities, (f) educated at all other universities, (g) solicitors, (h) barristers and (i) Queen's Counsel in each year since 2003.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173103","173103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18093","2013-10-29","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate  he has made of annual local authority spending on flood risk management in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172979","172979"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18094","2013-10-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent discussions (a) he and (b) Ministers in his Department have had with shale gas operators on their ability to meet the costs of (i) environmental clean-up and (ii) civil claims should pollution or damage to third party interests occur.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172981","172981"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18095","2013-10-29","Attorney General","2013-10-25","To ask the Attorney General, how many complaints of sexual discrimination or harassment have been lodged against employees of (a) the Law Officers' Departments and (b) its executive agencies by (i) employees and (ii) other individuals in each of the last five years; and how many such complaints resulted in disciplinary action.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172994","172994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18096","2013-10-29","Attorney General","2013-10-25","To ask the Attorney General, how many complaints of homophobic or transphobic discrimination or harassment have been lodged against employees of (a) the Law Officers' Departments and (b) its executive agencies by (i) employees and (ii) other individuals in each of the last five years; and how many such complaints resulted in disciplinary action.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172995","172995"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18097","2013-10-29","Attorney General","2013-10-25","To ask the Attorney General, how many complaints of age discrimination or harassment have been lodged against employees of (a) the Law Officers' Departments and (b) its executive agencies by (i) employees and (ii) other individuals in each of the last five years; and how many such complaints resulted in disciplinary action.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172996","172996"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18098","2013-10-29","Attorney General","2013-10-25","To ask the Attorney General, how many complaints of disability discrimination or harassment have been lodged against employees of (a) the Law Officers' Departments and (b) its executive agencies by (i) employees and (ii) other individuals in each of the last five years; and how many such complaints resulted in disciplinary action.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172997","172997"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18099","2013-10-29","Attorney General","2013-10-25","To ask the Attorney General, how many complaints of racial discrimination or harassment have been lodged against employees of (a) the Law Officers' Departments and (b) its executive agencies by (i) employees and (ii) other individuals in each of the last five years; and how many such complaints resulted in disciplinary action.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172998","172998"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18100","2013-10-29","Attorney General","2013-10-25","To ask the Attorney General, how many employment tribunal hearings have been lodged against the Law Officers' Departments on the grounds of pregnancy or maternity discrimination in each of the last five years; and how many such cases resulted in a ruling against his Department.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172999","172999"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18101","2013-10-29","Attorney General","2013-10-25","To ask the Attorney General, what proportion of employees within the Law Officers' Departments on each Civil Service pay scale have a physical or learning disability.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173000","173000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18102","2013-10-29","Attorney General","2013-10-25","To ask the Attorney General, what proportion of employees within the Law Officers' Departments on each Civil Service pay scale are (a) white British and (b) from black, Asian and from other minority ethnic groups.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173001","173001"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18103","2013-10-29","Attorney General","2013-10-25","To ask the Attorney General, what proportion of employees within the Law Officers' Departments on each Civil Service pay scale are (a) female and (b) male.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173002","173002"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18104","2013-10-29","Attorney General","2013-10-25","To ask the Attorney General, how many complaints of discrimination related to pregnancy or maternity have been lodged against employees of (a) the Law Officers' Departments and (b) its executive agencies by (i) current employees or (ii) prospective employees in each of the last five years; and how many such complaints resulted in disciplinary action.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173003","173003"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18105","2013-10-30","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what proportion of newly built properties were built on flood plains in each year from 2008.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173012","173012"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18106","2013-10-30","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average time taken is for each type of Class D criminal offence to reach court.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173054","173054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18107","2013-10-30","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average time taken is for each type of Class D criminal offence to reach court.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173058","173058"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18108","2013-10-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of reports that pensions providers are refusing low-paid employees pensions under the auto-enrolment scheme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jonathan Evans","Jonathan Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173027","173027"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18109","2013-10-30","Department of Health","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of excess winter deaths in England and Wales in winter 2013-14.","Biography information for Tom Greatrex","Tom Greatrex","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173087","173087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18110","2013-10-30","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the support available in other countries to businesses employing fewer than 10 people.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 173088","173088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17715","2013-10-28","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what proportion of the smart meters currently installed in UK homes were manufactured in the UK.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172716","172716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17716","2013-10-28","Department of Health","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to raise awareness of stillbirth and neonatal death; what steps his Department is taking to reduce the number of stillbirths; and what investment his Department plans in research on prevention of stillbirths and neonatal deaths.","Biography information for Mr Aidan Burley","Mr Aidan Burley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172717","172717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17717","2013-10-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the financial arrangements for the proposed waste incinerator at Hartlebury, Worcestershire.","Biography information for Sir Peter Luff","Peter Luff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172718","172718"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17718","2013-10-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people have applied to the Access to Elected Office for Disabled People Fund to date; and how many such applications have been successful.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172719","172719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17719","2013-10-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether grants from the Access to Elected Office for Disabled People Fund can be applied for to pay upfront costs of participating in a political party's selection process.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172720","172720"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17720","2013-10-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people who were recipients of Access to Elected Office for Disabled People Fund grants have stood for office; and for which political party since the Fund's establishment.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172721","172721"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17721","2013-10-28","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to include lead flood authorities as statutory consultees in all major planning applications.","Biography information for Nick Gibb","Mr Nick Gibb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172722","172722"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17722","2013-10-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he discussed religious freedom in Iran with Special Rapporteur Dr Ahmed Shaheed at the Interactive Dialogue at the UN on 23 October 2013; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lord Stunell","Sir Andrew Stunell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172723","172723"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17723","2013-10-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to prevent rabies entering the UK.","Biography information for Sir Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172724","172724"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17724","2013-10-29","Ministry of Defence","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent progress he has made on improving and increasing defence interoperability with the UK's (a) NATO allies and (b) non-NATO partners.","Biography information for Mr Bob Ainsworth","Mr Bob Ainsworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172726","172726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17725","2013-10-29","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the average cost to individual members of implementation of his proposed changes to the Firefighters' Pension Scheme.","Biography information for Mr Bob Ainsworth","Mr Bob Ainsworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172725","172725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17726","2013-10-29","Home Office","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many firearms license applications have been rejected on the grounds of a history of (a) domestic violence, (b) violent conduct and (c) drug or alcohol abuse in each of the last five years; if she will investigate trends of such refusals; and if she will publish the results of such an investigation in the Library.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172735","172735"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17727","2013-10-29","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to bring empty retail premises back into use; and what funding his Department has provided for this purpose since May 2010.","Biography information for Mr Bob Ainsworth","Mr Bob Ainsworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172727","172727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17728","2013-10-29","Department for Transport","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make an assessment of the effect of Liverpool John Lennon Airport on the (a) North West and (b) British economy.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172736","172736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17729","2013-10-29","Home Office","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make it her policy to gather information on the number of offences committed involving (a) legally held and (b) illegally held firearms.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172737","172737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17730","2013-10-29","Home Office","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether there has been a delay in publication of an evaluation framework for the national drugs strategy; and what the nature of any such delay is.","Biography information for Mr Bob Ainsworth","Mr Bob Ainsworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172728","172728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17731","2013-10-30","Department of Health","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to improve midwife retention rates.","Biography information for Mr Tim Yeo","Mr Tim Yeo","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172738","172738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17732","2013-10-29","Home Office","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of (a) cost savings and (b) the number of extra police officers able to be hired if police officer time spent on Police Federation business was not charged to the public purse and paid for by the Police Federation.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172729","172729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17733","2013-10-29","Department of Health","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many NHS patients in (a) Coventry, (b) the West Midlands and (c) England waited longer than 18 weeks for treatment in (i) 2011-12, (ii) 2012-13 and (iii) the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mr Bob Ainsworth","Mr Bob Ainsworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172730","172730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17734","2013-10-29","Home Office","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the cost to the public purse was of time spent by police officers conducting West Mercia Police Federation business during the working day in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172731","172731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17735","2013-10-29","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the current waiting time is for inmates awaiting enrolment on (a) domestic violence offender behaviour programme, (b) general offending behaviour programme, (c) sex offender behaviour programme, (d) substance misuse behaviour programme and (e) violence offender programme; and how many inmates are (i) currently undertaking and (ii) on the waiting list for each such programme.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172732","172732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17736","2013-10-29","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many applications for Bellwin Scheme funding have been rejected by his Department since May 2010; and who made each unsuccessful application.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172733","172733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17737","2013-10-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will raise the human rights for Baha'i in Iran with the Special Rapporteur on freedom of religion or belief, at the Interactive Dialogue at the UN on 29 October 2013; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lord Stunell","Sir Andrew Stunell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172734","172734"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17738","2013-10-28","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many new deputy judge advocates appointments in 2012 were (a) male, (b) female, (c) black, Asian and minority ethnic, (d) educated at the University of Oxford or the University of Cambridge, (e) educated at other Russell Group universities, (f) educated at all other universities, (g) solicitors, (h) barristers and (i) Queen's Counsel.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172749","172749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17739","2013-10-28","Home Office","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many joint investigative teams including the UK have been set up owing to Article 5 of the EU-USA mutual legal assistance agreement in each of the last five years; what the aims, activities, participants and achivements of each of these teams were; whether the UK would seek to engage with such teams if the UK ceases to be bound by that agreement pursuant to Article 10 of the Protocol on Transitional Provisions annexed to the EU treaties; what legislative and operational measures would need to be established by the UK to facilitate such engagement; and what assessment she has made of the feasibility of such engagement.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172739","172739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17740","2013-10-28","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many new masters, registrars, costs judges and district judges appointments in 2012 were (a) male, (b) female, (c) black, Asian and minority ethnic, (d) educated at the University of Oxford or the University of Cambridge, (e) educated at other Russell Group universities, (f) educated at all other universities, (g) solicitors, (h) barristers and (i) Queen's Counsel.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172750","172750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17741","2013-10-28","Department of Health","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what collaboration there will be between officials working on the update of the NICE guidelines for multiple sclerosis and on the NHS England review of the clinical commissioning policy for the Fampyra form of 4-Aminopyridine.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172740","172740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17742","2013-10-28","Home Office","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the cost to the public purse has been of UK participation in the EU-US extradition agreement in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172741","172741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17743","2013-10-28","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many new deputy masters, deputy registrars, deputy cost judges and deputy district judges appointments in 2012 were (a) male, (b) female, (c) black, Asian and minority ethnic, (d) educated at the University of Oxford or the University of Cambridge, (e) educated at other Russell Group universities, (f) educated at all other universities, (g) solicitors, (h) barristers and (i) Queen's Counsel.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172751","172751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17744","2013-10-28","Department of Health","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how the NHS England review of its commissioning policy for the Fampyra form of 4-Aminopyridine will be conducted; and what the timeline for this review is.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172752","172752"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17745","2013-10-28","Home Office","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what changes to the UK-US extradition agreement have been made as a result of the EU-US extradition agreement; and in how many cases such changes have had a significant effect on extradition between the UK and US in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172742","172742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17746","2013-10-28","Department of Health","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, for what reasons NHS England decided not to recommend that the Fampyra form of 4-Aminopyridine should be routinely prescribed on the NHS.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172753","172753"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17747","2013-10-28","Department of Health","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what criteria NHS England applied when deciding whether the (a) Fampyra form of 4-Aminopyridine and (b) Sativex form of nabiximols should be considered a specialist treatment.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172754","172754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17748","2013-10-28","Department for Transport","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made on the amount spent by his Department on cycling (a) between 2010 and 2015 and (b) between 2005 and 2010","Biography information for Alok Sharma","Alok Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172743","172743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17749","2013-10-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether his Department has signed up to the Time to Change Initiative to end mental health discrimination.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172755","172755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17750","2013-10-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to encourage employers to sign up to the Time to Change initiative to end mental health discrimination.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172756","172756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17751","2013-10-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what discussions he has had to encourage employers taking advantage of the Youth Contract to sign up to Time to Change to end mental health discrimination.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172757","172757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17752","2013-10-28","Department of Health","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many individual funding requests for the Fampyra form of 4-Aminopyridine and the Sativex form of nabiximols NHS England has received from each NHS region in each month of the last two years; and what the age of each such applicant was.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172744","172744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17753","2013-10-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether his Department has signed up to the Time to Change Initiative to end mental health discrimination.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172758","172758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17754","2013-10-28","Department of Health","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to reduce incidence of suicide in (a) Peterborough and (b) England; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stewart Jackson","Mr Stewart Jackson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172745","172745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17755","2013-10-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department is taking to encourage businesses to sign up to Time to Change through its health, work and wellbeing initiative.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172759","172759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17756","2013-10-28","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many households in each (a) parliamentary constituency and (b) nation and region of the UK have (i) signed up for a Green Deal plan and (ii) had measures installed under the Green Deal to date.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172746","172746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17757","2013-10-28","Home Office","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the cost to the public purse has been of UK participation in the EU-USA mutual legal assistance agreement in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172760","172760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17758","2013-10-28","Home Office","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what changes to the UK-US mutual legal assistance agreement have been required by the EU-US mutual legal assistance agreement; and in how many cases each of these changes has had a significant effect on mutual legal assistance between the UK and US in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172761","172761"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17759","2013-10-28","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many new High Court judges appointments in 2012 were (a) male, (b) female, (c) black, Asian and minority ethnic, (d) educated at the University of Oxford or University of Cambridge, (e) educated at other Russell Group universities, (f) educated at all other universities, (g) solicitors, (h) barristers and (i) Queen's Counsel.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172747","172747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17760","2013-10-28","Home Office","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the Government intends to retain unchanged existing provisions of the UK-US mutual legal assistance agreement required by the EU-US mutual legal assistance agreement if the UK ceases to be bound by that latter agreement pursuant to Article 10 of the Protocol on Transitional Provisions annexed to the EU treaties; and what her assessment is of whether the US will agree to such retention or will agree to necessary changes.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172762","172762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17761","2013-10-28","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many new judge advocates appointments in 2012 were (a) male, (b) female, (c) black, Asian and minority ethnic, (d) educated at the University of Oxford or University of Cambridge, (e) educated at other Russell Group universities, (f) educated at all other universities, (g) solicitors, (h) barristers and (i) Queen's Counsel.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172748","172748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17762","2013-10-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when his Department plans that all documents on the UK Trade and Investment website will be made consistent with the UN Guiding Principles on Business and Human Rights.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172763","172763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17763","2013-10-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whose responsibility it is to ensure that all documents on the UK Trade and Investment website are consistent with overall government policies.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172764","172764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17764","2013-10-28","Department for Education","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what public funds were received by the Barnfield Federation to handle the free school application for the former Fernwood Pre-Prep School in Bedfordshire.","Biography information for Ms Nadine Dorries","Nadine Dorries","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172765","172765"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17765","2013-10-28","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect of energy companies withdrawing their cheapest tariffs in order to comply with the requirement to offer all customers their lowest tariff.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172766","172766"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17766","2013-10-29","Department of Health","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he intends to take to ensure that the Government's strategy for recovering NHS costs from those not entitled to free NHS treatment is compatible with its strategies for (a) opposing female genital mutilation and (b) ending violence against women and girls.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172767","172767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17767","2013-10-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the performance of insurance companies in resolving cases of asbestos liability claims.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172768","172768"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17768","2013-10-29","Department for Transport","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the punctuality targets are for trains between (a) Edinburgh Waverley and London King's Cross and (b) Glasgow Central and London Euston; and what proportion of those targets are currently being met.","Biography information for Lord Darling of Roulanish","Mr Alistair Darling","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172769","172769"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17769","2013-10-29","Department for Transport","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans he has to (a) amend the current punctuality targets for trains between (i) Edinburgh Waverley and London King's Cross and (ii) Glasgow Central and London Euston and (b) announce any such amendment.","Biography information for Lord Darling of Roulanish","Mr Alistair Darling","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172770","172770"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17770","2013-10-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much his Department spent on (a) gas and (b) electricity in (i) 2010-11 and (ii) 2011-12.","Biography information for Jason McCartney","Jason McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172772","172772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17771","2013-10-28","Cabinet Office","2013-10-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much his Department spent on (a) gas and (b) electricity in (i) 2010-11 and (ii) 2011-12.","Biography information for Jason McCartney","Jason McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172773","172773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17772","2013-10-28","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much his Department spent on (a) gas and (b) electricity in (i) 2010-11 and (ii) 2011-12.","Biography information for Jason McCartney","Jason McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172774","172774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17773","2013-10-28","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how much her Department spent on (a) gas and (b) electricity in (i) 2010-11 and (ii) 2011-12.","Biography information for Jason McCartney","Jason McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172775","172775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17774","2013-10-28","Ministry of Defence","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much his Department spent on (a) gas and (b) electricity in (i) 2010-11 and (ii) 2011-12.","Biography information for Jason McCartney","Jason McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172776","172776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17775","2013-10-28","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which foreign countries provide how much funding to the cost of keeping their nationals jailed in the UK.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172771","172771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17776","2013-10-28","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how much his Department spent on (a) gas and (b) electricity in (i) 2010-11 and (ii) 2011-12.","Biography information for Jason McCartney","Jason McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172777","172777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17777","2013-10-29","Department for Education","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 2 September 2013, Official Report, column 69W, on the curriculum, whether any new sources of funding will be provided to assist schools in providing training for teachers; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172786","172786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17778","2013-10-28","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many foreign nationals who committed a crime in the UK have chosen to serve time in their country of origin since 1 January 2007.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172785","172785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17779","2013-10-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, which company supplied (a) gas and (b) electricity to his Department in (i) 2010-11 and (ii) 2011-12.","Biography information for Jason McCartney","Jason McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172778","172778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17780","2013-10-29","Department for Education","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 2 September 2013, Official Report, column 69W, on the curriculum, what discussions he has had with subject experts, publishers and school suppliers to identify what support for schools is already in place and what is still needed to fulfil the requirements of the new National Curriculum; which organisations or individuals his Department is working with in this area; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172787","172787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17781","2013-10-28","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, which company supplied (a) gas and (b) electricity to his Department in (i) 2010-11 and (ii) 2011-12.","Biography information for Jason McCartney","Jason McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172779","172779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17782","2013-10-28","Ministry of Defence","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which company supplied (a) gas and (b) electricity to his Department in (i) 2010-11 and (ii) 2011-12.","Biography information for Jason McCartney","Jason McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172780","172780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17783","2013-10-28","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, which company supplied (a) gas and (b) electricity to his Department in (i) 2010-11 and (ii) 2011-12.","Biography information for Jason McCartney","Jason McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172781","172781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17784","2013-10-29","Department for Education","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 2 September 2013, Official Report, column 69W, on the curriculum, when his Department will have formulated a communications plan for ensuring that schools are aware of the changes to the National Curriculum; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172788","172788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17785","2013-10-29","HM Treasury","2013-10-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what his policy is on levying stamp duty on the sale of properties under 2 million.","Biography information for Bob Stewart","Bob Stewart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172789","172789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17786","2013-10-28","Cabinet Office","2013-10-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps his Department is taking to reduce its spending on (a) gas and (b) electricity.","Biography information for Jason McCartney","Jason McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172782","172782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17787","2013-10-28","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to reduce its spending on (a) gas and (b) electricity.","Biography information for Jason McCartney","Jason McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172783","172783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17788","2013-10-28","Department for Education","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to reduce its spending on (a) gas and (b) electricity.","Biography information for Jason McCartney","Jason McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172784","172784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17789","2013-10-30","Department for Transport","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he has any plans to roll-out LED lighting on Britain's motorway network; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172790","172790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17790","2013-10-28","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what costs were incurred by her Department's estate in respect of (a) gas and (b) electricity supply in the 2012-13 financial year.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172791","172791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17791","2013-10-28","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what costs were incurred by his Department's estate in respect of (a) gas and (b) electricity supply in the 2012-13 financial year.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172792","172792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17792","2013-10-28","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 17 October 2013, Official Report, column 860W, on prisoners: repatriation, who paid for each such prisoner to return to their home country.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172798","172798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17793","2013-10-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what costs were incurred by his Department's estate in respect of (a) gas and (b) electricity supply in the 2012-13 financial year.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172793","172793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17794","2013-10-28","Department for International Development","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what costs were incurred by her Department's estate in respect of (a) gas and (b) electricity supply in the 2012-13 financial year.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172794","172794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17795","2013-10-28","Northern Ireland Office","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what costs were incurred by her Department's estate in respect of (a) gas and (b) electricity supply in the 2012-13 financial year.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172795","172795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17796","2013-10-28","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much the UK pays to each foreign country for UK nationals jailed in its prisons.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172799","172799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17797","2013-10-28","Department for Transport","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what costs were incurred by his Department's estate in respect of (a) gas and (b) electricity supply in the 2012-13 financial year.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172796","172796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17798","2013-10-28","HM Treasury","2013-10-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what costs were incurred by his Department's estate in respect of (a) gas and (b) electricity supply in the 2012-13 financial year.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172797","172797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17799","2013-10-28","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what target his Department has set for the number of homes within the UK to take out a Green Deal package.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172800","172800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17800","2013-10-28","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many times an offender given a custodial sentence by (a) a magistrates' court and (b) a Crown court has been immediately granted bail pending an appeal in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172801","172801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17801","2013-10-28","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 22 October 2013, Official Report, column 149W, on snow and ice, what assessment he has made of the success of the Buy Oil Early campaign.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172802","172802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17802","2013-10-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 21 October 2013, Official Report, column 55W, on farms, if he will list (a) all 195 regulations that his Department has abolished and (b) additional regulations that have been introduced since July 2010.","Biography information for Sir Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172803","172803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17803","2013-10-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in (a) Jarrow constituency, (b) South Tyneside, (c) the North East and (d) the UK who have been referred to the Work Programme have found (i) full-time employment, (ii) full-time employment that lasted less than six months and (iii) full-time employment that lasted more than six months.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172808","172808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17804","2013-10-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to enhance the work of the British Council in Latin America; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stewart Jackson","Mr Stewart Jackson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172804","172804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17805","2013-10-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in (a) Jarrow constituency, (b) South Tyneside, (c) the North East and (d) the UK who have been referred to the Work Programme have found part-time employment.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172809","172809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17806","2013-10-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in (a) Jarrow constituency, (b) South Tyneside, (c) the North East and (d) the UK have been referred to the Work Programme.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172810","172810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17807","2013-10-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in (a) Jarrow constituency, (b) South Tyneside, (c) the North East and (d) the UK who have been referred to the Work Programme have found any type of employment that lasted less than six months.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172811","172811"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17808","2013-10-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, when he plans to reply to the letter dated 16 August 2013 from the right hon. Member for Manchester, Gorton with regard to Mr Robin Wright.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172805","172805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17809","2013-10-29","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what public consultation and what meetings with stakeholders his Department has held in the Republic of Ireland regarding the new nuclear plant at Hinkley Point.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172825","172825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17810","2013-10-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in (a) Jarrow constituency, (b) South Tyneside, (c) the North East and (d) the UK who have been referred to the Work Programme have found any type of employment that lasted more than six months.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172812","172812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17811","2013-10-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what proportion of the UK's imported food supply enters the UK by (a) land, (b) shipping and (c) air freight.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172841","172841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17812","2013-10-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much his Department has funded to Work Programme providers in (a) Jarrow constituency, (b) South Tyneside, (c) the North East and (d) the UK.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172813","172813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17813","2013-10-28","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 22 October 2013, Official Report, columns 147-8W, on Green Deal scheme, what criteria his Department plans to use to evaluate the effectiveness of the 3 million advertising and awareness campaign to encourage Green Deal take-up.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172806","172806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17814","2013-10-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what proportion of the UK's food supply is produced (a) in the UK and (b) abroad.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172842","172842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17815","2013-10-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the current level of the UK's food security.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172843","172843"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17816","2013-10-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in (a) Jarrow constituency, (b) South Tyneside, (c) the North East and (d) the UK who have been referred to the Work Programme have found employment to date.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172814","172814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17817","2013-10-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in (a) Jarrow constituency, (b) South Tyneside, (c) the North East and (d) the UK who have been referred to the Work Programme have found part-time employment that lasted (i) more than and (ii) less than six months.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172807","172807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17818","2013-10-29","Department of Health","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people in (a) Ribble Valley constituency, (b) Lancashire and (c) the UK have been registered with NHS dentists in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172844","172844"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17819","2013-10-29","Department for Transport","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what funding his Department provides to the (a) Better Bus Area Fund, (b) Green Bus Fund and (c) Local Sustainable Transport Fund.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172845","172845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17820","2013-10-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many businesses in Peterborough have participated in the AGE 16 to 24 scheme to date; and how many and what proportion of such businesses were small and medium-sized enterprises.","Biography information for Mr Stewart Jackson","Mr Stewart Jackson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172815","172815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17821","2013-10-28","Northern Ireland Office","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what recent discussions she has had with the Ministry of Defence about the recruitment of army reservists in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172818","172818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17822","2013-10-28","HM Treasury","2013-10-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what financial assistance has been given to the Irish Republic in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172819","172819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17823","2013-10-29","Attorney General","2013-10-24","To ask the Attorney General, what the policy of the Crown Prosecution Service (CPS) is on seeking prosecution of police officers accused of crimes whilst working undercover; whether the CPS is taking steps to examine whether there is adequate evidence to charge Bob Lambert in relation to actions undertaken whilst operating undercover for the Metropolitan Police; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172846","172846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17824","2013-10-28","Northern Ireland Office","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what recent representations she has received from (a) the Chief Constable of Police Service of Northern Ireland, (b) the Police Federation and (c) the NI Policing Board on an increase in the number of Police Service of Northern Ireland officers.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172816","172816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17825","2013-10-28","Northern Ireland Office","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what assessment she has made of the talks facilitated by the Police Service of Northern Ireland in Cardiff on parading and protesting.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172820","172820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17826","2013-10-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the human rights situation in Iran and the persecution of people from religious minorities in that country.","Biography information for Meg Munn","Meg Munn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172827","172827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17827","2013-10-28","HM Treasury","2013-10-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the value of each (a) project and (b) guarantee is for each infrastructure scheme for which a UK Guarantee has been contracted.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172817","172817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17828","2013-10-28","HM Treasury","2013-10-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the statement by the Chief Secretary to the Treasury of 22 October 2013, Official Report, column 9WS, on infrastructure guarantees, what the criteria are for projects which have agreed to be listed on the gov.uk website; and which of the schemes named in the statement have secured an agreed Government guarantee to date.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172821","172821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17829","2013-10-28","HM Treasury","2013-10-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the statement by the Chief Secretary to the Treasury of 22 October 2013, Official Report, column 9WS, on infrastructure guarantees, in which region each of the 40 projects pre-qualified for the UK Guarantees scheme will be developed.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172822","172822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17830","2013-10-28","Department of Health","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of ethnic inequalities in mental health services; and what steps he is taking to tackle any such inequality.","Biography information for Tracey Crouch","Tracey Crouch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172823","172823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17831","2013-10-30","Department of Health","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will investigate ways to support children's early development, particularly the first 1,001 days from conception.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172838","172838"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17832","2013-10-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to tackle unemployment among those people who are without work but not currently claiming jobseeker's allowance.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172828","172828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17833","2013-10-30","Department of Health","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if the Government will investigate ways to identify families that require additional support to ensure children are protected in the first 1,001 days from conception.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172839","172839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17834","2013-10-29","Cabinet Office","2013-10-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment he has made of the relevance of unreleased Cabinet Office historical documents relating to Northern Ireland held at Swadlincote to the work of the Historical Enquiries Team in investigating cases from the past; and whether he plans to release these records to the National Archive under the Public Records Act 1958.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172829","172829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17835","2013-10-30","Department of Health","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps the Government is taking to address the disparity between supply and demand for organ donations in England.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172840","172840"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17836","2013-10-29","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of deputy masters, deputy registrars, deputy cost judges and deputy district judges were (a) male, (b) female, (c) black, Asian and minority ethnic, (d) educated at the University of Oxford or University of Cambridge, (e) educated at other Russell Group universities, (f) educated at all other universities, (g) solicitors, (h) barristers and (i) Queen's counsel in each year since 2003.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172834","172834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17837","2013-10-30","Department of Health","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps the Government is taking to use advertising campaigns and education in schools to promote organ donation.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172847","172847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17838","2013-10-29","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of masters, registrars, costs judges and district judges working in the Principal Registry of the Family Division were (a) male, (b) female, (c) black, Asian and minority ethnic, (d) educated at the University of Oxford or University of Cambridge, (e) educated at other Russell Group universities, (f) educated at all other universities, (g) solicitors, (h) barristers and (i) Queen's counsel in each year since 2003.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172835","172835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17839","2013-10-29","Northern Ireland Office","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what assessment she has made of the relevance of unreleased Northern Ireland Office historical documents held at Swadlincote to the work of the Historical Enquiries Team in investigating cases from the past; and whether she plans to release these records to the National Archive under the Public Records Act 1958.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172830","172830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17840","2013-10-29","Department for Education","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what training Independent Schools Inspectorate inspectors received on safeguarding and the protection of children in relation to practice in independent schools.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172836","172836"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17841","2013-10-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what progress he has made on implementing the recommendations of Cut the Red Tape: Report from the Business Taskforce.","Biography information for Bob Stewart","Bob Stewart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172837","172837"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17842","2013-10-29","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of district judges at a County court level were (a) male, (b) female, (c) black, Asian and minority ethnic, (d) educated at the University of Oxford or University of Cambridge, (e) educated at other Russell Group universities, (f) educated at all other universities, (g) solicitors, (h) barristers and (i) Queen's Counsel in each year since 2003.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172831","172831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17843","2013-10-29","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of recorders were (a) male, (b) female, (c) black, Asian and minority ethnic, (d) educated at the University of Oxford or University of Cambridge, (e) educated at other Russell Group universities, (f) educated at all other universities, (g) solicitors, (h) barristers and (i) Queen's Counsel in each year since 2003.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172832","172832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17844","2013-10-29","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of circuit judges were (a) male, (b) female, (c) black, Asian and minority ethnic, (d) educated at the University of Oxford or University of Cambridge, (e) educated at other Russell Group universities, (f) educated at all other universities, (g) solicitors, (h) barristers and (i) Queen's Counsel in each year since 2003.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172833","172833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17845","2013-10-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to encourage the Sri Lankan government to uphold human rights law.","Biography information for Bob Blackman","Bob Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172848","172848"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17846","2013-10-28","Ministry of Defence","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many investigations his Department has carried out into reported civilian casualties that might have involved British assets during the NATO campaign in Libya.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172868","172868"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17847","2013-10-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions his Department has held with civil society organisations in the Northern Province of Sri Lanka on the political and security situation in that country.","Biography information for Bob Blackman","Bob Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172849","172849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17848","2013-10-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much of the discretionary payment budget available to those affected by the under-occupancy penalty has been used in (a) Glasgow City, (b) Scotland and (c) the UK to date.","Biography information for John Robertson","John Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172858","172858"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17849","2013-10-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has plans to visit Jaffna and the former war zones in the Wanni region of Sri Lanka.","Biography information for Bob Blackman","Bob Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172850","172850"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17850","2013-10-28","Ministry of Defence","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what discussions officials of his Department have had with their EU counterparts on the supply of armed and unarmed unmanned aerial vehicles to the Syrian opposition.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172869","172869"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17851","2013-10-28","Department of Health","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his policy is on standardised tobacco packaging; and what recent discussions he has had on this issue with the Cabinet Secretary for Health and Wellbeing in Scotland.","Biography information for John Robertson","John Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172859","172859"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17852","2013-10-28","Scotland Office","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what steps he is taking to inform workers in the defence industry about the potential effect of Scottish independence on jobs.","Biography information for John Robertson","John Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172851","172851"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17853","2013-10-28","Ministry of Defence","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many trained and operational unmanned aerial vehicle (UAV) pilots there have been in the Army since 2004; and in which countries those pilots have flown UAVs.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172870","172870"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17854","2013-10-28","Scotland Office","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what steps he is taking to inform oil and gas workers about the potential effect of Scottish independence on jobs.","Biography information for John Robertson","John Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172852","172852"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17855","2013-10-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what guidance his Department issues to employers on the use of zero hours contracts.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172871","172871"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17856","2013-10-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what his policy is on the prohibition of the use of zero hours contracts.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172860","172860"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17857","2013-10-28","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate he has made of the number of people who have switched energy supplier in (a) Glasgow North West constituency, (b) Glasgow, (c) Scotland and (d) the UK in each of the last 60 months.","Biography information for John Robertson","John Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172853","172853"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17858","2013-10-28","Department of Health","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of people who smoke in (a) Glasgow North West constituency, (b) Glasgow, (c) Scotland and (d) the UK who are (i) under the age of 18 and (ii) over the age of 18.","Biography information for John Robertson","John Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172854","172854"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17859","2013-10-28","HM Treasury","2013-10-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much has accrued to the Exchequer through vehicle excise duty in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172861","172861"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17860","2013-10-28","Ministry of Defence","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer to the hon. Member for Gillingham and Rainham of 31 October 2012, Official Report, column 297W, on unmanned aerial vehicles, how many unmanned aerial vehicles have been lost or damaged in such a way that they have been taken permanently out of use since their introduction by the RAF.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172872","172872"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17861","2013-10-28","Department of Health","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what research his Department has commissioned into reference intakes on food packaging and their reliability in relation to children; and what discussions he has held on this issue with the Cabinet Secretary for Health and Wellbeing in Scotland.","Biography information for John Robertson","John Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172855","172855"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17862","2013-10-28","Ministry of Defence","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Answer to the hon. Member for Birmingham, Yardley of 25 March 2013, Official Report, column 939W, on unmanned aerial vehicles, what income his Department receives from the leasing of RAF Croughton and RAF Molesworth to the United States.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172873","172873"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17863","2013-10-28","Ministry of Defence","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer to the hon. Member for Romford of 10 June 2013, Official Report, column 18W, on unmanned air vehicles, how many tactical assessments have been carried out on unmanned aerial vehicles since October 2007; and if he will place copies of those assessments in the Library.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172959","172959"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17864","2013-10-28","Ministry of Defence","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer to the hon. Member for Blaydon of 14 June 2013, Official Report, column 353W, on counter-terrorism and human rights, if he will place in the Library a copy of the legal and technical briefing on the use by the UK of remotely piloted aircraft as discussed with the UN Special Rapporteur on Counter-terrorism and Human Rights.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172874","172874"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17865","2013-10-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of people that have been (a) granted and (b) refused the discretionary payment with regards to the under-occupancy penalty in (i) Glasgow North West constituency, (ii) Glasgow, (iii) Scotland and (iv) the UK.","Biography information for John Robertson","John Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172856","172856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17866","2013-10-28","Scotland Office","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what steps he is taking to inform civil servants about the potential effect of Scottish independence on jobs.","Biography information for John Robertson","John Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172857","172857"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17867","2013-10-28","Ministry of Defence","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 12 September 2013, Official Report, column 798W, on unmanned aerial vehicles, if he will place a copy of the current operating procedures developed for the UK Reaper Squadrons in the Library.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172960","172960"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17868","2013-10-28","Ministry of Defence","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Answer to the hon. Member for Moray of 3 September 2012, Official Report, column 72W, on unmanned aerial vehicles, what the total budget for the Unmanned Air Systems Capability Development Centre will be in the next three financial years; and what proportion of such costs will be met by contributions in kind by industry.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172875","172875"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17869","2013-10-28","Department for Transport","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions (a) he and (b) officials in his Department have had with rail companies operating in Yorkshire on (i) improving train punctuality, (ii) the frequency of rail services and (iii) local rail infrastructure improvements.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172864","172864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17870","2013-10-28","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether the criteria for funding from her Department to arts institutions include maximising access for children and young people.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172876","172876"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17871","2013-10-29","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate she has made of the number of volunteer libraries in the country.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172895","172895"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17872","2013-10-28","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent discussions she has had with the Secretary of State for Education on young people's access to the arts, heritage and creative sector.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172877","172877"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17873","2013-10-29","Department for Transport","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the current punctuality targets are for franchises on the (a) West Coast mainline and (b) East Coast mainline; and what he plans such targets to be in the next control period.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Mrs Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172896","172896"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17874","2013-10-28","Ministry of Defence","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what proportion of targeting decisions for the UK unmanned aerial vehicles in Afghanistan have been based on pattern of life analysis.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172866","172866"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17875","2013-10-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the classifications of primary health conditions recorded for claimants of employment and support allowance are.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172897","172897"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17876","2013-10-28","Ministry of Defence","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many remotely piloted aircraft weapons discharge reports have been referred to the ISAF Joint Incident Assessment Team.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172867","172867"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17877","2013-10-28","Ministry of Defence","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 12 September 2013, Official Report, column 798W, on unmanned aerial vehicles, which other aspects of the Reaper Agreement are currently the subject of review.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172961","172961"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17878","2013-10-29","Department of Health","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of drug treatment clients with parental responsibility who are prescribed opioid substitution therapy receive their treatment by (a) supervised consumption, (b) daily pick-up and (c) weekly pick-up regimes.","Biography information for Meg Munn","Meg Munn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172898","172898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17879","2013-10-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what information sources are drawn on in determining which primary health condition should be recorded for each claimant of employment and support allowance.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172899","172899"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17880","2013-10-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his Iranian counterpart on the situation of members of the Bah'i faith.","Biography information for Meg Munn","Meg Munn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172905","172905"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17881","2013-10-29","Department of Health","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many drug treatment clients who are prescribed opioid substitution therapy also have parental responsibility.","Biography information for Meg Munn","Meg Munn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172900","172900"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17882","2013-10-29","Department for International Development","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of UK-funded aid programmes in Belarus.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172906","172906"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17883","2013-10-28","Home Office","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 18 July 2013, Official Report, column 912W, if her Department will collate and hold information centrally on the use of unmanned aerial vehicles by police services in England and Wales.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172963","172963"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17884","2013-10-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he intends to issue a report on the deliberations of the Work Programme best practice group; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172901","172901"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17885","2013-10-28","Cabinet Office","2013-10-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will estimate how many (a) men and (b) women in (i) full-time employment, (ii) part-time employment and (iii) self-employment in each parliamentary constituency earned less than the rate defined by the Living Wage Foundation as a living wage in (A) 2012 and (B) 2013 to date.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172878","172878"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17886","2013-10-28","Cabinet Office","2013-10-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many part-time workers are working less than 24 hours a week.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172879","172879"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17887","2013-10-29","Department of Health","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people have had to wait more than (a) 28 days, (b) six months and (c) one year for treatment under the Improving Access to Psychological Therapies programme in the last five years.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172907","172907"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17888","2013-10-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions on the effect of that Department's policies on food poverty in the UK; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172902","172902"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17889","2013-10-29","Department of Health","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what real-terms expenditure on adult mental health services has been in each year since 1997-98.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172908","172908"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17890","2013-10-28","Ministry of Defence","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 15 October 2013, Official Report, column 636W, on Gulf States, whether RAF personnel stationed in support of the US in the Gulf have access to US intelligence and analysis used for the purposes of drone strikes.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172964","172964"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17891","2013-10-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many times the Work Programme best practice group has met since 24 April 2013.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172903","172903"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17892","2013-10-28","Ministry of Defence","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 15 October 2013, Official Report, column 636W, on Gulf States, whether RAF personnel stationed in support of the US in the Gulf includes drone pilots or sensor operators.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172965","172965"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17893","2013-10-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment has he made of the most recent report by the UN Special Rapporteur on human rights in Iran and freedom of religion in that country.","Biography information for Meg Munn","Meg Munn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172904","172904"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17894","2013-10-29","Department for International Development","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much her Department spends annually in Belarus (a) directly and (b) with multilateral organisations; and on what programmes such funding is spent.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172910","172910"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17895","2013-10-29","Department for International Development","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many times (a) she, (b) Ministers in her Department and (c) officials in her Department have visited Belarus since May 2010.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172912","172912"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17896","2013-10-29","Department for International Development","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many times she has met Ministers from the Belarusian government since taking office.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172913","172913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17897","2013-10-29","Department for International Development","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, in which countries her Department's contribution to EuropeAid is directed.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172914","172914"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17898","2013-10-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will estimate how many people in (a) Wrexham constituency and (b) each other constituency in Wales will be affected by the changes in universal credit payments on and after its introduction as each increase in the personal income tax allowance planned by the Government takes effect; and what the average change per month in universal credit payments would be for any such people in (i) Wrexham constituency and (ii) each other constituency in Wales.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172882","172882"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17899","2013-10-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 14 October 2013, Official Report, column 457W, on unmanned air vehicles, whether non-core functions or agencies of his Department have used unmanned aerial vehicles over the last five years.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172966","172966"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17900","2013-10-29","Department for Transport","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many people retained by HS2 Ltd on personal service contracts have been found not to have been compliant with their tax and National Insurance obligations until contacted by the Department's representive looking into this aspect of their employment.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172915","172915"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17901","2013-10-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to support small businesses in (a) Wrexham constituency, (b) Wales and (c) the UK.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172885","172885"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17902","2013-10-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what reports his Department has laid before each House of Parliament pursuant to section 70(9) of the Charities Act 2006 in 2012-13.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172927","172927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17903","2013-10-28","Cabinet Office","2013-10-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what recent estimate he has made of the number of people in part-time work who are seeking full-time employment in each parliamentary constituency in Wales.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172886","172886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17904","2013-10-29","Department for Transport","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 22 October 2013, Official Report, column 124W, on High Speed 2, if he will list the 48 people who have been engaged by HS2 Ltd in the last 12 months via personal service companies together with copies of their contracts.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172916","172916"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17905","2013-10-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in (a) Wrexham constituency, (b) Wales and (c) the UK claimed in-work credit in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172887","172887"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17906","2013-10-29","Department for Transport","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 22 October 2013, Official Report, column 120W, on High Speed 2, if he will publish (a) the case for strategic rail alternatives to High Speed 2 commissioned from WS Atkins, (b) the Professional Services Commercial analysis WP7 commissioined from PwC, (c) the professional Services Regional Economic Analysis commissioned from KPMG LLP and (d) the professional services full audit of HS2 Ltd modelling from Sinclair Knight Merz (Europe) Ltd (SKM).","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172917","172917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17907","2013-10-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many children were classed as living in poverty in each parliamentary constituency in the UK in each of the last five years; and what estimate he has made of the number of such children in each of the next three years.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172888","172888"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17908","2013-10-29","Department of Health","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 11 September 2013, Official Report, column 716W, on Warm Homes Healthy People Fund, if he will make a comparative assessment of the effectiveness of the delivery of the ring-fenced funding and the Warm Homes Healthy People Fund.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172918","172918"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17909","2013-10-28","Department of Health","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of emergency mental health care in the NHS.","Biography information for Tracey Crouch","Tracey Crouch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172889","172889"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17910","2013-10-29","Department for Transport","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which people engaged by (a) HS2 Ltd and (b) his Department with responsibility for the High Speed 2 project have (a) received bonuses or (b) been contracted with promises of bonus payments; what the value of each such bonus payments was; and what performance indicators were attached to such bonuses.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172919","172919"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17911","2013-10-29","Department of Health","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of progress to date towards the Coalition Agreement Commitment in the provision of 4,200 more health visitors.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172920","172920"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17912","2013-10-29","Department of Health","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to encourage NHS trusts to employ more health visitors.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172921","172921"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17913","2013-10-29","Department of Health","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of regional variations in standards of post-natal care; and what steps he is taking to ensure consistently high levels of care.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172922","172922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17914","2013-10-28","Department of Health","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many NHS employees have been dismissed for misconduct in the last 12 months; whether the records of those employees have been permanently marked to ensure that they will not be re-employed in the NHS; and how many of those employees have been (a) reported to the police and (b) prosecuted.","Biography information for Tracey Crouch","Tracey Crouch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172891","172891"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17915","2013-10-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the level of (a) exports and (b) imports between the UK and China was in each of the last five years by sector.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172923","172923"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17916","2013-10-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the level of (a) exports and (b) imports between the UK and its top 20 trading partners in Asia was in each of the last five years by sector.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172924","172924"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17917","2013-10-29","Department for Transport","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the statement of 24 October 2013 on Haulage, Road Tank Vehicle Compliance, which model of fuel tanker the statement refers to; for what reason they are not in full compliance with the European Agreement Concerning the International Carriage of Dangerous Goods by Road; what assessment he has made of the risk posed by such non-compliance to other road users; and what assessment he has made of vehicle inspection services by Bureau Veritas.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172968","172968"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17918","2013-10-29","Department of Health","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of staffing levels at places of safety in England as defined by the Mental Health Act 1983 for each year since 1997-98.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172953","172953"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17919","2013-10-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when he plans to publish his assessment of the (a) effectiveness and (b) humaneness of the badger cull; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tracey Crouch","Tracey Crouch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172894","172894"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17920","2013-10-29","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent discussions she has had with libraries about volunteer libraries failing to pay Public Lending Right fees.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172954","172954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17921","2013-10-29","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps she is taking to ensure that volunteer libraries pay Public Lending Right fees.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172955","172955"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17922","2013-10-29","Department for Transport","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will list the parliamentary constituencies which the KPMG report on the economic impact of High Speed 2 indicated would be negatively affected.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172925","172925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17923","2013-10-29","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many school age children participated in or accessed (a) dance or singing, (b) playing a musical instrument or writing music, (c) theatre, (d) opera/musical theatre, (e) carnival or circus, (f) street art, (g) visual art and photography, (h) film or video, (i) craft, (j) creative writing and (k) another cultural event in each year between 2009-10 and 2012-13.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172956","172956"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17924","2013-10-28","Attorney General","2013-10-24","To ask the Attorney General, what reports the Law Officers' Departments have laid before each House of Parliament pursuant to section 70(9) of the Charities Act 2006 in 2012-13.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172928","172928"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17925","2013-10-28","Cabinet Office","2013-10-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what reports his Department has laid before each House of Parliament pursuant to section 70(9) of the Charities Act 2006 in 2012-13.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172929","172929"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17926","2013-10-29","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many 16 to 24 year olds participated in or accessed (a) dance or singing, (b) playing a musical instrument or writing music, (c) theatre, (d) opera/musical theatre, (e) carnival or circus, (f) street art, (g) visual art and photography, (h) film or video, (i) craft, (j) creative writing and (k) another cultural event in each year between 2009-10 and 2012-13.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172957","172957"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17927","2013-10-28","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what reports his Department has laid before each House of Parliament pursuant to section 70(9) of the Charities Act 2006 in 2012-13.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172931","172931"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17928","2013-10-28","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what reports her Department has laid before each House of Parliament pursuant to section 70(9) of the Charities Act 2006 in 2012-13.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172932","172932"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17929","2013-10-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what comparative assessment he has made of the effect on the relative health of claimants and their dependants of changes to the jobseeker's allowance sanction regime introduced in October 2012.","Biography information for Sarah Teather","Sarah Teather","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172926","172926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17930","2013-10-28","Ministry of Defence","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what reports his Department has laid before each House of Parliament pursuant to section 70(9) of the Charities Act 2006 in 2012-13.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172933","172933"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17931","2013-10-28","Department for Education","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what reports his Department has laid before each House of Parliament pursuant to section 70(9) of the Charities Act 2006 in 2012-13.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172935","172935"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17932","2013-10-29","Home Office","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the exercise by immigration officials of powers under Schedule 7 of the Terrorism Act 2000 when they detained Baraa Shiban at Gatwick Airport on 23 September 2013.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172958","172958"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17933","2013-10-28","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what reports his Department has laid before each House of Parliament pursuant to section 70(9) of the Charities Act 2006 in 2012-13.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172936","172936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17934","2013-10-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what reports his Department has laid before each House of Parliament pursuant to section 70(9) of the Charities Act 2006 in 2012-13.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172937","172937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17935","2013-10-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports his Department has laid before each House of Parliament pursuant to section 70(9) of the Charities Act 2006 in 2012-13.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172938","172938"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17936","2013-10-28","Women and Equalities","2013-10-24","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what reports the Government Equalities Office has laid before each House of Parliament pursuant to section 70(9) of the Charities Act 2006 in 2012-13.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172939","172939"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17937","2013-10-28","Home Office","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what reports her Department has laid before each House of Parliament pursuant to section 70(9) of the Charities Act 2006 in 2012-13.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172941","172941"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17938","2013-10-28","Department for International Development","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what reports her Department has laid before each House of Parliament pursuant to section 70(9) of the Charities Act 2006 in 2012-13.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172942","172942"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17939","2013-10-28","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what reports his Department has laid before each House of Parliament pursuant to section 70(9) of the Charities Act 2006 in 2012-13.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172944","172944"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17940","2013-10-28","Northern Ireland Office","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what reports her Department has laid before each House of Parliament pursuant to section 70(9) of the Charities Act 2006 in 2012-13.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172946","172946"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17941","2013-10-28","Scotland Office","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what reports his Department has laid before each House of Parliament pursuant to section 70(9) of the Charities Act 2006 in 2012-13.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172948","172948"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17942","2013-10-28","Department for Transport","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what reports his Department has laid before each House of Parliament pursuant to section 70(9) of the Charities Act 2006 in 2012-13.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172949","172949"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17943","2013-10-28","HM Treasury","2013-10-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what reports his Department has laid before each House of Parliament pursuant to section 70(9) of the Charities Act 2006 in 2012-13.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172950","172950"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17944","2013-10-28","Wales Office","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what reports his Department has laid before each House of Parliament pursuant to section 70(9) of the Charities Act 2006 in 2012-13.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172951","172951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17945","2013-10-29","Department for Transport","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he expects to consult on the terms of the contract to operate Trans Pennine rail services between April 2015 and February 2016; and what form that consultation will take.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172970","172970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17946","2013-10-29","Home Office","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the number of head shops selling legal highs in (a) the UK and (b) each local authority area.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172971","172971"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17947","2013-10-29","Home Office","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the total value of legal highs sold in the UK (a) by head shops, (b) online and (c) by other outlets.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172972","172972"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17948","2013-10-29","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what recent estimate he has made of the number of second homes in the (a) Barrow-in-Furness and (b) South Lakeland council areas.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172973","172973"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17949","2013-10-29","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate she has made of the proportion of households in Barrow and Furness constituency which have (a) 3G network coverage and (b) 3G network coverage by more than one network provider.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172974","172974"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17950","2013-10-30","Leader of the House","2013-10-24","To ask the Leader of the House, if he will bring forward proposals in respect of the regulation of hon. Members and second jobs.","Biography information for Graeme Morrice","Graeme Morrice","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 900791","900791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17952","2013-10-29","Cabinet Office","2013-10-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many young people from Northamptonshire have taken part in the National Citizen Service to date.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172824","172824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17953","2013-10-29","Department for Education","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 15 October 2013, Official Report, column 696W, on Education Endowment Foundation, what information his Department holds on meetings between Ministers of his Department and EEF since May 2010.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172826","172826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17954","2013-10-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the Answer to the hon. Member for Penistone and Stocksbridge, of 25 April 2013, Official Report, column 1237W, on trapping, when he will publish the Government's findings; and if he will make statement.","Biography information for Tracey Crouch","Tracey Crouch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172862","172862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17955","2013-10-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent assessment his Department has made of the effect of local economic partnerships in Yorkshire.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172863","172863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17956","2013-10-28","HM Treasury","2013-10-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the Welsh Government has received a share of an estimated 832 million to be spent on the High Speed 2 project by the Department for Transport in 2015-16.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172865","172865"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17957","2013-10-28","Ministry of Defence","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 12 September 2013, Official Report, column 798W, on unmanned aerial vehicles, what the (a) location, (b) cost and (c) rank of personnel is of each UK Reaper Force Squadron.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172962","172962"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17958","2013-10-29","Department of Health","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of staffing levels at places of safety in England as defined by the Mental Health Act 1983.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172909","172909"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17959","2013-10-28","Cabinet Office","2013-10-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will estimate the median wage in real terms of those people in (a) work or self-employment, (b) employed for 35 hours or more per week, (c) part-time employment and (d) self-employment in each (i) local authority area and (ii) parliamentary constituency in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172880","172880"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17960","2013-10-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many such people in Wrexham constituency receive jobseeker's allowance (JSA); how many people in Wrexham constituency have been sanctioned and had their JSA stopped in the last year for which figures are available; and how many job vacancies there were in Wrexham constituency in that year.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172881","172881"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17961","2013-10-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many businesses in (a) Wrexham constituency, (b) Wales and (c) the UK were owned solely by women in the last five years.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172883","172883"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17962","2013-10-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many people in (a) Wrexham constituency, (b) Wales and (c) the UK started an apprenticeship in (i) 2012 and (ii) 2013 to date.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172884","172884"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17963","2013-10-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what arrangements are in place for parents with joint custody of children eligible to pay the under occupancy penalty.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172967","172967"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17964","2013-10-28","Home Office","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to ensure that the (a) police and (b) emergency services have sufficient training and resources to meet the needs of people with mental illness appropriately and respectfully.","Biography information for Tracey Crouch","Tracey Crouch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172890","172890"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17965","2013-10-28","Department of Health","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many inpatient beds are available for mental health patients in each mental health trust in each of the last five years; and what the average occupation level was for such beds in each trust in each such year.","Biography information for Tracey Crouch","Tracey Crouch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172892","172892"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17966","2013-10-28","Department for Education","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many incidents of bullying between pupils were recorded in schools in each local authority area in the last five years.","Biography information for Tracey Crouch","Tracey Crouch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172893","172893"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17967","2013-10-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to his answers of 10 October 2013, Official Report, columns 364-6W and 18 October 2013, Official Report, column 876W, if he will estimate the average annual cost in 2014-15 of a (a) full-time two year degree taught at a further education college, (b) full-time two year degree taught at an English higher education institution (HEI), (c) full-time three year degree taught at an English HEI and (d) four year degree taught at an English HEI.","Biography information for Mr John Denham","Mr John Denham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172969","172969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18080","2013-10-30","Deputy Prime Minister","2013-10-24","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what recent discussions he has had with members of the Royal Family on their role in the legislative process.","Biography information for Andrew George","Andrew George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 900785","900785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18092","2013-10-29","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if she will bring forward legislative proposals to amend section 39 of the Children and Young Persons Act 1933 so that it explicitly applies to social media.","Biography information for Sarah Teather","Sarah Teather","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172911","172911"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/18341","2013-10-30","Cabinet Office","2013-10-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when the Major Projects Authority Report into High Speed 2 will be published in full.","Biography information for Andrea Leadsom","Andrea Leadsom","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 900788","900788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17497","2013-10-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what representations or scientific advice he has received about the possible contribution of illegal killing of badgers to the 66 per cent drop in badger numbers in the Gloucestershire and Somerset cull zones.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172512","172512"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17498","2013-10-28","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many complaints about breach of the Code of Practice for Victims of Crime were referred to the Parliamentary Ombudsman in each year from 2008-09 to 2012-13.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172513","172513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17499","2013-10-25","Department for Transport","2013-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent communications his Department has had with the European Commission regarding the TEN-T core and comprehensive projects; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172488","172488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17500","2013-10-25","Department for Transport","2013-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect of the omission of Wales from the routing of the TEN-T corridor route through the UK to Ireland; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172489","172489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17501","2013-10-25","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what recent representations he has received from local authorities on pavement parking.","Biography information for Sir Kevin Barron","Mr Kevin Barron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172490","172490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17502","2013-10-25","Department for Transport","2013-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the risk to pedestrians posed by pavement parking.","Biography information for Sir Kevin Barron","Mr Kevin Barron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172491","172491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17503","2013-10-25","Department for Transport","2013-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what communications his Department has had with the European Commission regarding the routing of the TEN-T corridor through the UK to Ireland; when such communications were received; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172492","172492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17504","2013-10-28","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many complaints were made to each service provider covered by the Code of Practice for Victims of Crime for breach of that code in each year from 2008-09 to 2012-13.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172514","172514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17505","2013-10-25","Department for Transport","2013-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what communication his Department had with the Welsh Government on his negotiating position prior to formal discussions with the European Commission on the TEN-T infrastructure projects at the Transport Council in Brussels on 22 March 2012; and if he will publish (a) such communications and (b) the Government's negotiating position on this matter.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172493","172493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17506","2013-10-28","Department of Health","2013-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people treated for injuries related to (a) female genital mutilation and (b) domestic violence in 2012-13 were in the UK (i) illegally and (ii) as short-term visitors at the time of their treatment; and what provision he plans to make for such cases under the proposed new charging scheme for NHS treatment.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172516","172516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17507","2013-10-25","Department for Transport","2013-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that new (a) Class 68 diesels and (b) Class 88 bi-mode locomotives are able to couple and operate with the planned electric rolling stock for use on the North West Trans Pennine routes.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172494","172494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17508","2013-10-25","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many households have used the provisions of the Mortgage Repossessions (Protections of Tenants) Act 2010 since its implementation.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172495","172495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17509","2013-10-28","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average time taken is for each type of Class A criminal offence to reach court.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172518","172518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17510","2013-10-28","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of the support services available to witnesses of violent crime.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172519","172519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17511","2013-10-25","Department of Health","2013-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidance he gives to clinical commissioning groups on consistency in the long-term use of warfarin.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame M. Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172497","172497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17512","2013-10-28","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which Minister in his Department is responsible for the Code of Practice for Victims of Crime.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172520","172520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17513","2013-10-28","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the estimated number of people affected by fuel poverty was in each month since June 2010 in (a) the UK, (b) Scotland, (c) England, (d) Wales and (e) Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Tom Greatrex","Tom Greatrex","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172521","172521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17514","2013-10-25","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many people in (a) Doncaster, (b) South Yorkshire and (c) the UK have received a discount under a Green Deal plan on the most recent date for which figures are available.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172508","172508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17515","2013-10-25","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many people have agreed a Green Deal plan in (a) Doncaster, (b) South Yorkshire and (c) UK in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172509","172509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17516","2013-10-25","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of people in (a) Doncaster, (b) South Yorkshire and (c) England breached their probation order in (i) 2012-13 and (ii) 2009-10.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172510","172510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17517","2013-10-25","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many probation staff there were in (a) Doncaster and (b) South Yorkshire in (i) the last period date for which figures are available and (ii) May 2010.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172511","172511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17518","2013-10-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the evidential basis is for the identification of certain A-level subjects as facilitating subjects that increase a university applicant's chances of success.","Biography information for Graham Stuart","Mr Graham Stuart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172522","172522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17519","2013-10-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what is being done to protect and conserve bottlenose dolphins inhabiting the UK coastline.","Biography information for Neil Parish","Neil Parish","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172535","172535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17520","2013-10-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what performance targets he has established for speed of processing and payment of (a) income support, (b) housing benefit, (c) employment and support allowance and (d) jobseeker's allowance.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172523","172523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17521","2013-10-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what rate of repayment was achieved for crisis loans and budgeting loans in the four years prior to changes to the Discretionary Social Fund in 2013.","Biography information for Dame Anne Begg","Dame Anne Begg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172542","172542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17522","2013-10-28","Department for International Development","2013-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much funding her Department gave to the International Labour Organisation in each of the last 10 financial years.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172524","172524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17523","2013-10-28","Department for International Development","2013-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much aid was given to Zimbabwe in the latest year for which figures are available; and what conditions were attached to such aid.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172547","172547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17524","2013-10-28","Department for International Development","2013-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what meetings she has had with ministerial colleagues in the (a) Foreign and Commonwealth Office and (b) Department for Business, Innovation and Skills on trade with (i) India, (ii) countries in Africa and (iii) Bangladesh in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172525","172525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17525","2013-10-28","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what funding she plans to provide to improve sporting facilities in Chelmsford.","Biography information for Sir Simon Burns","Mr Simon Burns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172526","172526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17526","2013-10-28","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of the effect of the legacy of the London 2012 Olympic and Paralympic Games on sport in Chelmsford.","Biography information for Sir Simon Burns","Mr Simon Burns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172527","172527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17527","2013-10-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to ensure that employers comply with minimum wage legislation.","Biography information for Mr Bob Ainsworth","Mr Bob Ainsworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172532","172532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17528","2013-10-28","Home Office","2013-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she expects to publish an evaluation framework for the National Drugs Strategy.","Biography information for Mr Bob Ainsworth","Mr Bob Ainsworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172528","172528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17529","2013-10-28","Home Office","2013-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions (a) she, (b) Ministers in her Department and (c) officials in her Department have had with the National Audit Office on the completion and publication of the Drugs Strategy Evaluation Framework.","Biography information for Mr Bob Ainsworth","Mr Bob Ainsworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172529","172529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17530","2013-10-28","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many households in (a) Coventry, (b) Coventry North East constituency, (c) the West Midlands and (d) England were in fuel poverty in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mr Bob Ainsworth","Mr Bob Ainsworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172533","172533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17531","2013-10-25","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 14 October 2013, Official Report, column 502W, on community orders, what is considered as other in relation to the percentage of terminations of community and suspended sentence orders.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172549","172549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17532","2013-10-28","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people in prison must undertake a (a) domestic violence offender behaviour programme, (b) general offending behaviour programme, (c) sex offender behaviour programme, (d) substance misuse behaviour programme and (e) violence offender programme before they are eligible for release.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172531","172531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17533","2013-10-25","Home Office","2013-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to her Department's publication Tackling Child Sexual Exploitation Action Plan, published in November 2011, what plans she has to take further action in order to ensure the UK is compliant with the Council of Europe's Convention on the Protection of Children from Sexual Exploitation and Sexual Abuse.","Biography information for Patrick Mercer","Patrick Mercer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172550","172550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17534","2013-10-25","Home Office","2013-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she has any plans to extend eligibility for free UK passports to people over the age of 80 years.","Biography information for David Morris","David Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172551","172551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17535","2013-10-28","Home Office","2013-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of whether evidential flexibility has improved decision making and processing times with Tier 4 applications under the points-based system.","Biography information for Mr David Ward","Mr David Ward","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172553","172553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17536","2013-10-31","Department of Health","2013-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the contribution of 25 June 2013, Official Report, column 282, what progress he has made on a review of cross-border healthcare arrangements for people living in England but registered with GP practices in Wales.","Biography information for Jesse Norman","Jesse Norman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172534","172534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17537","2013-10-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the economic and environmental viability of offshore commercial fishing within the Pitcairn Islands' exclusive economic zone.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172554","172554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17538","2013-10-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will take steps to strengthen the level of marine protection around South Georgia and South Sandwich Islands in line with the International Union for the Conservation of Nature protected area management categories.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172555","172555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17539","2013-10-25","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many new deputy district judges appointments in 2010 were (a) male, (b) female, (c) black, Asian and minority ethnic, (d) educated at the University of Oxford or University of Cambridge, (e) educated at other Russell Group universities, (f) educated at all other universities, (g) solicitors, (h) barristers and (i) Queen's Counsel.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172556","172556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17540","2013-10-25","Department of Health","2013-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) elective and (b) emergency admissions took place in each (i) primary care trust and (ii) clinical commissioning group area for patients with (A) primary and (B) secondary diagnosis of a neurological condition, as defined under Diseases of the nervous system in the International Statistical Classification of Diseases and Related Health Problems 10th Revision, in each of the last five years for which data is available.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172580","172580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17541","2013-10-25","Department of Health","2013-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many emergency re-admissions within 28 days took place for patients in each (a) primary care trust and (b) clinical commissioning group area with a (i) primary and (ii) secondary diagnosis of a neurological condition, as defined under Diseases of the nervous system in the International Statistical Classification of Diseases and Related Health Problems 10th Revision, in each of the last five years for which data is available.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172581","172581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17542","2013-10-25","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many new district judges (County Courts) appointments in 2010 were (a) male, (b) female, (c) black, Asian and minority ethnic, (d) educated at the University of Oxford or University of Cambridge, (e) educated at other Russell Group universities, (f) educated at all other universities, (g) solicitors, (h) barristers and (i) Queen's Counsel.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172557","172557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17543","2013-10-25","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many new recorders appointments in 2010 were (a) male, (b) female, (c) black, Asian and minority ethnic, (d) educated at the University of Oxford or University of Cambridge, (e) educated at other Russell Group universities, (f) educated at all other universities, (g) solicitors, (h) barristers and (i) Queen's Counsel.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172558","172558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17544","2013-10-25","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many new circuit judges appointments in 2010 were (a) male, (b) female, (c) black, Asian and minority ethnic, (d) educated at the University of Oxford or University of Cambridge, (e) educated at other Russell Group universities, (f) educated at all other universities, (g) solicitors, (h) barristers and (i) Queen's Counsel.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172559","172559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17545","2013-10-25","Department of Health","2013-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many full-time equivalent specialist nurses for a neurological condition, as defined under Diseases of the nervous system in the International Statistical Classification of Diseases and Related Health Problems 10th Revision, were active in each (a) primary care trust and (b) clinical commissioning group in each of the last five years for which data is available.","Biography information for Laura Sandys","Laura Sandys","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172582","172582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17546","2013-10-25","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many new deputy masters, deputy registrars, deputy cost judges and deputy district judges appointments in 2010 were (a) male, (b) female, (c) black, Asian and minority ethnic, (d) educated at the University of Oxford or University of Cambridge, (e) educated at other Russell Group universities, (f) educated at all other universities, (g) solicitors, (h) barristers and (i) Queen's Counsel.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172560","172560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17547","2013-10-25","Department of Health","2013-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the prevalence of neurological conditions, as defined under diseases of the nervous system in the International Statistical Classification of Diseases and Related Health Problems 10th Revision.","Biography information for Laura Sandys","Laura Sandys","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172583","172583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17548","2013-10-25","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many new masters, registrars, costs judges and district judges appointments in 2010 were (a) male, (b) female, (c) black, Asian and minority ethnic, (d) educated at the University of Oxford or University of Cambridge, (e) educated at other Russell Group universities, (f) educated at all other universities, (g) solicitors, (h) barristers and (i) Queen's Counsel.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172561","172561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17549","2013-10-25","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many new deputy judge advocates appointments in 2010 were (a) male, (b) female, (c) black, Asian and minority ethnic, (d) educated at the University of Oxford or University of Cambridge, (e) educated at other Russell Group universities, (f) educated at all other universities, (g) solicitors, (h) barristers and (i) Queen's Counsel.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172562","172562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17550","2013-10-25","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many new judge advocates appointments in 2010 were (a) male, (b) female, (c) black, Asian and minority ethnic, (d) educated at the University of Oxford or University of Cambridge, (e) educated at other Russell Group universities, (f) educated at all other universities, (g) solicitors, (h) barristers and (i) Queen's Counsel.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172563","172563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17551","2013-10-25","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many new High Court judges appointments in 2010 were (a) male, (b) female, (c) black, Asian and minority ethnic, (d) educated at the University of Oxford or University of Cambridge, (e) educated at other Russell Group universities, (f) educated at all other universities, (g) solicitors, (h) barristers and (i) Queen's Counsel.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172564","172564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17552","2013-10-25","Department of Health","2013-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of (a) the economic and (b) societal cost of neurological conditions, as defined in the International Statistical Classification of Diseases and Related Health Problems 10th Revision.","Biography information for Laura Sandys","Laura Sandys","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172584","172584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17553","2013-10-25","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many new Lord Justices of Appeal appointments in 2010 were (a) male, (b) female, (c) black, Asian and minority ethnic, (d) educated at the University of Oxford or University of Cambridge, (e) educated at other Russell Group universities, (f) educated at all other universities, (g) solicitors, (h) barristers and (i) Queen's Counsel.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172565","172565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17554","2013-10-25","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many new deputy district judges (County Courts) appointments in 2011 were (a) male, (b) female, (c) black, Asian and minority ethnic, (d) educated at the University of Oxford or University of Cambridge, (e) educated at other Russell Group universities, (f) educated at all other universities, (g) solicitors, (h) barristers and (i) Queen's Counsel.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172566","172566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17555","2013-10-25","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many new district judges (County Courts) appointments in 2011 were (a) male, (b) female, (c) black, Asian and minority ethnic, (d) educated at the University of Oxford or University of Cambridge, (e) educated at other Russell Group universities, (f) educated at all other universities, (g) solicitors, (h) barristers and (i) Queen's Counsel.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172567","172567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17556","2013-10-25","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many new recorders appointments in 2011 were (a) male, (b) female, (c) black, Asian and minority ethnic, (d) educated at the University of Oxford or University of Cambridge, (e) educated at other Russell Group universities, (f) educated at all other universities, (g) solicitors, (h) barristers and (i) Queen's Counsel.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172568","172568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17557","2013-10-25","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many new circuit judges appointments in 2011 were (a) male, (b) female, (c) black, Asian and minority ethnic, (d) educated at the University of Oxford or University of Cambridge, (e) educated at other Russell Group universities, (f) educated at all other universities, (g) solicitors, (h) barristers and (i) Queen's Counsel.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172569","172569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17558","2013-10-25","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many new deputy masters, deputy registrars, deputy cost judges and deputy district judges appointments in 2011 were (a) male, (b) female, (c) black, Asian and minority ethnic, (d) educated at the University of Oxford or University of Cambridge, (e) educated at other Russell Group universities, (f) educated at all other universities, (g) solicitors, (h) barristers and (i) Queen's Counsel.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172570","172570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17559","2013-10-25","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many new masters, registrars, costs judges and district judges appointments in 2011 were (a) male, (b) female, (c) black, Asian and minority ethnic, (d) educated at the University of Oxford or University of Cambridge, (e) educated at other Russell Group universities, (f) educated at all other universities, (g) solicitors, (h) barristers and (i) Queen's Counsel.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172571","172571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17560","2013-10-25","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many new deputy judge advocates appointments in 2011 were (a) male, (b) female, (c) black, Asian and minority ethnic, (d) educated at the University of Oxford or University of Cambridge, (e) educated at other Russell Group universities, (f) educated at all other universities, (g) solicitors, (h) barristers and (i) Queen's Counsel.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172572","172572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17561","2013-10-25","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many new judge advocates appointments in 2011 were (a) male, (b) female, (c) black, Asian and minority ethnic, (d) educated at the University of Oxford or University of Cambridge, (e) educated at other Russell Group universities, (f) educated at all other universities, (g) solicitors, (h) barristers and (i) Queen's Counsel.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172573","172573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17562","2013-10-25","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many new High Court judges appointments in 2011 were (a) male, (b) female, (c) black, Asian and minority ethnic, (d) educated at the University of Oxford or University of Cambridge, (e) educated at other Russell Group universities, (f) educated at all other universities, (g) solicitors, (h) barristers and (i) Queen's Counsel.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172574","172574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17563","2013-10-25","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many new Lord Justices of Appeal appointments in 2011 were (a) male, (b) female, (c) black, Asian and minority ethnic, (d) educated at the University of Oxford or University of Cambridge, (e) educated at other Russell Group universities, (f) educated at all other universities, (g) solicitors, (h) barristers and (i) Queen's Counsel.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172575","172575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17564","2013-10-25","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many new deputy district judges appointments in 2012 were (a) male, (b) female, (c) black, Asian and minority ethnic, (d) educated at the University of Oxford or University of Cambridge, (e) educated at other Russell Group universities, (f) educated at all other universities, (g) solicitors, (h) barristers and (i) Queen's Counsel.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172576","172576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17565","2013-10-25","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many new district judges appointments in 2012 were (a) male, (b) female, (c) black, Asian and minority ethnic, (d) educated at the University of Oxford or University of Cambridge, (e) educated at other Russell Group universities, (f) educated at all other universities, (g) solicitors, (h) barristers and (i) Queen's Counsel.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172577","172577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17566","2013-10-25","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many new recorders appointments in 2012 were (a) male, (b) female, (c) black, Asian and minority ethnic, (d) educated at the University of Oxford or University of Cambridge, (e) educated at other Russell Group universities, (f) educated at all other universities, (g) solicitors, (h) barristers and (i) Queen's Counsel.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172578","172578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17567","2013-10-25","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many new circuit judges appointments in 2012 were (a) male, (b) female, (c) black, Asian and minority ethnic, (d) educated at the University of Oxford or University of Cambridge, (e) educated at other Russell Group universities, (f) educated at all other universities, (g) solicitors, (h) barristers and (i) Queen's Counsel.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172579","172579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17568","2013-10-29","Department of Health","2013-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will bring forward proposals to ban the use of colouring additives, such as sunset yellow, caroisine and quinoline yellow, in children's medicine; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172631","172631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17569","2013-10-25","Home Office","2013-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will bring forward proposals to repeal section 24 of the Animals (Scientific Procedures) Act 1986 in order to open animal experiments to the same level of accountability as that which government and other public bodies are already subject.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172585","172585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17570","2013-10-28","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what recent estimate he has made of the number of homes in Barrow and Furness constituency that do not have access to a mains gas supply.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172622","172622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17571","2013-10-28","Home Office","2013-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of burglaries in (a) Barrow and Furness constituency and (b) Cumbria were cleared up by police in each of the last three years.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172623","172623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17572","2013-10-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what trials are being conducted by his Department to encourage and help separated parents liable for child maintenance payments to keep making these payments; and what evaluation of the outcomes of such trials has been undertaken.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172587","172587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17573","2013-10-25","Department of Health","2013-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when his Department's dementia toolkit will be published.","Biography information for Patrick Mercer","Patrick Mercer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172589","172589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17574","2013-10-28","Department for Transport","2013-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will direct HS2 Ltd to commission a study on the potential economic effects on Warrington of (a) that town not having a station on the High Speed 2 line and (b) a reduction in the number of direct trains to London and Scotland from Warrington Bank Quay.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172624","172624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17575","2013-10-25","Department for International Development","2013-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent steps she has taken to increase the role of the Commonwealth Development Corporation in supporting entrepreneurship in developing countries.","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172590","172590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17576","2013-10-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many recorded incidents of TB in bison there have been in the UK in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Ben Gummer","Ben Gummer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172591","172591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17577","2013-10-25","Home Office","2013-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether UK contact points are obliged to attend plenary meetings of the European Judicial Network held pursuant to Article 5 of Council Decision 2008/976/JHA.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172597","172597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17578","2013-10-28","Department for Transport","2013-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will direct HS2 Ltd to commission research on the effects on small businesses in the Culcheth and Rixton area of Warrington of road closures and other disruption resulting from the building of the High Speed 2 line on the initial preferred route.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172625","172625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17579","2013-10-25","Ministry of Justice","2013-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will take steps to assess the effect of the Government's proposed changes to legal aid on access to court proceedings for low income parents in child access and custody proceedings; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lord Stunell","Sir Andrew Stunell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172592","172592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17580","2013-10-25","Ministry of Defence","2013-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 16 October 2013, Official Report, column 740W, on army: Germany, what additional expenditure his Department incurred in providing basing for these additional units at (a) Dalton Barracks, Abingdon, (b) Kendrew Barracks, Cottesmore and (c) Imjin Barracks, Gloucester, by category of expenditure.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172593","172593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17581","2013-10-25","Department of Health","2013-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department has taken to ensure that all emergency departments successfully implement a sepsis pathway.","Biography information for Andrew Miller","Andrew Miller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172594","172594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17582","2013-10-25","Home Office","2013-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what her assessment is of which aspects of the UK's bilateral extradition relationship with the US will be affected, and in what way, if the UK ceases to be bound by the EU-USA Extradition Agreement pursuant to article 10 of the Protocol on Transitional Provisions annexed to the EU Treaties.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172598","172598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17583","2013-10-25","Department of Health","2013-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will urge emergency departments to treat a patient with sepsis as an urgent priority, ensuring relevant treatment within one hour of arrival.","Biography information for Andrew Miller","Andrew Miller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172595","172595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17584","2013-10-25","Department of Health","2013-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to ensure that all emergency departments provide blood gas machines that can measure lactate for the early recognition of sepsis.","Biography information for Andrew Miller","Andrew Miller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172596","172596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17585","2013-10-28","Home Office","2013-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether UK authorities will continue to provide, in relation to other EU member states, the functions of contact points as provided for by Article 4 of Council Decision 2008/976/JHA if the UK ceases to be bound by that Council Decision pursuant to Article 10 of the Protocol on Transitional Provisions annexed to the EU treaties.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172612","172612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17586","2013-10-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 14 October 2013, Official Report, columns 489-90W, on food banks, what criteria Jobcentre Plus branches use in deciding when it is appropriate to signpost a person to a food bank.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172608","172608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/17587","2013-10-28","Home Office","2013-10-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the cost to the public purse has been of UK participation in Council Decision 2008/976/JHA in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 172613","172613"
