"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347122","2015-06-01","Ministry of Defence","2015-05-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will place in the Library copies of all correspondence between 2010 and 2015 between his Department and Public Health England in relation to use of Lariam or Mefloquine and reports of (a) hallucinations, (b) psychosis and (c) suicidal thoughts in personnel prescribed those medications; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 126","126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347123","2015-06-02","Department for Transport","2015-05-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the Answer of 26 February 2015 to Question 225524, what progress KPMG has made in its review of the bus market.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 282","282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347124","2015-06-02","Department for Transport","2015-05-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the Government's policy is on plans by the North East Combined Authority to implement a quality contract scheme for bus services in the Tyne and Wear area.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 283","283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347125","2015-06-01","Ministry of Defence","2015-05-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the safety of nuclear submarines on the Clyde; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 129","129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347126","2015-06-01","Ministry of Defence","2015-05-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will review the safety of nuclear submarines based on the Clyde.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 130","130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347127","2015-06-01","Ministry of Defence","2015-05-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to assure the public of the safety of the UK's nuclear submarines.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 131","131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347128","2015-06-01","Cabinet Office","2015-05-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether a reduction in the number of Parliamentary constituencies to 600 would be accompanied by increases to the budgets available to hon. Members for office running costs.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 273","273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347129","2015-06-01","Department for Education","2015-05-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many (a) primary free schools, (b) secondary free schools and (c) university technical colleges have been approved in each local authority area in England and Wales since May 2010.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 277","277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347130","2015-06-01","Home Office","2015-05-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many new psychoactive substances have been identified by the Forensic Early Warning System in each month since its was introduced; and how many of these substances have subsequently been (a) classified under the Misuse of Drugs Act 1971 and (b) subject to a temporary banning order.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 278","278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347131","2015-06-01","Department for Education","2015-05-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the trends in the number of students who take vocational GCSEs who go on to study at university.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 280","280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347132","2015-06-01","Department for Education","2015-05-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many vocational GCSEs were taken in each year since 2007.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 281","281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347133","2015-06-01","Cabinet Office","2015-05-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many UK citizens of voting age are currently living overseas; and how many citizens of EU countries of voting age excluding the UK, Ireland, Cyprus and Malta live in (a) the UK and (b) Islington South and Finsbury constituency.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 288","288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347134","2015-06-01","Department for Education","2015-05-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what forecast her Department has made of the number of unfilled teacher training routes in (a) mathematics, (b) physics and (c) all combined teacher training routes beginning in September 2015.","Biography information for Tristram Hunt","Tristram Hunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 76","76"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347135","2015-06-01","Department for Education","2015-05-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her Department's (a) mathematics teacher recruitment target and (b) recruitment levels of qualified maths teachers were in each year between 2011 and 2015.","Biography information for Tristram Hunt","Tristram Hunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 77","77"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347136","2015-06-01","Department for Education","2015-05-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her Department's (a) physics teacher recruitment target and (b) recruitment levels of qualified physics teachers were in each year between 2011 and 2015.","Biography information for Tristram Hunt","Tristram Hunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 78","78"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347137","2015-06-01","Department for Education","2015-05-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her Department's target is for the number of new trainee teachers to begin in schools in each year between 2015 and 2019.","Biography information for Tristram Hunt","Tristram Hunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 79","79"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347138","2015-06-01","Department for Education","2015-05-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many BTEC qualifications at each level were taken in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 295","295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347139","2015-06-01","Cabinet Office","2015-05-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when he expects the Boundary Commissions to begin their work on the next general review of Parliamentary constituencies; whether he expects this review to be conducted in accordance with Part 2 of the Parliamentary Voting System and Constituencies Act 2011; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 291","291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347140","2015-06-02","Ministry of Justice","2015-05-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the Answer of 24 February 2015 to Question 225118, what progress the court reform programme has made in the rebuilding of Sunderland Court.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 299","299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347141","2015-06-01","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-05-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if his Department will launch an investigation into the closure of the car dealer Carcraft.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 82","82"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347142","2015-06-01","Cabinet Office","2015-05-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to to the Written Statement of 9 January 2015, HCWS18, on maximising voter registration, what proportion of each of the funding streams has been spent in (a) England, Wales and Scotland combined, (b) England, (c) London, (d) the London Borough of Islington and (e) Islington South and Finsbury constituency to date.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 105","105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347143","2015-06-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-05-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the security situation in Iraq.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 114","114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347144","2015-06-01","Ministry of Defence","2015-05-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what support the UK is providing to the Iraqi government to counter Islamic State.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 86","86"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347145","2015-06-01","Cabinet Office","2015-05-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to to the Written Statement of 9 January 2015, HCWS18, on maximising voter registration, if the Government will provide further funding to electoral registration officers to maximise voter registration once the transition to individual electoral registration is complete.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 106","106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347146","2015-06-01","Ministry of Defence","2015-05-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent assessment he has made of the security situation in Syria.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 115","115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347147","2015-06-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-05-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the security situation in Afghanistan.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 116","116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347148","2015-06-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-05-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the security situation in Libya.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 117","117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347149","2015-06-01","Cabinet Office","2015-05-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will publish the minutes and a summary of the most recent meeting of the National Security Council.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 87","87"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347150","2015-06-01","Cabinet Office","2015-05-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the Answer of 6 May 2014 to Question HL6721, what steps the Government plans to take to maximise voter registration before 1 December 2015.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 107","107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347151","2015-06-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-05-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the security situation in Nigeria.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 118","118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347152","2015-06-01","Department of Health","2015-05-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect of the closure of accident and emergency services at King George Hospital on older people.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 119","119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347153","2015-06-01","Department of Health","2015-05-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the reasons are for the closure of accident and emergency services at King George Hospital.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 120","120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347154","2015-06-01","Department of Health","2015-05-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if (a) he and (b) Ministers in his Department will meet people affected by the closure of accident and emergency services at King George Hospital.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 121","121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347155","2015-06-01","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-05-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many new housing starts there have been in Hull local authority area in the last 10 years; and how many such housing starts have been of social housing.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 268","268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347156","2015-06-01","Department of Health","2015-05-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when the decision was taken to close accident and emergency services at King George Hospital.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 122","122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347157","2015-06-01","Cabinet Office","2015-05-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the Written Statement of 5 July 2013, Official Report, column 71WS, what proportion of (a) the Targeted Canvassing Fund, (b) the ERO Registration Fund, (c) the Innovation Fund and (d) Schools Outreach has been spent in (i) England, Wales and Scotland combined, (ii) England, (iii) London, (iv) the London Borough of Islington and (v) Islington South and Finsbury constituency to date.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 108","108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347158","2015-06-01","Home Office","2015-05-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department has taken to increase awareness of new psychoactive substances and their dangers in the last five years; and what the cost of such work has been.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 269","269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347159","2015-06-01","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2015-05-27","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, pursuant to the Written Statement of 18 December 2013, Official Report, column 106WS, when he expects the Electoral Commission to make its recommendation as to whether the transition to individual Electoral Registration should conclude in 2015 to 2016.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 109","109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347160","2015-06-01","Home Office","2015-05-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what facilities and resources her Department has to assess the chemical content of suspected new psychoactive substances that are identified in the UK.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 270","270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347161","2015-06-01","Cabinet Office","2015-05-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when the Government plans to respond to the 8th Report of the Political and Constitutional Reform Committee of Session 2014-15, What next on the redrawing of parliamentary constituency boundaries?, HC 600.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 111","111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347162","2015-06-01","Ministry of Defence","2015-05-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many advertisements have been placed and in which publications to advise armed forces personnel of their right to make a complaint following their illegal punishment following the receipt of a police caution in the last year; what the cost of placing such advertisements has been; how many such complaints have been received to date; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 157","157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347286","2015-06-02","Department of Health","2015-05-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential for virtual wards to improve health care delivery.","Biography information for Jesse Norman","Jesse Norman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 900002","900002"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347685","2015-06-02","Department of Health","2015-05-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to improve A&E provision in North Northamptonshire.","Biography information for Mr Peter Bone","Mr Peter Bone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 900013","900013"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347795","2015-06-02","Department of Health","2015-05-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of people are waiting a week or more to see or speak to a GP; and what assessment he has made of the effects of access to GPs on attendances at A&E departments.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 900024","900024"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347796","2015-06-02","Department of Health","2015-05-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the £22 billion efficiency savings identified in NHS England's Five Year Forward View will entail reductions in staff numbers.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 900021","900021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347797","2015-06-02","Department of Health","2015-05-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress has been made in achieving safety in hospitals in special measures.","Biography information for Stephen Metcalfe","Stephen Metcalfe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 900019","900019"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347798","2015-06-02","Department of Health","2015-05-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he plans to take to improve cancer survival rates over the next five years.","Biography information for Mr John Baron","Mr John Baron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 900023","900023"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347799","2015-06-02","Department of Health","2015-05-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps the Government has taken to support third-sector organisations in delivering health services in (a) Eddisbury and (b) England.","Biography information for Antoinette Sandbach","Antoinette Sandbach","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 900017","900017"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347800","2015-06-02","Department of Health","2015-05-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of how seven-day services will improve patient care.","Biography information for Maria Caulfield","Maria Caulfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 900022","900022"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/347801","2015-06-02","Department of Health","2015-05-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress has been made in achieving parity of esteem for mental health services.","Biography information for Simon Danczuk","Simon Danczuk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 900018","900018"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/604075","2015-06-01","Department of Health","2015-05-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what account he has taken of the research performed by Dubuc and Coleman in formulating a strategy for the assessment of the incidence of sex-selective abortion in England and Wales.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 17","17"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229326","2015-03-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department is taking to raise awareness among small and medium-sized businesses of insurance against cyber-attacks.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228929","228929"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229327","2015-03-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to Penalty Fair, the Intellectual Property Office study of criminal sanctions for copyright infringement available under the Copyright, Designs and Patents Act 1988, what plans his Department has to strengthen the penalties for online copyright infringement.","Biography information for Mr John Whittingdale","Mr John Whittingdale","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228923","228923"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229328","2015-03-26","Cabinet Office","2015-03-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people were employed on zero-hours contracts in (a) the UK, (b) Scotland, (c) England, (d) Wales and (e) Northern Ireland in each year since May 2010.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228945","228945"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229329","2015-03-26","Cabinet Office","2015-03-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment he has made of the success of the One Public Estate Programme in increasing co-ordination across the public sector on the use of public land and buildings; and what plans he has to expand that programme in the next Parliament.","Biography information for Robert Neill","Robert Neill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228890","228890"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229330","2015-03-26","HM Treasury","2015-03-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much unpaid inheritance tax was outstanding from estates notified for probate valued up to £1 million since 2005.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228885","228885"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229331","2015-03-26","HM Treasury","2015-03-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to ensure that other Departments comply with guidance published by his Department in the Green Book (a) on the production and use made of business cases and related matters, (b) that such business cases are normally published in full at the time of the announcement of a public sector spending proposal to which they relate and (c) that where there is a statutory justification for an exemption to disclosure of any part of a business case, such justification will be published contemporaneously with such an announcement.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228883","228883"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229332","2015-03-26","HM Treasury","2015-03-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make an assessment of the progress made by the short-term credit industry on full market participation in real-time data-sharing.","Biography information for Meg Hillier","Meg Hillier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228940","228940"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229333","2015-03-26","HM Treasury","2015-03-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will take steps to ensure that full market participation in real-time data-sharing in the short-term credit market includes participants who are non-payday lenders.","Biography information for Meg Hillier","Meg Hillier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228941","228941"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229334","2015-03-26","HM Treasury","2015-03-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what information his Department holds on the affordability criteria used by the Financial Conduct Authority to set rules to protect consumers taking out loans in the short-term credit market.","Biography information for Meg Hillier","Meg Hillier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228942","228942"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229335","2015-03-26","HM Treasury","2015-03-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will bring forward proposals to secure full market participation in real-time data-sharing in the short-term credit market.","Biography information for Meg Hillier","Meg Hillier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228943","228943"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229336","2015-03-26","HM Treasury","2015-03-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the average length of time was for a decision to be made on a working tax credit claim in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228908","228908"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229337","2015-03-26","HM Treasury","2015-03-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of his Department's performance against targets on the length of time for a decision to be made on a working tax credit claim.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228909","228909"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229338","2015-03-26","HM Treasury","2015-03-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the number of pensioners liable to pay income tax in the 2013-14 financial year who (a) did not have online access to and (b) were not sent tax forms by HM Revenue and Customs (HMRC); and what steps HMRC is taking to ensure those pensioners have access to such forms.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228896","228896"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229339","2015-03-26","HM Treasury","2015-03-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the HM Revenue and Customs publication Benefits and Credits, Tax Credits Error and Fraud Additional Capacity Trial, Final Evaluation, published in May 2014, for what reason section 1.7 listed in the contents page, Delegation of Commissioners' Powers, was not included in the body of that report; and if he will place in the Library a copy of that section.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228903","228903"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229340","2015-03-26","HM Treasury","2015-03-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he plans to answer Question 227268, tabled on 11 March 2015 by the hon. Member for Leeds West.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228904","228904"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229341","2015-03-26","HM Treasury","2015-03-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the average length of time was that an applicant waited for a decision on a Help to Buy application in each quarter since the launch of that scheme.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228905","228905"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229342","2015-03-26","Cabinet Office","2015-03-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the change in the average gross income of an employee in the (a) private and (b) public sector between the 2010-11 and 2015-16 financial years.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228898","228898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229343","2015-03-26","HM Treasury","2015-03-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the average length of time was for a decision to be made by HM Revenue and Customs related to a business VAT return in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228906","228906"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229344","2015-03-26","HM Treasury","2015-03-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the performance of HM Revenue and Customs against its targets on the processing and completion of corporate VAT returns.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228907","228907"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229345","2015-03-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what discussions he has had with the National Trust on the preservation of public parks.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228925","228925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229346","2015-03-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the performance of his Department against targets for the processing of new planning applications.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228910","228910"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229347","2015-03-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the average length of time was for a decision to be made on a planning application in each quarter since 2013.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228939","228939"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229348","2015-03-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Written Statement of 20 March 2015, HCWS 438, on unpublished research reports commissioned by the last Administration, what the evidential basis is for the assertion that his Department commissions research better than did previous administrations.","Biography information for Lord Blunkett","Mr David Blunkett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228868","228868"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229349","2015-03-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what his policy is on ensuring that new large-scale provision of housing takes place within mixed-use development schemes.","Biography information for Robert Neill","Robert Neill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228888","228888"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229350","2015-03-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 16 March 2015 to Question 226590, what steps the Government has taken to ensure that all local European Structural and Investment Fund Subcommittees reflect the views of small businesses.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228881","228881"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229351","2015-03-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what comparative assessment he has made of the benefit to the public purse of using surplus public land to (a) generate long-term revenue and (b) generate capital from the sale of that land.","Biography information for Robert Neill","Robert Neill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228887","228887"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229352","2015-03-26","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what progress has been made on the rollout of the Mobile Infrastructure Project in Mid Ulster; and how much has been paid to Arqiva for the rollout of that project in that area to date.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228891","228891"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229353","2015-03-26","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what progress has been made on the rollout of the Mobile Infrastructure Project in Fermanagh and South Tyrone; and how much has been paid to Arqiva for the rollout of that project in that area to date.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228892","228892"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229354","2015-03-26","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will support the erection of memorials to miners who lost their lives whilst working in the pits during the First and Second World Wars.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228931","228931"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229355","2015-03-26","Ministry of Defence","2015-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 2 February 2015 to Question 222433, on Syria, whether UK Reapers in Syria are conducting (a) pattern of life analyses, (b) collateral damage estimates and (c) battle damage assessments.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228913","228913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229356","2015-03-26","Ministry of Defence","2015-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 10 March 2015 to Question 226256, on RAF Croughton, what the dates were of the (a) Host Nation Notification and (b) Host Nation Response made in connection with the European Infrastructure Consolidated Review.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228912","228912"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229357","2015-03-26","Ministry of Defence","2015-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what progress has been made on the awarding of the Légion d'honneur to veterans of the Second World War.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228914","228914"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229358","2015-03-26","Ministry of Defence","2015-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether (a) Watchkeeper and (b) other unmanned aerial vehicles belonging to his Department were operated outside designated airspace in connection with the London 2012 Olympic and Paralympic Games.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228911","228911"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229359","2015-03-26","Department for Education","2015-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, who was consulted prior to her Department's decision to choose 55 Guildhall Street, Preston as the site for Eden Boys School for its first year of operation.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228894","228894"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229360","2015-03-26","Department for Education","2015-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what specialist support is provided within schools for pupils with mental health problems.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228880","228880"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229361","2015-03-26","Department for Education","2015-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what (a) meetings and (b) representations (i) she, (ii) ministers in her Department and (iii) officials in her Department have had, made to or received from (A) Lancashire County Council and (B) Preston City Council ministers and officials on (1) the temporary siting of Eden Boys School at 55 Guildhall Street, Preston and (2) its subsequent location.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228872","228872"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229362","2015-03-26","Department for Education","2015-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 4 February 2015 to Question 222713, what appropriate external support is available to a local area to improve the quality of special educational needs and disability services and their delivery.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228859","228859"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229363","2015-03-26","Department for Education","2015-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether it is mandatory for local authorities to report to her Department the number of educational psychologists they employ.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228860","228860"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229364","2015-03-26","Department for Education","2015-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what mechanisms are in place to monitor young people to ensure that they stay in some form of education or training until their 18th birthday.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228861","228861"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229365","2015-03-26","Department for Education","2015-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department takes when notified of a young person under the age of 18 who is not in education or training.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228862","228862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229366","2015-03-26","Department for Education","2015-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what funding her Department has allocated to the pilot of 200 specialist primary PE teachers.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228863","228863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229367","2015-03-26","Department for Education","2015-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether any of the twelve providers leading on the recruitment of new specialist primary PE teachers will be based in the West Midlands.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228864","228864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229368","2015-03-26","Department for Education","2015-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 10 February 2015 to Question 223548, if she will make it her policy to collect information on the number of young carers in receipt of school meals.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228865","228865"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229369","2015-03-26","Department for Education","2015-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 10 February 2015 to Question 223375, who her Department has commissioned to conduct the research study into the lives of young carers in England.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228866","228866"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229370","2015-03-26","Department for Education","2015-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 10 February 2015 to Question 223375, where she plans for the study into the lives of young carers in England to take place.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228867","228867"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229371","2015-03-26","Department for Education","2015-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment her Department made of parking, traffic flow and road safety issues when granting Eden Boys School the right to use 55 Guildhall Street, Preston for one year.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228895","228895"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229372","2015-03-26","Department for Education","2015-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assistance is provided in schools for children with special educational needs; and what standards and targets her Department sets for the provision and delivery of such assistance.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228928","228928"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229373","2015-03-26","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment he has made of the estimates contained in the OECD report, Nuclear Energy and Renewables: System Effects in Low-carbon Electricity Systems, 2012 of the additional system costs of onshore and offshore wind and solar power if they reach 10 per cent and 30 per cent penetration of the UK electricity market.","Biography information for Lord Lilley","Mr Peter Lilley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228949","228949"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229374","2015-03-26","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if he will make an assessment of the total extra system costs of meeting the target of generating 30 per cent of electricity from renewables by 2020 compared with continuing to rely on conventional sources of electricity generation including fossil fuels.","Biography information for Lord Lilley","Mr Peter Lilley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228950","228950"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229375","2015-03-26","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what proposals were put forward to his Department by Copper Consulting of Bristol in respect of the proposed designation of the geological disposal facility for nuclear waste as a nationally significant infrastructure project.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228884","228884"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229376","2015-03-26","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether his Department has received a report from Ray Noble relating to the Mozes community energy cooperative.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228877","228877"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229377","2015-03-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer given by Baroness Kramer on 18 June 2014, Lords Hansard, column 899, what her policy is on transferring the Public Estate Forest Land at Cinderford North Quarter site in the National Heritage Forest of Dean for development.","Biography information for Martin Horwood","Martin Horwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228919","228919"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229378","2015-03-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will invite the Pensions Regulator to submit a Climate Change Adaptation Report looking at the effect of climate change on the UK pensions sector.","Biography information for Martin Horwood","Martin Horwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228920","228920"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229379","2015-03-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his EU counterparts on the statement by the President of the European Council published on 18 March 2015 on support for Tunisia in response to the recent shootings in that country.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228900","228900"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229380","2015-03-26","Department of Health","2015-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of the efficacy of using BRCA gene testing techniques to diagnose certain types of cancers.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228879","228879"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229381","2015-03-26","Department of Health","2015-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many babies were born with a hole in their heart in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228926","228926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229382","2015-03-26","Department of Health","2015-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his comparative estimate is of the number of deaths due to cancer for which the primary cause was smoking in (a) 2004 and (b) 2014.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228899","228899"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229383","2015-03-26","Department of Health","2015-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the liabilities faced by the NHS from unprocessed care home claims.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228933","228933"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229384","2015-03-26","Department of Health","2015-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the Government will refund penalty charges for people who subsequently were given a medical exemption certificate.","Biography information for Mr John Leech","Mr John Leech","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228934","228934"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229385","2015-03-26","Department of Health","2015-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when his Department plans to publish the remaining stages of the Keogh Urgent and Emergency Care Review.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228948","228948"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229386","2015-03-26","Home Office","2015-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the changes in the rate of mephedrone use in the (a) Gosport and Fareham area and (b) UK.","Biography information for Caroline Dinenage","Caroline Dinenage","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228935","228935"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229387","2015-03-26","Home Office","2015-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she intends to reply to the letter to her dated 19 February 2015 from the right hon. Member for Manchester Gorton with regards to Mr J Holloway.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228937","228937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229388","2015-03-26","Home Office","2015-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what her Department's policy is on (a) the issue of passports and (b) legal recognition for those who do not associate with a particular gender; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228917","228917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229389","2015-03-26","Home Office","2015-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the capability of each local authority to accommodate the number of asylum seekers dispersed to those areas.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228878","228878"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229390","2015-03-26","Department for International Development","2015-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that a long-term, strategic approach is taken to funding of her Department's education projects.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228882","228882"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229391","2015-03-26","Department for International Development","2015-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what her Department's spend on malaria control was in 2013-14.","Biography information for Mr Stephen O'Brien","Mr Stephen O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228930","228930"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229392","2015-03-26","Department for International Development","2015-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what resources her Department is providing for the reconstruction of Kobane.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228946","228946"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229393","2015-03-26","Department for International Development","2015-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to facilitate a humanitarian corridor between Turkey and Kobane in order to ensure that adequate humanitarian supplies can pass into Kobane.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228947","228947"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229394","2015-03-26","Home Office","2015-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what information her Department holds on the number and proportion of criminal cases which could not proceed owing to diplomatic immunity in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228886","228886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229395","2015-03-26","Ministry of Justice","2015-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much it cost to run the Sentencing Guidelines Council in (a) 2011, (b) 2012, (c) 2013 and (d) 2014.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228893","228893"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229396","2015-03-26","Northern Ireland Office","2015-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, if she will ask the Police Ombudsman for Northern Ireland to publish guidance on the circumstances in which he will investigate complaints relating to incidents which occurred over one year ago.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228897","228897"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229397","2015-03-26","Prime Minister","2015-03-24","To ask the Prime Minister, when he last visited Scotland.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228922","228922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229398","2015-03-26","Prime Minister","2015-03-24","To ask the Prime Minister, what discussions he has had with his Israeli counterpart since the recent elections in that country on relations between the UK and Israel.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228927","228927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229399","2015-03-26","HM Treasury","2015-03-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate his Department has made of the potential effect that reducing air passenger duty on flights leaving UK airports by 50 per cent would have on (a) passenger numbers, (b) aircraft movements and (c) the number of foreign destinations served at each UK airport.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228901","228901"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229400","2015-03-26","HM Treasury","2015-03-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate his Department has made of the potential effect that reducing air passenger duty on flights leaving Scottish airports by 50 per cent would have on (a) passenger numbers, (b) aircraft movements and (c) the number of foreign destinations served at each UK airport.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228902","228902"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229401","2015-03-26","Department for Transport","2015-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much was spent on maintenance of the M6 between Junctions 31 and 32 in the last four years.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228932","228932"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229402","2015-03-26","Department for Transport","2015-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will take steps to ensure that Northern Rail and First Transpennine Express revise the timetable for Bolton to Manchester trains as a result of the Farnworth Tunnel engineering works.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Mr David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228944","228944"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229403","2015-03-26","Department for Transport","2015-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the total cost is of production of the Design Vision for High Speed 2.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228924","228924"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229404","2015-03-26","Department for Transport","2015-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what representations his Department has received from Network Rail since July 2014 on potential cancellation of projects because of constraints on capital funding.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228876","228876"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229405","2015-03-26","Department for Transport","2015-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to his Department's Road Investment Strategy, published on 1 December 2014, for what reasons improvements to the A27 at Arundel and Worthing are not included in Highways England's Strategic Business Plan 2015 to 2020, published on 9 December 2014; and when that plan will be updated to include that scheme.","Biography information for Nick Herbert","Nick Herbert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228875","228875"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229406","2015-03-26","Department for Transport","2015-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the (a) timetable and (b) process is for construction of the Arundel bypass announced in his Department's Road Investment Strategy published on 1 December 2014.","Biography information for Nick Herbert","Nick Herbert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228874","228874"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229407","2015-03-26","Department for Transport","2015-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he expects construction of the Arundel bypass announced in his Department's Road Investment Strategy published on 1 December 2014 to (a) begin and (b) be completed.","Biography information for Nick Herbert","Nick Herbert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228873","228873"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229408","2015-03-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in Preston constituency applied for hardship payments in 2014; and how many of those applications were successful.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228871","228871"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229409","2015-03-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 12 March 2015 to Question 226839, whether quarterly or monthly data is now available on the number of adverse employment and support allowance sanction decisions broken down by the Summary International Classification of Diseases since January 2014; and what the reason was for each such sanction.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228870","228870"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229410","2015-03-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 12 March 2015 to Question 226858 and with reference to his Department's response to the freedom of information requests 2014-79 and 2014-2282, whether his Department holds any quarterly or monthly data on the reasons for sanctions in such cases.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228869","228869"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229411","2015-03-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people who received the higher rate of the mobility component of disability living allowance have been assessed for personal independence payment (PIP) and not been awarded the enhanced mobility rate of PIP.","Biography information for Fiona O'Donnell","Fiona O'Donnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228889","228889"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229412","2015-03-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he intends to reply to the letter to him dated 19 February 2015 from the right hon. Member for Manchester Gorton with regards to Nurv Saadi.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228938","228938"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229413","2015-03-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, under what conditions married women can claim universal credit in their own right.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228936","228936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229414","2015-03-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many times he and Ministers in his Department visited Scotland in each year since May 2010.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228921","228921"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229415","2015-03-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what conditions are placed on jobseeker's allowance claimants who are in receipt of new enterprise grants.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228918","228918"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229416","2015-03-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether his Department provides funding for the use of ketamine as an anaesthetic in the developing world; what representations he has received on restrictions of use of that substance for that purpose; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228916","228916"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229417","2015-03-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what support is provided to people on jobseeker's allowance who are setting up their own businesses.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228915","228915"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229032","2015-03-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, which reports commissioned by his Department from external bodies between 1 September 2010 and 31 December 2014 have not yet been published; when each such report was commissioned; what the nature of the research so commissioned was; from which individual or body each such report was commissioned; what the value was of each report so commissioned; on what date each such report was received by his Department; for what reasons the research has not yet been published; and when he plans to publish each such report.","Biography information for Lord Blunkett","Mr David Blunkett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228652","228652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229035","2015-03-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the budget for the funding of adult skills in (a) the South East and (b) Eastbourne constituency is for (i) 2014-15 and (ii) 2015-16.","Biography information for Stephen Lloyd","Stephen Lloyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228643","228643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229036","2015-03-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment his Department has made of the effect on UK universities of the Government's decision to reduce the number of approved English test providers for people applying for a UK visa to two from 6 April 2015.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228662","228662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229038","2015-03-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the total amount of investment each local enterprise partnership has secured in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228751","228751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229040","2015-03-25","HM Treasury","2015-03-23","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to his Answer of 18 March 2015 to Question 228233, during the 15 inspections in February how many breaches of the national minimum wage were identified following each business inspection; and what remedies have been sought for employees following each such inspection.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228733","228733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229041","2015-03-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 18 March 2015 to Question 228233, how the increased resources for the Employment Agency Standards Inspectorate in this financial year have been allocated.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228734","228734"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229043","2015-03-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 18 March 2015 to Question 228233, what additional staffing the Employment Agency Standards Inspectorate has allocated to conduct targeted enforcement action in high risk areas.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228735","228735"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229045","2015-03-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 18 March 2015 to Question 228233, which potential breaches of the (a) Conduct of Employment Agencies and Employment Businesses Regulations 2003 and (b) Employment Agencies Act 1973 were identified in the inspections of employment businesses conducted by the Employment Agency Standards Inspectorate in February 2015.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228736","228736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229047","2015-03-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 18 March 2015 to Question 228233, what the most common breaches of obligations under the (a) Conduct of Employment Agencies and Employment Businesses Regulations 2003 and (b) Employment Agencies Act 1973 identified by the Employment Agency Standards Inspectorate are.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228737","228737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229049","2015-03-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 18 March 2015 to Question 228233 and the Written Statement of 4 November 2013, Official Report, 1WS, if he will ensure that staff seconded from the Employment Agency Standards Inspectorate (EAS) to HM Revenue and Customs will be returned to EAS.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228738","228738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229050","2015-03-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, (a) how many projects have been selected, (b) how much has been committed to and (c) how much was spent in each parliamentary constituency in England through the Regional Growth Fund in (i) 2010, (ii) 2011, (iii) 2012, (iv) 2013, (v) 2014 and (vi) 2015 to date.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228716","228716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229052","2015-03-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, when he plans to provide a substantive answer to Questions 225677, 225678, 225008 and 225009.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228760","228760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229054","2015-03-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent discussions he has had on the EU Accounting and Transparency Directives; and what steps he is taking to ensure compliance with those Directives.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228761","228761"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229056","2015-03-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to paragraph 5.27 of the Low Pay Commission Report 2015, if he will take steps alongside stakeholders in the entertainment industry to produce and publish national minimum wage guidance for that sector.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228763","228763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229058","2015-03-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will ensure that a substantive Answer to Questions 227859 and 227860 is provided before prorogation.","Biography information for Meg Hillier","Meg Hillier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228764","228764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229060","2015-03-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to support pubs.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228768","228768"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229062","2015-03-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether there has been a reduction in Bradford College's budget for Level 2 and Level 3 courses.","Biography information for Mr David Ward","Mr David Ward","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228788","228788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229063","2015-03-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the number of higher education institutes that participated in Israel Apartheid Week.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228792","228792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229065","2015-03-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if his Department will take steps to ensure that courses are not cut at Bradford College owing to reductions in its budget.","Biography information for Mr David Ward","Mr David Ward","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228804","228804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229067","2015-03-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many organisations have been accredited to (a) Cyber Essentials and (b) Cyber Essentials Plus; and how many insurance companies reference Cyber Essentials accreditation.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228816","228816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229068","2015-03-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 22 January 2014, Official Report, column 252W, on Research: Misconduct, whether his Department is aware of one or more cases in which a non-medical scientist was found to have committed research misconduct due to fabrication, falsification, or misrepresentation of data in the last 30 years.","Biography information for Lord Lilley","Mr Peter Lilley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228858","228858"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229069","2015-03-26","Cabinet Office","2015-03-23","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people died of Parkinson's disease in England in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228779","228779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229070","2015-03-25","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, with reference to the Treasury's announcement entitled Chancellor intervenes to honour fuel allowance benefits of ex-miners, published on 15 November 2013, if he will place in the Library the full criteria used in making decisions on concessionary fuel payments for former miners who worked in private-sector mines; and how many former miners received concessionary fuel payments as a result of that announcement.","Biography information for Joan Walley","Joan Walley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228648","228648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229071","2015-03-26","HM Treasury","2015-03-23","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much accrued to the Exchequer in stamp duty collected from the sale of properties worth over £1 million in (a) the UK, (b) Scotland, (c) Wales and (d) Northern Ireland in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228743","228743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229072","2015-03-26","HM Treasury","2015-03-23","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, on what telephone number can tax credit claimants contact Synnex-Concentrix UK to discuss mandatory reconsideration.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228744","228744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229073","2015-03-26","HM Treasury","2015-03-23","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much accrued to the Exchequer in capital gains tax arising from the sale of properties worth over £1 million in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228753","228753"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229074","2015-03-26","HM Treasury","2015-03-23","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Health on the effects on people's health of the cuts to alcohol duty in the Budget 2015.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228712","228712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229075","2015-03-26","HM Treasury","2015-03-23","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent representations he has received from the European Commission on his Department's timetable for proposed tax changes affecting community energy societies.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228663","228663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229076","2015-03-26","HM Treasury","2015-03-23","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate the Government has made of the additional cost to the public purse arising from additional (a) social security payments and (b) social care costs of people in receipt of annuity income reassigning that income to a third party in order to receive the value of that annuity as a lump sum.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228659","228659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229077","2015-03-26","HM Treasury","2015-03-23","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the figures in table 2.1 of Budget 2015 on a secondary market in annuities, how many people receiving an annuity income will have to reassign that income to a third party and take the value as a lump sum in order to generate the projected additional revenues of £535 million in 2016-17 and £540 million in 2017-18.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228657","228657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229078","2015-03-26","HM Treasury","2015-03-23","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the figures in table 2.1 of Budget 2015 on a secondary market in annuities, for what reason income tax revenue is projected to fall by £130 million in 2018-19 and £120 million in 2019-20.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228658","228658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229079","2015-03-26","HM Treasury","2015-03-23","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he plans to answer Question 226273, tabled on 4 March 2015 by the hon. Member for Birkenhead.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228666","228666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229080","2015-03-26","HM Treasury","2015-03-23","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many rental companies claimed interest relief in each year since May 2010; and how much such relief was awarded in each such year.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228795","228795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229081","2015-03-26","HM Treasury","2015-03-23","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what representations he received from existing large public-sector contractors before deciding to remove VAT charges for private-sector bidders on public-sector contracts.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228814","228814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229082","2015-03-26","HM Treasury","2015-03-23","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of removing VAT charges for private-sector bidders on public-sector contracts on drives to increase off-the-shelf ICT purchasing.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228815","228815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229083","2015-03-26","HM Treasury","2015-03-23","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 23 March 2015 to Question 226273, what directions have been issued by HM Revenue and Customs to Synnex-Concentrix UK with respect to its contract to process mandatory reconsideration of tax credit claims; and upon what results will Synnex-Concentrix UK be paid.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228762","228762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229084","2015-03-26","HM Treasury","2015-03-23","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what research reports his Department has commissioned from external bodies between September 2010 and December 2014 has not been published; when each such report was commissioned; what the nature of the research commissioned for each such report was; from whom each such research report was commissioned; what the value of each such commission was; on what date each such report was received by his Department; for what reason each such research report has not yet been published; and when he plans to publish each such report.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228843","228843"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229085","2015-03-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, for which spending announcements made by him or his Ministers since 1 September 2014 the relevant business case has not been made public; and for what reason each such case has not been published.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228812","228812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229086","2015-03-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he expects to reply to Question 224607, tabled by the hon. Member for Tooting on 20 February 2015 for answer on 24 February 2015.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228799","228799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229087","2015-03-25","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what representations he has received on introducing a statutory duty on the fire and rescue service to respond to major flooding; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Joan Walley","Joan Walley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228650","228650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229088","2015-03-26","Ministry of Defence","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether armed forces personnel have the right to be represented by a trade union in relation to (a) changes to terms and conditions of employment and (b) collective complaints to their employer.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228667","228667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229089","2015-03-26","Ministry of Defence","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when the UK ceased production of Polonium-210; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lord Campbell of Pittenweem","Sir Menzies Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228681","228681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229090","2015-03-26","Ministry of Defence","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 20 March 2015 to Question 227404, if he will place in the Library documents (a) DCDS(MilCap)/14/01/10, dated 28 January 2014 and (b) MAA/DG/COMMS/SENIOR MOD ZD743/ZD812 dated 13 December 2013.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228800","228800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229091","2015-03-26","Ministry of Defence","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 20 March 2015 to Question 227978, and with reference to MAA RA1210, how the validity of the ALARP argument, at the time of the Tornado collision over the Moray Firth, will be legally decided.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228801","228801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229092","2015-03-26","Ministry of Defence","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will place in the Library a copy of the document D/VCDS&2ndPUS/8/4 PR11 Tornado CWS Further Work identified in paragraph 1.4.6.606 of the Director General of the Military Aviation Report into the Tornado collision.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228802","228802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229093","2015-03-26","Ministry of Defence","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether, in respect of the current proposals to revise the British Underwater Training and Evaluation Centre range at Kyle of Lochalsh, the new 82 square kilometre area is based upon the current take-up zone or will include the no travel zone; whether the revised Ministry of Defence area map is based on existing inner or outer limits; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Charles Kennedy","Mr Charles Kennedy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228820","228820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229094","2015-03-26","Ministry of Defence","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if, in respect of the current proposals to revise the British Underwater Training and Evaluation Centre range at Kyle of Lochalsh, he will list the initial consultees involved prior to his letter of 3 November 2014 to the right hon. Member for Ross, Skye and Lochaber and others; what input was sought from Marine Scotland; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Charles Kennedy","Mr Charles Kennedy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228821","228821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229095","2015-03-26","Deputy Prime Minister","2015-03-23","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what progress he has made on further devolution in England.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228765","228765"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229096","2015-03-26","Department for Education","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many interim executive board applications she received in each of the last five years; how many of those applications were approved; and how many schools subject to an interim executive board subsequently became an academy or are in the process of becoming one.","Biography information for Heidi Alexander","Heidi Alexander","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228786","228786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229097","2015-03-26","Department for Education","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which reports commissioned by her Department from external bodies between 1 September 2010 and 31 December 2014 have not yet been published; when each such report was commissioned; what the nature of the research so commissioned was; from which individual or body each such report was commissioned; what the value was of each report so commissioned; on what date each such report was received by her Department; for what reasons the research has not yet been published; and when she plans to publish each such report.","Biography information for Lord Blunkett","Mr David Blunkett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228653","228653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229098","2015-03-26","Department for Education","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what contact there has been between Ministers and officials in her Department and Afzal Amin since May 2010.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228825","228825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229099","2015-03-26","Department for Education","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what contact her Department has had with (a) Curzon Education and (b) the Curzon Institute since May 2010; what contracts her Department holds with those bodies; and what the value of those contracts is.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228826","228826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229100","2015-03-26","Department for Education","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many bids her Department received for the contract to develop the assessment for Approved Child and Family Practitioner status.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228695","228695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229101","2015-03-26","Department for Education","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what funds have been allocated for the development of the assessment for Approved Child and Family Practitioner status.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228696","228696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229102","2015-03-26","Department for Education","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the reasons were for deciding to introduce an Approved Child and Family Practitioner qualification.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228697","228697"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229103","2015-03-26","Department for Education","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what skills and competences the proposed Approved Child and Family Practitioner qualification is intended to measure.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228698","228698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229104","2015-03-26","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment the Government has made of the potential effect of amending the licence conditions for retailers responsible for implementing smart meters so that they may use normative benchmark comparisons as an alternative to in-home displays on (a) the total cost of that implementation project and (b) the likelihood of achieving and sustaining the two per cent electricity and 2.8 per cent gas behavioural energy efficiency savings required for that project to be cost effective.","Biography information for Sir Robert Smith","Sir Robert Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228676","228676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229105","2015-03-26","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, when he expects to publish the monitoring and evaluation report commissioned by him from Leading Energy into projects in his Department's Renewable House Programme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lord Stunell","Sir Andrew Stunell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228711","228711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229106","2015-03-26","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many applications for onshore wind turbines based on Government-owned land were made in each year since 2009; and how many such applications received planning consent.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228740","228740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229107","2015-03-25","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, with reference to the Treasury's announcement entitled Chancellor intervenes to honour fuel allowance benefits of ex-miners, published on 15 November 2013, how many former miners who worked in private-sector mines are in receipt of the concessionary fuel allowance as a result of that announcement.","Biography information for Joan Walley","Joan Walley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228649","228649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229108","2015-03-26","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if he will make it his policy to promote a global agreement at the UN Climate Change Conference to provide greater certainty and stability to help unlock private sector investment in green technology; and what assessment he has made of the likelihood of such an agreement being reached.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228791","228791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229109","2015-03-25","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment he has made of the effect on (a) employment and (b) the economy in (i) Fife and (ii) Scotland of the possible closure of Longannet power station.","Biography information for Mike Weir","Mr Mike Weir","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228817","228817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229110","2015-03-26","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what transmission charges have been paid by power stations in Scotland (a) in total and (b) by each power station in each year from 2005 to date.","Biography information for Mike Weir","Mr Mike Weir","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228805","228805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229111","2015-03-26","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, which power stations in the UK received income via the transmission charging regime between 2005 and 2015; and how much such income was received.","Biography information for Mike Weir","Mr Mike Weir","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228806","228806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229112","2015-03-26","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what modelling of blackstart capability of Scottish electricity systems has been undertaken by the (a) Government and (b) National Grid in relation to the potential closure of Longannet power station.","Biography information for Mike Weir","Mr Mike Weir","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228807","228807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229113","2015-03-26","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what modelling of voltage control of the Scottish electricity system has been undertaken by (a) the Government and (b) the National Grid in relation to the potential closure of Longannet power station.","Biography information for Mike Weir","Mr Mike Weir","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228808","228808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229114","2015-03-26","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what modelling of security of electricity supply in Scotland has been undertaken by the (a) Government and (b) National Grid in relation to the potential closure of Longannet power station.","Biography information for Mike Weir","Mr Mike Weir","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228809","228809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229115","2015-03-26","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what recent steps he has taken to increase competition in the energy supply market.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228766","228766"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229116","2015-03-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what research her Department has commissioned from external bodies between September 2010 and December 2014 has not been published; when each such report was commissioned; what the nature of the research commissioned for each such report was; from whom each such research report was commissioned; what the value of each such commission was; on what date each such report was received by her Department; for what reason each such research report has not yet been published; and when she plans to publish each such report.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228841","228841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229117","2015-03-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to Greening Government Commitments Annual Report 2013 to 2014, published in February 2015, what steps she plans to take to improve implementation of policy on procurement of construction timber and office furniture by government departments.","Biography information for Martin Horwood","Martin Horwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228709","228709"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229118","2015-03-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the report of the United Nations Panel of Experts on the DPRK, published on 23 February 2015, what steps he has taken to prevent North Korean diplomats, officials and trade representatives from engaging in illicit activities.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228700","228700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229119","2015-03-26","Home Office","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the comments of 20 March 2015 by the North Korea Ambassador to the UK, what assessment she has made of the safety of refugees from North Korea.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228701","228701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229120","2015-03-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the comments of 20 March 2015 by the North Korean Ambassador to the UK, what assessment he has made of the North Korea's preparedness for nuclear war.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228702","228702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229121","2015-03-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the (a) legal and (b) judicial costs to the UK have been of contesting the claim brought by Mauritius under the UN Convention on the Law of the Sea to date; and what estimate he has made of future such costs.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228803","228803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229122","2015-03-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to secure the release of Raif Badawi and Alaa Abdel Fattah.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228725","228725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229123","2015-03-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has received from non-governmental organisations on the issuing of work visas to Syrian refugees in Jordan; and if he will raise this issue with the Jordanian government.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228793","228793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229124","2015-03-26","Department of Health","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his Department's (a) direct and (b) indirect involvement in (i) the procurement of dermatology services from Nottingham University Hospitals Trust to Circle in 2007 and (ii) the reprocurement of those services in 2012; and whether that involvement was in an advisory capacity.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228787","228787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229125","2015-03-26","Department of Health","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much has been spent on the prescription of drugs to manage Parkinson's disease in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228782","228782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229126","2015-03-26","Department of Health","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average (a) length and (b) cost was of a finished admission episode for people admitted to hospitals with fragility fractures in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228783","228783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229127","2015-03-26","Department of Health","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to statistics on NHS Stop Smoking Services, England - April 2014 to September 2014, published by the Health and Social Care Information Centre in January 2015, what assessment he has made of the factors that have contributed to the decline in the number of people who have reported stopping smoking through an NHS Stop Smoking Service.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228776","228776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229128","2015-03-26","Department of Health","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients waited more than six weeks for (a) an initial NHS hearing assessment and (b) a follow-up NHS hearing aid assessment in each of the last five years.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228784","228784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229129","2015-03-26","Department of Health","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many prescriptions have been issued for the drug Sunitinib in each of the last three years; and what restrictions his Department places on the use of that drug in the NHS.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228715","228715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229130","2015-03-26","Department of Health","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) children and (b) adults in each region of England were fitted with cochlear hearing aids in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228773","228773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229131","2015-03-25","Department of Health","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will recommend to NICE that it updates the EQ5D methodology to better represent meaningful quality of life measures used in assessing cost-effectiveness for interventions that could affect the long-term survival of stroke patients with associated disability.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228724","228724"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229132","2015-03-26","Department of Health","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much the NHS has spent on audiology services in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228770","228770"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229133","2015-03-25","Department of Health","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of cancer patients received (a) intensity modulated and (b) stereotactic radiotherapy in the most recent month for which figures are available.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228690","228690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229134","2015-03-25","Department of Health","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many training places for general practice were (a) commissioned and (b) filled in 2014-15 to date.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228691","228691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229135","2015-03-25","Department of Health","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to his contribution of 13 May 2013, Official Report, column 351, on health and social care, in what year he plans to end the ability of GPs to opt out of providing out-of-hours care.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228692","228692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229136","2015-03-26","Department of Health","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) children and (b) adults in England were fitted with bone anchored hearing aids in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228772","228772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229137","2015-03-26","Department of Health","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much the NHS has spent on (a) hearing aids, (b) cochlear hearing aids and (c) bone anchored hearing aids in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228771","228771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229138","2015-03-25","Department of Health","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department and NHS England have taken to ensure that Grade 5 training opportunities are available for midwives.","Biography information for Stephen Lloyd","Stephen Lloyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228694","228694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229139","2015-03-26","Department of Health","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the causes of increases in the number of hospital admissions of older people for cold-related illnesses since 2012.","Biography information for Andy Burnham","Andy Burnham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228717","228717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229140","2015-03-26","Department of Health","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients discharged from mental health in-patient care have taken their own life within (a) one week and (b) two weeks of that discharge in each year since 2010; and how many investigations have been undertaken into those deaths.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228774","228774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229141","2015-03-26","Department of Health","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many NHS patients have had a hearing test in (a) an audiology clinic, (b) an ear, nose and throat clinic and (c) an audiology department at a local hospital in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228769","228769"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229142","2015-03-26","Department of Health","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 23 March 2015 to Question 228266, what proportion of children and young people who were referred for early intervention treatment in psychosis services started that treatment within two weeks of that referral in the latest quarter for which data is available.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228775","228775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229143","2015-03-26","Department of Health","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much was spent by his Department on the provision of in-vitro fertilisation in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228777","228777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229144","2015-03-26","Department of Health","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many finished hospital episodes with a primary diagnosis of Parkinson's disease there were in England in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228780","228780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229145","2015-03-26","Department of Health","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 23 March 2015 to Question 227902, what assessment he has made of whether mental health services are adequately prioritised in clinical commissioning groups' spending plans.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228778","228778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229146","2015-03-26","Department of Health","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much has been granted from the public purse for research into Parkinson's disease in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228781","228781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229147","2015-03-26","Department of Health","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 1 May 2014, Official Report, columns 769-70W, on cochlear implants, how many cochlear operations there were in (a) 2013-14 and (b) 2014-15 to date; and what the ages were of the patients who had those operations.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228811","228811"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229148","2015-03-25","Department of Health","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the performance criteria are against which 999 ambulance call handlers are assessed.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228640","228640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229149","2015-03-25","Department of Health","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many times ambulances were diverted from (a) Red 1 Call responses and (b) Red 2 Call responses in (i) England and (ii) the North East Ambulance Service area in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228641","228641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229150","2015-03-25","Department of Health","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the equality implications of making human papilloma virus vaccination available to men who have sex with men between the ages of 16 and 40, while women over the age of 18 are not able to access the vaccine.","Biography information for Stephen Lloyd","Stephen Lloyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228642","228642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229151","2015-03-25","Department of Health","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of NICE's decision not to appraise the drug ponatinib for chronic myeloid leukaemia; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mark Tami","Mark Tami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228644","228644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229152","2015-03-25","Department of Health","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the drugs available for chronic myeloid leukaemia patients who are intolerant or resistant to tyrosine-kinase inhibitor therapies.","Biography information for Mark Tami","Mark Tami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228645","228645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229153","2015-03-25","Department of Health","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to commit to the referral of ultra-orphan drugs to NICE Highly Specialised Technologies; and if he will give a target date for this action.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228646","228646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229154","2015-03-25","Department of Health","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he has taken to help early diagnosis of (a) lysosomal acid lipase deficiency and (b) other very rare diseases; and what research his Department has commissioned into innovative medicines for ultra-rare diseases which have a substantial medical impact.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228647","228647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229155","2015-03-26","Department of Health","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the efficacy of the Food Freedom course offered to people with diabetes in Bristol and South Gloucestershire; and if he will take steps to increase take-up of that course.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228682","228682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229156","2015-03-26","Department of Health","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many training posts for nurses were commissioned in England in each year from 1989-90 to 1997-98.","Biography information for Heidi Alexander","Heidi Alexander","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228678","228678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229157","2015-03-26","Department of Health","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the average number of hours spent on administrative tasks each week by (a) nurses and (b) GPs in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Heidi Alexander","Heidi Alexander","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228679","228679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229158","2015-03-26","Department of Health","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what changes were made to the recording and presentation of A&E attendance data in 2003-04.","Biography information for Heidi Alexander","Heidi Alexander","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228680","228680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229159","2015-03-26","Department of Health","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Answers of 2 December 2014 to Question HL2907 and 17 March 2015 to Question HL5319 and the Written Statement of 24 November 2010, Official Report, columns WS101-2, on Questions for Written Answer: Correction, how many incidents of hospitalisation due to ovarian hyperstimulation syndrome (OHSS) have been reported to the Human Fertilisation and Embryology Authority (HFEA); what steps the HFEA takes to ensure that any suspected serious adverse reactions are reported to the licensing authority in accordance with the Human Medicines Regulations 2012; what steps the HFEA takes in cases of failure to report any such incidents to the Medicines and Healthcare Products Regulatory Agency; and whether he is satisfied that the HFEA is doing enough to protect patients from OHSS.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228699","228699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229160","2015-03-26","Department of Health","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people were living with a brain tumour, including all intercranial tumours, on the last date for which figures are available.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228707","228707"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229161","2015-03-26","Department of Health","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make an assessment of the implications for the NHS of the paper by Stephenson et al, A contemporary survival analysis of individuals with cystic fibrosis, published in the European Respiratory Journal, Volume 45, March 2015; and what steps he is taking to ensure that the NHS is adequately resourced to cope with an increase in cystic fibrosis patients over the next 10 years.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228708","228708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229162","2015-03-26","Department of Health","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he first contacted GSK about the price of the meningitis B vaccine.","Biography information for Frank Dobson","Frank Dobson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228705","228705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229163","2015-03-26","Department of Health","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many children died of meningitis B in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Frank Dobson","Frank Dobson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228718","228718"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229164","2015-03-26","Department of Health","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect of the abolition of the Patient Safety Agency and the transfer of its responsibility for the National Reporting and Learning System to NHS England on the number of patient safety alerts issued between June 2012 and December 2013.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228685","228685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229165","2015-03-26","Department of Health","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which NHS operational standards have not been met during the period from May 2010.","Biography information for Heidi Alexander","Heidi Alexander","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228677","228677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229166","2015-03-26","Department of Health","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, by what date he plans to start patient communications in care.data pathfinder areas on the implications for patients of that programme to begin.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228664","228664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229167","2015-03-26","Department of Health","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to improve diagnosis and treatment times in paediatric services.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228665","228665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229168","2015-03-26","Department of Health","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he expects negotiations on the meningitis B vaccine to be concluded before 30 March 2015.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228710","228710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229169","2015-03-26","Department of Health","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the Cancer Drugs Fund's policy is on funding Sunitib for the treatment of kidney cancer; and what the reasons are for any exclusions in the Cancer Drugs Fund's policy towards treatment of this form of cancer.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228742","228742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229170","2015-03-26","Department of Health","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many hospital beds in each sector or service there have been in (a) Sherwood Forest Hospitals and (b) Nottingham University Hospitals NHS Foundation Trusts in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228754","228754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229171","2015-03-26","Department of Health","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidance his Department issues to NHS England on sharing accountability for prescribed specialised services with clinical commissioning groups.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228713","228713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229172","2015-03-26","Department of Health","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many trained GPs were employed in the primary care trust serving Ashfield constituency in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228745","228745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229173","2015-03-26","Department of Health","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress NHS England has made in its review of regulations relating to dispensing appliance contractor licences.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228746","228746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229174","2015-03-26","Department of Health","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what consideration NHS England will give to small and medium-sized enterprises in its review of regulations relating to dispensing appliance contractor licences.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228747","228747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229175","2015-03-26","Department of Health","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what consideration NHS England will give to patient choice in its review of regulations relating to dispensing appliance contractor licences.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228748","228748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229176","2015-03-26","Department of Health","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what part consultation and stakeholder engagement will play in NHS England's review of regulations relating to dispensing appliance contractor licences.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228749","228749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229177","2015-03-25","Department of Health","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the cost of implementing the NHS Improving Quality Programme recommendation of the use of Intermittent Pneumatic Compression devices in stroke units to prevent potentially fatal blood clots in patients who have suffered stroke.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228723","228723"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229178","2015-03-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many temporary passports were issued overseas to British nationals who had lost or had their passports stolen whilst abroad in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jenny Willott","Jenny Willott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228732","228732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229179","2015-03-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how much revenue his Department has generated through the processing and issuing of temporary passports overseas to British nationals who had lost or had their passports stolen whilst abroad in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jenny Willott","Jenny Willott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228730","228730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229180","2015-03-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many temporary passports were issued by the British authorities in Spain to British nationals who had lost or had their passports stolen in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jenny Willott","Jenny Willott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228731","228731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229181","2015-03-26","Home Office","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what arrangements her Department plans to put in place to deal after Dissolution with (a) deportation orders and (b) other immigration cases raised by hon. Members.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228714","228714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229182","2015-03-26","Home Office","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, for what reasons her Department has reduced the number of approved English test providers for people applying for a UK visa to two from 6 April 2015.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228660","228660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229183","2015-03-26","Home Office","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate her Department has made of the cost to UK universities of reducing the number of approved English test providers for people applying for a UK visa to two from 6 April 2015.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228661","228661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229184","2015-03-26","Home Office","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 16 March 2015 to Question 226670, and with reference to paragraph 2.64 of the Budget 2015, what proportion of the additional funding will be for increased security funding for synagogues and mosques.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228687","228687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229185","2015-03-26","Home Office","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the (a) accessibility of legal aid for victims of human trafficking and (b) number of matter starts available for victims to pursue compensation and immigration claims.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228674","228674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229186","2015-03-26","Home Office","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to tackle extremism.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228767","228767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229187","2015-03-26","Home Office","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which reports commissioned by her Department from external bodies between 1 September 2010 and 31 December 2014 have not yet been published; when each such report was commissioned; what the nature of the research so commissioned was; from which individual or body each such report was commissioned; what the value was of each report so commissioned; on what date each such report was received by her Department; for what reasons the research has not yet been published; and when she plans to publish each such report.","Biography information for Lord Blunkett","Mr David Blunkett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228654","228654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229188","2015-03-26","House of Commons Commission","2015-03-23","To ask the hon. Member for Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross representing the House of Commons Commission, if Parliamentary ICT will trial device-independent software supporting open standards such as that used by the Cabinet Office.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228813","228813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229189","2015-03-26","House of Commons Commission","2015-03-23","To ask the hon. Member for Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross representing the House of Commons Commission, pursuant to the Answer of 23 March 2015 to Question 227858, if he will estimate how many unsolicited CDs and DVDs hon. Members received by post at their offices on the parliamentary estate in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Dame Joan Ruddock","Dame Joan Ruddock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228750","228750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229190","2015-03-26","Department for International Development","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much of the UK's funding for Ebola has been spent (a) for each purpose, (b) in each location and (c) on each recipient.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228675","228675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229191","2015-03-26","Department for International Development","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment her Department has made of the effect of integrating early childhood development interventions on nutrition, immunisation and education on the effectiveness on strength of local health systems; and what contribution such an assessment has made to decisions on the funding of (a) her Department's country programmes and (b) multilateral programmes supported by her Department.","Biography information for Mark Durkan","Mark Durkan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228683","228683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229192","2015-03-26","Department for International Development","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what reports she has received on an increase of arranged child marriages among Syrian refugees in Jordan; and what steps the Government is taking to protect children from such marriages.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228789","228789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229193","2015-03-26","Department for International Development","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is taking to encourage other EU member states to provide further assistance to support Syrian refugees and the domestic population of Jordan through humanitarian programmes in Jordan.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228790","228790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229194","2015-03-26","Department for International Development","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much UK aid has been spent in support of privatising electricity in Nigeria since 2002; and through which funding streams that aid was provided.","Biography information for Ann McKechin","Ann McKechin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228798","228798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229195","2015-03-25","Department for International Development","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 29 January 2015 to Question 221760, what assessment she has made of the ability of Syria's neighbouring countries to manage the safety and security of (a) Syrian refugees with urgent medical needs, children and victims of torture and sexual violence and (b) other Syrian refugees.","Biography information for Anas Sarwar","Anas Sarwar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228693","228693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229196","2015-03-26","Ministry of Justice","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the findings were of the research commissioned by the equalities policy lead in his Department into the needs of male and female prisoners to determine whether they are sufficiently different to warrant a different approach on the issue of prison clothing; and if he will place in the Library a copy of that research.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228794","228794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229197","2015-03-26","Ministry of Justice","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which reports commissioned by his Department from external bodies between 1 September 2010 and 31 December 2014 have not yet been published; when each such report was commissioned; what the nature of the research so commissioned was; from which individual or body each such report was commissioned; what the value was of each report so commissioned; on what date each such report was received by his Department; for what reasons the research has not yet been published; and when he plans to publish each such report.","Biography information for Lord Blunkett","Mr David Blunkett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228655","228655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229198","2015-03-26","Ministry of Justice","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which offences prisoners serving a sentence of 12 months or less committed over the course of the most recent year for which information is held.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228796","228796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229199","2015-03-26","Ministry of Justice","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when he plans to respond to the written Questions tabled by the hon. Member for Shipley where a letter was promised but has not yet been sent.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228797","228797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229200","2015-03-25","Ministry of Justice","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what guidance his Department issues on the use of local contractors in tendering processes.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228651","228651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229201","2015-03-26","Ministry of Justice","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 18 March 2015 to Question 208575 on bail what the individual offences were within the violence against person category referred to in the table.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228684","228684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229202","2015-03-26","Ministry of Justice","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many cases there have been of residential leasehold forfeiture in the last five years; how many such cases were presented to the county courts; and how many residential leases were forfeited.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228689","228689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229203","2015-03-26","Department for Transport","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which stations on Southern Railway's Metro line have lost services as a result of emergency changes to the timetable announced on 16 March 2015.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228671","228671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229204","2015-03-26","Department for Transport","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he plans to publish the contractual terms of the directly awarded franchise agreement with First Great Western Limited to run passenger rail services on the Great Western line; whether the franchise agreement makes provision for the role of the guard on Intercity Express Programme (IEP) trains; and what provisions for catering services on IEP trains are included in that franchise agreement in (a) first and (b) standard class.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228686","228686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229205","2015-03-26","Department for Transport","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many passengers using Southern Railway's Metro line have been compensated as a result of recent disruptions to rail services at London Bridge.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228672","228672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229206","2015-03-26","Department for Transport","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will commission a survey to establish the initial origins and final destinations within the London area of passengers leaving or entering Euston by InterCity services on the West Coast Mainline broken down by the non-London stations at which passengers boarded or disembarked.","Biography information for Frank Dobson","Frank Dobson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228706","228706"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229207","2015-03-26","Department for Transport","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the average sum of compensation to passengers using Southern Railway's Metro line has been as a result of recent disruption to rail services at London Bridge station.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228673","228673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229208","2015-03-26","Department for Transport","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect on (a) Heathrow and (b) Gatwick airport if cargo services were transferred to other airports; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228739","228739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229209","2015-03-26","Department for Transport","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will place a copy of the tripartite review by his Department, Network Rail and the Office of Rail Regulation of key enhancement programmes that he received on 1 September 2014 in the Library.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228703","228703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229210","2015-03-26","Department for Transport","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he has received a report in March 2015 from the Office of Rail Regulation assessing the efficient cost of Control Period 5 enhancement projects.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228704","228704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229211","2015-03-25","Department for Transport","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 19 March 2015 to Question 227614, when the Counter Fraud Committee of the Highways Agency was created.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228722","228722"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229212","2015-03-25","Department for Transport","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 19 March 2015 to Question 227614, how frequently the Counter Fraud Committee submits reports to the Audit Committee of the Highways Agency.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228720","228720"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229213","2015-03-25","Department for Transport","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 19 March 2015 to Question 227614, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the remit and powers of the Audit Committee of the Highways Agency.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228721","228721"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229214","2015-03-25","Department for Transport","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what guidelines he has set out for the Highways Agency on that body's process for completing grievance investigations.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228729","228729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229215","2015-03-25","Department for Transport","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 19 March 2015 to Question 227614, if he will publish the Counter Fraud Committee's reports to the Audit Committee of the Highways Agency.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228719","228719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229216","2015-03-25","Department for Transport","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many formal grievances were raised against each office of the Highways Agency's North of England management team in each year since 2006.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228726","228726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229217","2015-03-25","Department for Transport","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the (a) average, (b) shortest and (c) longest time taken to conclude investigations of grievances made against the Highways Agency's North of England management team was in each year between 2006 and 2014.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228728","228728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229218","2015-03-25","Department for Transport","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many investigations of grievances raised against the Highways Agency's North of England management team in each year since 2006 (a) were found in favour of the complainant, (b) were found in favour of the Highways Agency, (c) are unresolved and (d) are yet to conclude.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228727","228727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229219","2015-03-26","Department for Transport","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what research his Department has commissioned from external bodies between September 2010 and December 2014 has not been published; when each such report was commissioned; what the nature of the research commissioned for each such report was; from whom each such research report was commissioned; what the value of each such commission was; on what date each such report was received by his Department; for what reason each such research report has not yet been published; and when he plans to publish each such report.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228842","228842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229220","2015-03-26","Department for Transport","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will discuss with Network Rail the need to support businesses currently renting properties from Network Rail in the Brixton railway arches.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228822","228822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229221","2015-03-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, for what reason improving the mandatory reconsideration process was not included within the scope of his Department's employment and support allowance repeat claims project.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228847","228847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229222","2015-03-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many fit for work decisions were overturned by mandatory reconsideration in each month since October 2008.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228854","228854"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229223","2015-03-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many fit for work decisions overturned by mandatory reconsideration or appeal related to claimants with mental health difficulties in each month since October 2008.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228855","228855"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229224","2015-03-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of individuals previously entitled to claim employment and support allowance who will claim jobseeker's allowance following the changes proposed by the employment and support allowance repeat claims project.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228848","228848"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229225","2015-03-26","Cabinet Office","2015-03-23","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people with learning difficulties who wished to work but were unemployed there were in (a) Streatham constituency, (b) Lambeth local authority area and (c) the UK in each of the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228823","228823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229226","2015-03-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many employment and support allowance claimants have received payment of that benefit pending an appeal since October 2008.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228856","228856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229227","2015-03-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average length of time was that a claimant received payment of employment and support allowance pending appeal in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228857","228857"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229228","2015-03-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what research his Department has carried out into the proportion of UK businesses who are aware of Access to Work funding which can help people with a disability start work, stay in work, move into self-employment or start a business; and what research his Department has carried out into the proportion of employers who are aware that Access to Work funding can be used to help those with mental health conditions, learning difficulties or disabilities, and autism.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228824","228824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229229","2015-03-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many personal assistants are employed under the Independent Living Fund.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228844","228844"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229230","2015-03-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans he has to increase the Access to Work budget upon the closure of the Independent Living Fund in June 2015.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228845","228845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229231","2015-03-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of individuals previously entitled to claim employment and support allowance who will be entitled to but will not claim jobseeker's allowance following the changes proposed by the employment and support allowance repeat claims project.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228849","228849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229232","2015-03-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what criteria his Department applies to ensure the level of the Access to Work budget is responsive to need.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228846","228846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229233","2015-03-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, which reports commissioned by his Department from external bodies between 1 September 2010 and 31 December 2014 have not yet been published; when each such report was commissioned; what the nature of the research so commissioned was; from which individual or body each such report was commissioned; what the value was of each report so commissioned; on what date each such report was received by his Department; for what reasons the research has not yet been published; and when he plans to publish each such report.","Biography information for Lord Blunkett","Mr David Blunkett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228656","228656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229234","2015-03-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in each of the English regions have been in receipt of Carer's Allowance in each of the last five years.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228785","228785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229235","2015-03-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 8 July 2014, Official Report, columns 275-6W, on carer's allowance, what the actual average clearance time was in working days for carer's allowance cases in the most recent period for which data is available.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228810","228810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229236","2015-03-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the ONS nomis database, of the 350 people in Stockton-on-Tees who ceased to claim jobseeker's allowance in January 2015 for other reasons, how many of those people had sanctions placed on their entitlement claim.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228668","228668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229237","2015-03-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the ONS nomis database, of the 5,030 people in the North East who ceased to claim jobseeker's allowance in January 2015 for other reasons, how many of those people had sanctions placed on their entitlement claim.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228669","228669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229238","2015-03-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many employment and support allowance claimants in the work related activity group received (a) one sanction, (b) two sanctions and (b) three sanctions in 2014.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228758","228758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229239","2015-03-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the longest duration of sanction imposed on a claimant in the work related activity group was in (a) 2013 and (b) 2014.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228757","228757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229240","2015-03-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people have joined each of the three options in the Help to Work programme in each month since May 2014.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228756","228756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229241","2015-03-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will place in the Library the research his Department has commissioned on links between securing a short-hours job and a subsequent gain of longer-hours jobs.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228759","228759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229242","2015-03-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many benefit sanctions were applied to claimants resident in (a) Airdrie and Shotts constituency, (b) North Lanarkshire, (c) Scotland and (d) the UK in each month since July 2010.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228741","228741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229243","2015-03-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of personal independence payment claims in (a) Airdrie and Shotts constituency, (b) North Lanarkshire, (c) Scotland and (d) the UK in each month since April 2013 were disallowed pre-referral to the assessment providers; and how many such claims were disallowed due to the claimant not returning the Part 2 form within the time limit.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228755","228755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229244","2015-03-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what research his Department has commissioned on links between securing a short-hours job and securing a longer-hours job; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228752","228752"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229245","2015-03-26","Cabinet Office","2015-03-23","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the ONS nomis database, of the 5,030 people in the North East who ceased to claim jobseeker's allowance in January 2015 for other reasons, how many (a) ceased claiming, (b) failed to sign, (c) went on to full-time education, (d) went abroad, (e) reached retirement age, (f) passed away and (g) did so for unknown reasons.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228670","228670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229246","2015-03-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what training is provided to GPs and other healthcare professions on completing the ESA 50 form; and what steps his Department is taking to monitor and update that training.","Biography information for Joan Walley","Joan Walley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228688","228688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229247","2015-03-26","Cabinet Office","2015-03-23","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the median income from work was of residents of Blackpool South constituency in (a) 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012, (d) 2013, (e) 2014 and (f) 2015 to date.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228831","228831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229248","2015-03-26","Cabinet Office","2015-03-23","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what proportion of people in employment in Blackpool South constituency were earning (a) the minimum wage or below and (b) the living wage or below in (i) 2010, (ii) 2011, (iii) 2012, (iv) 2013, (v) 2014 and (vi) 2015.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228832","228832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229249","2015-03-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what research reports his Department has commissioned from external bodies between September 2010 and December 2014 has not been published; when each such report was commissioned; what the nature of the research commissioned for each such report was; from whom each such research report was commissioned; what the value of each such commission was; on what date each such report was received by his Department; for what reason each such research report has not yet been published; and when he plans to publish each such report.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228840","228840"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229250","2015-03-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Written Statement of 20 March 2014, HCWS438, on what date each of the reports listed was received by his Department; on what date the last payment was made to each research organisation commissioned to produce each of those reports; and for what reason each of those reports had not previously been published.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228830","228830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229251","2015-03-25","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what research reports his Department has commissioned from external bodies between September 2010 and December 2014 have not been published; when each such report was commissioned; what the nature of the research commissioned for each report was; from whom each such research report was commissioned; what the value of each such commission was; on what date each such report was received by his Department; for what reason each such research report has not yet been published; and when he plans to publish each such report.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228819","228819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229252","2015-03-26","Department for Education","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many times the right hon. Member for Surrey Heath has visited her Department since 14 July 2014; and what the date was of each such visit.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228828","228828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229253","2015-03-26","Department for Education","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much her Department has spent since May 2010 on underwriting the salaries of staff at free schools when their school did not open or open on time as planned.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228829","228829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229254","2015-03-26","Department for Education","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will publish a list of free schools indicating how many children have been enrolled at each school and how many pupils are funded at each school.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228827","228827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229255","2015-03-26","Department of Health","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many finished consultant episodes with a primary or secondary diagnosis of (a) age-related macular degeneration, (b) glaucoma, (c) diabetic retinopathy and (d) cataracts there were in the NHS in England in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Liz Kendall","Liz Kendall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228836","228836"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229256","2015-03-26","Department of Health","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the rate was of (a) age-related macular degeneration, (b) glaucoma and (c) diabetic retinopathy per 100,000 population by age group in (i) 2013-14 and (ii) 2014-15 to date.","Biography information for Liz Kendall","Liz Kendall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228837","228837"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229257","2015-03-26","Department of Health","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many finished hospital admission episodes with a primary or secondary diagnosis of fractures attributable to osteoporosis there were amongst (a) women under, (b) women over, (c) men under and (d) men over the age of 50 in 2013-14.","Biography information for Liz Kendall","Liz Kendall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228838","228838"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229258","2015-03-25","Department of Health","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what research reports his Department has commissioned from external bodies between September 2010 and December 2014 have not been published; when each such report was commissioned; what the nature of the research commissioned for each report was; from whom each such research report was commissioned; what the value of each such commission was; on what date each such report was received by his Department; for what reason each such research report has not yet been published; and when he plans to publish each such report.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228818","228818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229259","2015-03-26","Department of Health","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many free sight tests were provided on the NHS to people aged (a) under and (b) over 60 in England in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Liz Kendall","Liz Kendall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228835","228835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229260","2015-03-26","Home Office","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many police community support officers were registered full-time in Blackpool South constituency in (a) 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012, (d) 2013, (e) 2014 and (f) January to March 2015.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228833","228833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229261","2015-03-26","Home Office","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many police officers (a) took voluntary redundancy, (b) retired before their statutory age in Blackpool in (i) 2010, (ii) 2011, (iii) 2012, (iv) 2013, (v) 2014 and (vi) January to March 2015.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228834","228834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229262","2015-03-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average length of time was that his Department took to process a personal independence payment from (a) a motor neurone disease sufferer and (b) another disabled person in the most recent period for which data is available.","Biography information for Liz Kendall","Liz Kendall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228839","228839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229263","2015-03-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effect on child poverty of the introduction of child maintenance service charges.","Biography information for Mike Wood","Mike Wood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228852","228852"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229264","2015-03-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what support will be provided to people no longer entitled to claim employment and support allowance following the changes proposed by the employment and support allowance repeat claims project who are eligible for but do not claim jobseeker's allowance.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228850","228850"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229265","2015-03-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many fit for work decisions were overturned on appeal in each month since October 2008.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228851","228851"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229266","2015-03-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the gender impact of the introduction of child maintenance service charges.","Biography information for Mike Wood","Mike Wood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228853","228853"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229536","2015-03-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what funding his Department has allocated for adult skills training in east Durham in 2015-16; and what amount was allocated for that purpose in 2014-15.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame M. Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 908353","908353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229537","2015-03-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what discussions he has had with mobile phone operators on the effects of adverse weather on their systems; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Charles Kennedy","Mr Charles Kennedy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 908354","908354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229538","2015-03-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent assessment he has made of the contribution of EU membership to business and the economy in the UK.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 908352","908352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229539","2015-03-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to tackle late payment to small businesses.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 908351","908351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/229540","2015-03-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to promote regional growth.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 908356","908356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228767","2015-03-24","Attorney General","2015-03-20","To ask the Attorney General, what the average hourly pay is of employees in the Law Officers' Departments identified as (a) White or White British and (b) from a Black, Asian or other minority ethnic group.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228577","228577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228768","2015-03-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many start-up businesses have been created in (a) England, (b) London and (c) Hendon constituency since 2010.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228564","228564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228769","2015-03-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps the Government has taken to tackle the movement of counterfeit clothing into the UK.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228530","228530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228770","2015-03-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department is taking to ensure market compliance with EU Regulation 1007/2011 on textile labelling in regard to (a) the new requirement for textile products containing non-textile parts of animal origin to be clearly labelled as such and (b) other provisions in the regulation.","Biography information for Mark Pritchard","Mark Pritchard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228532","228532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228771","2015-03-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the average hourly pay is of employees in his Department identified as (a) White or White British and (b) from a Black, Asian or other minority ethnic group.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228576","228576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228772","2015-03-24","Cabinet Office","2015-03-20","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the average hourly pay is of employees at each grade in his Department identified as (a) White or White British and (b) from a Black, Asian or other minority ethnic group.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228571","228571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228773","2015-03-24","Cabinet Office","2015-03-20","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what guidance has been issued to Government departments on the use of premium rate numbers to access public services.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228569","228569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228774","2015-03-25","HM Treasury","2015-03-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what representations he has received on the decision of the Financial Conduct Authority to withdraw from the Connaught Income Fund Series 1 settlement negotiations.","Biography information for Guto Bebb","Guto Bebb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228573","228573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228775","2015-03-25","HM Treasury","2015-03-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will request the Financial Conduct Authority to ensure that its investigation into the Connaught Income Fund Series 1 will result in adequate compensation for investors in that fund; and if he will request a timescale for the payment of such compensation.","Biography information for Guto Bebb","Guto Bebb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228574","228574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228776","2015-03-25","HM Treasury","2015-03-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent discussions he has had with the Financial Conduct Authority on the Connaught Income Fund Series 1 settlement negotiations.","Biography information for Guto Bebb","Guto Bebb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228575","228575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228777","2015-03-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many national insurance numbers are currently issued in the UK.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228544","228544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228778","2015-03-25","HM Treasury","2015-03-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans he has for the future of HM Revenue and Customs' offices at Swansea; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228548","228548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228779","2015-03-24","HM Treasury","2015-03-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent steps the Government has taken to tackle the movement of counterfeit cigarettes into the UK.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228531","228531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228780","2015-03-25","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much the Government plans to invest in affordable housing in the South East of England between 2015 and 2020; and how many affordable homes he forecasts will be built in that region in that period.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228536","228536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228781","2015-03-25","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much the Government has spent on affordable housing in (a) England, (b) the South East, (c) Surrey and (d) Elmbridge in each year since 2005.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228549","228549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228782","2015-03-25","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many council houses have been sold in (a) London and (b) each London borough since 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228550","228550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228783","2015-03-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what funding his Department makes available for individual Holocaust memorial projects.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228558","228558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228784","2015-03-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many neighbourhood forums have been established under the Localism Act 2011.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228567","228567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228785","2015-03-25","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will request that the Natural History Museum stops its practice of gender-specific marketing of toys.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228563","228563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228786","2015-03-24","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what plans the Government has to increase participation of blind people in sport.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228521","228521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228787","2015-03-24","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department has taken to increase participation of people with cerebral palsy in sport.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228522","228522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228788","2015-03-24","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent assessment his Department has made of the legacy of the 2012 London Olympic and Paralympic Games.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228523","228523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228789","2015-03-24","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what progress his Department has made on providing 95 per cent of rural areas with superfast broadband by 2017.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228524","228524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228790","2015-03-24","Ministry of Defence","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of how many jobs his Department (a) directly and (b) indirectly supports through its supply chain in (i) the North West, (ii) Lancashire and (iii) Preston.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228539","228539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228791","2015-03-24","Department for Education","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the average hourly pay is of employees in her Department identified as (a) White or White British and (b) from a Black, Asian or other minority ethnic group.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228578","228578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228792","2015-03-25","Department for Education","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what (a) discussions, (b) meetings and (c) other communications she has had with the Tauheedul Education Trust since 13 February 2015 on the application for change of use from offices to state funded school for Universal House, 35-37 London Road, Preston.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228552","228552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228793","2015-03-24","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what recent discussions his Department has had with the Department of Health on the link between toxic fumes and respiratory conditions.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228526","228526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228794","2015-03-24","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Education on installing solar technology in schools.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228582","228582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228795","2015-03-24","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate has Department has made of the UK's tidal energy resource.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228584","228584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228796","2015-03-24","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate he has made of what proportion of Europe's tidal energy production is represented by the UK's tidal energy resource production.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228585","228585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228797","2015-03-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions officials in her Department have had with their counterparts in EU member states and officials in the European Commission on the revision of the European School Milk Scheme.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228597","228597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228798","2015-03-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether her Department plans to participate in the European School Milk Scheme in future years.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228598","228598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228799","2015-03-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate she has made of the number of dairy farmers who have ceased trading in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228559","228559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228800","2015-03-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions her Department has had with the Chinese government on whether it plans to expand its temporary ban on ivory imports.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228566","228566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228801","2015-03-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received on China's artificial island expansion in disputed waters in the South China Sea.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228565","228565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228802","2015-03-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent steps his Department has taken to protect Christians and other minority groups across the Middle East.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228525","228525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228803","2015-03-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to the oral evidence taken by the Committees on Arms Export Controls on 1 December 2014, HC 608, when the report of the review of extant exporting licensing and the licensing of new applications for Israel will be published.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228599","228599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228804","2015-03-25","Department of Health","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average length of stay in hospital was for people with a primary diagnosis of chronic obstructive pulmonary disease in England in each year from 2009-10 to 2014-15.","Biography information for Liz Kendall","Liz Kendall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228589","228589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228805","2015-03-25","Cabinet Office","2015-03-20","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people died as a result of chronic obstructive pulmonary disease in England in each year from 2009-10 to 2014-15.","Biography information for Liz Kendall","Liz Kendall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228590","228590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228806","2015-03-25","Department of Health","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much was spent on the prescription of drugs to manage chronic obstructive pulmonary disease in the NHS in each year from 2009-10 to 2014-15.","Biography information for Liz Kendall","Liz Kendall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228591","228591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228807","2015-03-25","Department of Health","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people were recorded on a general practice register with a diagnosis of chronic obstructive pulmonary disease in England in each year from 2009-10 to 2014-15.","Biography information for Liz Kendall","Liz Kendall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228588","228588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228808","2015-03-24","Department of Health","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to reduce the level of substance abuse by teenagers.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228516","228516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228809","2015-03-24","Department of Health","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if his Department will commission research on the long-term effects of video game addiction on primary school-aged children.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228517","228517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228810","2015-03-24","Department of Health","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent steps his Department has taken to encourage confectionery retailers to reduce the sugar content of their products.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228518","228518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228811","2015-03-24","Department of Health","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps the Government is taking to provide support and assistance to the families of chronic alcoholics.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228519","228519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228812","2015-03-24","Department of Health","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps the Government is taking to provide support and assistance for patients with bowel cancer.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228520","228520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228813","2015-03-24","Department of Health","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions his Department has had with the Department for Education on increasing the level of healthy-eating advertising within primary schools.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228540","228540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228814","2015-03-25","Cabinet Office","2015-03-20","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people had been diagnosed with a brain tumour, including all intercranial tumours, in (a) England, (b) Scotland, (c) Wales and (d) Northern Ireland on the last date for which figures are available.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228535","228535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228815","2015-03-25","Department of Health","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 24 February 2015 to Question 223927, if he will review the range of data collected centrally within his Department and the subjects of Parliamentary Questions received by his Department in the present Parliament to ensure that a higher proportion of hon. Members' Questions can be answered with substantive information.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228557","228557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228816","2015-03-25","Department of Health","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will provide funding to the Nursing and Midwifery Council to enable it to avoid increasing annual registration fees for registered nurses.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228551","228551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228817","2015-03-24","Department of Health","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of using artificial human organs in medical testing.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228545","228545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228818","2015-03-24","Department of Health","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, on how many occasions 999 ambulance call handlers have been diverted to assist with 111 calls in (a) England and (b) the North East Ambulance Service area in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228546","228546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228819","2015-03-24","Department of Health","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the level of sickness and absence of 999 ambulance call handlers was in (a) England and (b) the North East Ambulance Service area in the last year.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228547","228547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228820","2015-03-25","Home Office","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the date was of each meeting of the Sexual Violence Against Children and Vulnerable Adults National Task Force since it was set up; and which government departments (a) were invited to and (b) attended each such meeting.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228587","228587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228821","2015-03-24","Home Office","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the National Centre for the 3Rs was offered additional funding for the next financial year; and whether that body accepted that funding.","Biography information for Jim Dowd","Jim Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228586","228586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228822","2015-03-25","Home Office","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many citizens of Islamic countries have been refused visas when attempting to enter the UK to attend academic conferences in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228595","228595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228823","2015-03-24","Department for International Development","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will take steps to encourage better dialogue between factory workers and management in Bangladesh's garment industry.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228581","228581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228824","2015-03-24","Department for International Development","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what progress has been made on encouraging companies to sign up to the Ethical Trading Initiative.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228583","228583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228825","2015-03-25","Department for International Development","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what the value is of contracts her Department holds with (a) Adam Smith International, (b) PwC and (c) KPMG.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228533","228533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228826","2015-03-25","Department for International Development","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answers of 19 and 22 January 2015 to Questions 220652, 220623, 221273 and 221277, how much has been spent on the Economic Development Strategy in 2014-15 to date.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228534","228534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228827","2015-03-24","Department for International Development","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how her Department is using international aid to tackle poverty in Rwanda.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228527","228527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228828","2015-03-24","Department for International Development","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how her Department is using international aid to increase the literacy rate amongst women in Nigeria.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228528","228528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228829","2015-03-24","Department for International Development","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how her Department is using international aid to tackle the water shortage in Bangladesh.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228529","228529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228830","2015-03-24","Department for International Development","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what monitoring her Department undertakes of the content of UN Relief and Works Agency educational materials in Gaza and the West Bank.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228560","228560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228831","2015-03-24","Ministry of Justice","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what plans his Department has to bring forward legislative proposals to prohibit the squatting of premises in the commercial property sector.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228568","228568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228832","2015-03-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many convictions there have been for offences concerning dangerous dogs under the Anti-Social, Crime and Policing Act 2014.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228570","228570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228833","2015-03-25","Department for Transport","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many times national rail stations were closed because of overcrowding in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228537","228537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228834","2015-03-25","Department for Transport","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which organisation holds the franchise for each London bus route.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228538","228538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228835","2015-03-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to prevent illegal parking on private property and land.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228561","228561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228836","2015-03-24","Department for Transport","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department plans to announce the timetable for the Greater Western franchise before 30 March 2015.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228580","228580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228837","2015-03-25","Women and Equalities","2015-03-20","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, if she will hold discussions with the Natural History Museum on targeting boys and girls equally.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228562","228562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228838","2015-03-25","Ministry of Justice","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people in Preston constituency are currently appealing against refusal of employment and support allowance.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228553","228553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228839","2015-03-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many jobseeker's allowance claimants in Preston constituency are currently sanctioned.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228554","228554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228840","2015-03-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many employment and support allowance claimants in Preston constituency are currently sanctioned.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228555","228555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228841","2015-03-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in Preston constituency claiming (a) jobseeker's allowance and (b) employment and support allowance currently have court costs, fines and victim surcharges deducted from their benefits.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228556","228556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228842","2015-03-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average hourly pay is of employees in his Department identified as (a) white or white British and (b) from a black, Asian or other minority ethnic group.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228579","228579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228843","2015-03-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that there is no gap in funding for refugees between the ending of Home Office support and the start of jobseeker's allowance payments.","Biography information for Chris Williamson","Chris Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228572","228572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228844","2015-03-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the accessibility to his Department and its agencies to deaf people and people who use British Sign Language.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228541","228541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228845","2015-03-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many items of correspondence his Department or its agencies have sent to Ms Hazel McRae.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228542","228542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228846","2015-03-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what his policy is on providing employment and support allowance for claimants whose medical assessments are significantly delayed who are then judged to be fit for work, but may not have been for a part of the intervening period; and what mechanism his Department has in place for such claimants to make representations to his Department in such cases.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228543","228543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228847","2015-03-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of spending on the development of the Universal Credit digital service in (a) 2013-14, (b) 2014-15, (c) 2015-16, (d) 2017-18, (e) 2018-19 and (f) 2019-20.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228592","228592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228848","2015-03-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many times ministers or officials from his Department visited Wales since April 2012 to discuss the Jobs Growth Wales programme.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228593","228593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228849","2015-03-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what liaison his Department has had with HM Revenue and Customs since June 2011 to ensure that companies accepting Work Programme participants pay National Minimum Wage.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228594","228594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228850","2015-03-25","Cabinet Office","2015-03-20","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what plans the Government has to promote opendata and data sharing; and whether he plans to conduct a review of data sharing.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228603","228603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228851","2015-03-25","Cabinet Office","2015-03-20","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many prime-time television advertising slots the Government has purchased in each of the last 12 months; and what the cost was in each such case.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228619","228619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228852","2015-03-25","Cabinet Office","2015-03-20","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many full-time equivalent Civil Service jobs there were (a) in total and (b) in each government department and its agencies in (i) the City of York, (ii) Yorkshire and the Humber, (iii) England and (iv) the UK (A) in May 2010 and (B) at the latest date for which figures are available.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Sir Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228620","228620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228853","2015-03-25","Cabinet Office","2015-03-20","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many providers took part in the GOV.UK Verify trial; and how many such providers will be in place when that scheme is rolled out across central Government.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228638","228638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228854","2015-03-25","HM Treasury","2015-03-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, where he plans digital tax accounts will be held; how he plans to protect such accounts against cyber attacks; and what safeguards he plans to put in place for those accounts to protect privacy.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228639","228639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228855","2015-03-25","HM Treasury","2015-03-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 10 March 2015 to Question 225793, for what reason the Driver and Vehicle Licensing Agency imposes a five per cent surcharge on people who pay by monthly direct debit, but does not do so on people who pay by annual direct debit.","Biography information for Guto Bebb","Guto Bebb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228622","228622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228856","2015-03-25","Home Office","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the effect of landlord immigration checks in the private rented sector on landlords' willingness to rent.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228629","228629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228857","2015-03-25","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether he plans to visit York before the General Election.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Sir Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228607","228607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228858","2015-03-24","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what funding has been allocated to (a) the arts, (b) sport and (c) heritage from the National Lottery in each of the last eight years for which figures are available; and what the aggregate equivalent figures are for (i) the arts, (ii) sport and (iii) heritage from (A) 2006 to 2010 and (B) 2010 to 2014.","Biography information for Chris Heaton-Harris","Chris Heaton-Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228614","228614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228859","2015-03-24","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what changes to the proportion of National Lottery funding committed to (a) the arts, (b) sport and (c) heritage there have been in the last five years.","Biography information for Chris Heaton-Harris","Chris Heaton-Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228613","228613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228860","2015-03-24","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the Government's objectives are for the December 2015 UN Climate Change Conference.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228601","228601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228861","2015-03-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much the Rural Payments Agency claimed under the European School Milk Scheme in each year since 2005.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228611","228611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228862","2015-03-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what independent veterinary evidence she has sought from outside her Department on the effects on badger cubs of moving the proposed badger cull from autumn 2015 to June 2015.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228616","228616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228863","2015-03-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate she has made of the number of additional (a) badger cubs and (b) adult badgers that will be killed as a result of moving the proposed badger cull from autumn 2015 to June 2015.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228617","228617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228864","2015-03-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she has taken to ensure that animal products originating in Israeli settlements in the occupied Palestinian territory are not imported into the UK with sanitary or phytosanitary certification issued by the Israeli authorities; and when those steps were taken.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228634","228634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228865","2015-03-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to the government of Bahrain concerning the cases of Nabeel Rajab and Hussain Jawad and other human rights activists charged with expression-related offences.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228630","228630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228866","2015-03-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the implications for his policies of the communication to Bahrain by the UN Chair-Rapporteur of the Working Group on Arbitrary Detention, Special Rapporteur on freedom of expression, Special Rapporteur on free assembly and Special Rapporteur on the situation of human rights defenders on 14 October 2014, expressing concerns about the trial of Mr Nabeel Rajab in Bahrain; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228615","228615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228867","2015-03-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what information his Department holds on whether the recent KPMG report is the first independent study there has been on the feasibility of resettlement in the British Indian Ocean Territory.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228636","228636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228868","2015-03-25","Department of Health","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answers of 27 February 2015 to Questions 225235 and 225238, by what process NHS England is developing the interim commissioning policies referred to in those Answers; whether funding has been allocated to support those policies; and whether those policies have been discussed by the Clinical Priorities Advisory Group.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228635","228635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228869","2015-03-25","Department of Health","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many recorded episodes of births before admission there were in each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228637","228637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228870","2015-03-25","Department of Health","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress has been made on introducing hourly ward rounds for nurses; how those rounds will be monitored and recorded; and what assessment he has made of the potential effect on staff time of such recording.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228618","228618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228871","2015-03-25","Department of Health","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much the Government has allocated to development of new drugs and treatments for chronic obstructive pulmonary disease each year from 2009-10 to 2014-15.","Biography information for Liz Kendall","Liz Kendall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228612","228612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228872","2015-03-25","Department of Health","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether face-down physical restraint is included in the list of never ever events that must be reported to the Strategic Executive Information System.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228605","228605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228873","2015-03-25","Department of Health","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many NHS trusts across the country have a youth advisory partnership group or similar engagement provision for young people using services.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228606","228606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228874","2015-03-25","Department of Health","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many and which police forces directly refer people with mental health problems into primary mental health services.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228604","228604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228875","2015-03-25","Department of Health","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will set a target date by which all GP-registered patients in England will be able to access a GP, 8am to 8pm, seven days a week.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228628","228628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228876","2015-03-25","Department of Health","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when the last deep clean of hospitals in the NHS took place.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228610","228610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228877","2015-03-25","Home Office","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average response time to a 999 call was for police services in the Blackpool Constabulary area in each year from 2010 to 2015 to date.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228626","228626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228878","2015-03-25","Home Office","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many and what proportion of reports of violent crime in the Blackpool Constabulary area led to a prosecution in each year from 2010 to 2015 to date.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228627","228627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228879","2015-03-25","Home Office","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many police officers served in the Blackpool Constabulary on (a) 1 March 2010 and (b) 1 March 2015; and how many such officers were categorised as front-line staff.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228625","228625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228880","2015-03-25","Home Office","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the effect of landlord immigration checks on non-EEA residents trying to rent, who have entered the UK on temporary documents and are waiting for a biometric residence permit.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228633","228633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228881","2015-03-24","House of Commons Commission","2015-03-20","To ask the hon. Member for Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross representing the House of Commons Commission, whether the Commission made an assessment of the risks of being locked into one supplier when the decision was taken to trial Apple iPad for select committees.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228624","228624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228882","2015-03-24","Department for International Development","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what her policy is on the proposed Sustainable Development Goals and the Special Summit on Sustainable Development in September 2015.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228602","228602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228883","2015-03-25","Prime Minister","2015-03-20","To ask the Prime Minister, whether he plans to visit York before 7 May 2015.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Sir Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228609","228609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228884","2015-03-24","Department for Transport","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much his Department has allocated to support the programme set out in the Report by Transport for the North entitled The Northern Powerhouse, published in March 2015; and what proportion of the £2.7 billion of investment referred to in that Report will be guaranteed by the Government.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228600","228600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228885","2015-03-25","Department for Transport","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will review compensation arrangements for passengers using Southern Railway's Metro line who have been affected by the recent disruption to rail services at London Bridge station.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228632","228632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228886","2015-03-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people waited more than (a) one month, (b) two months and (c) three months for a decision on their employment and support allowance claim in each year since May 2010.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228623","228623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228887","2015-03-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the value was of payments for each type of benefit not paid as a result of sanctions against individual claimants in each year since 2010-11 in (a) Yorkshire and the Humber and (b) the City of York; and how many claimants were sanctioned in each such year in each such area.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Sir Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228621","228621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228888","2015-03-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average housing benefit paid in (a) Islington, (b) Greater London and (c) England was for tenants of (i) council property, (ii) housing associations and (iii) the private sector in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228631","228631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228889","2015-03-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 18 March 2015 to Question 227535, how much his Department has spent on funding work clubs since April 2012.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228596","228596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228890","2015-03-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-03-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will meet the Chairman of the Trussell Trust before 7 May 2015.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Sir Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228608","228608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228469","2015-03-24","Attorney General","2015-03-19","To ask the Attorney General, for what reasons the Crown Prosecution Service made the decision that it would not be in the public interest to pursue a private prosecution on gender abortion charges against Dr Prabha Sivaraman and Dr Palaniappan Rajmohan.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228357","228357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228470","2015-03-23","Attorney General","2015-03-19","To ask the Attorney General, when he last met one of his counterparts from an EU member state; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Baroness McIntosh of Pickering","Miss Anne McIntosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228351","228351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228471","2015-03-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to paragraph 1.179 of Budget 2015, what estimate he has made of how many PhD and post-graduate students in (a) the UK, (b) Scotland, (c) England, (d) Wales and (e) Northern Ireland will receive the proposed financial support in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228325","228325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228472","2015-03-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department plans to take to further develop UK trade with Turkey over the next five years.","Biography information for Nick de Bois","Nick de Bois","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228393","228393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228473","2015-03-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what contribution his Department plans to make to the EU consultation on the Digital Single Market.","Biography information for Mike Weatherley","Mike Weatherley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228398","228398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228474","2015-03-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to ensure the growth of graduate entry level STEM jobs in the North West.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228400","228400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228475","2015-03-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to paragraph 1.177 of Budget 2015, how much his Department has allocated for the uptake of support for PhD and post graduate students in (a) the UK, (b) Scotland, (c) England, (d) Wales and (e) Northern Ireland in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228469","228469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228476","2015-03-24","Cabinet Office","2015-03-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what proportion of the workforce was paid at least the living wage in (a) Rutherglen and Hamilton West constituency, (b) South Lanarkshire, (c) Scotland and (d) the UK in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Tom Greatrex","Tom Greatrex","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228488","228488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/228477","2015-03-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many young people living in (a) Rutherglen and Hamilton West constituency, (b) South Lanarkshire, (c) Scotland and (d) the UK entered higher education in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Tom Greatrex","Tom Greatrex","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 228489","228489"
