"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750745","2017-07-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the cost of replicating EURATOM in the UK.","Biography information for Antoinette Sandbach","Antoinette Sandbach","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4129","4129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750746","2017-07-13","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what assessment he has made of the costs of setting up an alternative judicial structure in place of the European Court of Justice to arbitrate in international matters connected with nuclear energy.","Biography information for Antoinette Sandbach","Antoinette Sandbach","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4130","4130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750747","2017-07-17","Ministry of Justice","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many drones carrying contraband goods were seized within prison grounds in 2016-17.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4436","4436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750748","2017-07-17","Ministry of Justice","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many mobile phones were seized in prisons in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4437","4437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750749","2017-07-17","Ministry of Justice","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the street value was of the drugs recovered in prisons in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4438","4438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750750","2017-07-17","Ministry of Justice","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many days have been lost due to sickness and (b) what the sickness absence rate was in the prison service in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4439","4439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750751","2017-07-17","Department for Education","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many educational psychologists were employed in all local authorities in (a) 2016 and (b) 2017.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4435","4435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750752","2017-07-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will set out the (a) remit, (b) membership, (c) timetable and (d) resources of the proposed Homelessness Reduction Taskforce.","Biography information for Mr Mark Prisk","Mr Mark Prisk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4316","4316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750753","2017-07-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on NHS cancer patients of the Government’s decision for the UK to leave Euratom.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4432","4432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750754","2017-07-17","Department of Health","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will estimate the amount accrued to the public purse of measures to recover the costs of using the NHS from overseas nationals in each of the (a) next and (b) last five years.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4443","4443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750755","2017-07-17","Department of Health","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he plans to take to reduce rates of staff bullying in the NHS.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4441","4441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750756","2017-07-17","Department of Health","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans his Department has to increase the number of psychiatrists employed by the NHS.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4442","4442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750757","2017-07-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what further plans he has to introduce combined authorities in non-metropolitan or unitary authority areas.","Biography information for Mr Bob Seely","Mr Bob Seely","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4429","4429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750758","2017-07-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the per capita funding was to each (a) combined and (b) local authority fire authority; and whether such funding to local authorities is provided as a discrete budget.","Biography information for Mr Bob Seely","Mr Bob Seely","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4427","4427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750759","2017-07-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he plans to introduce a fifth round of the Coastal Communities Fund.","Biography information for Mr Bob Seely","Mr Bob Seely","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4426","4426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750760","2017-07-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the level of New Homes Bonus payments made to Isle of Wight Council in each of the last four years were; and what the affordable and other housing delivery figures were on which those payments were made.","Biography information for Mr Bob Seely","Mr Bob Seely","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4430","4430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750761","2017-07-13","Department of Health","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to eliminate zero hour contracts for social care workers.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4413","4413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750762","2017-07-13","Home Office","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent meetings (a) Ministers and (b) officials of her Department have had with the National Crime Agency and Regional Serious Crime Unit on the provision of extra support and funding to Merseyside Police to tackle recent rises in gun crime.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4414","4414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750763","2017-07-13","Home Office","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the oral contribution of the Under-Secretary of State for the Home Department, of 3 July 2017, Official Report, column 886, what additional support has been provided to Merseyside Police to tackle recent increases in gun crime by the (a) National Crime Agency and (b)  Regional Serious Crime Unit.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4416","4416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750764","2017-07-13","Home Office","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent meetings (a) Ministers and (b) officials of her Department have had with Merseyside Police on the provision of extra support to tackle recent rises in gun crime.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4415","4415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750765","2017-07-13","Department for Transport","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many public service vehicles inspected by the Driver and Vehicle Standards Agency were identified as having tyres that exceed the 10-year age limit in each year since January 2014.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4421","4421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750766","2017-07-13","Department for Transport","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 6 July 2017 to Question 1855, how many inspections into the age of public service vehicle tyres were carried out by the Driver and Vehicle Standards Agency in each year since January 2014.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4420","4420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750767","2017-07-13","Department for Transport","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many accidents involving coaches or buses were caused by a defective tyre in each year since October 2012.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4419","4419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750768","2017-07-13","Department for Transport","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make an assessment of the adequacy of legislation related to parking on pavements in ensuring pedestrian safety.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4418","4418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750769","2017-07-13","Department for Transport","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make an assessment of the effect of parked cars obstructing pavements on the safety of visually impaired and blind pedestrians.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4417","4417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750770","2017-07-13","Department for International Trade","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many new international trade agreements the Government has concluded since 1 January 2017.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4270","4270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750771","2017-07-13","Ministry of Justice","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what plans his Department has to review policies regarding the retention of documents relating to applications made under the Gender Recognition Act 2004.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4369","4369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750772","2017-07-17","Department for Education","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will make it her policy to annually review funding levels to local authorities for the provision of 30 hours free childcare until 2020.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4347","4347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750773","2017-07-17","Department for Education","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will make an assessment of the effect of the Government’s 30 hours free childcare policy on the financial viability of childcare providers.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4346","4346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750774","2017-07-17","Department for Education","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment will be made of the effect of the cost of (a) the national minimum wage, (b) the living wage and (c) other employment costs on the level of funding required from her Department to deliver 30 hours free childcare.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4200","4200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750775","2017-07-17","Department for Education","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the effect of 30 hours free childcare places on (a) the availability of places for three and four-year-olds whose parents are not working and (b) funded two-year-old places.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4199","4199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750776","2017-07-17","Department for Transport","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions his Department has had with representatives of the Scottish Government on the merger of British Transport Police in Scotland with Police Scotland; and what steps have been agreed to maintain coordination of intelligence and operations between police forces.","Biography information for Stephen Kerr","Stephen Kerr","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4160","4160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750777","2017-07-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what discussions his Department has had with the Scottish Government on strategic initiatives to support small businesses in Scotland; and what the agreed steps to be taken were at those discussions.","Biography information for Stephen Kerr","Stephen Kerr","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4159","4159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750778","2017-07-13","Home Office","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to Section 2(1) of the Ireland Act 1949, what the status of Irish citizens will be after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4182","4182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750779","2017-07-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the potential effect on the fisheries sector of the UK leaving the EU without agreeing a trade deal with the EU.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4374","4374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750780","2017-07-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the effect on the agricultural sector of the UK leaving the EU without agreeing a trade deal with the EU.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4375","4375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750781","2017-07-13","Department for Education","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children were home-schooled in each (a) local authority and (b) parliamentary constituency by age for (i) the most recent period for which figures are available and (ii) each year since 2010; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4142","4142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750782","2017-07-13","Department for Education","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what level of Key Stage 2 attainment has been achieved by pupils permanently excluded from state funded mainstream secondary schools in the academic year 2015-16 prior to their exclusion for each year since 2010.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4143","4143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750783","2017-07-13","Department for Education","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children are registered in independent (a) enrolled and (b) offsite alternative education provided for excluded young people more than one day a week in each (i) local authority and (ii) parliamentary constituency for (A) the most recent period for which figures are available and (B) each year since 2010; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4408","4408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750784","2017-07-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to the World Health Organisation to enable Taiwan to regain observer status.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4281","4281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750785","2017-07-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 3 July 2017 to Question 1490, on food: waste, what his policy is on the European Parliament’s proposals to (a) set a target to halve food waste across supply chains by 2030, (b) review making those targets mandatory and (c) introduce a specific food waste hierarchy.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4318","4318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750786","2017-07-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what representations the Government made at the Environmental Ministerial Meeting of the G7 in Bologna on 11 and 12 June 2017; and what contribution he made to discussions on food waste and separate food waste collections.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4206","4206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750787","2017-07-18","Department of Health","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether any funding from the public purse has been disbursed to (a) Marie Stopes International and (b) the British Pregnancy Advisory Service for the purposes of campaigning for a change in the law on abortion in Northern Ireland; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4444","4444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750788","2017-07-17","Department of Health","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he has any plans to bring the time limit for abortions on grounds of disability into line with abortions on other grounds.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4348","4348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750789","2017-07-17","Department of Health","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that people with Down’s syndrome do not feel discriminated against as a result of the introduction of non-invasive prenatal testing for Down’s syndrome.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4359","4359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750790","2017-07-18","Department of Health","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps the Government has taken to ensure that women resident in Northern Ireland seeking an abortion in mainland Britain are made aware of the risks involved in undergoing an abortion.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4360","4360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750791","2017-07-17","Home Office","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which police services are involved in the airwave replacement programme.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4391","4391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750792","2017-07-17","Home Office","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what funding her Department is allocating to each police service for the airwave replacement programme.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4392","4392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750793","2017-07-17","Home Office","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what (a) proportion and (b) total amount of special grants were allocated by her Department to cover legal fees in each financial year since 2012-13.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4406","4406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750794","2017-07-13","Department for Education","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what background checks were carried out on Johnson Kane before schools were transferred to management by the Education Fellowship Trust.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4286","4286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750795","2017-07-13","Department for Education","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what information her Department holds on Johnson Kane.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4285","4285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750796","2017-07-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of landlords’ gas safety checks in respect of carbon monoxide; and whether such checks should be carried out on more than just a representative sample of gas equipment in any one premises.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4272","4272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750797","2017-07-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many incidents of pollution of English watercourses have resulted in bathing restrictions being implemented on (a) watercourses and (b) beaches in each year for which data is available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4145","4145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750798","2017-07-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many people or companies which have polluted English watercourses have done so on (a) two, (b) three, (c) four and (d) more than four occasions since these incidents have been recorded.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4146","4146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750799","2017-07-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate has been made of the total cost of incidents of pollution of English watercourses in each year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4154","4154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750800","2017-07-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment has been made of the effectiveness of an enforcement undertaking in reducing the incidence of pollution of English watercourses.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4155","4155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750801","2017-07-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many recordable pollution incidents there were for English waterways in each year for which information is available; and what proportion of those offences resulted in (a) successful prosecution and (b) an enforcement undertaking.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4156","4156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750802","2017-07-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many polluters who were offered an enforcement undertaking for polluting English watercourses failed to fulfil their legally binding voluntary agreements.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4157","4157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750803","2017-07-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many enforcement undertaking offers have been made to those who have polluted watercourses in England in each year since 2011.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4158","4158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750804","2017-07-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the number and proportion of houses of multiple occupation which were (a) registered and (b) not registered in each local authority area is in each year for which data is available in ranked order for each year.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4144","4144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750805","2017-07-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 5 July 2017 to Question 840, on multiple occupation: licensing, which local authorities have accessed new information from tenancy deposit protections schemes in order to identify mandatory licensable houses of multiple occupation since that data has been made available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4183","4183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750806","2017-07-13","HM Treasury","2017-07-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many companies in Wales are known to have paid employees less than the minimum wage in each year for which figures are available; and if he will list those companies and their location.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4274","4274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750807","2017-07-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he expects to commence the review of Approved Document B.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4226","4226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750808","2017-07-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department is taking to incentivise businesses to invest in rooftop solar.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4225","4225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750809","2017-07-17","Department for Education","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans she has to amend safeguarding guidance for schools better to protect girls from sexual assault.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4398","4398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750810","2017-07-17","Department for Education","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what progress her Department is making on developing new guidance for schools on delivering sex and relationships education.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4399","4399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750811","2017-07-13","Department for Education","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she plans to provide additional training to teachers on child protection and safeguarding.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4267","4267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750812","2017-07-13","Ministry of Defence","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many members of the armed forces have been recruited from the Blaenau Gwent postcode area in the last five years.","Biography information for Nick Smith","Nick Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4376","4376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750813","2017-07-13","Ministry of Defence","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the effect of recent reserve centre closures on recruitment to the armed forces.","Biography information for Nick Smith","Nick Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4377","4377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750814","2017-07-17","Department of Health","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the Government’s policy is on maintaining the public sector pay cap for (a) nurses and (b) care workers.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4400","4400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750815","2017-07-17","Cabinet Office","2017-07-11","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether he plans to bring forward legislative proposals for the removal of the hereditary peers from the House of Lords in the current Parliament.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4339","4339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750816","2017-07-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to invest in solar energy over the course of the current Parliament.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4313","4313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750817","2017-07-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to reduce dependence on non-renewable sources of energy.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4340","4340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750818","2017-07-17","HM Treasury","2017-07-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the return to the public purse has been of (a) Fixed Odds Betting Terminals and (b) other forms of gambling in the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4390","4390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750819","2017-07-17","Department for Education","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of student loans have been repaid in full (a) since the new system was introduced and (b) from the establishment of the original scheme.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4345","4345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750820","2017-07-17","Department for Transport","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make it his policy to seek a derogation from Regulation (EC) 561/2006 for lorries carrying livestock; and if he will make  a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4395","4395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750821","2017-07-17","Department for Transport","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what progress he has made on developing a scheme to improve safety and traffic flow on the on the A417 missing link in Gloucestershire; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4310","4310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750822","2017-07-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his foreign counterparts in the Kashmir region on stability in Kashmir; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4256","4256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750823","2017-07-17","Department for Transport","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions he has had with Network Rail on the electrification of the TransPennine Rail Network.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4263","4263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750824","2017-07-17","Department for Transport","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate his Department has made of the cost of the electrification of the TransPennine Rail Network.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4262","4262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750825","2017-07-17","Department for Transport","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the timetable is for work to begin on electrification of the TransPennine Rail Network.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4261","4261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750826","2017-07-17","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what her policy is on the arms-length principle for the funding of the arts.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4314","4314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750827","2017-07-17","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what her policy is on the additionality principle for the funding of projects from the National Lottery.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4315","4315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750828","2017-07-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will rank each English local authority by the change in the number of social housing units in ach such local authority since (a) 1987, (b) 1997 and (c) 2007.","Biography information for Ms Karen Buck","Ms Karen Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4253","4253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750829","2017-07-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the change was in the proportion of homeless household (a) applications and (b) acceptances who were BAME over the last 10 years.","Biography information for Ms Karen Buck","Ms Karen Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4251","4251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750830","2017-07-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what proportion of nominations to (a) local authorities and (b) registered social landlord properties were homeless households in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Ms Karen Buck","Ms Karen Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4252","4252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750831","2017-07-17","Department for Education","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will set out which English local authorities have a total of five per cent or more surplus school places in (a) primary, (b) secondary and (c) all schools.","Biography information for Ms Karen Buck","Ms Karen Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4254","4254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750832","2017-07-17","Department of Health","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he last met representatives of the charity Breathe Easy to discuss the diagnosis and treatment of lung disease; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4191","4191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750833","2017-07-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to his Oral contribution of 10 July 2017, Official Report, column 56, on export licensing: High Court judgment, on what dates the Government has raised the matter of minors on death row in Saudi Arabia with the government of that country; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4319","4319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750834","2017-07-13","Home Office","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she expects paragraph 11 of Schedule 10 of the Immigration Act 2016 to be brought into force.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4224","4224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750835","2017-07-17","Home Office","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 3 July 2017 to Question 1480, on human trafficking, on which statistics the Government based its approach to human trafficking and modern slavery; and if she will place a copy of those statistics in the Library.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4397","4397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750836","2017-07-17","Home Office","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 3 July 2017 to Question 1480, on human trafficking, whether the National Crime Agency has ceased to produce its standalone annual strategic assessment of the nature and scale of human trafficking in the UK; and if she will make  a statement.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4396","4396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750837","2017-07-13","Home Office","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to paragraph 6 of her Department’s policy paper, Safeguarding the position of EU citizens in the UK and UK nationals in the EU, published on 26 June 2017, whether EU citizens who are full-time carers for their relatives will be eligible to qualify for settled status.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4289","4289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750838","2017-07-13","Home Office","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to paragraph 6 of her Department’s policy paper, Safeguarding the position of EU citizens in the UK and UK nationals in the EU, published on 26 June 2017, whether non-EU family members who are married to a disabled or terminally ill EU citizen who passes away before having accrued five years’ residence will be eligible to qualify for settled status.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4290","4290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750839","2017-07-13","Home Office","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to paragraph 6 of her Department’s policy paper, Safeguarding the position of EU citizens in the UK and UK nationals in the EU, published on 26 June 2017, whether EU citizens who are full-time carers for a relative who dies before the EU citizen carer has accrued five years’ residence will be eligible to qualify for settled status.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4288","4288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750840","2017-07-17","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to paragraph 49 of his Department’s policy paper Safeguarding the position of EU citizens in the UK and UK nationals in the EU, published on 26 June 2017, whether EU citizens and UK nationals who are not benefiting from healthcare arrangements before the specified date will be able to do so at a date in the future.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4393","4393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750841","2017-07-13","Home Office","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to paragraph 6 of her Department’s policy paper Safeguarding the position of EU citizens in the UK and UK nationals in the EU, published on 26 June 2017, what provision the Government plans to make available with respect to the legal status and rights of EU citizens in the UK who are potential victims of trafficking and modern slavery.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4422","4422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750842","2017-07-17","HM Treasury","2017-07-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the annual yield to the Treasury of increasing the higher rate of income tax to (a) 45 pence and (b) 50 pence for those earning over £150,000 in (i) the UK and (ii) Scotland; and how many people would be affected in each category.","Biography information for Stewart Hosie","Stewart Hosie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4280","4280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750843","2017-07-17","HM Treasury","2017-07-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the cost to the public purse was of his Department's communications team in 2016-17, and what the projected costs are for 2017-18.","Biography information for Stewart Hosie","Stewart Hosie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4279","4279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750844","2017-07-13","HM Treasury","2017-07-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the cost of sickness pay to staff in his Department was in the most recent year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Stewart Hosie","Stewart Hosie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4275","4275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750845","2017-07-13","HM Treasury","2017-07-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many receptions he has hosted for representations of the print and broadcast media in the last year; how many people attended those receptions; and what the cost to the public purse was for each of those receptions.","Biography information for Stewart Hosie","Stewart Hosie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4276","4276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750846","2017-07-13","HM Treasury","2017-07-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much (a) his Department and (b) each (i) non-departmental public body and (ii) executive agency for which his Department is responsible spent on external consultants and advisers in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Stewart Hosie","Stewart Hosie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4277","4277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750847","2017-07-17","HM Treasury","2017-07-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much was spent on advertising by (a) his Department and (b) each of its (i) non-departmental public bodies and (ii) executive agencies in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Stewart Hosie","Stewart Hosie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4278","4278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750848","2017-07-17","Home Office","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the report from Refugee Action, entitled Slipping through the gaps, published in July 2017, for what reasons her Department is not meeting targets for section 95 and section 98 support for asylum seekers; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4194","4194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750849","2017-07-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has raised the issue of the continuing imprisonment of Liu Xiaobo with his counterpart in China; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4168","4168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750850","2017-07-13","Department for Transport","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of accessibility for disabled people on Transport for London stations; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Bob Blackman","Bob Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4190","4190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750851","2017-07-13","Department of Health","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the estimated average annual cost is to the NHS of providing Brineura (Cerliponase Alfa) to someone with the CLN2 variant of Batten Disease.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4139","4139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750852","2017-07-13","Department of Health","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average annual cost is to the NHS of care and treatment of people with (a) any Neuronal Ceroid Lipofuscinosis disease and (b) the CLN2 variant of that disease.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4140","4140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750853","2017-07-13","Department of Health","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people in the UK are undergoing care and treatment for (a) all Neuronal Ceroid Lipofuscinosis diseases, (b) the CLN2 and (c) the CLN5 variants of that disease.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4141","4141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750854","2017-07-13","Home Office","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what targets she has set for local police forces to tackle cybercrime; and how work to meet those targets will be funded.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4153","4153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750855","2017-07-17","Ministry of Justice","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what safeguards the Government has in place to protect donors when appointing professionals as attorneys in the event of the firm such attorneys work for being closed down.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4380","4380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750856","2017-07-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many local authorities in the East of England (a) over-spent, (b) under-spent and (c) exactly spent their Discretionary Housing Payment funding allocations in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4382","4382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750857","2017-07-17","Department of Health","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, on what date he plans to publish the proposed Green Paper on Social Care.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4383","4383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750858","2017-07-17","Home Office","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she expects to publish the independent review into deaths and serious incidents in police custody, announced on 23 July 2015.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4201","4201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750859","2017-07-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what plans he has to bring forward proposals for three days of paid volunteering leave for employees.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4356","4356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750860","2017-07-17","Department for Education","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, for what reasons the application from Warrington Collegiate to change its name to Warrington and Vale Royal College on its merger with Mid Cheshire College has been refused; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4358","4358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750861","2017-07-17","Department for Education","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent discussions she has had with (a) Warrington Borough Council, (b) representatives of Warrington head teachers and (c) trade union representatives on the effect of the school funding formula on schools in Warrington North constituency.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4353","4353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750862","2017-07-17","Ministry of Justice","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what training is provided to prison officers to support inmates who (a) are elderly and frail and (b) suffer from dementia.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4355","4355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750863","2017-07-17","Home Office","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, What steps she has taken to implement the recommendations of the report of HM Inspectorate of Constabulary into crime recording in the Cheshire Police force, published on 15 June 2017; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4203","4203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750864","2017-07-13","Ministry of Justice","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps the Government is taking to bring about the release of prisoners subject to a sentence of imprisonment for public protection who have served their tariff.","Biography information for Alex Chalk","Alex Chalk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4257","4257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750865","2017-07-13","Home Office","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what conclusions on gender and passport markings the Government has drawn from its 2016 survey of International Civil Aviation Association Organisation members.","Biography information for Alex Chalk","Alex Chalk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4185","4185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750866","2017-07-17","Home Office","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many and what proportion of calls to the Police 101 number were answered within the target of 30 seconds in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4264","4264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750867","2017-07-13","Home Office","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the operating and staffing costs are for call centres delivering the police 101 service for each year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4269","4269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750868","2017-07-17","Home Office","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many and what proportion of calls to the Police 101 number were abandoned by the caller after failing to get a response in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4401","4401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750869","2017-07-17","Home Office","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many and what proportion of callers to the Police 101 number waited more than an hour for their call to be answered in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4404","4404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750870","2017-07-17","Home Office","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average time taken was to answer a call to the Police 101 number in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4405","4405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750871","2017-07-17","Home Office","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many Police 101 call centres have been (a) closed and (b) merged since 7 May 2015.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4403","4403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750872","2017-07-17","Department of Health","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment has been made of the presence of flammable cladding on hospitals; what the timetable is for assessing all hospital buildings for the presence of such cladding; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4162","4162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750873","2017-07-17","Department for Transport","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what his Department’s target is for efficiency savings by British Transport Police; and how he intends to allocate proceeds from that efficiency programme.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4163","4163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750874","2017-07-17","Department for Transport","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the cost of the airway replacement programme for the British Transport Police; and what additional funding his Department will provide to the British Transport Police to complete that programme.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4164","4164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750875","2017-07-17","Department for Transport","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what capabilities are exempt from his Department’s target for efficiency savings by the British Transport Police.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4165","4165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750876","2017-07-17","Department for Transport","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what his policy is on the devolution of transport policing to Scotland.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4166","4166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750877","2017-07-17","Department for Transport","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether it is his policy for the British Transport Police to be merged with other police forces; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4167","4167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750878","2017-07-13","Department for Transport","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what requirements he places in franchise agreements with train-operating companies for minimum staffing levels.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4128","4128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750879","2017-07-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when he plans to publish his response to the results of his Department's consultation on tips, gratuities, service and other charges that closed in June 2016.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4127","4127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750880","2017-07-17","Ministry of Defence","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many cases have been opened as part of Operation Northmoor; and how many of those cases have been (a) closed and (b) remain ongoing.","Biography information for Will Quince","Will Quince","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4195","4195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750881","2017-07-13","Home Office","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when the evaluation of the pilot for a new national referral mechanism to identify and support victims of modern slavery will be published.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4283","4283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750882","2017-07-13","Home Office","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when guidance on victim identification and support provided for in section 49 of the Modern Slavery Act 2015 will be (a) completed and (b) published.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4363","4363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750883","2017-07-13","Home Office","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to ensure that the UK will continue to have access to the European Criminal Records Information System and Schengen Second Generation Information Services when the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4265","4265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750884","2017-07-13","Home Office","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to ensure that the rights to support for victims of modern slavery will be maintained after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4284","4284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750885","2017-07-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether the Government plans to introduce legislative proposals to transpose EU labour law into UK primary legislation.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4331","4331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750886","2017-07-13","Home Office","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the Government plans to bring forward legislative proposals further to protect the rights of victims of human trafficking and modern slavery as a result of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4330","4330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750887","2017-07-17","Home Office","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average response time for answering 101 calls made to Lancashire Constabulary was in each month between 1 January 2016 and 30 June 2017.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4341","4341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750888","2017-07-19","Department of Health","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many transvaginal mesh implants were performed in each quarter from 1 January 2017 by (a) Lancashire Teaching Hospitals, (b) University Hospitals of Morecambe Bay, (c) Blackpool Teaching Hospitals, (d) Bolton NHS, (e) East Lancashire Hospital, (f) Southport and Ormskirk Hospitals, (g) Warrington and Halton Hospitals and (h) St Helens and Knowsley Teaching Hospitals.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4181","4181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750889","2017-09-05","Women and Equalities","2017-07-11","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what funding the Government Equalities Office plans to make available to tackle period poverty; and whether she plans to meet her equivalent in the Scottish Parliament to discuss its initiative to provide sanitary products to women and girls on low incomes.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4361","4361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750890","2017-07-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will take steps to compile information on the number of Motability vehicles which have been recalled in England between (a) January to March and (b) April to June 2017.","Biography information for Stephen Pound","Stephen Pound","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4294","4294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750891","2017-07-13","HM Treasury","2017-07-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the number of employers in Penistone and Stocksbridge constituency that will not be required to pay the apprenticeship levy.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4239","4239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750892","2017-07-13","HM Treasury","2017-07-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many employers will be required to pay the apprenticeship levy in (a) Penistone and Stocksbridge constituency and (b) Yorkshire and the Humber.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4240","4240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750893","2017-07-13","Department for Education","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many students were required to re-sit their (a) English and (b) mathematics GCSE exams in the latest academic year for which information is available.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4241","4241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750894","2017-07-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when he plans to publish the response to his Department’s consultation Proposals to ban the use of plastic microbeads in cosmetics and personal care products in the UK, issued on 20 December 2016.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4334","4334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750895","2017-07-13","Department for Transport","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the Answer of 27 March 2017 to Question 69282, what the number of (a) Audis, (b) SEATs, (c) Skodas, (d) commercial vehicles and (e) Volkswagen private cars was to which fixes had been applied by the time of the (i) April, (ii) May, (iii) June and (iv) July meetings.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4255","4255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750896","2017-07-13","Prime Minister","2017-07-11","To ask the Prime Minister, what steps she plans to take to tackle abuse of electoral candidates; what plans she has to investigate past instances of such abuse; and which Ministers will be responsible for that work.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4219","4219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750897","2017-07-13","Prime Minister","2017-07-11","To ask the Prime Minister, if she will ensure that Ministers drawing up plans to tackle abuse of electoral candidates take account of the findings of the All-Party Parliamentary Group Inquiry into Electoral Conduct, published in 2013, and updates to that report.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4220","4220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750898","2017-07-13","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether her Department plans to provide to the Minister tasked with taking forward the Government’s investigation into the abuse of electoral candidates details of the All-Party Parliamentary Group Inquiry into Electoral Conduct relating to social media and communications.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4222","4222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750899","2017-07-13","Cabinet Office","2017-07-11","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether his Department plans to provide to the Minister tasked with taking forward the Government’s investigation into the abuse of electoral candidates details of the All-Party Parliamentary Group Inquiry into Electoral Conduct and its subsequent updates.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4221","4221"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750900","2017-07-13","Department of Health","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when the Government plans to publish a response to the report Old Problems, New Solutions: Improving Acute Psychiatric Care for Adults in England, published by the Commission on Acute Psychiatric Care in February 2016.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4135","4135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750902","2017-07-17","Home Office","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many EU citizens residing in the UK have a disability.","Biography information for Angela Crawley","Angela Crawley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4350","4350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750903","2017-07-13","Home Office","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions she has had with disability groups on the effect of proposals for settled status on EU citizens in the caring professions living in the UK.","Biography information for Angela Crawley","Angela Crawley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4335","4335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750904","2017-07-17","HM Treasury","2017-07-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will bring forward proposals to require the beneficial ownership of companies and trusts to be made public.","Biography information for Angela Crawley","Angela Crawley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4351","4351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750905","2017-07-17","HM Treasury","2017-07-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department is taking to tackle rising inflation.","Biography information for Angela Crawley","Angela Crawley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4349","4349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750906","2017-07-17","HM Treasury","2017-07-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department is taking to tackle wage stagnation.","Biography information for Angela Crawley","Angela Crawley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4352","4352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750907","2017-07-17","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, when she plans to publish her response to the Leveson Inquiry and its implementation.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4204","4204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750908","2017-07-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when he last met his counterpart in Saudi Arabia; and what issues were discussed at that meeting.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4178","4178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750909","2017-07-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment  he has made of the potential effect of jobcentre closures on claimants who have difficulty using PCs and the Internet.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4177","4177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750910","2017-07-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate  he has made of the additional caseload for Cofa Court Jobcentre in Coventry as a result of closure of the Torrington Avenue Jobcentre.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4179","4179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750911","2017-07-17","Department for International Trade","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, What the overall trade surplus was in (a) strawberries, (b) cream, (c) cheddar cheese and (d) gin in the last 12 months for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4180","4180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750912","2017-07-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how much his Department spent on new stocks of wines and spirits for hospitality purposes in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4258","4258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750913","2017-07-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how much his Department has spent on hospitality in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4259","4259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750914","2017-07-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his Russian counterpart on that country increasing its funding contribution to the Organisation for Security and Cooperation in Europe.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4237","4237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750915","2017-07-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his counterparts in (a) Armenia and (b) Azerbaijan on those states increasing their funding contributions to the Organisation for Security and Cooperation in Europe.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4236","4236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750916","2017-07-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how much funding the Government has provided to the Organisation for Security and Cooperation in Europe in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4287","4287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750917","2017-07-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his US counterpart on the US State Department’s planned financial reductions to bilateral assistance for Tunisia.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4235","4235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750918","2017-07-17","Ministry of Defence","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what stocks of (a) antiques, (b) paintings and (c) fine wines are held by his Department; if he will list any such assets sold over the last five years together with the sale proceeds from such transactions; and whether he plans to sell further such assets.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4192","4192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750919","2017-07-17","Ministry of Defence","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the value was of repayments his Department made to Government Hospitality for wines and spirits in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4193","4193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750920","2017-07-13","Ministry of Defence","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent meetings his Department has had with representatives from (a) BAE Systems and (b) Turkish Aerospace Industries on the development of the proposed TFX fighter aircraft.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4234","4234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750921","2017-07-13","Ministry of Defence","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Answer of 27 October 2016 to Question 49899, what assessment he has made of the implications of his Department’s policies of the announcement by the Russian defence ministry that it is halting cooperation with the US within the framework of the Memorandum on the Prevention of Incidents and Ensuring Air Safety in Syria.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4271","4271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750922","2017-07-17","Ministry of Defence","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the implications for his Department’s policies of the US and Russian Federation’s ceasefire deal in South-West Syria.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4260","4260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750923","2017-07-13","Ministry of Defence","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what funding has been (a) approved and (b) considered for the development of an additional unmanned air systems capability for the Queen Elizabeth class aircraft carriers.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4336","4336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750924","2017-07-13","Ministry of Defence","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which unmanned air systems (UAS) are planned to operate from the Queen Elizabeth class carriers from initial operational capability; and whether he intends to conduct a review of UAS that could be marinised and deployed on those carriers.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4337","4337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750925","2017-07-13","Ministry of Defence","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to ensure UK manufacturers will be able to continue to engage with EU defence research and development programmes after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4233","4233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750926","2017-07-17","Department of Health","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of drugs for the treatment and post-treatment needs of breast cancer patients contain lactose; and what provision is made for breast cancer patients who are intolerant or allergic to lactose.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4161","4161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750927","2017-07-13","Home Office","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many public engagements for which a media calling notice was issued were attended by a departmental Minister in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4302","4302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750928","2017-07-17","Home Office","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many Border Force officers are currently employed; and how many such officers she estimates will be required after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4342","4342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750929","2017-07-13","Department of Health","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many public engagements for which a media calling notice was issued were attended by a departmental Minister in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4301","4301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750930","2017-07-13","Scotland Office","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how many public engagements for which a media calling notice was issued were attended by a departmental Minister in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4304","4304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750931","2017-07-13","Department for Transport","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many public engagements for which a media calling notice was issued were attended by a departmental Minister in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4305","4305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750932","2017-07-13","Ministry of Justice","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many public engagements for which a media calling notice was issued were attended by a departmental Minister in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4303","4303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750933","2017-07-13","Ministry of Defence","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many public engagements for which a media calling notice was issued were attended by a departmental Minister in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4298","4298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750934","2017-07-13","Ministry of Defence","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he expects the Defence Fulfilment Centre in Donnington to be fully operational.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4291","4291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750935","2017-07-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many public engagements for which a media calling notice was issued were attended by a departmental Minister in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4300","4300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750936","2017-07-13","Department for Education","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many public engagements for which a media calling notice was issued were attended by a departmental Minister in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4299","4299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750937","2017-07-17","HM Treasury","2017-07-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many customs officers are currently employed by HM Revenue and Customs to carry out border activity in the UK; and how many such officers he estimates will be required for such activity after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4343","4343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750938","2017-07-13","Cabinet Office","2017-07-11","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what proportion of central Government purchasing has come from small and medium-sized enterprises in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4273","4273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750939","2017-07-17","HM Treasury","2017-07-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he plans to reduce rates of VAT charged on particular goods or services after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4321","4321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750940","2017-07-13","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how many public engagements for which a media calling notice was issued were attended by a departmental Minister in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4297","4297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750941","2017-07-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many public engagements for which a media calling notice was issued were attended by a departmental Minister in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4296","4296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750942","2017-07-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many public engagements for which a media calling notice was issued were attended by a departmental Minister in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4307","4307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750943","2017-07-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what plans he has to support the shale industry in Scotland; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4317","4317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750944","2017-07-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many public engagements for which a media calling notice was issued was attended by a departmental Minister in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4295","4295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750945","2017-07-13","Wales Office","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how many public engagements for which a media calling notice was issued were attended by a departmental Minister in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4306","4306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750946","2017-07-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what progress the Environment Agency has made in upgrading water pumps at Dock Bridge pumping station in Lytham.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4368","4368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750947","2017-07-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many unannounced onsite inspections the Environment Agency has conducted at Cuadrilla Resources’ shale gas site at Preston New Road since November 2016.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4365","4365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750948","2017-07-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many onsite inspections the Environment Agency has conducted at Cuadrilla Resources’ shale gas site at Preston New Road since November 2016.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4366","4366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750949","2017-07-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what progress the Environment Agency has made on dredging Liggard Brook to prevent flooding in Lytham.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4367","4367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750950","2017-07-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment his Department has made of fish stocks in the River Wyre.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4332","4332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750951","2017-07-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment his Department has made of fish stocks in the River Ribble.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4333","4333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750952","2017-07-13","Ministry of Defence","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans his Department has to upgrade and improve the accommodation for service personnel and their families at Weeton Army Camp.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4370","4370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750953","2017-07-13","Department for Education","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she has taken to ensure that schools in Fylde constituency benefit from an increase in funding under the new national funding formula.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4371","4371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750954","2017-07-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment the Environment Agency has made of the environmental effect of Cuadrilla Resources’ shale gas site at Preston New Road.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4364","4364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750955","2017-07-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many people have been prosecuted for angling illegally in Lancashire in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4362","4362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750956","2017-07-13","Department for Transport","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions officials of hisDepartment have had with Balfour Beatty on commercial flight operations at Blackpool Airport","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4373","4373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750957","2017-07-13","Department for Transport","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions officials of his Department have had with Balfour Beatty on proposals to sell Blackpool Airport.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4372","4372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750958","2017-07-17","Attorney General","2017-07-11","To ask the Attorney General, when the Serious Fraud Office investigation into the G4S electronic monitoring contract initiated in 2013 will be concluded; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4205","4205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750960","2017-07-17","Home Office","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if the Secretary of State will review the advice given to residents in tower blocks in the event of a fire.","Biography information for Tonia Antoniazzi","Tonia Antoniazzi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 900507","900507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/752241","2017-07-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether he has plans to bring forward legislative proposals to tackle abuses in the leasehold sector.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 900524","900524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/752242","2017-07-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what plans he has to increase the engagement of community organisations in decision making on Neighbourhood Plans.","Biography information for Mary Robinson","Mary Robinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 900525","900525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/752243","2017-07-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what reports he has received from local authorities of racist abuse by or towards electoral candidates during the 2017 General Election.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 900517","900517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/752244","2017-07-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what progress he is making on a devolved settlement for Yorkshire.","Biography information for John Grogan","John Grogan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 900519","900519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/752245","2017-07-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what progress the Government has made on building more homes.","Biography information for Edward Argar","Edward Argar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 900520","900520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/752246","2017-07-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps the Government is taking to support coastal communities.","Biography information for Sir Edward Leigh","Sir Edward Leigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 900523","900523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/752247","2017-07-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the trend in the number of new homes available for social rent since 2010.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 900522","900522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/753753","2017-07-19","Scotland Office","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what progress is being made on the Government's negotiations with the Scottish Government and local partners on delivering the next phase of City Deals in Scotland.","Biography information for Stephen Kerr","Stephen Kerr","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 900495","900495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/753754","2017-07-19","Scotland Office","2017-07-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what progress has been made on the Stirling and Clackmannanshire City Deal; and what further steps can be taken to accelerate that deal.","Biography information for Luke Graham","Luke Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 900498","900498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749980","2017-07-13","Department for International Trade","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what the cost to the public purse was of the Government's participation in the recent legal action brought by the Campaign Against Arms Trade.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3883","3883"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749981","2017-07-12","Attorney General","2017-07-10","To ask the Attorney General, how many contracts put out to tender by the Law Officers' Departments have been (a) cancelled and (b) re-tendered in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3997","3997"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749982","2017-07-12","Attorney General","2017-07-10","To ask the Attorney General, what proportion of public procurement contracts the Law Officers' Departments awarded through framework agreements in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4012","4012"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749983","2017-07-12","Attorney General","2017-07-10","To ask the Attorney General, what the average number of bids received for each contract put out to tender by the Law Officers' Departments was in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3982","3982"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749984","2017-07-12","Cabinet Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the average number of bids received for each contract put out to tender by his Department was in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3983","3983"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749985","2017-07-12","Cabinet Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 5 July 2017 to Question 1977, on Democratic Unionist Party, whether meetings between the Conservative Party and the Democratic Unionist Party which led to the agreement on confidence and supply took place in government buildings; whether other government resources were used during those meetings; whether any special advisers were present during any part of those meetings; and whether any civil servant was present during any part of those meetings.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3967","3967"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749986","2017-07-12","Cabinet Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps his Department is taking to monitor adherence to changes made to steel procurement guidelines in the last two years by (a) local authorities and (b) central Government Departments; and what assessment he has made of the ability of (i) local authorities and (ii) central Government Departments to adhere to those procurement guidelines.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3955","3955"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749987","2017-07-12","Cabinet Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment he has made of the effect on the amount of British steel used in UK procurement projects of introducing compulsory disclosure of certification and steel origin.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3954","3954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749988","2017-07-12","Cabinet Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what proportion of public procurement contracts his Department awarded through framework agreements in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4013","4013"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749989","2017-07-12","Cabinet Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the Answer of 3 November 2016 to Question 50641, the Answers of 4 November 2016 to Questions 50626, 50627, 50632 and 50636, the Answer of 8 November 2016 to Question 50633 and the Answer of 17 November 2016 to Question 50639, if he will make it his policy to record information on the level of British steel procured by each Government Department.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3948","3948"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749990","2017-07-12","Cabinet Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many contracts put out to tender by the Crown Commercial Service have been (a) cancelled and (b) re-tendered in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3949","3949"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749991","2017-07-12","Cabinet Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many and what proportion of people in Vale of Clwyd constituency worked in the public sector in each year for which data is available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3943","3943"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749992","2017-07-12","Cabinet Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many 18 to 25-year olds in Vale of Clwyd constituency were recorded (a) in the latest census estimate and (b) on the electoral register.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3944","3944"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749993","2017-07-12","Cabinet Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if the Government will develop a kite mark type certification system incorporating social and environmental standards for Government procurement of UK steel.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3947","3947"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749994","2017-07-13","Cabinet Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the (a) amount and (b) proportion of public procurement spent by the Government placed with small and medium-sized firms in Wales in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4097","4097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749995","2017-07-13","Cabinet Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many (a) women and (b) men working in Arfon constituency earn less than the national living wage.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4048","4048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749996","2017-07-13","Cabinet Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of household debt in (a) Arfon constituency and (b) Wales in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4047","4047"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749997","2017-07-13","Home Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will publish the third direction issued by the Prime Minister to the Intelligence Services Commissioner.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4052","4052"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749998","2017-07-12","Cabinet Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many contracts put out to tender by his Department have been (a) cancelled and (b) re-tendered in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3998","3998"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749999","2017-07-12","Cabinet Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people working in (a) Jarrow constituency, (b) South Tyneside, (c) the North East and (d) the UK earn less than £10 per hour.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3920","3920"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750000","2017-07-13","Cabinet Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to his oral contribution of 26 June 2017, Official Report, column 348, if he will list the public sector buildings which are now undergoing checks.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3903","3903"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750001","2017-07-12","Cabinet Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will provide a list of ministerial residences and their authorised occupants.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3866","3866"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750002","2017-07-12","Cabinet Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when he plans to publish his Department's Annual Report and Accounts 2016-17.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3867","3867"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750003","2017-07-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to his oral contribution of 5 July 2017, Official Report, column 1156, on revenue-raising powers for mayors, who will disburse the new funding referred; how that funding will be disbursed; and whether that funding will be available to all local authorities across England.","Biography information for Heidi Allen","Heidi Allen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3826","3826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750004","2017-07-12","Cabinet Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what grant in aid was awarded to the trustees of Chequers in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3868","3868"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750005","2017-07-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what grant in aid was awarded to the trustees of Chevening in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3869","3869"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750006","2017-07-12","HM Treasury","2017-07-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what grant in aid was awarded to the trustees of Dorneywood in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3870","3870"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750007","2017-07-12","Northern Ireland Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, pursuant to the Answer of 5 July 2017 to Question 2270, on political parties: finance, for what reasons the Government chose 1 July 2017 as the start date.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3768","3768"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750008","2017-07-12","Northern Ireland Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, pursuant to the Answer of 5 July 2017 to Question 2270, on political parties: finance, when the Government announced the 1 July 2017 start date.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3769","3769"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750009","2017-07-13","Cabinet Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when he plans to respond to Question 2304, tabled by the hon. Member for Croydon North on 30 June 2017.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3783","3783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750010","2017-07-13","HM Treasury","2017-07-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 5 July 2017 to Question 2292, whether he plans to publish the results of the research on foreign exchange (a) separately from the Government's response to the consultation, (b) in conjunction with the Government's response to the consultation or (c) not at all; if he will bring forward amendments to the draft Payment Services regulations as a result of the findings; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3784","3784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750011","2017-07-13","HM Treasury","2017-07-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the number and value of contracts awarded by his Department was to Deloitte in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3754","3754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750012","2017-07-13","HM Treasury","2017-07-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of the recent rise in consumer price index on household savings.","Biography information for Kirsty Blackman","Kirsty Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3803","3803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750013","2017-07-13","HM Treasury","2017-07-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what forecast he has mad of the change in the level of real-terms pay for the 2017-18 financial year.","Biography information for Kirsty Blackman","Kirsty Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3810","3810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750014","2017-07-12","HM Treasury","2017-07-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of the recent rise in the consumer price index on the level of household disposable income.","Biography information for Kirsty Blackman","Kirsty Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3842","3842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750015","2017-07-13","HM Treasury","2017-07-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many times the employment status service tool on HM Revenue and Customs' website has been used since its public beta launch; and what proportion of that use has resulted in the client being informed that the (a) intermediaries legislation applies, (b) intermediaries legislation does not apply and (c) status cannot be determined.","Biography information for Kirsty Blackman","Kirsty Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3817","3817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750016","2017-07-12","HM Treasury","2017-07-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether it is the Government's policy that new claims for employer supported childcare vouchers will not be accepted from April 2018.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3728","3728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750017","2017-07-12","HM Treasury","2017-07-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether it is the Government's policy that families with more than two children who make new claims for universal credit will no longer be able to claim child tax credit from November 2018.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3729","3729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750018","2017-07-12","HM Treasury","2017-07-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he expects a new double taxation treaty with Malawi to be signed.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3735","3735"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750019","2017-07-12","HM Treasury","2017-07-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether it is his policy to conclude a revised double taxation treaty with Malawi by July 2017.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3736","3736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750020","2017-07-12","HM Treasury","2017-07-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what progress has been made in negotiating a new double taxation treaty with Malawi since January 2017.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3737","3737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750021","2017-07-12","HM Treasury","2017-07-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will take steps to ensure the new double taxation treaty with Malawi will support Malawi's development.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3738","3738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750022","2017-07-12","HM Treasury","2017-07-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many times he has visited Dorneywood since becoming Chancellor of the Exchequer.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3862","3862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750023","2017-07-13","HM Treasury","2017-07-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of the public sector pay gap on the average levels of household pay in the last five years.","Biography information for Kirsty Blackman","Kirsty Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3895","3895"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750024","2017-07-13","HM Treasury","2017-07-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the total amount of tax relief paid by higher rate taxpayers who had contributed to their pensions in that year was in the most recent year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3897","3897"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750025","2017-07-13","HM Treasury","2017-07-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether HM Revenue and Customs has (a) completed or (b) extended the phased exit from the Aspire contract.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4057","4057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750026","2017-07-13","HM Treasury","2017-07-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, by what date he expects HM Revenue and Customs to have concluded its investigation into Hermes.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4056","4056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750027","2017-07-13","HM Treasury","2017-07-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when his Department notified the Welsh Government that the entire debt relating to the Circuit of Wales project could be classified against the Welsh Government's capital spending.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4039","4039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750028","2017-07-13","HM Treasury","2017-07-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what representations his Department has received from the Welsh Government on the Circuit of Wales project.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4031","4031"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750029","2017-07-13","HM Treasury","2017-07-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when the Welsh Government first discussed the balance sheet treatment of debt relating to the Circuit of Wales project with his Department.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4038","4038"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750030","2017-07-12","HM Treasury","2017-07-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans the Government has to remove the public sector pay cap during the course of the current Parliament.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3921","3921"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750031","2017-07-12","HM Treasury","2017-07-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will list by country where stocks of gilts are held by overseas investors and foreign central banks; and how much and what proportion of such stocks are held in different countries.","Biography information for Neil O'Brien","Neil O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3931","3931"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750032","2017-07-12","HM Treasury","2017-07-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 4 July 2017 to Question 1597, whether the Secretary of State for Scotland has made representations during those discussions for Scotland to receive additional funding as a result of the confidence and supply agreement between the Government and the Democratic Unionist Party.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3924","3924"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750033","2017-07-12","HM Treasury","2017-07-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will list by country flows of interest payments on UK central Government debt held by overseas investors and foreign central banks.","Biography information for Neil O'Brien","Neil O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3932","3932"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750034","2017-07-12","HM Treasury","2017-07-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect on the NHS of changes to the IR35 regulations; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3933","3933"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750035","2017-07-12","HM Treasury","2017-07-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many contracts exist between HM Revenue and Customs and (a) KPMG, (b) Ernst & Young, (c) Deloitte and (d) PwC; and what the value is of each such contract.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4094","4094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750036","2017-07-12","HM Treasury","2017-07-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what his policy is on making it mandatory for all pension providers to provide relevant data to pensions dashboards.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4093","4093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750037","2017-07-12","HM Treasury","2017-07-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many contracts put out to tender by his Department have been (a) cancelled and (b) re-tendered in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4010","4010"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750038","2017-07-12","HM Treasury","2017-07-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what proportion of public procurement contracts his Department awarded through framework agreements in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4025","4025"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750039","2017-07-12","HM Treasury","2017-07-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the average number of bids received for each contract put out to tender by his Department was in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3995","3995"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750040","2017-07-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the average number of bids received for each contract put out to tender by his Department was in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3984","3984"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750041","2017-07-12","Home Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 27 June 2017 to Question 1333, how many fire pumps were stationed in the London Borough of (a) Southwark and (b) Lambeth in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3940","3940"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750042","2017-07-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what proportion of public procurement contracts his Department awarded through framework agreements in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4014","4014"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750043","2017-07-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he plans to respond to representations received for the consultation on the housing white paper which closed on 2 May 2017.","Biography information for Sir Gary Streeter","Mr Gary Streeter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3963","3963"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750044","2017-07-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what number and proportion of housing cladding samples have been tested within 24 hours of receipt.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4089","4089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750045","2017-07-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, by what date all the non-ACM housing cladding samples received to date will be tested.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4090","4090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750046","2017-07-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, for what reasons non-ACM housing cladding samples received by his Department have not yet been tested.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4091","4091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750047","2017-07-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many housing cladding samples of all types the Government has received; and how many such samples have been tested to date.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4092","4092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750048","2017-07-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to the contribution of Lord Ahmad of Wimbledon of 23 March 2015 to proceedings on the Selective Licensing of Houses (Additional Conditions) (England) Order 2015, Official Report, HL Deb, column 331, whether the review of the impact of those changes 18 months after their introduction has been undertaken; and if he will place a copy of that review in the Library.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4098","4098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750049","2017-07-12","Department of Health","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many elderly people Southampton City Council supports with adult social care.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4119","4119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750050","2017-07-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the annual financial cost of adult social care was to Southampton City Council in the last seven years.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4120","4120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750051","2017-07-12","Department for Education","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many young people Southampton City Council supports for child services.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4121","4121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750052","2017-07-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the annual financial cost was to Southampton City Council of supporting child services in the last seven years.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4122","4122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750053","2017-07-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of whether additional costs to local authorities for fire prevention measures in tower blocks will reduce expenditure on the maintenance of other social housing.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3909","3909"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750054","2017-07-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of changes in local authority funding on the capacity of (a) South Tyneside and (b) Gateshead local authority to deliver essential services.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3935","3935"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750055","2017-07-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many meetings his Department has had with representatives of house building companies on the introduction of fire sprinklers in each year for which information is available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3911","3911"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750056","2017-07-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many building control officers were employed in each local authority area in (a) 2010 and (b) the latest year for which information is available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3912","3912"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750057","2017-07-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the unit costs of retrofitting sprinkler fire protection in Callow Towers high rise flats in Sheffield.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3913","3913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750058","2017-07-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many contracts put out to tender by his Department have been (a) cancelled and (b) re-tendered in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3999","3999"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750059","2017-07-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what information his Department holds on the number of residential tower blocks which are (a) currently being built and (b) due to start construction soon.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3904","3904"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750060","2017-07-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of recommending a moratorium on the construction of new residential tower blocks until the recommendations of the inquiry into the Grenfell Tower fire have been published.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3905","3905"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750061","2017-07-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to his oral contribution of 26 June 2017, Official Report, column 348, if he will list the 15 buildings that are part of the Government estate that require further investigation.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3902","3902"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750062","2017-07-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when his Department plans to respond to the Casey Review into opportunity and integration.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3859","3859"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750063","2017-07-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many disabled people have waited for longer than six months for adaptions to their home funded by Disability Facilities Grants in England in each of the last seven years.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3823","3823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750064","2017-07-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what recent meetings he has attended on leasehold reform.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3832","3832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750065","2017-07-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will make it compulsory for a declaration of disability to feature on local authority application forms for (a) discretionary housing and (b) hardship payment.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3820","3820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750066","2017-07-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many local authorities in England are Disability Confident.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3821","3821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750067","2017-07-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether he plans to increase funding for the Disabled Facilities Grant.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3822","3822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750068","2017-07-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when his Department plans to publish its social integration strategy; and what assessment that strategy will make of the effect of youth full-time social action on social integration.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3837","3837"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750069","2017-07-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the proportion of leasehold properties affected by contracts specifying the periodic doubling of ground rent.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3834","3834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750070","2017-07-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the proportion of help to buy properties which are (a) leasehold and (b) freehold.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3833","3833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750071","2017-07-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many planning appeals have been made on affordable housing allocations in each of the last 10 years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3831","3831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750072","2017-07-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the effect of borough-wide licensing schemes on the value of buy-to-rent properties in (a) London and (b) each London borough.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3795","3795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750073","2017-07-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the adequacy of insurance cover held by Kensington and Chelsea Council to meet the costs of the consequences of the Grenfell Tower fire; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Desmond Swayne","Sir Desmond Swayne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3813","3813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750074","2017-07-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many disabled people are employed (a) full-time and (b) part-time by local authorities in England.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3805","3805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750075","2017-07-13","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether she has made an assessment of the findings of the Fixed Odds Betting Terminals All Party Parliamentary Group Inquiry report, published on 31 January 2017.","Biography information for Patricia Gibson","Patricia Gibson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3806","3806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750076","2017-07-12","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, if she will take steps to record how many young people are engaged in full-time social action; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3838","3838"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750077","2017-07-13","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, when the Review of Stakes and Prizes will be published.","Biography information for Patricia Gibson","Patricia Gibson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3756","3756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750078","2017-07-13","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of the fitness for purpose of age certification for videogames.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3779","3779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750079","2017-07-13","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of the penalties for (a) parents or guardians and (b) retailers who knowingly provide videogames to children who are younger than the recommended age rating.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3780","3780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750080","2017-07-13","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions her Department has had with BT and Openreach on the location of unlit fibre and ducting laid across the UK.","Biography information for Stephen Kerr","Stephen Kerr","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3751","3751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750081","2017-07-13","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions her Department has had with BT and Openreach on pilot projects to utilise fibre laid above ground via existing utility poles, especially in rural areas of Scotland.","Biography information for Stephen Kerr","Stephen Kerr","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3752","3752"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750082","2017-07-13","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what recent discussions she has had with the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union on the potential benefits for UK performers touring abroad of retaining membership of the European Health Insurance Card system after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3818","3818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750083","2017-07-13","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether the Government plans to re-join Eurimages.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3819","3819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750084","2017-07-13","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps she is taking to ensure the UK's continued participation in the Sectoral Social Dialogue Committees on (a) live performance and (b) audio-visual after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3824","3824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750085","2017-07-13","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of the potential effect on the travelling of orchestras and orchestral performers of new visa arrangements for people entering the UK from the EU after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3825","3825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750086","2017-07-12","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of the (a) time taken and (b) costs paid by small businesses to access British Telecom ducts under physical infrastructure access regulations.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3871","3871"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750087","2017-07-12","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether funding for the creative industries will remain at the same level as currently received from Creative Europe in the event that the UK ceases paying into Creative Europe when the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3959","3959"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750088","2017-07-13","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what recent discussions she has had with representatives of the performing arts industry on diversity and social mobility of performers in that industry.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4051","4051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750089","2017-07-12","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what recent assessment she has made of the capacity of smaller charities to fundraise.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4087","4087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750090","2017-07-12","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps she is taking to support fundraising mentoring in the charitable sector.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4088","4088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750091","2017-07-12","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how many contracts put out to tender by her Department have been (a) cancelled and (b) re-tendered in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4000","4000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750092","2017-07-12","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what proportion of public procurement contracts her Department awarded through framework agreements in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4015","4015"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750093","2017-07-12","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what the average number of bids received for each contract put out to tender by her Department was in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3985","3985"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750094","2017-07-12","Ministry of Defence","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what proportion of public procurement contracts his Department awarded through framework agreements in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4016","4016"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750095","2017-07-12","Ministry of Defence","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many contracts put out to tender by his Department have been (a) cancelled and (b) re-tendered in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4001","4001"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750096","2017-07-12","Ministry of Defence","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what forms of military support the UK has given to the Syrian Democratic Forces who are taking part in the ground assault against Daesh in Raqqa.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3972","3972"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750097","2017-07-12","Ministry of Defence","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that the activities of its military partners in the counter-Daesh offensive in Syria are consistent with international laws aimed at protecting civilians in armed conflicts.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3973","3973"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750098","2017-07-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, which governing entity or entities the Government expects will take control of Raqqa after the removal of Daesh from that city; and what steps the Government is taking to prevent the creation of a political vacuum in that city.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3974","3974"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750099","2017-07-12","Ministry of Defence","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that its prime contractors adhere to the Government's procurement practices and guidelines set out for the procurement of UK steel.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3946","3946"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750100","2017-07-12","Ministry of Defence","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the average number of bids received for each contract put out to tender by his Department was in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3986","3986"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750101","2017-07-13","Ministry of Defence","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans he has to visit cadet detachments in Northern Ireland in the current calendar year.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3896","3896"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750102","2017-07-12","Department for Education","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her policy is on offering free breakfasts for all primary school children.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3745","3745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750103","2017-07-12","Department for Education","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions she has had with (a) cultural and (b) scientific institutions on the introduction of a new curriculum fund.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3775","3775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750104","2017-07-13","Department for Education","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what information her Department holds on the average wage paid to nursery nurses in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3757","3757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750105","2017-07-13","Department for Education","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what qualifications are held by nursery nurses at each employment level.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3758","3758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750106","2017-07-13","Department for Education","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many local authorities have made representation to her Department on their ability to deliver 30 hours free childcare to all applicable children from September 2017.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3759","3759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750107","2017-07-13","Department for Education","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what guidance her Department has given to nurseries and childcare providers on charging for (a) meals, (b) activities, (c) nappies and (d) any other items outwith the 30 free hours of childcare provided from September 2017.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3760","3760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750108","2017-07-12","Department for Education","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will consider setting a lower interest rate for student loans.","Biography information for Stephen Hammond","Stephen Hammond","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3771","3771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750109","2017-07-13","Department for Education","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much of her Department's budget allocated to 16 to 19-year old education was reallocated to other budgets in the financial years (a) 2014-15, (b) 2015-16 and (c) 2016-17.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3811","3811"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750110","2017-07-13","Department for Education","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what progress she has made on her plans to abolish SATs at Key Stage 1; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen McPartland","Stephen McPartland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3891","3891"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750111","2017-07-12","Department for Education","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what information her Department holds on the average salary for a graduate from a Russell group university.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4107","4107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750112","2017-07-12","Department for Education","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of the proportion of jobs in the UK economy that will require a degree level education in the next 10 years.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4109","4109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750113","2017-07-12","Department for Education","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many teach second teachers there are in (a) England, (b) the South East and (c) Southampton.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4126","4126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750114","2017-07-12","Department for Education","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what information her Department holds on the average salary for a university graduate; and what that figure is for people who did not attend university.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4108","4108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750115","2017-07-12","Department for Education","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children were in good or outstanding schools in (a) England, (b) the South East and (c) Southampton in each of the last seven years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4123","4123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750116","2017-07-12","Department for Education","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many STEM teachers there are in (a) England, (b) the South East and (c) Southampton.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4124","4124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750117","2017-07-12","Department for Education","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many teach first teachers there are in (a) England, (b) the South East and (c) Southampton.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4125","4125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750118","2017-07-12","Department for Education","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent discussions she has had with headteachers in (a) Jarrow constituency, (b) South Tyneside local authority area and (c) Gateshead local authority area on (i) school funding and (ii) the effect of the new school funding formula on schools in those areas.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3919","3919"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750119","2017-07-12","Department for Education","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the potential effect of the proposed school funding formula on the number of teaching posts in (a) Jarrow constituency, (b) South Tyneside, (c) the North East and (d) the UK.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3917","3917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750120","2017-07-12","Department for Education","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many contracts put out to tender by her Department have been (a) cancelled and (b) re-tendered in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4002","4002"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750121","2017-07-12","Department for Education","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of public procurement contracts her Department awarded through framework agreements in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4017","4017"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750122","2017-07-12","Department for Education","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the average number of bids received for each contract put out to tender by her Department was in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3987","3987"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750123","2017-07-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the average number of bids received for each contract put out to tender by his Department was in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3988","3988"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750124","2017-07-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what proportion of public procurement contracts his Department awarded through framework agreements in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4018","4018"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750125","2017-07-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many contracts put out to tender by his Department have been (a) cancelled and (b) re-tendered in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4003","4003"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750126","2017-07-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether it is the Government's policy to (a) maintain or (b) increase the proportion of UK agricultural funding allocated to Scotland under the system that replaces the EU Common Agricultural Policy.","Biography information for Ian Blackford","Ian Blackford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3964","3964"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750127","2017-07-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make it his policy that farmers and crofters in Scotland will receive at least the same level of support after the UK leaves the EU as they do at present.","Biography information for Ian Blackford","Ian Blackford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3966","3966"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750128","2017-07-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make it his policy to guarantee funding for the Less Favoured Area Support Scheme for 2019.","Biography information for Ian Blackford","Ian Blackford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3965","3965"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750129","2017-07-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many trees have been planted in public spaces in the last seven years.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4117","4117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750130","2017-07-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many trees have been planted in Southampton in the last seven years.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4118","4118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750131","2017-07-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many consignments of dogs were exported from the UK to (a) EU and (b) non-EU countries in 2016.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3804","3804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750132","2017-07-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to meet its air quality targets by supporting people from low-income backgrounds to buy (a) hybrid and (b) electric vehicles.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","Mr William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3770","3770"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750133","2017-07-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many local authorities have declared an air quality management area.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3733","3733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750134","2017-07-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether all Overseas Territories and Crown Dependencies have central registers of beneficial ownership in operation; and what plans he has to make those registers public.","Biography information for Dame Margaret Hodge","Dame Margaret Hodge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3734","3734"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750135","2017-07-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the legal minimum wage is in the British Indian Ocean Territory.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3766","3766"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750136","2017-07-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to his Department's freedom of information case FOI2007-15 on legal costs and Chagos Islands, what additional cost to the public purse has been incurred in the Bancoult, Chagos Refugee Group and Chagos Islanders case since 4 February 2015.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3792","3792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750137","2017-07-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, which countries that are allies of the UK are not governed through some form of parliamentary democracy.","Biography information for Christian Matheson","Christian Matheson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3844","3844"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750138","2017-07-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to the Government of India on behalf of the six ex-Army personnel being held in Chennai Jail.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3900","3900"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750139","2017-07-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the annual running costs of No. 1 Carlton Gardens were in each of the last seven years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3849","3849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750140","2017-07-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has received on the alleged genocide in West Papua.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3857","3857"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750141","2017-07-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when he last met his Iraqi counterpart; and what issues were discussed at that meeting.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3858","3858"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750142","2017-07-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his counterpart in El Salvador on potential reform of abortion laws in that country.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4027","4027"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750143","2017-07-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his counterparts in the Bahrain Government on the treatment of (a) Ebtisam Al-Sayegh and (b) Mohammed Khalil al Shakouri.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4041","4041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750144","2017-07-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when he last met his Yemeni counterpart.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4065","4065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750145","2017-07-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to the Government of Saudi Arabia on the situation in Yemen.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4066","4066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750146","2017-07-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when he last met his Qatari counterpart; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4067","4067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750147","2017-07-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when he plans to appoint a new Special Envoy for Yemen.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4068","4068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750148","2017-07-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many Ambassadorial posts were vacant on 1 July 2017.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4069","4069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750149","2017-07-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many contracts put out to tender by his Department have been (a) cancelled and (b) re-tendered in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4004","4004"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750150","2017-07-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what proportion of public procurement contracts his Department awarded through framework agreements in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4019","4019"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750151","2017-07-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the average number of bids received for each contract put out to tender by his Department was in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3989","3989"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750152","2017-07-12","Department of Health","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average number of bids received for each contract put out to tender by his Department was in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3990","3990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750153","2017-07-12","Department of Health","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of public procurement contracts his Department awarded through framework agreements in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4020","4020"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750154","2017-07-12","Department of Health","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many contracts put out to tender by his Department have been (a) cancelled and (b) re-tendered in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4005","4005"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750155","2017-07-12","Department of Health","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the timeline is for national procurement of non-invasive prenatal testing for Down's syndrome as recommended by the National Screening Committee in November 2016.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3971","3971"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750156","2017-07-12","Department of Health","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when non-invasive prenatal testing for Down's syndrome as recommended by the National Screening Committee in November 2016 will be made available through the NHS.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3970","3970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750157","2017-07-12","Department of Health","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress his Department has made on developing a national strategy for children of alcoholics.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3976","3976"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750158","2017-07-12","Department of Health","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to improve the recruitment and retention of nurses.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4103","4103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750159","2017-07-12","Department of Health","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what financial support is offered to nursing students.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4104","4104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750160","2017-07-12","Department of Health","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what financial support is offered to nursing students with dependents.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4105","4105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750161","2017-07-12","Department of Health","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many nurses from (a) EU, (b) non-EU and (c) commonwealth countries are employed by the NHS; and how those numbers have changed in the last seven years.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4106","4106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750162","2017-07-12","Department of Health","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many nurses joined the workforce at Southampton General Hospital in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4102","4102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750163","2017-07-13","Department of Health","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has carried out to ensure that the proposed £1,000 financial assistance offered to GP practices which accept the full repairing lease contract will be sufficient to cover the legal and survey work associated with those leases.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4033","4033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750164","2017-07-13","Department of Health","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to review the Carr-Hill funding formula for GP practices with atypical populations.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4034","4034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750165","2017-07-13","Department of Health","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect of increased service charges on GP surgeries which lease their buildings from NHS Property Services.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4035","4035"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750166","2017-07-13","Department of Health","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect on GP funding of the proposed full repairing leases offered to GP surgeries.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4036","4036"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750167","2017-07-13","Department of Health","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with the leaders of the (a) review of neonatal services and (b) Maternity Transformation Programme to ensure that their work plans are co-ordinated to ensure continuity of care for mothers whose babies are admitted to neonatal care.","Biography information for Jack Dromey","Jack Dromey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4054","4054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750168","2017-07-13","Department of Health","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the remit is of the review of neonatal services; and whether that remit includes the tariff for (a) neonatal and (b) transitional care.","Biography information for Jack Dromey","Jack Dromey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4053","4053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750169","2017-07-12","Department of Health","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what changes have been made to the monitoring guidance on safety of (a) domestic and (b) imported blood products in each year since guidance was introduced.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3915","3915"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750170","2017-07-12","Department of Health","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people have died as a result of contaminated blood products in each Parliamentary constituency in each of the last 30 years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3914","3914"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750171","2017-07-12","Department of Health","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when his Department plans to publish the (a) consultation on improving social care and (b) green paper on social care funding.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3910","3910"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750172","2017-07-13","Department of Health","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, to what extent the Maternity Transformation Programme is considering the tariff for transitional care as part of its review of the maternity tariff.","Biography information for Jack Dromey","Jack Dromey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4055","4055"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750173","2017-07-13","Department of Health","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make it his policy to introduce mandatory screening for severe combined immunodeficiency disorder at birth.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3908","3908"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750174","2017-07-12","Department of Health","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps the Government is taking to (a) publicise adolescent mental health issues on the internet and (b) support the prevention of adolescent mental health issues arising from social media.","Biography information for Alex Chalk","Alex Chalk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3922","3922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750175","2017-07-13","Cabinet Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people, broken down by age, with severe combined immunodeficiency disorder have died from that condition in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3907","3907"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750176","2017-07-13","Department of Health","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, on what basis the deadline of October 2017 has been set for GP surgeries to agree full repairing leases with NHS Property Services.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4037","4037"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750177","2017-07-12","Department of Health","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department plans to hold a public inquiry into contaminated blood products.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3852","3852"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750178","2017-07-13","Department of Health","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what meetings he had on his visit to Houston, Texas in February 2017; and what the (a) purpose and (b) cost to the public purse was of those meetings.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3830","3830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750179","2017-07-13","Department of Health","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, (a) how many officials in his Department received a performance-related pay bonus and (b) what the cost of those bonuses was to the public purse in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3828","3828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750180","2017-07-13","Department of Health","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he plans to renew the NHS Outcomes Framework for 2017-18.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3827","3827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750181","2017-07-12","Department of Health","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what support his Department gives to NHS trusts and hospitals to improve the recruitment and retention of (a) maternity unit, (b) paediatric unit and (c) other hospital staff.","Biography information for Trudy Harrison","Trudy Harrison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3836","3836"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750182","2017-07-13","Department of Health","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many healthcare assistants were employed by the NHS in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3906","3906"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750183","2017-07-13","Department of Health","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he has received representations from members of the public on the future of Professor Malone Lee's Urology Clinic at the Whittington Hospital.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3885","3885"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750184","2017-07-13","Department of Health","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what meetings the Parliamentary under-Secretary of State had during his visit to the Arab Health Conference in Dubai; and what the (a) purpose and (b) cost to the public purse was of those meetings.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3886","3886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750185","2017-07-13","Department of Health","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will discuss with the Chancellor of the Exchequer and the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union making available funds no longer required for EU budget payments from 2019-20 for projects exclusively to support disabled people.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3785","3785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750186","2017-07-13","Department of Health","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress he is making on implementing NHS sustainability and transformation plans.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3788","3788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750187","2017-07-13","Department of Health","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will publish the full list of NHS estates under consideration for sale under the recommendations of the Naylor Review, the estimated value of each such site and a breakdown of the location of those sites; and whether each such site is currently being used for patient care.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3789","3789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750188","2017-07-12","Department of Health","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many irritable bowel disease specialist nurses have been employed by the NHS in England in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3750","3750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750189","2017-07-12","Department for Education","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what support through the NHS, social care and voluntary sector her Department provides for child and young person carers helping parents with chronic and terminal illness.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3741","3741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750190","2017-07-12","Home Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the extension of the Syrian Vulnerable Persons Resettlement scheme will include people leaving Syria of Palestinian nationality and origin; and whether she has had discussions with the United Nations Relief and Works Agency on the inclusion of such people.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3739","3739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750191","2017-07-12","Home Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the number of police officers referred to the National Police Federation Welfare Support Programme in each year from 2010 to date.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3740","3740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750192","2017-07-12","Home Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Government's policy paper, entitled Safeguarding the position of EU citizens in the UK and UK nationals in the EU, published on 26 June 2017, whether EU citizens with indefinite leave to remain in the UK will need to reapply for settled status once the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Nicky Morgan","Nicky Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3748","3748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750193","2017-07-12","Home Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Answer of 16 December 2016 to Question 56787, whether the document issued in exercise of her powers under the Road Traffic Act 1988 to approve a breath-testing device was intended to carry legislative weight.","Biography information for Ian Blackford","Ian Blackford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3749","3749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750194","2017-07-12","Home Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 7 July 2017 to Question 2344, on drugs: Greater Manchester, what discussions she has had with Greater Manchester Police on the availability of the new crystalised form of the drug Spice in that area, and not generally about synthetic cannabinoids, such as those found in Spice.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3767","3767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750195","2017-07-13","Home Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many police forces have (a) made applications to her Department for additional funding and (b) been granted funding from the Police Special Grant in (i) 2015, (ii) 2016 and (iii) 2017.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3755","3755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750196","2017-07-13","Home Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will publish, for each fire and rescue service in England, the number of fire and rescue service officers who have been dedicated to inspecting and auditing buildings under the Regulatory Reform (Fire Safety) Order 2005 in (a) 2005-06, (b) 2006-07, (c) 2007-08, (d) 2008-09, (e) 2009-10, (f) 2010-11, (g) 2011-12, (h) 2012-13, (i) 2013-14, (j) 2014-15 and (k) 2015-16.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3761","3761"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750197","2017-07-13","Home Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will publish the number of fire and rescue service officers who have been dedicated to inspecting and auditing buildings under the Regulatory Reform (Fire Safety) Order 2005 in (a) 2005-06, (b) 2006-07, (c) 2007-08, (d) 2008-09, (e) 2009-10, (f) 2010-11, (g) 2011-12, (h) 2012-13, (i) 2013-14, (j) 2014-15 and (k) 2015-16.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3762","3762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750198","2017-07-13","Home Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications for permanent residence are processed each day by her Department.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3763","3763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750199","2017-07-13","Home Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate her Department has made of the number of days sickness absence for police officers in each force in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3764","3764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750200","2017-07-13","Home Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what her target is for the maximum amount of time asylum seekers spend in initial accommodation; and in what proportion of cases that target has been met since May 2015.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3765","3765"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750201","2017-07-13","Home Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate her Department has made of the proportion of the police effort in response to the Manchester terrorist attack funded by the ring-fenced counter-terrorism budget; and what the total cost to Greater Manchester Police was of the response to that attack.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3809","3809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750202","2017-07-13","Home Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many technical inspectors were employed by each fire authority in each year since 2004.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3796","3796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750203","2017-07-13","Home Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many on-site inspectors were employed in each fire authority in each year since 2004.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3797","3797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750204","2017-07-13","Cabinet Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, in what ways the National Cyber Security Centre interacts with Government Departments; and whether that Centre meets regularly with those Departments.","Biography information for Nick Thomas-Symonds","Nick Thomas-Symonds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3798","3798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750205","2017-07-13","Cabinet Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what plans the National Cyber Security Centre has to help universities (a) fight organised cyber-crime and (b) further prevent a cyber-attack.","Biography information for Nick Thomas-Symonds","Nick Thomas-Symonds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3799","3799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750206","2017-07-13","Home Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department has taken to help the public to protect themselves against the threat of cyber-crime.","Biography information for Nick Thomas-Symonds","Nick Thomas-Symonds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3800","3800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750207","2017-07-13","Cabinet Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will ensure that regular reviews of the National Cyber Security Centre take place and the outcomes of those reviews are placed in the Library.","Biography information for Nick Thomas-Symonds","Nick Thomas-Symonds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3801","3801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750208","2017-07-13","Cabinet Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what plans he has to measure the effectiveness of the National Cyber Security Centre; and whether any targets have been set by his Department.","Biography information for Nick Thomas-Symonds","Nick Thomas-Symonds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3802","3802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750209","2017-07-13","Home Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, for what reason the phoneline provided by UK Visas and Immigration for people to make inquiries about the status of their visa application is charged at £1.37 per minute on top of network charges; and what the average length of time is for people who call the line to wait on hold.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3890","3890"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750210","2017-07-17","Cabinet Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how the National Crime Agency, the National Cyber Security Centre and other relevant agencies are identifying and helping to address the cyber security vulnerabilities of third sector health providers.","Biography information for Tommy Sheppard","Tommy Sheppard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3901","3901"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750211","2017-07-13","Home Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many times each police force has declared a critical incident due to the volume of calls it is receiving in each year from 2010 to date.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3893","3893"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750212","2017-07-12","Home Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if her Department will assess the potential merits of people widowed to police officers prior to April 2015 being entitled to a widow's pension in the event of their re-marriage.","Biography information for Andrew Bridgen","Andrew Bridgen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3835","3835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750213","2017-07-12","Home Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what funding her Department plans to make available for policy measures to promote alternative narratives to extremism in 2016-17, 2017-18 and 2018-19.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3848","3848"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750214","2017-07-13","Home Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 3 July 2017 to Question 1480, on human trafficking, if she will place in the Library a copy of the data used by the National Crime Agency in making its assessment of the nature and scale of modern slavery in the UK.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3816","3816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750215","2017-07-12","Home Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the number of UK citizens or residents who have fought alongside ISIS; and how many have now returned to the UK.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3851","3851"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750216","2017-07-12","Home Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 10 July 2017 to Question 2980, if she will take steps to assist people who have changed their name through marriage to obtain a change of name in the passport they hold from another country when that person holds dual nationality; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3923","3923"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750217","2017-07-13","Home Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, in what proportion of settlement visa application cases for which a 10-day priority service has been paid for a decision has been made within 10 days in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3889","3889"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750218","2017-07-13","Home Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people were transported to a place of safety under the Mental Health Act 1983 by (a) ambulance and (b) police vehicle in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4044","4044"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750219","2017-07-13","Home Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, on what date she plans to respond to the recommendation of the Police Pay Review Body for 2017-18.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4045","4045"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750220","2017-07-13","Home Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 10 July 2017 to Question 2790, on immigration: EU nationals, what criteria for (a) conduct and (b) criminality will be employed when assessing applications for settled status by non-UK EU citizens living in the UK.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4042","4042"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750221","2017-07-12","Home Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people were removed from the UK as a result of representations made by their spouse in 2016.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4072","4072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750222","2017-07-12","Home Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she plans to use any current or ex-Ministry of Defence properties as accommodation for asylum seekers under the Compass contracts; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4084","4084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750223","2017-07-12","Home Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what financial support the UK gave (a) Europol and (b) Interpol in 2016-17.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4080","4080"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750224","2017-07-12","Home Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the final financial package given to Justice Goddard was in respect of her chairing of the Independent Inquiry into Child Sexual Abuse.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4081","4081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750225","2017-07-12","Home Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many and which detention centres she has visited since her appointment.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4082","4082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750226","2017-07-12","Cabinet Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many overseas students were in the UK on 1 June 2017; and how many such students there were by country of origin.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4073","4073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750227","2017-07-12","Home Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what additional support she plans to make available to UK Visas and Immigration to deal with the issue of EU nationals in the UK.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4079","4079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750228","2017-07-12","Home Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people are currently employed at UK Visas and Immigration.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4070","4070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750229","2017-07-12","Home Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications for settlement visas for spouses were refused in 2016.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4071","4071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750230","2017-07-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what discussions the Government has had with the Scottish Government about the Government's proposals to adopt the International Holocaust Remembrance Alliance definition of anti-Semitism.","Biography information for Paul Masterton","Paul Masterton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3945","3945"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750231","2017-07-12","Home Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what initial accommodation centres are currently being used under the Compass asylum accommodation contracts.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3975","3975"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750232","2017-07-12","Home Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many contracts put out to tender by her Department have been (a) cancelled and (b) re-tendered in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4006","4006"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750233","2017-07-12","Home Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans she has to lay regulations under the Immigration and Asylum Act 1999 relating to changes in asylum support and the role of local authorities; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3969","3969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750234","2017-07-12","Home Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of public procurement contracts her Department awarded through framework agreements in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4021","4021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750235","2017-07-12","Home Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to her Written Statement, HCWS23, published on 3 July 2017, on resettlement, if the Government will take referrals from the UN Relief and Works Agency in order to ensure that people of Palestinian nationality and origin can be included.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3938","3938"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750236","2017-07-12","Home Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to her Written Statement, HCWS23, published on 3 July 2017, on resettlement, if she will review the case of Yousef Hasan.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3939","3939"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750237","2017-07-12","Home Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average number of bids received for each contract put out to tender by her Department was in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3991","3991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750238","2017-07-12","House of Commons Commission","2017-07-10","To ask the right hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington, representing the House of Commons Commission, whether the source of recent cyber attacks on the House has been identified; and what steps are being taken to deter future attacks.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3773","3773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750239","2017-07-13","Department for International Development","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is taking to help other Departments spending resources on aid achieve good or very good ratings under the international aid transparency initiative.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3807","3807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750240","2017-07-13","Department for International Development","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will ensure that any changes to the OECD Development Assistance Committee rules are proposed on the basis of increasing the beneficial effects of aid spending on the world's poorest and most vulnerable communities.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3808","3808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750241","2017-07-13","Department for International Development","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will ensure that spending on aid by all Government Departments conforms to the International Development Act 2002.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3881","3881"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750242","2017-07-13","Department for International Development","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is taking to ensure that there is interest in and take-up from the Small Charities Challenge Fund from charities in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3899","3899"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750243","2017-07-12","Department for International Development","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what the average number of bids received for each contract put out to tender by her Department was in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3992","3992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750244","2017-07-12","Department for International Development","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what support her Department provides to projects intended to foster coexistence between Palestinians and Israelis.","Biography information for Paul Masterton","Paul Masterton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3942","3942"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750245","2017-07-12","Department for International Development","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what proportion of public procurement contracts her Department awarded through framework agreements in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4022","4022"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750246","2017-07-12","Department for International Development","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many contracts put out to tender by her Department have been (a) cancelled and (b) re-tendered in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4007","4007"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750247","2017-07-12","Ministry of Justice","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many contracts put out to tender by his Department have been (a) cancelled and (b) re-tendered in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4008","4008"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750248","2017-07-12","Ministry of Justice","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of public procurement contracts his Department awarded through framework agreements in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4023","4023"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750249","2017-07-12","Ministry of Justice","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average number of bids received for each contract put out to tender by his Department was in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3993","3993"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750250","2017-07-12","Ministry of Justice","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the oral Answer of 2 November 2016, Official Report, column 879, what steps his Department has taken to use 2011 census classifications, including on Gypsies and Travellers, to audit racial disparities in public service outcomes.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4059","4059"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750251","2017-07-13","Ministry of Justice","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will publish the (a) direct resource expenditure and (b) overall resource expenditure for Feltham Young Offenders Institution between 2011 and 2017.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4099","4099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750252","2017-07-13","Ministry of Justice","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the report by HM Chief Inspector of Prisons published on 30 June 2017 following an unannounced inspection of Feltham Young Offenders Institution; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4101","4101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750253","2017-07-13","Ministry of Justice","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many staff and officers were employed at Feltham Young Offenders Institution between 2011 and 2017.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4100","4100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750254","2017-07-13","Ministry of Justice","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many County Court Judgments were issued for non-payment of private parking prosecutions in each of the last 12 months; and how many of those judgments were processed at Northampton Crown Court.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3882","3882"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750255","2017-07-13","Ministry of Justice","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the number of (a) directly employed staff and (b) people employed in support of Hindley Prison is.","Biography information for Yvonne Fovargue","Yvonne Fovargue","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3884","3884"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750256","2017-07-12","Ministry of Justice","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the contribution from the Minister for the Cabinet Office on 2 November 2016, Official Report, column 879, what work is being done to progress work to distinguish Gypsies and Travellers using 2011 census classifications in his Department.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3873","3873"
