"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448204","2016-01-29","Cabinet Office","2016-01-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much real estate the Government owns in Plymouth.","Biography information for Oliver Colvile","Oliver Colvile","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24415","24415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448205","2016-01-29","Cabinet Office","2016-01-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many young people have taken part in the National Citizen Service in Bolton West constituency.","Biography information for Chris Green","Chris Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24396","24396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448206","2016-02-01","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment she has made of the potential contribution to energy efficiency and low carbon energy from buildings markets to (a) improving infrastructure and (b) implementing the Government's (i) long-term economic plan, (ii) obligations under the Climate Change Act 2008 and (c) commitments to relieve fuel poverty.","Biography information for Mike Wood","Mike Wood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24408","24408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448207","2016-02-01","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if she will issue a call for evidence from industry and other stakeholders seeking suggestions on Government interventions and policies to further develop the energy efficiency and low carbon energy markets; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mike Wood","Mike Wood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24409","24409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448208","2016-01-29","Cabinet Office","2016-01-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many young people in (a) Bolton borough and (b) Wigan borough have taken part in the National Citizen Service.","Biography information for Chris Green","Chris Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24410","24410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448209","2016-02-01","HM Treasury","2016-01-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make it his policy to extend the rural fuel duty rebate scheme to parts of Northern Ireland where cheaper fuel is readily available from the Irish Republic.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24377","24377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448211","2016-01-29","HM Treasury","2016-01-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 26 January 2016 to Question 22515, if he will estimate the amount paid out in supplements following the late payment of VAT returns in (a) 2015-16 and (b) each of the previous 10 years.","Biography information for Kit Malthouse","Kit Malthouse","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24393","24393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448212","2016-01-29","HM Treasury","2016-01-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many lone parents have received letters from Concentrix since 1 January 2015 questioning their reported living arrangements and requesting proof that they are not cohabiting in order to assess their continued eligibility to receive tax credits.","Biography information for Angela Crawley","Angela Crawley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24418","24418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448213","2016-01-29","HM Treasury","2016-01-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with his Chinese counterpart on developments in the stock market in that country.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24421","24421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448214","2016-01-29","HM Treasury","2016-01-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to minimise the risk of future bank failures.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24420","24420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448215","2016-01-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department has taken to ensure transparency of commission and other charges, levied by private pension funds on individuals.","Biography information for Tom Tugendhat","Tom Tugendhat","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24449","24449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448216","2016-01-29","HM Treasury","2016-01-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department has taken to measure the annual cost of commission and other charges levied on individual private pension plans by financial advisers in the last five years.","Biography information for Tom Tugendhat","Tom Tugendhat","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24450","24450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448217","2016-01-29","HM Treasury","2016-01-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department has taken to ensure transparency of commission and other charges levied by financial advisers during the sale of financial products to individuals.","Biography information for Tom Tugendhat","Tom Tugendhat","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24451","24451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448218","2016-01-29","HM Treasury","2016-01-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department has taken to ensure transparency of commission and other charges levied by financial advisers on individual pension plans.","Biography information for Tom Tugendhat","Tom Tugendhat","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24452","24452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448219","2016-01-29","HM Treasury","2016-01-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what information his Department holds on the annual cost of commission and other charges levied by financial advisers during the sale of financial products to individuals in the last five years.","Biography information for Tom Tugendhat","Tom Tugendhat","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24453","24453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448220","2016-01-29","HM Treasury","2016-01-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, which companies have had meetings with Ministers of his Department since May 2015 to discuss those companies' tax status.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24494","24494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448221","2016-02-01","HM Treasury","2016-01-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he plans to reply to the letter from the hon. Members for East Worthing and Shoreham and Kingston upon Hull West and Hessle on the British Mercantile Marine Memorial Collection which was sent on 28 October 2015 and resent on 5 January 2016.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24559","24559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448222","2016-01-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what information his Department holds on charges other than commission payments levied on private pension funds by individuals.","Biography information for Tom Tugendhat","Tom Tugendhat","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24461","24461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448223","2016-01-29","HM Treasury","2016-01-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the merits of making public the rules for country-by-country reporting of tax and profits by multinational companies.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24622","24622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448224","2016-02-01","HM Treasury","2016-01-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the evidential basis is for tax relief on pension contributions encouraging savings in pension schemes.","Biography information for Rob Marris","Rob Marris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24640","24640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448225","2016-02-01","HM Treasury","2016-01-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people have claimed the marriage allowance introduced in April 2015 to date; and what steps his Department is taking to ensure that eligible people apply for that allowance.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24585","24585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448226","2016-01-29","HM Treasury","2016-01-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with (a) Members of the European Parliament, (b) EU Commissioners and (c) EU finance ministers on making public the rules for country-by-country reporting of tax and profits by multinational companies.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24621","24621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448227","2016-01-29","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what guidance his Department provides to local planning authorities on whether (a) a Local Plan and (b) other local planning policies can be amended following the granting of planning permission on appeal for substantive development.","Biography information for Oliver Dowden","Oliver Dowden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24533","24533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448228","2016-01-29","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what guidance his Department has issued on whether the existence of extant planning permission for development in the Green Belt would count as exceptional circumstances to permit a planning application for an alternative, less intrusive form of development in that location.","Biography information for Oliver Dowden","Oliver Dowden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24534","24534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448229","2016-01-29","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what guidance his Department issues to local authorities on (a) a Local Development Order and (b) Supplementary Planning Guidance to facilitate alternative, less intrusive development on a specific location in the Green Belt where there is already extant planning permission for development in that location.","Biography information for Oliver Dowden","Oliver Dowden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24535","24535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448230","2016-01-29","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what progress he has made on empowering tenants in the private rented sector to ensure landlords carry out reasonable repairs.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24500","24500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448231","2016-01-29","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many affordable housing completions there were in Ellesmere Port and Neston constituency for each of the last 10 years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24593","24593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448232","2016-01-29","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will publish the distributional analysis of the introduction of the two per cent social care precept.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24592","24592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448233","2016-02-01","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he expects to report on the findings of his Department's consultation on changes to the Local Government Pension Scheme.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24476","24476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448234","2016-01-29","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether the Greater Manchester Combined Authority is legally required to consult all councillors in the 10 metropolitan district councils on the sites identified in the draft Greater Manchester Spatial Framework Development Plan.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24411","24411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448235","2016-01-29","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether the Greater Manchester Combined Authority is legally required to consult the public on the sites identified in the draft Greater Manchester Spatial Framework Development Plan.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24412","24412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448236","2016-01-29","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will meet the hon. Member for Denton and Reddish to discuss the consultation process for the draft Greater Manchester Spatial Framework Development Plan.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24413","24413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448238","2016-01-29","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what plans he has for call-in and scrutiny arrangements for the work of the Greater Manchester Combined Authority.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24400","24400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448240","2016-02-01","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many (a) kilometres of duct and (b) poles have been installed with financial support from BDUK.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24649","24649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448241","2016-01-29","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how much his Department spent (a) in real terms and (b) as a share of departmental spending on (i) temporary agency staff, (ii) consultants, (iii) non-payroll staff, (iv) administration and (v) marketing and advertising for (A) 2010-11, (B) 2011-12, (C) 2012-13 and (D) 2014-15.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24498","24498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448242","2016-01-29","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, when his Department plans to publish the UK Digital Strategy.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24520","24520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448243","2016-02-01","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Strategic Defence and Security Review, which improvements in performance in the delivery of the Successor submarine programme (a) have been achieved and (b) he expects to be achieved in the next 12 months.","Biography information for Kate Hollern","Kate Hollern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24641","24641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448244","2016-02-01","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether there is an approved Outline Business Case for the investment proposals for the next phase of work on the Successor submarine programme.","Biography information for Kate Hollern","Kate Hollern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24642","24642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448245","2016-02-01","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the estimated completion and entry into service dates are for each of the proposed Successor Trident submarines.","Biography information for Kate Hollern","Kate Hollern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24643","24643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448246","2016-02-01","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether there is an approved Final Business Case for the £600 million of further design work proposed for the Successor submarine programme.","Biography information for Kate Hollern","Kate Hollern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24645","24645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448247","2016-02-01","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Strategic Defence and Security Review, what the stages will be in the staged investment programme for the Successor submarine programme; and what the estimated timetable for each of those stages is.","Biography information for Kate Hollern","Kate Hollern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24644","24644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448248","2016-01-29","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what discussions he has had with NATO on monitoring Russian manoeuvres along its borders with NATO member states.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24469","24469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448249","2016-01-29","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent discussions his Department has had with NATO on progress with NATO's Force Integration Units.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24470","24470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448250","2016-01-29","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent steps his Department has taken in conjunction with NATO to ensure flexibility in NATO's capacity to respond to hostile actions.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24471","24471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448251","2016-01-29","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what discussions he has had with NATO on the emergency provision of troops to (a) Poland and (b) the Balkan states.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24472","24472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448252","2016-01-29","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent discussions the Government has had with NATO on reductions to the number of Russian nuclear strike missiles.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24473","24473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448253","2016-01-29","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent discussions he has had with NATO on improvements to the road network in European NATO member states to permit more effective movement of troops and logistic support.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24474","24474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448254","2016-01-29","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 27 January 2016 to Question 23346, how many of the breaches referred to related to documents categorised before April 2014 as (a) top secret, (b) secret, (c) confidential, (d) restricted, (e) protected and (f) unclassified; and how many such breaches related to documents categorised after April 2014 as (i) top secret, (ii) secret and (iii) official-sensitive or official.","Biography information for Stephen Phillips","Stephen Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24625","24625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448255","2016-01-29","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many armed forces personnel who have taken Mefloquine have been treated for psychiatric problems in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24460","24460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448256","2016-01-29","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what discussions he has had with the United States Department of Defense about safety of the F-35 ejection system.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24457","24457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448257","2016-01-29","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to paragraph 4.57 of the National Security Strategy and Strategic Defence and Security Review 2015, in which month of 2016 his Department plans to (a) complete its study of the physiological impacts of combat roles in the armed forces on women and (b) announce a final decision on women undertaking the full range of combat roles.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24502","24502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448258","2016-01-29","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what discussions his Department has had with NATO on tackling negative reporting on NATO and its member states from Russian media outlets.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24439","24439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448259","2016-01-29","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to mitigate against (a) high level missile and (b) cyber threats from Russia.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24438","24438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448260","2016-01-29","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department has an insurance policy in place for civilian residents on the land around RAF Northolt to cover possible damage to their properties.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24399","24399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448261","2016-01-29","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what discussions he has had with (a) NATO and (b) the Balkan states on increasing the number of NATO troops and amount of materiel in those states.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24441","24441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448262","2016-02-01","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent discussions his Department has had with Rolls-Royce on the future direction of its nuclear submarine power plant business; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24487","24487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448263","2016-02-01","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate his Department has made of the number of jobs in each region and part of the UK that (a) have been and (b) will be created by the Successor submarine programme.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24550","24550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448264","2016-02-01","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he expects the target strength of army reservists to be met.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24485","24485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448265","2016-01-29","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many missions have been flown by UK military forces in Syria to provide direct humanitarian aid to civilians; where those missions took place; what aid was supplied; and what the cost was of those missions.","Biography information for Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24454","24454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448266","2016-01-29","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many members of the (a) Army Reserve, (b) Royal Auxiliary Air Force and (c) Royal Navy Reserve have signed terms and conditions of service under the New Employment Model.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24455","24455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448267","2016-01-29","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what discussions he has had with the Polish government on the allocation of UK or NATO forces to Poland to counter any threats to that country from Russia.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24440","24440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448268","2016-01-29","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what protections exist for British veterans of the Iraq War who are subject to prosecutions for alleged crimes committed while undertaking their service.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24435","24435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448269","2016-01-29","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether Veterans Welfare Service staff are permitted to represent ex-servicemen and women at tribunal hearings to contest War Pension Scheme decisions made by Veterans UK.","Biography information for Jo Cox","Jo Cox","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24620","24620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448270","2016-01-29","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how his Department responds to and investigates the death of non-combatant employees on military bases.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24617","24617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448271","2016-01-29","Department for Education","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps are being taken in primary schools to address obesity.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24437","24437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448272","2016-01-29","Department for Education","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps the Government is taking to work with schools and teacher training providers to (a) increase the number of science and mathematics teachers and (b) to ensure that such teachers work in the schools where they are most needed.","Biography information for Chris Green","Chris Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24398","24398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448273","2016-01-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what discussions he has had with the Chancellor of the Exchequer on measures to ensure that banks and other financial institutions are not able to profit from the merging of any further education institutions as a result of his Department's area reviews.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24499","24499"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448274","2016-02-01","Department for Education","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children in care are currently subject to Staying Put arrangements in each local authority area.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24560","24560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448275","2016-02-01","Department for Education","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when she plans to publish the findings of the review into children's residential care undertaken by Sir Martin Norey.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24591","24591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448276","2016-01-29","Department for Education","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of the Your Life campaign in changing the perceptions of STEM subjects amoung young people.","Biography information for Chris Green","Chris Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24577","24577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448277","2016-01-29","Department for Education","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much of the available funding for the Pupil Premium Summer School Programme was spent in 2015; and how much was spent on food provision for children outside term time.","Biography information for Ruth Smeeth","Ruth Smeeth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24531","24531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448278","2016-01-29","Department for Education","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what funding was available for the Pupil Premium Summer School Programme in 2015.","Biography information for Ruth Smeeth","Ruth Smeeth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24532","24532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448279","2016-01-29","Department for Education","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will ensure that creative subjects are included in the new Ebac; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24570","24570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448280","2016-01-29","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps she plans to take to increase renewable energy generation when the renewables obligation scheme ends in 2017.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24601","24601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448281","2016-01-29","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment she has made of the impact of the Energy Bill on Northern Ireland's ability to contribute to the achievement of the UK's international climate change obligations.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24458","24458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448282","2016-01-29","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if she will list by title the documents requested and not released under the Freedom of Information Act 2000 relating to (a) nuclear power and (b) Hinkley Point C nuclear power plant since May 2010.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24501","24501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448283","2016-01-29","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what proportion of electricity in the UK was generated by UK coal-fired power stations in 2015.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24448","24448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448284","2016-02-01","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment has been made of the effects of the reduction in the feed-in tariff on 14 January 2016 on small scale hydro producers.","Biography information for Richard Arkless","Richard  Arkless","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24391","24391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448285","2016-02-01","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what recent discussions she has had with energy companies on the progress of building new nuclear power stations.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24442","24442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448286","2016-01-29","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what discussions she has had with her German counterparts on the building of new coal power stations in that country.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24618","24618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448287","2016-01-29","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what discussions she has had with ministerial colleagues on contingency plans for power cuts; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24619","24619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448288","2016-01-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions her Department has had with the Chinese government on the sale of wildlife from Zimbabwe.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24424","24424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448289","2016-01-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions she has had with Ministers of the Northern Ireland Executive on steps to increase exports of food from Northern Ireland to China.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24425","24425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448290","2016-02-01","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment her Department has made of the effectiveness of grant allocations to local authorities in England in tackling (a) Japanese knotweed and (b) other invasive non-native species since 2011.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24380","24380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448291","2016-02-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what progress the Government has made on putting in place a blue belt to protect marine habitats and species in the UK's Overseas Territories.","Biography information for David Warburton","David Warburton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24388","24388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448292","2016-01-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the rural productivity plan published by her Department in August 2015, when she will publish the calls for evidence on reviewing the planning and regulatory constraints facing rural businesses and the measures that can be taken to address them.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24623","24623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448293","2016-01-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his US counterpart on Russian violations of the Intermediate-Range Nuclear Forces Treaty.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24459","24459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448294","2016-01-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will raise with the government of Bulgaria the issue of the Ahmadiyya Muslim community being denied the right to register as a religious organisation in Bulgaria.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24616","24616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448295","2016-01-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the human rights situation in the Maldives.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24567","24567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448296","2016-01-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the independence of the legal system in the Maldives.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24568","24568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448297","2016-01-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with the Maldives government on the unconditional release of former President Nasheed.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24527","24527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448298","2016-01-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 4 January 2016 to Question 20771, how many staff are employed in the Coalition Communications Cell; and what the annual operating budget of that unit is.","Biography information for Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24493","24493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448299","2016-01-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assistance the Government is giving to Libya for protection of oil fields and production lines in that country.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24422","24422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448300","2016-01-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his counterpart in China on the recent disappearance of five people who work for a Hong Kong publishing company and bookseller.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24423","24423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448301","2016-01-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with the Romanian government about a NATO Black Sea fleet.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24456","24456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448302","2016-02-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will urge the Iranian authorities to commute immediately the death sentences of the juvenile offenders identified in the report, Growing up on death row: the death penalty and juvenile offenders in Iran, published by Amnesty International on 26 January 2010.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24561","24561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448303","2016-01-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 4 January 2016 to Question 20769, how many individuals have been subject to sanctions imposed by the UK Government for (a) brokering oil deals between Daesh and the Assad regime and (b) other matters covered by UN Security Council Resolution 2253.","Biography information for Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24492","24492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448304","2016-01-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the level of Russian funding for political groups in NATO member states who oppose NATO and nuclear weapons.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24466","24466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448305","2016-01-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to counter Russian propaganda directed at the UK or at NATO.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24464","24464"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448306","2016-01-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with the Turkish government on access to the Black Sea for merchant shipping.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24465","24465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448307","2016-01-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with the BBC and NATO on more effective use of the BBC World Service to counter inaccurate reporting from Russian media outlets.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24463","24463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448308","2016-01-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with the government of Russia on human rights violations in that country.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24462","24462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448309","2016-02-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of whether (a) cluster munitions have been used in the Yemen conflict and (b) there is a clear risk that such munitions were dropped from British-made aircraft.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24586","24586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448310","2016-02-01","Department of Health","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 22 January 2016 to Question 23722, what estimate his Department has made of the additional cost to social care providers of paying the new national living wage.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24584","24584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448311","2016-02-01","Department of Health","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the financial monitoring and accounts returns submitted to his Department, which NHS (a) trusts and (b) foundation trusts have reported that their planned agency nursing spend (i) will and (ii) will not exceed the ceiling trajectory set by Monitor.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24545","24545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448312","2016-02-01","Department of Health","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the financial monitoring and accounts returns submitted to his Department, what the planned agency costs are forecast to be as a proportion of the total nursing costs in each NHS (a) trust and (b) foundation trust in 2015-16.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24544","24544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448313","2016-02-01","Department of Health","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what forecast his Department has made of the budget of his Department's consultation, entitled Infected blood: reform of financial and other support; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24488","24488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448314","2016-02-01","Department of Health","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans his Department has to support earlier diagnosis and treatment of rheumatoid arthritis to allow people with that condition to stay in work for longer.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24541","24541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448315","2016-02-01","Department of Health","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients have been infected with HIV and hepatitis C through treatment with NHS-supplied blood or blood products; how much his Department has paid to patients so infected with those diseases to date; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24489","24489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448316","2016-02-01","Department of Health","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to improve pancreatic cancer survival rates.","Biography information for Dr Alasdair McDonnell","Dr Alasdair McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24548","24548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448317","2016-02-01","Department of Health","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 19 January 2016 to Question 21837, what the average cost to the NHS is of a colonoscopy performed following a positive screening test for bowel cancer.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24445","24445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448318","2016-02-01","Department of Health","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 19 January 2016 to Question 21839, what steps he is taking to ensure that engagement with the National Bowel Screening Programme continues to increase; and what (a) national and (b) local targets his Department has for such engagement.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24443","24443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448319","2016-01-29","Department of Health","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people had gastrointestinal operations in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24428","24428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448320","2016-01-29","Department of Health","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people of each age group and gender were diagnosed with irritable bowel syndrome in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24429","24429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448321","2016-01-29","Department of Health","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to reduce the incidence of substance addiction in people aged over 50.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24430","24430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448322","2016-01-29","Cabinet Office","2016-01-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people of each age group and gender died from diabetes-related diseases in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24431","24431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448323","2016-01-29","Department of Health","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he expects that retinal implant chips will be available through the NHS to treat blindness.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24432","24432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448324","2016-01-29","Department of Health","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to increase public awareness of rare diseases.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24433","24433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448325","2016-01-29","Department of Health","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to work with charities and campaigners on raising awareness and improving prevention of prostate cancer.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24434","24434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448326","2016-02-01","Department of Health","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 19 January 2016 to Question 21838, what estimate he has made of the cost of (a) training and (b) funding the extra 250 gastroenterologist and 200 non-medical endoscopists that will increase capacity for colonoscopy and endoscopy.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24444","24444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448327","2016-01-29","Department of Health","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many companies which comprised a single person were paid for services by NHS trusts in 2014-15.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24394","24394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448328","2016-02-01","Department of Health","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make changes to the clinical guidelines for motor neurone disease to improve diagnosis and treatment.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24378","24378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448329","2016-02-01","Department of Health","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his policy is on introducing fortification of bread with folic acid.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24382","24382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448330","2016-02-01","Department of Health","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many clinical commissioning groups in England have published recovery plans in each of the last three years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24389","24389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448331","2016-02-01","Department of Health","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many clinical commissioning groups he estimates will publish a recovery plan in the next 12 to 18 months; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24390","24390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448332","2016-01-29","Department of Health","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 22 January 2016 to Question 22716, if he will commission a survey on the effects of delays in the publication of the hepatitis C framework on (a) all people and (b) members of the South Asian population in England with hepatitis C.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24401","24401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448333","2016-02-01","Department of Health","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many adults were recorded as obese in (a) England, (b) London, (c) each primary care trust in London and (d) each London borough in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24402","24402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448334","2016-02-01","Department of Health","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department has taken to increase access to specialist community perinatal mental health care.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24403","24403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448335","2016-02-01","Department of Health","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans his Department has to improve the identification and treatment of perinatal mental health issues; and how this will be monitored.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24404","24404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448336","2016-02-01","Department of Health","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the announcement by the Prime Minister on enhancing mental health services on 11 January 2016, what the basis is for the figure of £290 million to be invested in perinatal mental health care; how that funding will be allocated; and how the efficacy of that funding will be measured.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24405","24405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448337","2016-02-01","Department of Health","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans his Department has to ensure that clinical commissioning groups (a) improve access to, (b) provide training to health professionals on and (c) increase the number of healthcare professionals working in perinatal mental health.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24406","24406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448338","2016-02-01","Department of Health","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what provision there is for people with perinatal mental health issues living in clinical commissioning group areas where there is no specialist community perinatal mental health team.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24407","24407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448339","2016-02-01","Department of Health","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the financial monitoring and accounts returns submitted to his Department, what the (a) year to date and (b) forecast outturn spend is in each NHS (i) trust and (ii) foundation trust on total agency nursing costs, excluding outsourced bank, in 2015-16.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24546","24546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448340","2016-02-01","Department of Health","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to raise awareness of the symptoms of pancreatic cancer.","Biography information for Dr Alasdair McDonnell","Dr Alasdair McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24547","24547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448341","2016-01-29","Department of Health","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how Academic Health Science Networks are able to contribute to the Accelerated Access Review.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24496","24496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448342","2016-01-29","Department of Health","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the implications are for his policies on encouraging the recruitment and development of BAME and women at senior staffing levels in the NHS of the findings of the Interim Report in the Review of Operational Productivity in NHS providers, undertaken by Lord Carter of Coles and published in June 2015.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24497","24497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448343","2016-01-29","Department of Health","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the cost is of each patient who attends a Same Day Walk-In Centre in the Fylde and Wyre Clinical Commissioning Group area.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24512","24512"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448344","2016-01-29","Department of Health","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the value is in each financial year of each service contracted out by Fylde and Wyre Clinical Commissioning Group.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24513","24513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448345","2016-01-29","Department of Health","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, on what grounds Experts by Experience was not considered under TUPE arrangements when Remploy took over its contracts.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24514","24514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448346","2016-01-29","Department of Health","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what representations he has received about the importance of Experts by Experience in the NHS.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24515","24515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448347","2016-01-29","Department of Health","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much Fylde and Wyre Clinical Commissioning Group spent on contracts with Same Day Walk-In Centres in (a) 2013-14 and (b) 2014-15.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24511","24511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448348","2016-01-29","Department of Health","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what representations he has received on the level of payments by Remploy to Experts by Experience; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24518","24518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448349","2016-02-01","Department of Health","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure people affected by historical hepatitis C and HIV-infected NHS blood treatments have their views adequately heard in its consultation entitled Infected blood: reform of financial and other support, published in January 2016; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24478","24478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448350","2016-01-29","Department of Health","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that the recommendations from the Accelerated Access Review interim report and the Cancer Drugs Fund consultation are not contradictory.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24506","24506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448351","2016-01-29","Department of Health","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what lessons have been learned from the implementation of recommendations contained in NHS England's report, entitled Innovation, Health and Wealth, published in December 2011; and how his Department is implementing those lessons in the Accelerated Access Review.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24575","24575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448352","2016-02-01","Department of Health","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many children aged (a) four to five and (b) 10 to 11 years were recorded as obese in (i) England, (ii) London, (iii) each primary care trust in London and (iv) each London borough in 2014-15.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24481","24481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448353","2016-02-01","Department of Health","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of open MRI scanners available to the NHS in each region.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24480","24480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448354","2016-01-29","Department of Health","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what targets his Department has for the transfer of documents between GP surgeries when a patient moves to a different area.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24595","24595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448355","2016-01-29","Department of Health","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with the devolved administrations in (a) Wales, (b) Scotland and (c) Northern Ireland on the speed and efficiency of transfer of patient records between administrations.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24596","24596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448356","2016-01-29","Department of Health","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many GP surgeries have adopted the use of the GP2GP system developed by the Health and Social Care Information Centre.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24597","24597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448357","2016-01-29","Department of Health","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average time taken for the transfer of documents between GP surgeries when a patient move to a different health area was in each of the last five years.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24598","24598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448358","2016-01-29","Department of Health","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to NHS's consultation, Specialised services policy and specifications, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the procedure in use by NHS England to develop commissioning policies for specialised medicines.","Biography information for Chris Green","Chris Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24565","24565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448359","2016-01-29","Department of Health","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department plans to take in response to the report it commissioned entitled Evaluating the role and contribution of innovation to health and wealth in the UK, published in January 2016; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24564","24564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448360","2016-01-29","Department of Health","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if his Department will make an assessment of the effectiveness of the spread of the six highest impact innovations identified in NHS England's report, entitled Innovation, Health and Wealth, published in December 2011; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24576","24576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448361","2016-02-01","Department of Health","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to improve early diagnosis rates of pancreatic cancer.","Biography information for Dr Alasdair McDonnell","Dr Alasdair McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24632","24632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448362","2016-02-01","Department of Health","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many sales of land of what value and to whom there have been in each health trust area in London (a) on the open market or (b) below market value in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24635","24635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448363","2016-02-01","Department of Health","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many units of (a) housing and (b) affordable housing have been built on each parcel of NHS land sold in London since 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24633","24633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448364","2016-02-01","Department of Health","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many parcels of NHS land were for sale in each health trust area in London on 1 January 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24634","24634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448365","2016-02-01","Department of Health","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant the Answer of 18 December 2015 to Question 20074, on mental health services: children, when he expects that the thematic review will be (a) finished and (b) published.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24629","24629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448366","2016-02-01","Department of Health","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 18 December 2015 to Question 20074, on mental health services: children, whether it is planned that the thematic review will consider children who have been abused as a specific theme separate to children and young people more generally.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24630","24630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448367","2016-02-01","Department of Health","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 22 January 2016 to Question 23217, which clinical commissioning groups have provided details of where their plans are published; and where such transformation plans can be accessed.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24631","24631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448368","2016-01-29","Cabinet Office","2016-01-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what his most recent estimate is of the number of migrants entering the EU; and what the proportion is of those migrants who are entering the UK.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24467","24467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448369","2016-01-29","Cabinet Office","2016-01-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what his most recent estimate is of the number of EU migrants entering the UK.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24468","24468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448370","2016-01-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what his Department's planned expenditure on the Police Intellectual Property Crime Unit is for (a) 2016-17, (b) 2017-18, (c) 2018-19 and (d) 2019-20.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24521","24521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448371","2016-01-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate his Department has made of how many full time police officers will work in the Police Intellectual Property Crime Unit in (a) 2016-17, (b) 2017-18, (c) 2018-19 and (d) 2019-20.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24522","24522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448372","2016-01-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many full-time police officers worked in the Police Intellectual Property Crime Unit in (a) 2013-14, (b) 2014-15 and (c) 2015-16.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24523","24523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448373","2016-01-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many successful convictions were secured by the Police Intellectual Property Crime Unit in (a) 2013-14, (b) 2014-15 and (c) 2015-16.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24524","24524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448374","2016-01-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what his Department's spending on the Police Intellectual Property Crime Unit was in (a) 2013-14, (b) 2014-15 and (c) 2015-16.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24525","24525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448375","2016-01-29","Home Office","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to Advice Note: 05/2015, paragraph 9 of the Harm-Benefit Analysis Process, how many project licences applications under the Animals (Scientific Procedures) Act 1986 were recommended by the Animals and Science Regulation Unit in each year since 2012.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24519","24519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448376","2016-01-29","Home Office","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many project licence applications under the Animals (Scientific Procedures) Act 1986 were (a) granted and (b) not granted on the basis of the harm-benefit analysis.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24508","24508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448377","2016-01-29","Home Office","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many times she rejected the recommendations of the Animals in Science Regulation Unit for project licences in each year since 2012.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24509","24509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448378","2016-02-01","Department for Education","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what representations she has received in the last year from (a) Christian, (b) Jewish and (c) Muslim faith schools on the Counter Extremism Strategy used in schools; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24479","24479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448379","2016-01-29","Home Office","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to paragraph 12 of Advice Note: 05/2015 on the Harm-Benefit Analysis Process, how many project licence applications were withdrawn at the (a) concept and (b) draft stage as a result of advice from the Animals in Science Regulation Unit that the application would clearly fail the harm-benefit analysis in each year since 2012.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24507","24507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448380","2016-01-29","Home Office","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many times project licence applications were referred to an independent assessor in each year since 2012.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24510","24510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448381","2016-02-01","Home Office","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made on the effect of the visa refund fee scheme on the number of Chinese people visiting the UK.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24381","24381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448382","2016-01-29","Home Office","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the total number of people from the UK who have joined Daesh.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24419","24419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448383","2016-02-01","Home Office","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much revenue from (a) CRB checks and (b) Disclosure and Barring Service checks has been raised for the public purse in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24579","24579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448384","2016-02-01","Home Office","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) CRB checks and (b) Disclosure and Barring Service checks have been carried out in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24578","24578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448385","2016-01-29","Department for International Development","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether she plans to discuss the issue of education for children in areas of conflict at the World Humanitarian Summit in Istanbul in May 2016; and what plans she has to ensure children have access to education in those areas.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24414","24414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448386","2016-01-29","Department for International Development","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assistance the Government has given to former Gurkhas who are homeless as a result of recent earthquakes in Nepal.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24426","24426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448387","2016-01-29","Department for International Development","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what programmes her Department has in place to facilitate access to wells and water in developing countries.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24427","24427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448388","2016-02-01","Department for International Development","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what estimate her Department has made of the value of funding her Department has allocated to Libya which has been spent in the city of Sirte; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24446","24446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448389","2016-02-01","Department for International Development","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what progress her Department has made on implementing its response to the Eleventh Report from the International Development Committee, Session 2013-14, on Disability and development, HC 947.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr   Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24383","24383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448390","2016-02-01","Department for International Development","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment her Department has made of the effect of the sustainable development goals on the UK's aid spending on health initiatives; and if her Department will issue a guidance note on that spending.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr   Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24384","24384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448391","2016-02-03","Department for International Development","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is taking to (a) help up-skill and (b) provide technical education for the Bangladeshi workforce.","Biography information for Julian Knight","Julian Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24648","24648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448392","2016-01-29","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people were (a) charged with and (b) convicted of paying for the sexual services of a child under the Sexual Offences Act 2003 in each calendar year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Mr Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24517","24517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448393","2016-02-01","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prison officers have taken severance and redundancy packages in each month since May 2015.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24637","24637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448394","2016-02-01","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prison officers taking voluntary early departure since May 2010 have had (a) up to six, (b) six to 12, (c) 12 to 18, (d) 18 to 24 and (e) over 24 months' continuous service.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24638","24638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448395","2016-02-01","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prison officers have taken up the voluntary early departure scheme in each month since May 2010; how much has been paid in severance in each month to those prison officers; what average amount is paid in severance to those prison officers; and what the average continuous service was of those prison officers.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24639","24639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448396","2016-02-01","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many knives have been confiscated in prisons in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24558","24558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448397","2016-02-01","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many Law Society mental health panel accredited representatives there were on the Law Society panel available for First Tier Tribunal (mental health) hearings in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24627","24627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448398","2016-02-01","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) First Tier Tribunal (mental health) hearings in England and (b) Mental Health Review Tribunal hearings in Wales there have been in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24628","24628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448399","2016-02-01","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoner officers who have received severance or redundancy packages since May 2010 have been re-employed as prison officers.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24636","24636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448400","2016-01-29","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many complaints on what subjects the Independent Monitoring Board of each prison received from prisoners in the last 12 months for which figures are available.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24615","24615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448401","2016-02-01","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many failures there have been in contracts for the running of prisons at each institution in each of the last five years; what those failures were; and what financial penalties were attached to each such failure.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24385","24385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448402","2016-02-01","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many incidents relating to safety of children in secure training centres and young offender institutions have been raised by Barnardo's advocates with (a) Youth Justice Board monitors and (b) local children's safeguarding boards in each of the last three years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24386","24386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448403","2016-01-29","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many employment tribunal (ET) cases involved employees and employers from the maritime industry in each year since 2008-09; and what proportion of the total number of ET cases such cases were in each such year.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24447","24447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448404","2016-01-29","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been released from custodial sentences as a result of wrongful convictions in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24436","24436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448405","2016-01-29","Leader of the House","2016-01-27","To ask the Leader of the House, what date is planned for the State Opening of Parliament in 2016.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24624","24624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448406","2016-01-29","Home Office","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make it her policy to grant right of abode in this country to former British-Hong Kong servicemen.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24490","24490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448407","2016-01-29","Home Office","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if the Prime Minister will issue a response to (a) Early Day Motion 722, Right of abode for former British-Hong Kong servicemen and (b) petitions on this subject presented at 10 Downing Street on 5 November 2014.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24491","24491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448408","2016-01-29","Scotland Office","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what recent discussions he has had with the Scottish Government on the screening of asylum seekers in Scotland.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24613","24613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448409","2016-01-29","Scotland Office","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, if he will take steps to provide compensation for people in Scotland who have lost out financially as a result of the increase in the women's pension age.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24526","24526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448410","2016-01-29","Scotland Office","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, when Ministers in his Department last met Citizens Advice Scotland; what was discussed at that meeting; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24612","24612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448411","2016-01-29","Scotland Office","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, which local authorities in Scotland on what dates he (a) has visited and (b) plans to visit.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24608","24608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448412","2016-01-29","Scotland Office","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how much his Department has spent on (a) taxis, (b) first class train tickets and (c) business class air travel in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24609","24609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448413","2016-01-29","Scotland Office","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how many recruitment and employment agencies his Department has used to source staff in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24610","24610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448414","2016-01-29","Scotland Office","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions on the effect of the increase in state pension age on women resident in Scotland who were born in the 1950s; and when the last such discussion was.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24611","24611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448415","2016-01-29","Scotland Office","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how much his Department spent on advertising, marketing and external communications in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24606","24606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448416","2016-01-29","Scotland Office","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how much his Department spent on renovations and repairs to Dover House in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24607","24607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448417","2016-01-29","Scotland Office","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, pursuant to the Answer of 21 July 2015 to Question 7427, what discussions he has had with Ministers of the Scottish Government on the implications of holding a referendum on the UK's membership of the EU within eight weeks of elections to the Scottish Parliament.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24605","24605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448418","2016-01-29","Department for Transport","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment he has made of the effect of the Brazilian government's enforcement of domestic cabotage legislation on the offshore supply sector in the North Sea.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24573","24573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448419","2016-01-29","Department for Transport","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with which private bus operators his Department has discussed the planned Buses Bill.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24602","24602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448420","2016-01-29","Department for Transport","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with Network Rail on improved responsiveness for emergency repairs; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Ansell","Caroline Ansell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24603","24603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448421","2016-01-29","Department for Transport","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with train operating companies on improving the claim process for compensation for delays; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Ansell","Caroline Ansell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24604","24604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448422","2016-01-29","Department for Transport","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect on the price of airline tickets of the falling price of oil.","Biography information for Mike Freer","Mike Freer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24572","24572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448423","2016-01-29","Department for Transport","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to address the congestion and air quality impacts of increases in numbers of private hire vehicles.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24599","24599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448424","2016-01-29","Department for Transport","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has recently made of the effectiveness of taxi and private hire vehicle regulations relating to passenger safety.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24600","24600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448425","2016-02-01","Department for Transport","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what savings have been made as a result of the seven-year contract awarded to the Post Office by the DVLA on 1 April 2013 in each financial year.","Biography information for Karl McCartney","Karl McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24554","24554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448426","2016-02-01","Department for Transport","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, on how many occasions vehicle owners have been fined for failing to pay for their vehicle tax since October 2014.","Biography information for Karl McCartney","Karl McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24555","24555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448427","2016-02-01","Department for Transport","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much vehicle owners have been fined for failing to pay for their vehicle tax since October 2014.","Biography information for Karl McCartney","Karl McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24556","24556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448428","2016-02-01","Department for Transport","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what savings his Department has made from ending the paper vehicle tax disc.","Biography information for Karl McCartney","Karl McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24557","24557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448429","2016-02-01","Department for Transport","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 21 January 2016 to Question 22808, what Network Rail maintenance, renewal or enhancement works that were planned to be carried out under blockade the 2015-16 Christmas and New Year period were deferred.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24551","24551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448430","2016-02-01","Department for Transport","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the value is of refunds unclaimed by people who sold their vehicles but then failed to apply for a refund of vehicle tax since 2010.","Biography information for Karl McCartney","Karl McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24552","24552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448431","2016-02-01","Department for Transport","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many railway stations in Great Britain were equipped with ITSO-compliant smartcard readers on the most recent date for which figures are available; and how many ITSO-compliant smartcards had been issued by (a) South Eastern, (b) Govia Thameslink Railway, (c) c2c, (d) Greater Anglia, (e) London Midland, (f) East Midland Trains and (g) Great Western Railway on the most recent date for which figures are available.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24477","24477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448432","2016-02-01","Department for Transport","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the oral contribution of the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs of 19 January 2016, Official Report, column 1364, what the evidential basis is for his statement that his Department will go further still in raising cycling spending per head.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24646","24646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448433","2016-01-29","Department for Transport","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to Transport for London's press release of 20 January 2016, TfL sets out plans to modernise and enhance London's private hire industry, what representations he has received from the Mayor of London on the introduction of legislation that would enable TfL to restrict overall numbers of private hire drivers and vehicles.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24566","24566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448434","2016-01-29","Department for Transport","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what proportion of the revenue raised by Southern Rail in the last five years was passed back to GTR by his Department.","Biography information for Ms Nusrat Ghani","Nusrat Ghani","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24395","24395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448435","2016-01-29","Department for Transport","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate his Department has made of the level of planned investment by local enterprise partnerships in cycling and walking infrastructure through the local growth fund.","Biography information for Chris Green","Chris Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24397","24397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448436","2016-01-29","Department for Transport","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment he has made of the effect of the low oil price since summer 2014 on the number of UK seafarers employed on offshore supply vessels in the North Sea.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24416","24416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448437","2016-02-01","Department for Transport","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions he has had with the Maritime and Coastguard Agency on staffing levels at coastguard stations in the Irish Sea.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24379","24379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448438","2016-01-29","Department for Transport","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what representations his Department has received on the protection of hedgehogs in Regent's Park from trucks using the London Zoo car park for the construction of High Speed 2.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24387","24387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448439","2016-02-01","Women and Equalities","2016-01-27","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, how many meetings she has had with chief executives of FTSE 100 companies since May 2015 at which she raised the issue of increasing the number of women on company boards.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24539","24539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448440","2016-02-01","Cabinet Office","2016-01-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment the Government has made of the gender balance of public appointments to (a) executive non-departmental public bodies, (b) advisory non-departmental public bodies, (c) independent monitoring boards and (d) non-ministerial departments made since May 2015.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24540","24540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448441","2016-02-01","Women and Equalities","2016-01-27","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, how many meetings she has had with businesses since May 2015 on increasing the number of women on company boards; and who those meetings were with.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24538","24538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448442","2016-02-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much has been allocated to the Work and Health Innovation Fund; and what evaluation measures will be in place to monitor initiatives helping people with health conditions such as rheumatoid arthritis stay in work.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24542","24542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448443","2016-02-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of people the Work and Health Innovation Fund will assist; and whether that fund will include initiatives to help people with (a) rheumatoid arthritis and (b) other long-term conditions stay in work.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24543","24543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448445","2016-02-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 26 January 2016 to Question 23063, on universal credit, when his Department plans to provide that notification to claimants.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24392","24392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448446","2016-01-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many cases have come before the Court of Appeal challenging the lawfulness of the under-occupancy penalty on the grounds of the effect of that policy on (a) victims of domestic violence and (b) seriously disabled children who need overnight care.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24516","24516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448447","2016-02-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, in what circumstances the housing element of advance payments of universal credit can be paid directly to a landlord.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24553","24553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448448","2016-01-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effect of the triple lock pension policy of the number of pensioners living in poverty in (a) Windsor, (b) the South East and (c) the UK.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24574","24574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/448449","2016-01-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people took part in the Access to Work programme in each year from 2010 to 2013.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24563","24563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/449582","2016-02-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department is taking to promote opportunities for study and work in the UK to highly-skilled migrants with qualifications in STEM subjects.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 903389","903389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/449583","2016-02-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change on the effect of government policy on the renewables industry in Scotland.","Biography information for Natalie McGarry","Natalie McGarry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 903391","903391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/449584","2016-02-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent steps he has taken to support the steel industry.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 903393","903393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/449585","2016-02-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if the Government will bring forward proposals to enable the prosecution of UK businesses through the UK courts for breaches of human rights abroad when the UK's National Action Plan to implement the UN Guiding Principles on Business and Human Rights is next updated.","Biography information for Corri Wilson","Corri Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 903387","903387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/449586","2016-02-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many small businesses have received financial assistance from (a) peer to peer lenders and (b) other sources in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Mr Geoffrey Robinson","Mr Geoffrey Robinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 903388","903388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447669","2016-01-28","Attorney General","2016-01-26","To ask the Attorney General, pursuant to the Answer of 20 January 2016 to Question 22432, by what measure the Director of the Serious Fraud Office judges whether there is a significant public interest element in a case.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24101","24101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447670","2016-01-28","Attorney General","2016-01-26","To ask the Attorney General, pursuant to the Answer of 20 January 2016 to Question 22432, what measure the Director of the Serious Fraud Office uses to judge actual or potential economic harm.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24102","24102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447671","2016-01-28","Attorney General","2016-01-26","To ask the Attorney General, pursuant to the Answer of 20 January 2016 to Question 22432, how the Director of the Serious Fraud Office measures the undermining of UK PLC commercial or financial interests in the (a) City of London and (b) UK.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24099","24099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447672","2016-01-28","Attorney General","2016-01-26","To ask the Attorney General, pursuant to the Answer of 20 January 2016 to Question 22432, what the figure is for high actual or potential loss listed in the Statement of Principle.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24189","24189"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447673","2016-01-28","Attorney General","2016-01-26","To ask the Attorney General, pursuant to the Answer of 20 January 2016 to Question 22432, whether a case considered by the Serious Fraud Office must meet all Statement of Principle considerations.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24190","24190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447674","2016-01-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 22 January 2016 to Question 23237, if he will place in the Library a list of the recent representations he has received on the privatisation of the Green Investment Bank.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24217","24217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447675","2016-01-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 25 January 2016 to Question 23263, if he will place in the Library a copy of the minutes of his Department's meetings with the National Audit Office on the issue of value for money from the privatisation of the Green Investment Bank.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24218","24218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447676","2016-01-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to promote opportunities for businesses in the South West to access high growth markets abroad.","Biography information for David Warburton","David Warburton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24224","24224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447677","2016-01-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, which organisations contributed to UK Trade and Investment's Northern Powerhouse Investment Pitchbook; and who provided the assessment and shortlisting of developments included in that document.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24237","24237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447678","2016-01-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what support his Department is providing to businesses to increase exports to developing economies.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24097","24097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447679","2016-01-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what support his Department is providing to universities to increase collaboration with research institutions in developing economies.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24098","24098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447680","2016-01-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, which organisations he has consulted on the changes to Sunday trading in the 12 months.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24119","24119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447681","2016-01-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether the National Dementia Research Institute will conduct research into Parkinson's dementia as part of its core work.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24135","24135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447682","2016-01-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what guidance his Department provides to employers on supporting young apprentices with mental health conditions.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24147","24147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447683","2016-01-28","HM Treasury","2016-01-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the oral Answer from the Prime Minister on 9 December 2015, Official Report, column 982, how the National Illegal Money Lending Team England will be funded; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24171","24171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447684","2016-01-29","Cabinet Office","2016-01-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Justice on the application of Government guidance on public consultations to the consultation on the Government's proposed Bill of Rights.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24185","24185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447685","2016-01-29","Cabinet Office","2016-01-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether his Department has undertaken a value for money assessment of the National Citizen Service; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24120","24120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447686","2016-01-29","Cabinet Office","2016-01-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much funding the National Citizen Service received in each of the last five years; how much it is estimated to receive in each of the next three years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24121","24121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447687","2016-01-28","HM Treasury","2016-01-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make it his policy not to impose a tax on insurance premiums on health cash plans; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24089","24089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447688","2016-01-28","HM Treasury","2016-01-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to table 2.7 on page 85 of the Spending Review and Autumn Statement 2015, which Departments will fund the cross-government overseas development aid spending set out in that table in each of the five years from 2015-16 to 2019-20.","Biography information for Stephen Phillips","Stephen Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24173","24173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447689","2016-01-28","HM Treasury","2016-01-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, to which (a) government departments, (b) agencies, (c) commercial companies and (d) charities HM Revenue and Customs (HMRC) Fast Stream civil servants are (i) attached or (ii) seconded; what the average length of time is for such (A) attachments and (B) secondments; and what assessment HMRC makes of the benefits of those attachments and secondments to its own work and to the tax payer.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24169","24169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447690","2016-01-29","HM Treasury","2016-01-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what meetings he has had with external organisations on Google's tax arrangements in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24175","24175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447691","2016-01-29","HM Treasury","2016-01-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether it is his policy to implement the proposal to legally require Landfill Operators to provide 10 per cent match funding to release Landfill Communities Fund monies and to remove the Contributing Third Party.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24176","24176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447692","2016-01-29","HM Treasury","2016-01-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many notices under section 93 of the Finance Act 2015 were issued by HM Revenue and Customs in the period from 1 April 2015 to 31 December 2015.","Biography information for Nigel Mills","Nigel Mills","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24180","24180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447693","2016-01-29","HM Treasury","2016-01-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many notifications under section 92 of the Finance Act 2015 were received by HM Revenue and Customs during the period from 1 April 2015 to 31 December 2015.","Biography information for Nigel Mills","Nigel Mills","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24181","24181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447694","2016-01-28","HM Treasury","2016-01-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the revenue that will accrue to the Exchequer from the insurance premium tax on health cash plans; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24174","24174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447695","2016-02-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 14 December 2015 to Question 19988, what progress  he has made on finalising monitoring arrangements; and if he will support monitoring of the use of public transport and investment in the North East's bus and rail networks as part of those arrangements.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24228","24228"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447696","2016-01-28","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will take steps to introduce mandatory electrical safety checks for private rented sector properties.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24193","24193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447697","2016-01-28","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what progress his Department has made on improving tenants' access to longer-term family friendly tenancies.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24194","24194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447698","2016-02-01","Home Office","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what response she has made to the recent letter from the Chair of Cambridgeshire and Peterborough Fire and Rescue Authority detailing improvements in that Authority's pay and recruitment arrangements following Ministerial intervention; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stewart Jackson","Mr Stewart Jackson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24263","24263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447699","2016-01-28","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, under what circumstances Ministers in his Department are consulted when a local authority is seeking to dispose of school land for new housing development.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24153","24153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447700","2016-01-28","Department for Transport","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make an assessment of the effect of changes in local authority funding announced in the Autumn Statement and Spending Review 2015 on road safety strategies in local authorities.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24129","24129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447701","2016-01-28","Department for Education","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she has been approached by (a) Stockport local authority, (b) Tameside local authority and (c) the Greater Manchester combined authority to approve the re-designation of school land for housing development in the last three years.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24151","24151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447702","2016-01-28","Department for Education","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what factors she takes into account when considering a request from a local authority to dispose of school sites for redevelopment for new housing.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24152","24152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447703","2016-01-28","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what representations he has received from Calderdale Council since 2010 on the level of local authority funding from central Government.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24095","24095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447704","2016-01-28","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what representations he has received from Calderdale Council since 2010 on the level of the Revenue Support Grant.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24096","24096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447705","2016-01-28","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, by what date it is planned that 100 per cent of residents of (a) Calder Valley and (b) West Yorkshire will have access to superfast broadband.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24094","24094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447706","2016-01-29","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many (a) kilometres of new duct and (b) poles installed by BT with funding from BDUK have been made available for use by other communications providers.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24109","24109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447707","2016-01-29","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, in which BDUK contract areas (a) new duct and (b) poles installed by BT with funding from BDUK have been made available for use by other communications providers.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24105","24105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447708","2016-01-28","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what his policy is on (a) the number and type of wheelchair access and accompanying person spaces at sports stadiums and (b) ticketing prices and arrangements for those spaces; and what support his Department advises such stadiums to extend to those who use wheelchairs and those who accompany them.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24148","24148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447709","2016-01-28","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions he has had with (a) broadcasters and (b) Ofcom on the Ofcom review into the regulatory framework of independent television production; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Nigel Adams","Nigel Adams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24149","24149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447710","2016-01-28","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what guidance his Department gives on the number and type of wheelchair spaces which should be available for disabled people in music venues across the UK.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24168","24168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447711","2016-01-28","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, when he expects part two of the Leveson Inquiry to take place; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24200","24200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447712","2016-01-28","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, when he expects the Clementi review into governance of the BBC to be published.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24201","24201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447713","2016-01-28","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what meetings Ministers and officials in his Department have had with the Premier League on investment in grassroots sport since 2010.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24202","24202"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447714","2016-01-28","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department is taking to help members of the public to attend First World War centenary events held in 2016 in (a) Orkney, (b) Manchester and (c) Thiepval.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24203","24203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447715","2016-01-28","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, when his Department will launch its consultation on the universal service obligation on superfast broadband; and for how long that consultation will be open.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24204","24204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447716","2016-01-28","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many meetings Ministers and civil servants in his Department have had with Ministers and civil servants in the Department for Communities and Local Government on the impact of the local government financial settlement on local arts and culture organisations and projects.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24205","24205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447717","2016-01-28","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, to provide details of each of the meetings that (a) Ministers and (b) civil servants in his Department have had with the Department for Communities and Local Government since May 2015 on the impact of the local government finance settlement on local arts and culture organisations and projects.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24206","24206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447718","2016-01-28","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department is undertaking to assist local authorities in preparing bids for the 2021 UK City of Culture.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24207","24207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447719","2016-02-04","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what preparations the Government is making for the auction of 5G spectrum.","Biography information for Drew Hendry","Drew Hendry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24229","24229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447720","2016-02-04","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, for what reasons the universal service obligation for broadband was set at 10mb; and if he will make it his policy to increase the minimum universal service requirements to reflect higher levels set in other European countries.","Biography information for Drew Hendry","Drew Hendry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24231","24231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447721","2016-02-04","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that all areas of the UK benefit from the award of 2.3 and 3.4 GHz spectrum bands.","Biography information for Drew Hendry","Drew Hendry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24230","24230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447722","2016-01-28","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, on what the £1 million funding provided to the City of Hull to create a legacy as part of its status as the 2017 UK City of Culture was spent.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24208","24208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447723","2016-01-28","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, when he will implement section 40 of the Crime and Courts Act 2013 on awards of costs; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24209","24209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447724","2016-01-29","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the Fleet Ready Escort will meet the Russian ship Mikhail Dudin as he passes through the UK's Exclusive Economic Zone.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24225","24225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447725","2016-01-28","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assistance the UK has given to the Ministries of Defence and armed forces of Poland, Lithuania and Ukraine to help set up a joint multinational brigade.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24198","24198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447726","2016-01-28","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to paragraph 6.55 of the National Security Strategy and Strategic Defence Review 2015, what assessment he has made of the Royal Navy's operational need for an additional two offshore patrol vessels; what estimate he has made of the total cost of each such vessel; and what estimate he has made of the size of crew required by each such vessel.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24212","24212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447727","2016-01-28","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Answer of 27 January 2015 to Question 221410, when he expects the concept phase of the development of a collision warning system for the Typhoon aircraft to be complete; and when he expects an investment decision to be made.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24213","24213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447728","2016-01-29","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Answer of 2 February 2015 to the hon. Member for West Bromwich East to Question 222431, if he will place in the Library a copy of the Reaper User Group terms of reference.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24110","24110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447729","2016-01-29","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much the Royal Air Force Airbus A400M cost from development and approval to the end of 2015.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24122","24122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447730","2016-01-29","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the lifetime cost to the public purse of the Royal Air Force Airbus A400M.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24123","24123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447731","2016-01-29","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether cost comparisons were made between the Boeing C-17 Globemaster and Airbus A400M prior to approval for procurement of the Airbus A400M.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24124","24124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447732","2016-01-29","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the lifetime cost to the public purse of  Army Air Corps and Fleet Air Arm Augusta Westland AW159 Wildcat helicopters.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24125","24125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447733","2016-01-29","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much the Army Air Corps and Fleet Air Arm Augusta Westland AW159 Wildcat helicopters cost from development and approval to the end of 2015.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24126","24126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447734","2016-01-29","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 23 November 2015 to the hon. Member for Bolton South East to Question 16740, to what extent his Department uses US contractors for the training of UK Reaper operators and support personnel.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24127","24127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447735","2016-01-29","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Prime Minister's speech at the Lord Mayor's Banquet on 16 November 2015, what equipment his Department plans to procure under the £2 billion programme of new investment in the special forces.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24140","24140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447736","2016-01-29","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) unauthorised entries to military bases, (b) thefts or losses of classified material, (c) successful cyber attacks on his Department's systems and (d) other security breaches took place in (i) 2014 and (ii) 2015; and what steps his Department took in response to each such breach.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24141","24141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447737","2016-01-29","Department for Education","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to page nine of her Department's response to the Education Committee's Fifth Report of Session 2014-15, Life Lessons: PSHE and SRE in schools, published in July 2015, CM 9121, when her Department plans to report back to the Committee on its full consideration of the arguments made by the Committee on introducing PSHE and SRE as statutory subjects in primary and secondary schools.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24103","24103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447738","2016-01-28","Department for Education","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she has been approached by (a) Stockport local authority, (b) Tameside local authority and (c) Greater Manchester combined authority to approve the removal of protected school land for development under Schedule 14 of the Education Act 2011 in the last three years.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24210","24210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447739","2016-01-28","Department for Education","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what factors she takes into account in considering a request from a local authority to dispose of school sites under Schedule 14 of the Education Act 2011.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24211","24211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447740","2016-01-28","Department for Education","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many pupils in England have been taught in schools rated as outstanding or good by Ofsted in each of the last ten years.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24196","24196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447741","2016-01-28","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps her Department is taking to work with local authorities to reduce the level of fuel poverty.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24195","24195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447742","2016-01-28","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate her Department has made of the proportion of available gas reserves that need to be left in the ground to ensure that global warming is kept to within two degrees.","Biography information for Michelle Donelan","Michelle Donelan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24128","24128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447743","2016-01-29","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment her Department has made of potential sources for exploring fracking sites where sufficient fresh water is not available at that site.","Biography information for Michelle Donelan","Michelle Donelan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24139","24139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447744","2016-01-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent estimate she has made of the number of part-carcasses that are imported from New Zealand.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24132","24132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447745","2016-01-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many copies of the Agra-Europe report on Brexit her Department has.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24130","24130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447746","2016-01-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions she has had with flood insurers on the launch of Flood Re in April 2016.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24134","24134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447747","2016-01-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if her Department and the Rural Payments Agency will issue partial payments to farmers that have not been paid by early February 2016.","Biography information for Michael Tomlinson","Michael Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24177","24177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447748","2016-01-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if the Rural Payments Agency will inform all farmers who are expecting payments of the specific timings that those payments will be expected.","Biography information for Michael Tomlinson","Michael Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24170","24170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447749","2016-01-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether the Government will (a) fund or (b) conduct algal harvesting in order to improve water quality in Poole Harbour.","Biography information for Michael Tomlinson","Michael Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24192","24192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447750","2016-01-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the implications for his policy on Bahrain of the analysis and conclusions of the report by Americans for Democracy and Human Rights in Bahrain, entitled Shattering the Façade, published in November 2015.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24235","24235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447751","2016-01-28","Department of Health","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to prevent the spread of the Zika virus to the UK.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24167","24167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447752","2016-01-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with the UN, the EU and South American countries on the trafficking of women in countries affected by the Zika virus.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24164","24164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447753","2016-01-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with the UN and the EU on helping the Haitian authorities conclude the second round of a presidential election.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24161","24161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447754","2016-01-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what support the Government has provided for post-conflict resolution in Papua New Guinea and Bougainville.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24137","24137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447755","2016-01-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the implications of the cancellation of presidential elections in Haiti.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24162","24162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447756","2016-01-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the effectiveness of the UN stabilization meeting in Haiti in maintaining security in Haiti.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24150","24150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447757","2016-01-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make it his policy to support an independent inquiry into alleged breaches of international humanitarian law in Yemen by the UN Human Rights Council.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24114","24114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447758","2016-01-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what information he holds on the specific role and responsibilities of the UN Special Advisor on Genocide; whether he holds any information on the work undertaken by the Special Advisor in relation to the genocide being perpetrated against Christians and other minorities in Syria and Iraq; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24104","24104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447759","2016-01-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to advance democratic rights in Bahrain.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24100","24100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447760","2016-01-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to his oral Answer of 12 January 2016, Official Report, column 697, on how many occasions the Government has used personnel who are present as a quick check when a report has been received of a potential breach of international humanitarian law in Yemen.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24111","24111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447761","2016-01-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has made an assessment of who is responsible for reported airstrikes that have (a) targeted and (b) hit as collateral damage (i) cultural heritage monuments, (ii) ancient heritage sites and (iii) museums in Yemen.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24112","24112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447762","2016-01-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when the Government has requested the sending state to (a) waive, (b) suspend and (c) remove the rights to diplomatic immunity of an individual diplomat to the UK since 2010.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24113","24113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447763","2016-01-28","Department of Health","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions he has had with the UN, the EU and authorities in affected countries on (a) the spread of the Zika virus and (b) strategies to prevent the spread of the virus.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24163","24163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447764","2016-01-29","Department of Health","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will engage with the #itaffectsme campaign on raising awareness of mental health issues.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24143","24143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447765","2016-01-28","Department of Health","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure mental health services are accessible to BAME communities.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24131","24131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447766","2016-01-29","Department of Health","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 26 January 2016 to Question 23676, when the work being undertaken by Health Education England and NHS England to which he refers will be completed.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24144","24144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447767","2016-01-29","Department of Health","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which organisation is responsible for the personal property of people detained under the Mental Health Act 2007.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24145","24145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447768","2016-01-29","Department of Health","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many men take their own lives in the first year after the birth of their child.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24146","24146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447769","2016-01-28","Department of Health","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to prevent the spread of the Zika virus in the UK.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24166","24166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447770","2016-01-28","Department of Health","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the criteria are for making a ministerial directive against the closure or downsizing of a hospital.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24155","24155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447771","2016-01-29","Department of Health","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department plans to amend social care charging guidance so that compensation awarded to military veterans injured before 6 April 2005 is fully disregarded from financial assessments for support.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24183","24183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447772","2016-01-28","Department of Health","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of the NHS' budget is spent on research and campaigns on (a) gender-specific cancers and (b) fertility treatment.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24172","24172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447773","2016-01-28","Department of Health","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of additional dialysis beds and staff costs to the NHS in the event of NICE's review of TA 85 [ID456] of immunosuppressant agents for kidney transplant is upheld.","Biography information for Mark Durkan","Mark Durkan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24191","24191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447774","2016-01-29","Department of Health","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assistance his Department has offered to Harrow Clinical Commissioning Group to help it avoid its projected deficit of £116.4 million by 2018-19; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24188","24188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447775","2016-01-29","Department of Health","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that injured military veterans do not have to pay social care costs out of their military compensation; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24184","24184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447776","2016-01-29","Home Office","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the information that a person has been arrested and bailed and subsequently released without charge by the Police is required to be provided to the Disclosure and Barring Service (DBS); how long such information is required to remain on that individual's DBS records; and for how long the DBS is required to disclose that information to enquirers.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24227","24227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447777","2016-01-29","Home Office","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average end-to-end time was for applications to the Disclosure and Barring Service (DBS) processed by the Metropolitan Police Force in each year since 2010; and whether her Department makes financial support available for people who are unable to begin work pending a DBS certificate.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24186","24186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447778","2016-01-28","Home Office","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have been extradited from Bangladesh to the UK in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24156","24156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447779","2016-01-28","Home Office","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have been extradited from India to the UK in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24157","24157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447780","2016-01-28","Home Office","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have been extradited from Pakistan to the UK in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24158","24158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447781","2016-01-28","Home Office","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, under what arrangements people can be extradited from Pakistan to the UK.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24159","24159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447782","2016-01-28","Home Office","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans she has to negotiate an extradition treaty with Pakistan.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24160","24160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447783","2016-01-29","Department for International Development","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much UK aid has been provided to (a) Bougainville and (b) Papua New Guinea in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24138","24138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447784","2016-01-29","Department for International Development","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what support her Department is providing to projects that develop opportunities for educational co-operation between Palestinians and Israelis.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24136","24136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447785","2016-01-28","Department for International Development","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what support her Department offers to countries affected by the Zika virus.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24165","24165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447786","2016-01-29","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many data protection breaches there have been by HM Courts and Tribunals Service when dealing with non-devolved tribunals in Scotland since April 2013.","Biography information for Kirsty Blackman","Kirsty Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24107","24107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447787","2016-01-29","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what guidance HM Courts and Tribunals Service use on data protection breaches with regard to non-devolved tribunals in Scotland.","Biography information for Kirsty Blackman","Kirsty Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24106","24106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447788","2016-01-28","Prime Minister","2016-01-26","To ask the Prime Minister, when the Cabinet will next hold a meeting in Wales.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24154","24154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447789","2016-01-29","Prime Minister","2016-01-26","To ask the Prime Minister, pursuant to the Answer of 14 September 2015 to Question 9202, what steps he has taken to reduce the number of peers.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24219","24219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447790","2016-01-28","Department for Transport","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to monitor and evaluate levels of cycling and attitudes to cycling in (a) London, (b) the Cycle Cities and (c) the rest of the UK.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24090","24090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447791","2016-01-28","Department for Transport","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if his Department will undertake a survey of existing cycling and walking infrastructure in English local authorities.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24091","24091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447792","2016-01-28","Department for Transport","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much funding for cycling (a) London and (b) each of the cities which received Cycle City Ambition Grants received in 2014-15; and what the average level of such funding other areas received in that period.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24092","24092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447793","2016-01-29","Department for Transport","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when meetings have taken place between the Rail North board and his Department in the last six months; and what the subject of those meetings was.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24220","24220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447794","2016-01-29","Department for Transport","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what progress he has made on an exemption from the European Commission on the Directive 2006/125/EC on driving licences to enable electric vehicles over 3.5 tonnes to be driven on a B licence.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24216","24216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447795","2016-01-29","Department for Transport","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what rail routes are planned to be designated driver controlled operation in the Northern Franchise.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24223","24223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447796","2016-01-29","Department for Transport","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether meetings of Rail North will be held in public.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24222","24222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447797","2016-01-29","Department for Transport","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what involvement Rail North will have in designating which routes are driver controlled operation in the Northern Franchise.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24221","24221"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447798","2016-01-28","HM Treasury","2016-01-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the reasons are for the different criteria for emissions applying to cars than to motorcycles when road tax values are applied.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24245","24245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447799","2016-01-28","Department for Transport","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent representations he has received about the future of the emergency towing vessels in the Northern Isles; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24197","24197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447800","2016-01-28","Department for Transport","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 11 January 2016 to Question 20570, when the budget for the British Transport Police in 2016-17 will be established.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24232","24232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447801","2016-01-28","Department for Transport","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the financial contribution of Transport for London to the British Transport Police budget is for (a) 2015-16 and (b) 2016-17.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24236","24236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447802","2016-01-28","Department for Transport","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to his Department's press release of 13 January 2016, entitled Transport sector all geared up for winter weather, what plans his Department has to ensure safety of cyclists in the event of bad weather.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24233","24233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447803","2016-01-28","Department for Transport","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to reduce accidents involving pedestrians and (a) cyclists, (b) motorcyclists, (c) cars and (d) heavy goods vehicles.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24234","24234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447804","2016-02-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what progress his Department is making in reducing welfare dependency and increasing wages in Peterborough; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stewart Jackson","Mr Stewart Jackson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24264","24264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447805","2016-01-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of people who were at any time included in the universal credit in-work conditionality pilot are no longer receiving any element of that credit.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24242","24242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447806","2016-01-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether the universal credit in-work conditionality pilots track outcomes for people who are no longer in receipt of that credit.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24243","24243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447807","2016-01-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people receiving universal credit and aged under 25 are subject to a 48 hour working week claimant commitment agreement under the terms of the universal credit in-work conditionality pilot.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24244","24244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447808","2016-01-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to protect pensioners' incomes in (a) Kettering and (b) England.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24226","24226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447809","2016-01-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he plans to publish draft regulations on housing benefit for 18 to 21 year olds.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24093","24093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447810","2016-01-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the outcomes have been of the universal credit in-work conditionality pilots.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24117","24117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447811","2016-01-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what projection his Department has made of the annual spend on the contracted-out element of back to work support for the forthcoming Work and Health Programme; and how that spend compares with the annual spend on the current Work Programme and Work Choice.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24118","24118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447812","2016-01-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people have signed revised claimant commitments as part of the universal credit in-work conditionality pilots.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24115","24115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447813","2016-01-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether he plans to commission and publish an independent evaluation of the universal credit in-work conditionality pilots.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24116","24116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447814","2016-01-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he plans to reply to the letter from the hon. Member for Birkenhead to him dated 19 January 2016 on the state pension.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24182","24182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447815","2016-01-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what data his Department holds on the distribution of contributions to defined-contribution pension schemes for each (a) income level and (b) age.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24178","24178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447816","2016-01-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what data his Department holds on the distribution of deemed contributions to defined-benefit pension schemes for each (a) income level and (b) age.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24179","24179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447817","2016-01-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of people who have suffered a six-month or longer period of sickness in each of the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24187","24187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447818","2016-01-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment he has made of the potential effects of plans to restrict housing benefit for 18 to 21 year olds on those people; and which groups of young people will be exempted from those restrictions.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24199","24199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447819","2016-01-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, which categories of young people it is his policy will be exempt from the new restrictions to housing benefit eligibility.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24133","24133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447820","2016-01-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answers of 23 November 2015 to Questions 16300 and 16301, what proportion of cases with a current liability the 110 non-compliant cases that have been closed as part of the CSA case closure programme represent.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24142","24142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447821","2016-01-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to maintain the UK's position as a market for investment by global pharmaceutical companies.","Biography information for Kit Malthouse","Kit Malthouse","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24238","24238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447822","2016-01-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will make an assessment of the link between government support for UK Life Sciences and pharmaceutical research and development investment in the UK.","Biography information for Kit Malthouse","Kit Malthouse","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24239","24239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447823","2016-01-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the number of student loan borrowers with post-2012 student loan arrangements in (a) Birmingham, Ladywood constituency, (b) the City of Birmingham and (c) the West Midlands metropolitan county.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24240","24240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447824","2016-01-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department is taking to support the life sciences industry.","Biography information for Kit Malthouse","Kit Malthouse","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24275","24275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447825","2016-01-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will make an assessment of the implications for his policy on apprenticeships of the finding of the Institution of Mechanical Engineers in its report, Engineered in Britain, published in December 2015, that more than half of manufacturers think that a lack of skilled people is the biggest danger to UK manufacturing.","Biography information for Philip Boswell","Phil Boswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24343","24343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447826","2016-01-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent steps he has taken to advertise the ACAS-administered Pay and Work Rights Helpline to seafarers recruited from overseas to work in the UK shipping industry.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24305","24305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447827","2016-01-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to ensure effective enforcement of the National Minimum Wage in the maritime sector.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24306","24306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447828","2016-01-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much funding has been allocated to apprenticeships in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Philip Boswell","Phil Boswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24266","24266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447829","2016-01-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many and what proportion of his Department's Named Day Questions have been answered on the named day since September 2015.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24374","24374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447830","2016-01-29","Cabinet Office","2016-01-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people have taken part in the National Citizen Service (NCS) in each of the last five years; how many people he estimates will take part in the NCS in the next three years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24310","24310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447831","2016-01-29","HM Treasury","2016-01-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what information his Department holds on accumulated pension wealth on the lifetime allowance basis.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24315","24315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447832","2016-01-29","HM Treasury","2016-01-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, on what basis his Department assessed the effect of changes to the (a) annual allowance and (b) lifetime allowance on pension contributions.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24316","24316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447833","2016-01-29","HM Treasury","2016-01-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the number of full-time equivalent staff at HM Revenue and Customs on 31 March (a) 2016 and (b) 2017.","Biography information for Rob Marris","Rob Marris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24317","24317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447834","2016-01-28","HM Treasury","2016-01-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to paragraph 1.144 of the Spending Review and Autumn Statement 2015, how much of the £15 million annual VAT revenue from female sanitary products has been (a) spent to date and (b) allocated for future spending; by what process the recipients of those funds are determined; and whether he plans a further round of allocations for financial year 2016-17.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24344","24344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447835","2016-01-28","HM Treasury","2016-01-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will publish the value for money review of the relocation of Oldham HM Revenue and Customs Office to Manchester city centre.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24298","24298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447836","2016-01-29","HM Treasury","2016-01-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what representations he has received from (a) providers of supported housing and (b) organisations representing people with disabilities on the effect of a cap on housing benefit on the provision of supported housing.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24251","24251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447837","2016-01-28","HM Treasury","2016-01-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what feasibility studies or other assessments of basic income schemes have been carried out by HM Treasury officials since 1990; and if he will place copies of any such studies or assessments in the Library.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24355","24355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447838","2016-01-29","HM Treasury","2016-01-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what modelling his Department undertakes on the effect on changes to pension contributions of changes to (a) annual allowance and (b) lifetime allowance; and what sources his Department uses for such modelling.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24255","24255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447839","2016-01-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the loss of income to providers of supported housing from a cap on housing benefit at the rate of local housing allowance.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24250","24250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447840","2016-01-28","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what progress his Department is making on encouraging buy-to-let mortgage lenders to allow longer tenancies in their terms and conditions.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24354","24354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447841","2016-02-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment his Department has made of the effectiveness of round 2 of the Build to Rent scheme in delivering new homes; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stewart Jackson","Mr Stewart Jackson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24376","24376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447842","2016-01-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effect on local authority budgets of people in supported housing not remaining in that housing as a result of a cap on housing benefit at the rate of local housing allowance.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24256","24256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447843","2016-01-29","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the progress made by the Troubled Families initiative in the Peterborough City Council area since 2011; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stewart Jackson","Mr Stewart Jackson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24329","24329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447844","2016-01-29","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many units of housing he expects to be built in the London borough of Newham in each year to 2020.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24336","24336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447845","2016-01-28","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how his Department will measure the progress of the roll-out of the broadband universal service obligation.","Biography information for Drew Hendry","Drew Hendry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24268","24268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447846","2016-01-29","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of Ofcom's review of the future regulatory framework of the independent television production sector; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for David Warburton","David Warburton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24328","24328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447847","2016-01-29","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will discuss with his counterparts in the devolved administrations how to maximise the practical steps being taken across the UK to increase female participation in sports.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24339","24339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447848","2016-01-28","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what his Department's planned expenditure on grant-in-aid to Arts Council England is for (a) 2016-17, (b) 2017-18, (c) 2018-19 and (d) 2019-20.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24352","24352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447849","2016-01-28","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate his Department has made of the income that Arts Council of England will receive from National Lottery funding in (a) 2016-17, (b) 2017-18, (c) 2018-19 and (d) 2019-20.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24353","24353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447850","2016-01-28","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate he has made of the reduction in staff numbers in his Department needed to meet the efficiency and reform savings announced in the Spending Review and Autumn Statement 2015 for the 2015-16 financial year and in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24349","24349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447851","2016-01-28","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions he has had with the BBC on an extension of the current BBC Charter period by order of the Queen in Council.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24351","24351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447852","2016-01-28","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate his Department has made of the proportion of households that will have access to superfast broadband in (a) 2016-17, (b) 2017-18, (c) 2018-19 and (d) 2019-20.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24345","24345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447853","2016-01-28","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, on what dates the inter-Ministerial group on tourism has met; and who is a member of that group.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24346","24346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447854","2016-01-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many apprenticeships were created in the tourism sector in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12, (c) 2012-13 and (d) 2014-15.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24347","24347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447855","2016-01-28","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of satellite broadband for serving rural areas; and what steps his Department is taking to ensure parity of service and cost with other types of broadband supply.","Biography information for Drew Hendry","Drew Hendry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24214","24214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447856","2016-01-28","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the timetable is for the submission of his Department's proposed planning application for Atomic Weapons Establishment (a) Aldermaston and (b) Burghfield.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24295","24295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447857","2016-01-28","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he expects the Mensa warhead assembly and disassembly facility at the Atomic Weapons Establishment Burghfield to begin operation.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24296","24296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447858","2016-01-28","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many times (a) Brimstone missiles, (b) Hellfire missiles and (c) Paveway IV guided bombs have been deployed against targets in (i) Iraq since September 2014 and (ii) Syria since December 2015.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24285","24285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447859","2016-01-28","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the total crew complement of HMS Ocean was on its most recent deployment; of what the Embarked Military Forces she carried consisted; and how many helicopters of which type she carried.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24276","24276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447860","2016-01-28","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which assets his Department plans to decommission over the next 12 months.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24277","24277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447861","2016-01-28","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what his current estimate is of the cost of decommissioning HMS Ocean.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24278","24278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447862","2016-01-28","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when the Government plans to publish its shipbuilding strategy.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24279","24279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447863","2016-01-28","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much income his Department has received from the sale of surplus equipment in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24284","24284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447864","2016-01-28","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many times HMS Ocean has been deployed in the most recent year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24283","24283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447865","2016-01-28","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) permanent staff, (b) temporary staff and (c) contractors are employed at the Atomic Weapons Establishment; and how many such staff he expects to be employed at that Establishment in each of the next three years.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24292","24292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447866","2016-01-28","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) AWE personnel and (b) contractors are working on legacy decommissioning projects at the Atomic Weapons Establishment.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24293","24293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447867","2016-01-28","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the costs are of the Mk4A Trident warhead modification programme for each year of the Nuclear Warhead Capability Sustainment Programme.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24294","24294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447868","2016-01-28","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the total crew complement by rank and specialisation was of each of the Royal Navy's (a) Type 45 Destroyers and (b) Type 23 Frigates on their most recent deployment.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24280","24280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447869","2016-01-28","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many nations have Maritime Patrol Aircraft based at RAF Lossiemouth; how many Maritime Patrol Aircraft are based at RAF Lossiemouth; and which nations have had Maritime Patrol Aircraft based at RAF Lossiemouth at any point in the most recent year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24281","24281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447870","2016-01-28","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the maximum crew complement is of each of the Royal Navy's (a) Type 45 Destroyers and (b) Type 23 Frigates.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24282","24282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447871","2016-01-28","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 26 January 2016 to Question 23285, by what mechanisms the UK strongly asserts its right, and supports that of all States, to exercise Freedom of Navigation in accordance with the International Rules Based System in the South China Sea.","Biography information for Stephen Phillips","Stephen Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24366","24366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447872","2016-01-29","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the contingency fund for the new generation of successor Trident submarines was based on a full quantitative risk assessment of the project.","Biography information for Kate Hollern","Kate Hollern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24257","24257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447873","2016-01-29","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to paragraph 4.75 of the Strategic Defence and Security Review, whether he has established the new team in his Department to act as the single sponsor for all aspects of the nuclear enterprise including procurement.","Biography information for Kate Hollern","Kate Hollern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24258","24258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447874","2016-01-29","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to paragraph 4.75 of the Strategic Defence and Security Review, whether his Department has recruited an experienced, commercial specialist to lead the new nuclear enterprise sponsor team.","Biography information for Kate Hollern","Kate Hollern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24259","24259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447875","2016-01-28","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many and what proportion of (a) Tornado and (b) Typhoon aircraft in the Sustainment Fleet are (i) undergoing planned maintenance, (ii) undergoing upgrade work and (iii) held in temporary storage.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24357","24357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447876","2016-01-29","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to his Statement of 20 July 2015, Official Report, columns 1233-4, on Counter-ISIL Coalition Strategy, if he will publish the location of UK personnel, other than special forces, embedded in other nations' armed forces on a monthly basis.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24323","24323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447877","2016-01-29","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will place in the Library a copy of the UK red card policy for personnel embedded in other nations' armed forces.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24324","24324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447878","2016-01-29","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what coordination he is undertaking with other EU member states on the deployment of military assets to rescue migrants and refugees at risk of drowning in the Mediterranean.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24322","24322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447879","2016-01-29","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to his Statement of 20 July 2015, HCWS 149, whether UK personnel embedded with the US military are subject to US military and domestic criminal law, or UK law, or both.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24325","24325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447880","2016-01-28","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) Tornado and (b) Typhoon aircraft are (i) in the Forward Available Fleet, (ii) in the Sustainment Fleet and (iii) awaiting decommissioning or disposal.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24356","24356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447881","2016-01-28","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many and what proportion of (a) Tornado and (b) Typhoon aircraft in the Forward Available Fleet are classed as short term unserviceable as a result of undergoing (i) short term maintenance and (ii) other short term works.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24358","24358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447882","2016-01-28","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) Tornado and (b) Typhoon aircraft have been temporarily taken out of service as a result of weather damage sustained during (i) combat operations and (ii) training exercises in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24359","24359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447883","2016-01-28","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much has been spent on (a) maintenance of and (b) upgrade works for (i) Tornado, (ii) Typhoon and (iii) Reaper drones in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24360","24360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447884","2016-01-28","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Tornado aircraft are fitted with the Honeywell Traffic Alert and Collision Avoidance System II; and how many are currently being fitted with that system.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24361","24361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447885","2016-01-28","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he expects the process of fitting Tornado aircraft with the Honeywell Traffic Alert and Collision Avoidance System II to be completed.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24362","24362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447886","2016-01-29","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to his Written Statement of 20 July 2015, HCWS 149, if he will make it his policy to publish the (a) numbers, (b) units and (c) dates of embedded service of UK personnel embedded in other nations' armed forces on a monthly basis.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24370","24370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447887","2016-01-29","Department for Education","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to her contribution of 25 January 2016, Official Report, column 12, what funding streams and programmes made up the £70 million which the Government is spending on careers advice in the current Parliament.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24368","24368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447888","2016-01-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what plans he has to provide assistance to further education institutions which incur financial penalties as a result of triggering break clauses in the loan agreements they hold with banks resulting from his Department's area reviews.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24265","24265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447889","2016-01-29","Department for Education","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many school-aged children in each London borough attended a maintained school outside their borough of residency on 1 January of each year from 2010 to 2016.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24303","24303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447890","2016-01-29","Department for Education","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the average distance between home and school was for school-aged children in (a) London and (b) each London borough on 1 January in each year from 2010 to 2016.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24301","24301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447891","2016-01-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will make an assessment of the financial penalties potentially faced by further education institutions resulting from triggering break clauses in the loan agreements they hold with banks resulting from his Department's area reviews.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24367","24367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447892","2016-01-28","Department for Education","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will take steps to prevent the E-ACT Academy chain from dismissing community governors from its school governing bodies.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24297","24297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447893","2016-01-28","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to her oral contribution of 18 January 2016, Official Report, column 1152, on subsidies for low carbon power, what recent estimate she has made of the year by which new nuclear generation at (a) Hinkley point C, (b) Sizewell C, (c) Wylfa Newydd, (d) Oldbury and (e) Moorside is likely to operate on a subsidy-free basis; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24364","24364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447894","2016-01-28","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether the entering into force of the agreement between the UK and EDF to proceed with Hinkley Point C is conditional on the Flamanville successfully demonstrating capability of operation; what recent conversations her Department has had with EDF about the findings of the French Nuclear Safety Authority on tests on the Flamanville EPR reactor vessel head and bottom and the implications for her policies  on new nuclear power; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24363","24363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447895","2016-01-28","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps she has taken to protect recipients of Green Deal funding from companies whose work is not of an acceptable standard.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24271","24271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447896","2016-01-29","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what plans she has for long-term sustainable household energy efficiency measures in the period after 2017.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24341","24341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447897","2016-01-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to support milk producers in ensuring milk prices in supermarkets are maintained.","Biography information for Richard Arkless","Richard  Arkless","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24318","24318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447898","2016-01-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to work with farmers and land owners in areas susceptable to flooding to encourage them to allow parts of their land to flood to avoid flooding elsewhere.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24300","24300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447899","2016-01-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of increasing the use of upland management schemes in areas susceptible to flooding as a method of flood prevention.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24299","24299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447900","2016-01-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to support military efforts to tackle Islamic State in Libya.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24290","24290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447901","2016-01-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to help stabilise Libya.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24291","24291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447902","2016-01-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what information he has about the individual who currently holds the position of UN Special Advisor on Genocide; what recent representations to that individual about the killings by Daesh of Christians and other minorities in Syria and Iraq; and what plans he has to meet the Special Advisor to discuss the crisis in those countries.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24314","24314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447903","2016-01-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has received on the interpretation and implementation of the UN Convention on the Prevention and Punishment of Genocide in relation to the killings by Daesh of Christians and other minorities in Syria and Iraq; what response he has made to such representations; what steps he is taking to establish an international consensus on that issue; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24335","24335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447904","2016-01-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what information he holds on the number of Iraqi and Syrian Christians and other religious minorities who have been murdered or displaced from their homes by Daesh in each of the last five years; and what steps he is taking to provide practical assistance and asylum opportunities to persecuted Christians seeking to flee that region.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24334","24334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447905","2016-01-29","Department of Health","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people were (a) eligible and (b) participated in the bowel cancer screening programme in (i) England and (ii) each of that programme's five hubs and (iii) each of the 63 screening centres included in that programme in 2014-15.","Biography information for Mr John Baron","Mr John Baron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24375","24375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447906","2016-01-29","Department of Health","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, on what grounds the discharge of youths from Child and Adolescent Mental Health Services (CAMHS) is based on school years rather than date of birth; and if he will change the basis for discharge from CAMHS.","Biography information for Michelle Donelan","Michelle Donelan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24333","24333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447907","2016-01-29","Department of Health","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many prescriptions were issued for medication in each London borough in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24369","24369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447908","2016-01-28","Department of Health","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of nurse training places in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24269","24269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447909","2016-01-29","Department of Health","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much his Department and its executive agencies spent on advertising to promote awareness of the health risks associated with alcohol in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24319","24319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447910","2016-01-29","Department of Health","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people from BAME communities registered to become organ donors in each of the last five years; and what assessment he has made of trends in such registration.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24337","24337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447911","2016-01-29","Department of Health","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will discuss with his counterparts in the devolved administrations steps to ensure that programmes such as Young People's Improving Access to Psychological Therapies can be implemented across the UK.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24338","24338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447912","2016-01-29","Department of Health","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress his Department has made on establishing ex gratia financial support for people who were affected prior to 1991 by (a) HIV and (b) hepatitis C over the last 12 months.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24340","24340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447913","2016-01-29","Department of Health","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of junior doctors have taken a break from NHS training after completing their foundation year in each of the last 10 years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24312","24312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447914","2016-01-29","Department of Health","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people applied to study medicine at university in each of the last 10 years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24313","24313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447915","2016-01-28","Department of Health","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he plans to amend current charging rules for veterans injured in service before 5 April 2015 on compensation awarded under the War Pensions Scheme being taken into account in assessing the cost of their social care support.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24342","24342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447916","2016-01-28","Department of Health","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if his Department will change local authority public health team regulations to ensure that (a) public mental health no longer falls under the heading of miscellaneous and (b) there is parity of esteem between physical and mental health in the activity of such teams.","Biography information for Jason McCartney","Jason McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24286","24286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447917","2016-01-28","Department of Health","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent representations he has received from thalidomide survivors' groups; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24287","24287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447918","2016-01-28","Department of Health","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions the Minister for Public Health has had with mental health charities on the importance of public mental health interventions.","Biography information for Jason McCartney","Jason McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24241","24241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447919","2016-01-28","Department of Health","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which NHS Walk-in Centres have closed in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Mr David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24215","24215"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447920","2016-01-28","Department of Health","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of hospitals in England that have at least one embedded specialist nurse dealing specifically with organ donation.","Biography information for Dame Caroline Spelman","Mrs Caroline Spelman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24365","24365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/447921","2016-01-29","Department of Health","2016-01-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many companies have been ordered by the NHS Identity Team to stop using the NHS logo in the last three years.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 24246","24246"
