"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177515","2015-02-05","Department of Health","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many diabetes specialist nurses were employed in East Lancashire in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223083","223083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177516","2015-02-05","Department of Health","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people were diagnosed with diabetes in East Lancashire in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223084","223084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177517","2015-02-05","Department of Health","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of people in (a) Pendle constituency and (b) Lancashire who have been diagnosed with diabetes are receiving the nine basic monitoring tests.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223085","223085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177518","2015-02-05","Department of Health","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 2 February 2014 to Question 222307, when his Department next plans to meet the manufacturers of the MenB vaccine; and by what date he expects negotiations with those manufacturers to be concluded.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223086","223086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177519","2015-02-05","Department for Education","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many registered educational psychologists are (a) employed by her Department and (b) working in schools in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223021","223021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177520","2015-02-05","Department of Health","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, purusant to the Answer of 26 January 2015 to Question 221173, if he will make it his policy to require NHS England to (a) improve the collection of data relating to musculoskeletal conditions and (b) determine the number of people with musculoskeletal conditions who have had an operation cancelled for non-clinical reasons in this financial year.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223006","223006"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177521","2015-02-05","Department of Health","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which NHS bodies are responsible for monitoring costs and performance of PFI contracts.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223023","223023"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177522","2015-02-05","Department of Health","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his assessment is of the effect on service providers of the proposed methodology for determining national prices for NHS services.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223008","223008"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177523","2015-02-09","Department of Health","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress has been made by the working group established to develop a robust process to support the sustainable long-term commissioning of cancer drugs; when he expects the outcomes of their work to be published; and what steps he will take to reduce variations in access to cancer drugs depending on when an application to the Cancer Drugs Fund is made.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223060","223060"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177524","2015-02-09","Department of Health","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to Public Health England's report on HIV in the UK, published in November 2014, what the evidential basis was of the conclusions in the report; from what sources that data was derived; how frequently such data is published; and when data equivalent to that data will next be published.","Biography information for Sir Simon Burns","Mr Simon Burns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223027","223027"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177525","2015-02-09","Department of Health","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what data is used to inform the quality dashboard programme developed by NHS England to monitor the quality of HIV care; from what sources that data was derived; how frequently such data is published; and when equivalent data will next be published.","Biography information for Sir Simon Burns","Mr Simon Burns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223028","223028"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177526","2015-02-09","Department of Health","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people had hernia operations in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223197","223197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177527","2015-02-05","Department of Health","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to reduce translation and interpretation costs in the NHS.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223190","223190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177528","2015-02-09","Department of Health","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make an estimate of the potential cost of implementing each clause of the National Health Service (Amended Duties and Powers) Bill.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223177","223177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177529","2015-02-09","Department of Health","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Royal College of Paediatrics and Child Health Medical Workforce Census 2013, published in December 2014, what plans he has to facilitate integration between child health services and child mental health services.","Biography information for Stuart Andrew","Stuart Andrew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223146","223146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177530","2015-02-09","Department of Health","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Royal College of Paediatrics and Child Health Medical Workforce Census 2013, published in December 2014, what plans he has to increase the community paediatric workforce.","Biography information for Stuart Andrew","Stuart Andrew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223147","223147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177531","2015-02-05","Department of Health","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the incurred but not reported provision for clinical negligence is in 2014-15.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223120","223120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177532","2015-02-05","Department of Health","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many Strategic Executive Information System reports dating from before the Health and Social Care Act 2012 are waiting conclusion.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223214","223214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177533","2015-02-05","Department of Health","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will bring forward proposals to amend the statutory guidance for the Care Act 2014 to ensure that local authorities take steps to discourage the use of zero-hours contracts by the care providers they commission.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223229","223229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177534","2015-02-05","Department of Health","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when the independent market study of alcohol labelling will be published.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223212","223212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177535","2015-02-05","Department of Health","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to reduce (a) demographic and (b) geographic inequalities in (i) cervical screening uptake and (ii) HPV vaccination rates.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame M. Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223210","223210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177536","2015-02-09","Department of Health","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much the Government has invested in research into psychological therapies in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223261","223261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177537","2015-02-09","Department of Health","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress he has made on agreeing a collective target with industry on the responsible promotion of food under the Responsibility Deal.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223262","223262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177538","2015-02-09","Department of Health","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much funding his Department is providing for the Health Exercise and Nutrition for the Really Young programme; and in which area it is being rolled out.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223258","223258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177539","2015-02-09","Department of Health","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what training health visitors receive on nutrition.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223259","223259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177540","2015-02-09","Department of Health","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to set minimum nurse staffing levels on wards in English hospitals.","Biography information for Roger Williams","Roger Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223257","223257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177541","2015-02-09","Department of Health","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will direct NHS England to publish all submissions to its Stereotactic Radiosurgery Review.","Biography information for Tessa Munt","Tessa Munt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223266","223266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177542","2015-02-09","Department of Health","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will direct NHS England to enable University College London Hospital to use the Gamma Knife on the same terms as it enables University Hospitals Bristol to use that equipment.","Biography information for Tessa Munt","Tessa Munt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223267","223267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177543","2015-02-05","Department of Health","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of the NHS budget is spent on prevention of ill health.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223235","223235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177544","2015-02-09","Home Office","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the performance of Dorset Police in meeting the standards required by its service level agreement with the Disclosure and Barring Service; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223269","223269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177545","2015-02-09","Home Office","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many and what proportion of police checks commissioned by the Disclosure and Barring Service from Dorset Police were completed within (a) 60, (b) 25, (c) 18 and (d) 14 days in the most recent six months for which figures are available; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223270","223270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177546","2015-02-05","Ministry of Justice","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many appeals against decisions (a) not to award and (b) to stop support provided under section 4 of the Immigration and Asylum Act 1999 there have been in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sarah Teather","Sarah Teather","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223220","223220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177547","2015-02-05","Home Office","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many unaccompanied asylum-seeking children granted discretionary leave to remain were subject to an enforced removal after turning 18 in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sarah Teather","Sarah Teather","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223221","223221"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177548","2015-02-05","Home Office","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many individuals have applied for an administrative review under paragraph 34M of Part 1 of the Immigration Rules since 20 October 2014.","Biography information for Sarah Teather","Sarah Teather","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223224","223224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177549","2015-02-05","Home Office","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many asylum applicants receiving support under section 4 of the Immigration and Asylum Act 1999 have been receiving that support for more than (a) two, (b) four and (c) six years; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sarah Teather","Sarah Teather","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223236","223236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177550","2015-02-09","Home Office","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 2 February 2015 to Questions 221902, how many of the asylum claimants referred to in the Answer were granted leave to remain in the UK.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223158","223158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177551","2015-02-05","Home Office","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to reduce translation and interpretation costs in police forces.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223192","223192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177552","2015-02-05","Ministry of Justice","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the availability of drugs in prisons.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223036","223036"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177553","2015-02-05","Cabinet Office","2015-02-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment he has made of recent trends in the level of (a) violent crime and (b) theft in Ealing, Southall constituency.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223007","223007"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177554","2015-02-09","Home Office","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of foreign national arrests under Operation Nexus were made up of each of the top three nationalities involved in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223103","223103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177555","2015-02-09","Home Office","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she expects to appoint the next Independent Chief Inspector of Borders and Immigration.","Biography information for Sarah Teather","Sarah Teather","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223108","223108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177556","2015-02-09","Home Office","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people granted discretionary leave to remain in the last three years have subsequently been (a) granted and (b) refused a further grant of leave to remain.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223109","223109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177557","2015-02-05","Home Office","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of how many (a) pleasure, (b) class XII and (c) other small vessels enter UK ports of entry each year without (i) passport and (ii) physical checks.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223102","223102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177558","2015-02-09","Home Office","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many drink-driving offences were recorded by police force and successful prosecutions there have been in (a) England and (b) Wales in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223163","223163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177559","2015-02-09","Home Office","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) arrests were made and (b) prosecutions conducted for road traffic offences in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223162","223162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177560","2015-02-05","Home Office","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many dangerous driving offences were recorded by each police force in (a) England and (b) Wales in each of the last five years; and how many of those offences were successfully prosecuted in each of those countries in each of those years.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223122","223122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177561","2015-02-09","Home Office","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many drink-driving offences were recorded by each police force in (a) England and (b) Wales in each of the last five years; and how many successful prosecutions of such offences there were in each of those countries in each of those years.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223164","223164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177562","2015-02-09","Home Office","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many driving offences relating to mobile telephone use were recorded by each police force in (a) England and (b) Wales in each of the last five years; and how many such offences were successfully prosecuted in each of those countries in each of those years.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223165","223165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177563","2015-02-05","Home Office","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will ensure that the gender of the (a) perpetrator and (b) victim of incidents marked as domestic violence cases are recorded along with the nature of the domestic relationship in each case.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223072","223072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177564","2015-02-09","Home Office","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what guidance her Department has issued to schools, colleges and universities on their obligations to tackle extremism.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223065","223065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177565","2015-02-05","Department for International Development","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what the objectives are for the World Bank's Global Partnership for Social Accountability; what role her Department plays on that partnership's steering committee; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Sir Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223025","223025"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177566","2015-02-09","Ministry of Justice","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what criteria are applied to children and young people applying to the Exceptional Case Funding scheme.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223066","223066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177567","2015-02-09","Ministry of Justice","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will passport all (a) children and (b) young people aged from 18 to 24 through the Exceptional Case Funding scheme.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223067","223067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177568","2015-02-05","Ministry of Justice","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the religious belief was of each person convicted of terrorist-related offences in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223073","223073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177569","2015-02-05","Ministry of Justice","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, was the (a) original offence, (b) original sentence, (c) amount of the original sentence served, (d) date of the subsequent offence resulting in a custodial sentence, (e) type of further offence committed, (f) length of the subsequent custodial sentence handed down and (g) amount of the subsequent sentence actually served for each offender released from custody after serving a sentence handed down following the riots in London in 2011 who has subsequently been returned to custody.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223075","223075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177570","2015-02-05","Ministry of Justice","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people who were not sentenced to a term of imprisonment after offending during the riots in London in 2011 have subsequently been convicted of a further offence.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223076","223076"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177571","2015-02-05","Ministry of Justice","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what terrorist-related offences were committed by which prisoners released from prison in 2013 and 2014; what the length of each sentence given to each such prisoner was; and how long was served in each such case.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223077","223077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177572","2015-02-05","Ministry of Justice","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the largest amounts were of each class of drug charged as a drugs possession only offence in the last year for which information is available.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223070","223070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177573","2015-02-05","Ministry of Justice","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners convicted of what terrorist-related offences have been released on temporary licence since 14 November 2014.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223078","223078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177574","2015-02-09","Ministry of Justice","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many applications from people aged (a) under 18 and (b) 18 to 24 to the Exceptional Case Funding scheme have been successful.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223099","223099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177575","2015-02-09","Ministry of Justice","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many orders for compensation for victims were made in courts in North Wales in the last three years for which information is available.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223110","223110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177576","2015-02-05","Ministry of Justice","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to reduce translation and interpretation costs in the courts.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223191","223191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177577","2015-02-09","Ministry of Justice","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much compensation has been ordered to be paid by courts in North Wales in the last three years for which records are available; and how much of that sum has been recovered from those ordered to pay compensation.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223159","223159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177578","2015-02-09","Ministry of Justice","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answers of 2 February 2015 to Questions 221907 and 221908 if he will review the provision of legal aid to potential victims of human trafficking in advance of their referral to the UK national referral mechanism.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223156","223156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177579","2015-02-09","Ministry of Justice","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 2 February 2015 to Questions 221878, 221879 and 221883, and with reference to his statement in those answers that figures in relation to the number of civil claims brought by victims of trafficking and damages awarded are not available, what the evidential basis is for his assessment that the remedies available to victims of trafficking under the civil law of tort are adequate and effective.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223157","223157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177580","2015-02-05","Ministry of Justice","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of whether the number of judges recruited in each year is sufficient to meet the needs of the Tribunal Service.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223237","223237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177581","2015-02-05","Prime Minister","2015-02-03","To ask the Prime Minister, what discussions have taken place in the National Security Council of measures to protect (a) nuclear facilities and (b) other strategic national infrastructure from unmanned aerial vehicle attacks in (i) 2014 and (ii) 2015.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223039","223039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177582","2015-02-05","Department for Transport","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to ensure that public transport operators reduce fares to pass onto passengers the benefit of falling petrol and diesel prices.","Biography information for Gordon Henderson","Gordon Henderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223111","223111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177583","2015-02-05","Department for Transport","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether any changes are planned to the notification system for those pets killed on the strategic road network after the micro-chipping law comes into force in 2016.","Biography information for Jason McCartney","Jason McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223087","223087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177584","2015-02-05","Department for Transport","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to ensure that where Network Rail pays compensation to a train operating company, there is a duty on the company (a) to pass on a proportion of that compensation to all affected passengers and (b) to pro-actively inform passengers of that automatic entitlement; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223225","223225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177585","2015-02-05","Department for Transport","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 26 January 2015 to Question 222065, what amount was spent on each of the 10 largest items of media and publicity expenditure in 2013-14.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223207","223207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177586","2015-02-05","Department for Transport","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 29 January 2015 to Question 222103, how many vehicles were clamped by the DVLA wheel-clamping service in 2013-14.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223206","223206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177587","2015-02-05","Department for Transport","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 2 February 2015 to Question 222099, what the amount spent was on each instance of reprographic expenditure totalling more than £10,000 in 2013-14.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223200","223200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177588","2015-02-05","Department for Transport","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 22 January 2015 to Question 221264, in respect of which projects or programmes were the sums for Ove Arup & Partners Limited, Atkins Limited, Environmental Resources Management Limited and CH2M Hill UK incurred.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223199","223199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177589","2015-02-05","Department for Transport","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 29 January 2015 to Question 222103, what proportion of the costs relating to the Modernising Employment Contract Buyout and subsequent merger of VOSA and DSA to form the DVSA were paid in (a) severance payments for employees and (b) lieu of notice; and how many people were in receipt of such payments.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223198","223198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177590","2015-02-09","Department for Transport","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will have discussions with Network Rail on West Coast Mainline possession in the light of recent disruption on the Chiltern line.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223263","223263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177591","2015-02-05","Department for Transport","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 3 February 2015 to Question 222607, what savings have accrued to the public purse from closure of driving centres in Scotland since 2010-11.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223130","223130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177592","2015-02-05","Wales Office","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what recent meetings he has held with the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport on improving broadband access in areas along the Wales-England border.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223041","223041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177593","2015-02-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many Work Programme participants have entered Payment Group One since June 2011; and how many of those participants were identified as being not in employment, education or training before entering the programme.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223096","223096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177594","2015-02-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department has taken to reclaim overpayments from Work Programme providers since June 2011; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223098","223098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177595","2015-02-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what progress has been made in establishing a network of mental health, intellectual and cognitive champions in each Atos Medical Examination Centre since November 2010.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223097","223097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177596","2015-02-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many applications were made for short-term benefit advance in 2014; and how many of these applications were successful.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223104","223104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177597","2015-02-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many jobseeker's allowance claimants have been sanctioned on (a) one, (b) two and (c) three occasions or more; and what the average length of each sanction is.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223105","223105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177598","2015-02-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average time taken to process new claims for jobseeker's allowance was in 2014.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223107","223107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177599","2015-02-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what efficiency audit his Department's National Partnership Team has undertaken of the effectiveness of measures established to ensure the take-up of the attendance allowance.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223115","223115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177600","2015-02-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what investigation he has carried out of the cancellation of the eligibility for benefits of the family of Tommi Miller from Cambridge after his cancer returned following remission; and what steps he has taken to ensure such cancellations do not take place in similar circumstances in future.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223113","223113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177601","2015-02-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what representations he has received on the standard of service provided by the Health and Safety Executive when engaged in an intervention inspection; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mark Garnier","Mark Garnier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223022","223022"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177602","2015-02-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the current average time is from the point of application for people with (a) cancer and (b) motor neurone disease to receive their benefit entitlement under the special rules for terminal illness.","Biography information for Mr Ian Davidson","Mr Ian Davidson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223035","223035"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177603","2015-02-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether his Department still plans to publish average waiting times for personal independence payment assessments and decisions in March 2015.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223024","223024"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177604","2015-02-05","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what discussions his Department has had with water companies on payment of the living wage in that sector.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223140","223140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177605","2015-02-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many calls were made to the winter fuel payment helpline 08459 151515 in each of the last five financial years; how much revenue was generated by these calls; and when he expects to end the use of this number.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223167","223167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177606","2015-02-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 3 February 2015 to Question 222124, what information his Department holds on money withheld in benefit sanctions.","Biography information for Ann McKechin","Ann McKechin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223166","223166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177607","2015-02-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the average proportion of pensioners' energy bills that was met by the winter fuel payment in winter (a) 2003-04 and (b) 2013-14.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223155","223155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177608","2015-02-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent representations he has received in favour of allowing work programme participants to claim the new enterprise allowance; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223153","223153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177609","2015-02-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to reduce translation and interpretation costs in benefit offices.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223193","223193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177610","2015-02-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Impact Assessment for the Welfare Reform Act 2012, whether his estimate of the number of people who will have higher entitlement as a result of universal credit in each of the next five years is the same as that in that Assessment.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223271","223271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177611","2015-02-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Impact Assessment for the Welfare Reform Act 2012, whether his estimate of the number of people who will have lower entitlement as a result of universal credit in each of the next five years is the same as that in that Assessment.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223272","223272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177612","2015-02-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Impact Assessment for the Welfare Reform Act 2012, whether his estimate of the net decrease in social security payments that will arise from the introduction of universal credit in each of the next five years is the same as that in that Assessment.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223273","223273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177613","2015-02-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 27 January 2015 to Question 222298, how much was paid to overseas recipients of (a) pension credit, (b) winter fuel allowance and (c) the Christmas bonus in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223208","223208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177614","2015-02-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much his Department estimates it will raise in child maintenance service charges in (a) the UK, (b) Scotland, (c) England, (d) Wales and (e) Northern Ireland in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223209","223209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177615","2015-02-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Impact Assessment for the Welfare Reform Act 2012, whether his estimate of the decrease in social security payments that will arise from the introduction of universal credit due to reduced fraud, error and overpayments in each of the next five years is the same as that in that Assessment.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223274","223274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177616","2015-02-05","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when his Department plans to announce its decision on the funding of local welfare provision in 2015-16.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223218","223218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177617","2015-02-05","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will put safeguards in place to ensure that families affected by future reductions in local welfare provision do not use high-cost lenders.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223217","223217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177618","2015-02-05","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when the Government plans to publish the results of its consultation on local welfare provision in 2015 to 2016.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223216","223216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/178181","2015-02-09","Home Office","2015-02-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of the Government's strategy for ending female genital mutilation.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 907501","907501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177064","2015-02-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 19 January 2015 to Question 220513, what proportion of those start-up loans drawn down by Black and minority ethnic people were to individuals of (a) Pakistani, (b) Indian and (c) Bangladeshi ethnic origin.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222840","222840"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177065","2015-02-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 28 January 2015 to Question 221259, on how many occasions banks which have accessed funds on behalf of borrowers under the Enterprise Finance Guarantee scheme have subsequently made a claim on the public purse following default.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222830","222830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177066","2015-02-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 28 January 2015 to Question 221259, how many companies which accessed funds under the Enterprise Finance Guarantee scheme subsequently received public funds following liquidation.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222831","222831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177067","2015-02-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 28 January 2015 to Question 221259, how many companies which accessed funds from each lender under the Enterprise Finance Guarantee scheme have defaulted.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222832","222832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177068","2015-02-05","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department has taken that benefit micro enterprises in Glasgow South West constituency.","Biography information for Mr Ian Davidson","Mr Ian Davidson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222864","222864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177069","2015-02-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to ban large firms requiring pay to stay agreements from companies seeking to remain or become their approved suppliers.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222851","222851"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177070","2015-02-05","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many young people living in (a) Leeds and (b) Leeds Central constituency entered higher education in each of the last 20 years.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222909","222909"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177071","2015-02-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimates of university application numbers his Department used when making the decision to remove student number controls.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222895","222895"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177072","2015-02-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent estimate his Department has made of numbers of applications to English universities in (a) 2015-16, (b) 2016-17, (c) 2017-18, (d) 2018-19 and (e) 2019-20; and what effect the decision to remove student number controls in December 2013 has had on those estimates.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222896","222896"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177073","2015-02-05","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that local small businesses will be part of the supply chain for the Hinkley Point C development.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222899","222899"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177074","2015-02-05","HM Treasury","2015-02-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether his Department has made an assessment of the effect on the market for Cloud services of refunding VAT for contracted-out services but not for Cloud services.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222929","222929"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177075","2015-02-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, for what reason the value of extant standard individual export licences to Israel and the Occupied Palestinian Territories fell from £7.9 billion, as stated in his letter of 12 May 2014 to the hon. Member for Tonbridge and Malling, to £93 million, as stated in his letter of 15 December 2014 to the same hon. Member.","Biography information for Sir John Stanley","Sir John Stanley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222938","222938"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177076","2015-02-05","Cabinet Office","2015-02-02","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many and what proportion of people aged 50 and over were unemployed for longer than (a) 12 months and (b) two years in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222930","222930"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177077","2015-02-04","Cabinet Office","2015-02-02","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what guidance he has issued on the criteria for the classification of major projects; what documentation would be necessary to ensure classification as such a project; and whether a business case and impact assessment is required for classification as a major project.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222986","222986"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177078","2015-02-04","HM Treasury","2015-02-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to paragraph 1.201 in the Autumn Statement 2014, how the £78 million allocated to The Factory Manchester will be spent; and from which departmental budget that funding will come.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222979","222979"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177079","2015-02-04","HM Treasury","2015-02-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to paragraph 1.133 in the Autumn Statement 2014, how the £141 million allocated to the Olympicopolis project will be spent; and from which departmental budget that funding will come.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222980","222980"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177080","2015-02-05","HM Treasury","2015-02-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much his Department has allocated to the Conflict, Stability and Security Fund in (a) 2014-15 and (b) 2015-16.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222960","222960"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177081","2015-02-05","HM Treasury","2015-02-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what amount his Department has allocated for advertising in each financial year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222865","222865"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177082","2015-02-05","HM Treasury","2015-02-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the viability of proposals for the creation of a Citizens' Wealth Fund.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222857","222857"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177083","2015-02-04","HM Treasury","2015-02-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if his Department will make an assessment of the effect that accelerated payment notices have had on small and medium-sized businesses.","Biography information for Mark Field","Mark Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222933","222933"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177084","2015-02-04","HM Treasury","2015-02-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent steps he has taken to encourage banks to offer their services to money service businesses.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222940","222940"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177085","2015-02-04","HM Treasury","2015-02-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much revenue was accrued to the Exchequer in air passenger duty from Manchester Airport in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222889","222889"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177086","2015-02-04","HM Treasury","2015-02-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment was undertaken of the effect of a zero-rate air passenger duty in Scotland on airports in Northern England before taking the decision to devolve the setting of that duty.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222890","222890"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177087","2015-02-04","HM Treasury","2015-02-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate his Department has made of the potential cost to Manchester Airport of a zero-rate air passenger duty for Scotland.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222891","222891"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177088","2015-02-05","HM Treasury","2015-02-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the income tax gap in Scotland in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222911","222911"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177089","2015-02-05","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the cost is of recent appointments to the Independent Improvement Panel to Birmingham City Council; and what body is funding those costs.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222916","222916"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177090","2015-02-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what discussions he has had with his counterparts in other European countries on homelessness.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222897","222897"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177091","2015-02-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the contribution of the hon. Member for St Albans of 26 January 2015, Official Report, column 648, if he will make it his policy to issue new guidance during the planning process that will put an obligation on commercial buildings to have zero-carbon or low-carbon emissions.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222942","222942"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177092","2015-02-05","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the proposal to withdraw funding for the Local Welfare Assistance scheme on (a) families and (b) households on low incomes.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222925","222925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177093","2015-02-05","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, under what circumstances the interim mayor of Greater Manchester city-region will be appointed for a further term.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222931","222931"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177094","2015-02-05","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether public scrutiny arrangements will be established before devolution of budgets to the eleventh leader of Greater Manchester planned under the devolution agreement.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222928","222928"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177095","2015-02-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many people were sleeping rough in (a) the UK, (b) England, (c) Yorkshire, (d) Kirklees and (e) Huddersfield in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222836","222836"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177096","2015-02-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what meetings he has had with charities and lobbying organisations on homelessness in the last two years.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222837","222837"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177097","2015-02-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what guidance his Department issues to local authorities on measures to reduce homelessness.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222838","222838"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177098","2015-02-05","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he took to ensure that the identities and needs of local communities were reflected in the proposal to amend the constitution of Greater Manchester Combined Authority.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222881","222881"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177099","2015-02-05","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what consultations his Department had with local communities on the proposal to amend the constitution of Greater Manchester Combined Authority.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222882","222882"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177100","2015-02-05","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether responses to the consultation on the proposal to amend the constitution of Greater Manchester Combined Authority will be published.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222883","222883"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177101","2015-02-05","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Written Statement of 28 November 2014, Official Report, column 54WS, on small-scale developers, what estimate his Department has made of the financial effect on (a) Cumbria County Council and (b) Copeland Borough Council of financial credit being deducted from affordable housing contributions for vacant buildings brought into lawful use.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222955","222955"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177102","2015-02-05","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Written Statement of 28 November 2014, Official Report, column 54WS, on small-scale developers, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of obligations under the amended Section 106 of the Town and Country Planning Act 1990 on the availability of affordable housing.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222956","222956"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177103","2015-02-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will bring forward legislative proposals giving local authorities powers to implement rent controls.","Biography information for Ian Paisley","Ian Paisley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222996","222996"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177104","2015-02-04","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, which sectors that receive creative tax reliefs have implemented voluntary levies for training since May 2010.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222984","222984"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177105","2015-02-04","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will bring forward legislative proposals for a British Sign Language Bill to promote the use of British Sign Language.","Biography information for Ian Paisley","Ian Paisley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222997","222997"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177106","2015-02-04","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many local broadband projects have not provided detailed maps and postcode checkers to his Department for its rural broadband project.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222975","222975"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177107","2015-02-04","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether his Department will be represented at the #Digital4EU stakeholder forum hosted by the European Commission in Brussels on 24 February 2015.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222985","222985"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177108","2015-02-04","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what the initial deadline was for his Department's rural broadband project; and what deadline he now expects for that project.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222976","222976"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177109","2015-02-04","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will publish the outline business case for phase 2 of the rural broadband project.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222977","222977"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177110","2015-02-04","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he took to develop and cost other procurement frameworks for phase 2 of the rural broadband project.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222978","222978"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177111","2015-02-04","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what (a) meetings, (b) emails, (c) letters and (d) telephone calls have taken place between his Department and PCS and Prospect unions in 2015 to date.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222987","222987"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177112","2015-02-04","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent representations he has received on the possible privatisation of the (a) National Gallery and (b) Imperial War Museum.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222988","222988"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177113","2015-02-04","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, which organisations in receipt of grant-in-aid from his Department pay the (a) Living Wage and (b) London Living Wage.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222989","222989"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177114","2015-02-04","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what the full cost of his Department's rural broadband advertising campaign is, by type of advertising and media market; how much has been and will be spent on the rural broadband advertising campaign (a) on TfL advertising and (b) elsewhere in London; and for what reason the rollout of rural fibre broadband has been advertised in cities.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222973","222973"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177115","2015-02-04","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what change in the level of participation there has been in (a) dance, (b) music, (c) theatre and (d) arts and crafts in primary schools in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222981","222981"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177116","2015-02-04","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what change in level of participation there has been in (a) dance, (b) arts and crafts and (c) cultural computer activities in secondary schools in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222982","222982"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177117","2015-02-04","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to the oral evidence to the Public Accounts Committee of 28 January 2015, HC 925, what estimate he has made of the potential cost of providing broadband via satellite to people who would still be unable to receive 2mbps through the copper or fibre networks by the end of 2015; whether he plans to meet that cost from a pre-existing fund; what assessment he has made of the viability of that plan; what estimate he has made of the time it will take to implement that plan; and what estimate has he made of the monthly cost to consumers of that broadband provision.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222974","222974"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177118","2015-02-04","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to the oral evidence to the Public Accounts Committee of 28 January 2015, HC 925, Questions 29 and 30, if he will publish the market research conducted in October 2014 on the rural broadband advertising campaign; whether he conducted an impact assessment for the rural broadband advertising campaign; and what the target audience was for that campaign.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222972","222972"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177119","2015-02-04","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many public libraries have (a) closed and (b) become volunteer-run since May 2010.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222966","222966"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177120","2015-02-04","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, when he plans to publish his response to the Digital Communications Infrastructure Strategy consultation, published on 6 August 2014.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222967","222967"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177121","2015-02-04","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he is taking to reduce the cost to consumers of superfast broadband.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222968","222968"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177122","2015-02-04","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions he has had with Ofcom on that body's consultation on its list of major political parties for elections taking place on 7 May 2015.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222969","222969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177123","2015-02-04","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he is taking to rebalance arts and culture funding between London and the South East and the rest of the country.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222970","222970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177124","2015-02-04","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will publish the contents of full Freedom of Information releases for his Department between April and September 2014.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222971","222971"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177125","2015-02-04","Department for Education","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what change there has been in the number of pupils sitting GCSEs in (a) applied arts and design, (b) art and design, (c) drama, (d) media, film and television and (e) music since May 2010.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222983","222983"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177126","2015-02-05","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the compliance of the current Deputy Chair of Ofcom with the provisions of the Ofcom Board Members' Code of Conduct in respect of impartiality.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222879","222879"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177127","2015-02-05","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what due diligence processes he followed when appointing the current Deputy Chair of the Ofcom Board.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222880","222880"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177128","2015-02-04","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 15 October 2014 to Question 209985, how much of the Super Connected Cities Programme budget has been spent to date in (a) England, (b) Wales, (c) Scotland and (d) Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222937","222937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177129","2015-02-04","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, which recommendations of the Reports entitled the Rural broadband programme from the National Audit Office, published on 5 July 2013, HC535, and Public Accounts Committee, published on 11 September 2013 and 25 March 2014, HC474 and HC834, his Department and BDUK are implementing for the phase 2 broadband contracts.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222965","222965"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177130","2015-02-04","Ministry of Defence","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether military personnel are permitted to sit or re-sit GCSEs once their initial training has come to an end.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222945","222945"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177131","2015-02-04","Ministry of Defence","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether detainees aged under 18 years are accommodated separately from adults at the Military Corrective Training Centre.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222946","222946"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177132","2015-02-04","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what plans his Department has to honour in London the contribution of Indian troops to the First World War.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222941","222941"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177133","2015-02-04","Ministry of Defence","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 10 November 2014 to Question 213663, when he plans to announce which of the 5,000 ships under construction will be designated under the Protection of Military Remains Act 1986.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222936","222936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177134","2015-02-04","Ministry of Defence","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when a Defence Minister last visited the Falkland Islands.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222935","222935"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177135","2015-02-05","Ministry of Defence","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the (a) scale and (b) result is of recent air operations against ISIL.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222901","222901"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177136","2015-02-04","Ministry of Defence","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many and what proportion of applications for (a) security clearance and counter-terrorist checks and (b) developed vetting have not met the performance targets set for DBS for the processing of such applications in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222843","222843"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177137","2015-02-05","Ministry of Defence","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the cost to the public purse was of providing training courses for the Burmese Army to date; and what funding for that purpose has been allocated for (a) 2014-15 and (b) 2015-16.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222964","222964"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177138","2015-02-04","Ministry of Defence","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much his Department allocated to the Conflict Pool in (a) 2014-15 and (b) each of the five previous financial years.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222952","222952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177139","2015-02-05","Ministry of Defence","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much his Department has allocated to the Conflict, Stability and Security Fund in (a) 2014-15 and (b) 2015-16.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222957","222957"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177140","2015-02-04","Deputy Prime Minister","2015-02-02","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what the Government's policy is on online voting.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222850","222850"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177141","2015-02-05","Department for Education","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions officials from her Department have had with Luton local authority on the implications of the decision to withdraw approval for Luton Girls' Academy.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222878","222878"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177142","2015-02-05","Department for Education","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much funding her Department has provided to ACE Trust Ltd for the development of Luton Girls' Academy.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222877","222877"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177143","2015-02-05","Department for Education","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when the decision was taken to withdraw approval for Luton Girls' Academy.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222860","222860"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177144","2015-02-05","Department for Education","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many first choice school admissions applications were submitted to Luton Girls' Academy for entry in September 2014.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222861","222861"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177145","2015-02-04","Department for Education","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many Sure Start centres and children's centres there were in (a) Leeds and (b) Leeds Central constituency on 1 January in each year since the introduction of those centres.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222898","222898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177146","2015-02-05","Department for Education","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of pupils attended schools that were rated (a) inadequate and (b) requires improvement in each local authority area in each of the most recent five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222913","222913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177147","2015-02-05","Department for Education","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of children under the age of one (a) started an episode of need, (b) were referred to children's social care services, (c) were subject to a child protection plan and (d) were in care in each local authority area in each of the most recent five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222914","222914"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177148","2015-02-04","Department for Education","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will issue guidelines to local authorities on implementing the Children and Families Act 2014 which relate to funding arrangements for children with special educational needs.","Biography information for Ian Paisley","Ian Paisley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222998","222998"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177149","2015-02-04","Department for Education","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will make it her policy to introduce compulsory paediatric first aid training for all nursery staff.","Biography information for Ian Paisley","Ian Paisley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222990","222990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177150","2015-02-04","Department for Education","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will introduce legislative proposals to make it compulsory that supply teachers have access to pension rights on an equal basis to other teachers.","Biography information for Ian Paisley","Ian Paisley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222994","222994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177151","2015-02-04","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if he will make it his policy to implement the Affordable Warmth Manifesto published by the End Fuel Poverty Coalition in September 2014.","Biography information for Ian Paisley","Ian Paisley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222995","222995"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177152","2015-02-05","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate he has made of the cost to his Department of officiating the 13th onshore oil and gas licensing round; and how much his Department recouped from the sale of licences in that round.","Biography information for Tom Greatrex","Tom Greatrex","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222920","222920"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177153","2015-02-04","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what guidance his Department issues on planning applications for on-shore wind farms; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Henry Bellingham","Mr Henry Bellingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222842","222842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177154","2015-02-04","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what discussion his Department has had with HM Treasury on the viability of the development and operation of deep offshore underground coal gasification projects from licences issued by the Coal Authority.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222841","222841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177155","2015-02-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answers of 29 Jaunuary 2015 from the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Water, Forestry, Rural Affairs and Water Management, Official Report, column 987, on water companies: social tariff, what discussions she has had with the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions on entitlement to water companies' social tariff schemes and to benefit entitlements.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame M. Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222833","222833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177156","2015-02-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate she has made of the number of cats (a) killed and (b) injured by firearms in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Chris Williamson","Chris Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222847","222847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177157","2015-02-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 29 January 2015 from the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Water, Forestry, Rural Affairs and Water Management, Official Report, column 987, on water companies: social tariff, whether the criteria used by water companies for local social tarrif schemes are based on the eligibility criteria for universal credit and income support.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame M. Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222835","222835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177158","2015-02-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 29 January 2015 from the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Water, Forestry, Rural Affairs and Water Management, Official Report, column 987, on water companies: social tariff, which water companies have a social tariff scheme; how many customers benefit from each scheme; and what the eligibilty criteria are for each scheme.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame M. Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222834","222834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177159","2015-02-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer from the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Water, Forestry, Rural Affairs and Water Management, Official Report, column 987, on water companies: social tariffs, what discussions she has had with (a) water companies and (b) other government departments on a scheme of social tariffs that is consistent across England; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame M. Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222894","222894"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177160","2015-02-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 20 January 2015, Official Report, column 79, whether he met the Saudi Arabia Deputy Foreign Minister; and with whom he has discussed the case of Raif Badawi.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Alexander","Mr Douglas Alexander","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222907","222907"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177161","2015-02-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what progress has been made on repairing desecrated headstones of British soldiers at Benghazi War Cemetery, Libya.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222953","222953"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177162","2015-02-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how much his Department allocated to the Conflict Pool in (a) 2014-15 and (b) each of the five previous financial years.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222951","222951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177163","2015-02-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received on progress made by the Libyan authorities on arresting and prosecuting people who desecrated the headstones of British soldiers at Benghazi War Cemetery in February 2012.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222954","222954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177164","2015-02-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to note 19 on page 106 of the British Council's Annual Report, 2013-14, what the reasons were for the losses and special payments.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222848","222848"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177165","2015-02-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether any official visits from (a) Kazakhstan, (b) Azerbaijan, (c) Kuwait, (d) Abu Dhabi, (e) Albania and (f) Libya were arranged or accompanied by Tony Blair since Mr Blair left office.","Biography information for Andrew Bridgen","Andrew Bridgen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222869","222869"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177166","2015-02-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether any officials of his Department have been seconded to work directly for Tony Blair on (a) the Quartet and (b) other projects since Mr Blair left office.","Biography information for Andrew Bridgen","Andrew Bridgen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222870","222870"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177167","2015-02-04","Cabinet Office","2015-02-02","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether Tony Blair has carried out any work for the Government since he left office.","Biography information for Andrew Bridgen","Andrew Bridgen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222868","222868"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177168","2015-02-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what information his Department holds on the cost of Tony Blair's work for the Quartet.","Biography information for Andrew Bridgen","Andrew Bridgen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222867","222867"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177169","2015-02-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations his Department has received from Tony Blair on (a) Kazakhstan, (b) Azerbaijan, (c) Kuwait, (d) Abu Dhabi, (e) Albania and (f) Libya since Mr Blair left office.","Biography information for Andrew Bridgen","Andrew Bridgen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222871","222871"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177170","2015-02-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether Tony Blair has been provided with (a) transport and (b) accommodation in posts in (i) Azerbaijan, (ii) Kazakhstan, (iii) Kuwait, (iv) Abu Dhabi, (v) Albania and (vi) Libya since Mr Blair left office.","Biography information for Andrew Bridgen","Andrew Bridgen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222872","222872"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177171","2015-02-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how much his Department has allocated to the Conflict, Stability and Security Fund in (a) 2014-15 and (b) 2015-16.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222958","222958"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177172","2015-02-04","Department of Health","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if the Government will introduce legislative proposals to allow the NHS to recoup the cost of treating patients who are admitted from private hospitals.","Biography information for Ian Paisley","Ian Paisley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222991","222991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177173","2015-02-05","Department of Health","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many outpatient and inpatient appointments were (a) emergency and (b) elective with a (i) primary and (ii) secondary diagnosis of HIV in (A) England and (B) each clincial commissioning group area in each of the last 12 months; and what the average waiting time was for each such appointment.","Biography information for Sir Simon Burns","Mr Simon Burns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222963","222963"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177174","2015-02-05","Department of Health","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure progress on price negotiations with Novartis for the Meningitis B vaccine.","Biography information for Stuart Andrew","Stuart Andrew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222863","222863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177175","2015-02-05","Department of Health","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many contracts Public Health England has awarded to Alliance-Boots in each of the last four years; what each such contract was for; and what the total value was of each such contract.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222844","222844"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177176","2015-02-05","Department of Health","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many contracts NHS bodies entered into with Alliance-Boots in each of the last five years; what services were provided for in each such contract; and what the total value was of each such contract.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222845","222845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177177","2015-02-05","Department of Health","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many contracts NHS England has awarded to Alliance-Boots in each of the last four years; what each such contract was for; and what the total value was of each such contract.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222846","222846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177178","2015-02-05","Department of Health","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to ensure that the Meningitis B vaccine is added to the childhood immunisation programme in 2015.","Biography information for Stuart Andrew","Stuart Andrew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222862","222862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177179","2015-02-05","Department of Health","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of potential changes to the number of organ donations from a move to an opt-out system for organ donations; and what steps his Department is taking to increase the number of organ donors.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222858","222858"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177180","2015-02-05","Department of Health","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what requirements to participate in clinical trials without charging there are in contracts issued to private healthcare providers.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222859","222859"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177181","2015-02-05","Department of Health","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people were diagnosed with diabetes in (a) Lancashire and (b) England in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222875","222875"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177182","2015-02-04","Department of Health","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to paragraph 5.26 of his Department's report, An Intelligence Framework for Cancer published in December 2011, what discussions he has had with Public Health England on funding a new database to support the introduction of Primary HPV screening through a single national screening database.","Biography information for Andrew Bridgen","Andrew Bridgen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222866","222866"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177183","2015-02-05","Department of Health","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many diabetes specialist nurses were employed in (a) Lancashire and (b) England in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222874","222874"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177184","2015-02-05","Department of Health","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of the annual cost of providing insulin to people diagnosed with diabetes.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222876","222876"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177185","2015-02-04","Department of Health","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, for what reason doctors receive extra payments for signing death certificates.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222854","222854"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177186","2015-02-05","Department of Health","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will meet bodies representing cancer sufferers to discuss the evaluation of the Be Clear on Cancer regional pilot for ovarian cancer.","Biography information for Stuart Andrew","Stuart Andrew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222849","222849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177187","2015-02-04","Department of Health","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average payment to a doctor for signing a death certificate was in the most recent year for which figures are available; and how many doctors received payments for signing death certificates in that year.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222855","222855"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177188","2015-02-04","Department of Health","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of the cost of adding very long-chain acyl-CoA dehydrogenase to the heel prick newborn screening test.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222852","222852"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177189","2015-02-04","Department of Health","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department has taken to help early diagnosis of very long-chain acyl-CoA dehydrogenase deficiency.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222853","222853"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177190","2015-02-04","Department of Health","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what meetings his Department has had with representatives of (a) Waitrose and (b) Asda as part of the Responsibility Deal in the last three months; and what issues were discussed at those meetings.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222944","222944"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177191","2015-02-04","Department of Health","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Quality and Outcomes Framework, how much GPs have received in remuneration for assessing nerve damage and poor blood supply to the feet in people with diabetes in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222943","222943"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177192","2015-02-05","Department of Health","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much the NHS spent on the lease of photocopier machines in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222923","222923"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177193","2015-02-05","Department of Health","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he plans to dispose of the assets of the NHS no longer in use; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222900","222900"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177194","2015-02-04","Department of Health","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many cases of meningitis B there have been in people (a) under five, (b) aged five to 18 and (c) over 18 in the last five years.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222893","222893"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177195","2015-02-05","Department of Health","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how he plans to ensure that NHS England area teams follow Monitor's guidelines on local pricing for mental health services; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222902","222902"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177196","2015-02-05","Department of Health","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect of the 2014-15 national tariff deflator on out-of-area placements for mental health patients.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222903","222903"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177197","2015-02-05","Department of Health","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, for what reason NHS England has not published information on payments made over £25,000 since June 2014.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222904","222904"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177198","2015-02-04","Department of Health","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information his Department has published for patients diagnosed with endometriosis.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222886","222886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177199","2015-02-04","Department of Health","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department has taken to ensure that women diagnosed with endometriosis receive detailed information on that condition.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222887","222887"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177200","2015-02-04","Department of Health","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions he has had with patients' groups on endometriosis.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222888","222888"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177201","2015-02-05","Department of Health","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) doctors, (b) nurses, (c) social workers and (d) psychiatrists (i) trained or (ii) graduated with specialist skills in elderly care since 2005.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222919","222919"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177202","2015-02-05","Department of Health","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when his Department next plans to publish data derived from the HIV and AIDS reporting system (HARS); what data from HARS will be made available publicly and at what frequency; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Simon Burns","Mr Simon Burns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222915","222915"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177203","2015-02-05","Department of Health","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress his Department has made on price negotiations for the meningitis B vaccine.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222910","222910"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177204","2015-02-04","Home Office","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to tackle human trafficking in the Medway towns.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222885","222885"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177205","2015-02-05","Home Office","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many incidents of domestic violence were reported to the police in the last three years; and in how many of those cases there was a complaint of coercive control.","Biography information for Mr Elfyn Llwyd","Mr Elfyn Llwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222926","222926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177206","2015-02-05","Home Office","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what research her Department has (a) conducted and (b) commissioned into the incidence of coercive control in domestic violence complaints.","Biography information for Mr Elfyn Llwyd","Mr Elfyn Llwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222927","222927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177207","2015-02-04","Home Office","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many non-human primates, of what species and from what country of origin, were imported into the UK for the purposes of scientific research in 2014; and how many of those were (a) wild-caught, (b) captive born or F1 generation and (c) captive bred.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222873","222873"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177208","2015-02-04","Department for International Development","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much her Department allocated to the Conflict Pool in (a) 2014-15 and (b) each of the five previous financial years.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222950","222950"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177209","2015-02-05","Department for International Development","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much her Department has allocated to the Conflict, Stability and Security Fund in (a) 2014-15 and (b) 2015-16.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222959","222959"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177210","2015-02-04","Ministry of Justice","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will take steps to ensure that all victims of domestic abuse access legal aid for family cases.","Biography information for Ian Paisley","Ian Paisley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222992","222992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177211","2015-02-05","Ministry of Justice","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) children under 18 and (b) 18 to 24 year olds have applied for legal aid under the Exceptional Case Funding Scheme in (i) 2013-14 and (ii) 2014-15 to date.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222961","222961"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177212","2015-02-05","Ministry of Justice","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the speech by the Minister of State for Justice and Civil Liberties of 24 September 2014 at the Family Mediation Association Annual Conference 2014, whether his Department plans to seek the views of children, young people and expert non-governmental organisaitons in its review of children's access to legal aid.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222962","222962"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177213","2015-02-05","Ministry of Justice","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many children received (a) social welfare, (b) family, (c) immigration and (d) prison legal aid in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222917","222917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177214","2015-02-05","Ministry of Justice","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) children under 18 and (b) 18 to 24 year olds received legal aid in (i) 2011-12, (ii) 2012-13 and (iii) 2013-14.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222918","222918"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177215","2015-02-05","Ministry of Justice","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people released from prison did not attend the first scheduled meeting with their probation officer in the most recent year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222912","222912"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177216","2015-02-04","Ministry of Justice","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners were released from prison on a Friday in each of the most recent five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222892","222892"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177217","2015-02-09","Department for Transport","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will issue a Direction to the Chief Executive of Network Rail to reply to the letter of 27 October 2014 from the hon. Member for Tonbridge and Malling on the need to lengthen the platforms at Cowden, Hever and Edenbridge Town stations by 27 July 2015.","Biography information for Sir John Stanley","Sir John Stanley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222939","222939"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177218","2015-02-05","Department for Transport","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the criteria were for the relocation of Whitehaven Coastguard headquarters to the inland Sneckyeat Industrial Estate.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222924","222924"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177219","2015-02-04","Department for Transport","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what procedure exists for notifying owners of pets that are killed on the strategic road network.","Biography information for Jason McCartney","Jason McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222932","222932"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177220","2015-02-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent estimate he has made of the number of people affected by the under-occupancy penalty in (a) Copeland Borough Council area and (b) Cumbria County Council area.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222922","222922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177221","2015-02-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in (a) Leeds and (b) Leeds Central constituency are claiming incapacity benefit because of a mental health problem.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222908","222908"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177222","2015-02-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of how many residents of the British Overseas Territories in receipt of UK state pensions have had those pensions frozen.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222934","222934"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177223","2015-02-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many invoices issued under the Health and Safety Executive's Fee for Intervention scheme have been queried by invoicees since October 2012; and what proportion of the total number of invoices such invoices amount to.","Biography information for Mark Garnier","Mark Garnier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222949","222949"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177224","2015-02-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what representations he has received in each of the last three years on sums charged above £20,000 under the Health and Safety Executive's Fee for Intervention scheme.","Biography information for Mark Garnier","Mark Garnier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222947","222947"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177225","2015-02-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effect on small and medium-sized enterprises of the Fee for Intervention scheme used by the Health and Safety Executive.","Biography information for Mark Garnier","Mark Garnier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222948","222948"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177226","2015-02-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will produce overarching guidance to ensure that Universal Credit data sharing between his Department and local support providers is undertaken in a consistent and appropriate manner.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222905","222905"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177227","2015-02-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 26 January 2015 to Question 221544, what the unrounded forecast agreed with OBR is for the number of claimants of Universal Credit in May 2015.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222906","222906"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177228","2015-02-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the effect of the under-occupancy penalty on his Department's expenditure in this Parliament; and under what categories of expenditure that effect has happened.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222921","222921"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177229","2015-02-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the efficacy of ATOS's use of cognitive behavioural therapy for people suffering from Myalgic Encephalopathy and Chronic Fatigue Syndrome.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222856","222856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177230","2015-02-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make it his policy to collate and publish information on the weekly amount and duration of jobseeker's allowance hardship payments.","Biography information for Mr Michael Meacher","Mr Michael Meacher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222884","222884"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177231","2015-02-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department plans to take to ensure that schemes identified by the Independent Project Board as having excessive charges take effective and timely action in response and will be subject to sanctions if they do not do so.","Biography information for David Mowat","David Mowat","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222839","222839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177232","2015-02-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make it his policy to implement a separate back to work support system for people suffering from mental health conditions to provide them with personalised help and specialist support.","Biography information for Ian Paisley","Ian Paisley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222993","222993"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177492","2015-02-05","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what recent discussions he has had with his EU counterparts on carbon and renewables targets.","Biography information for David Mowat","David Mowat","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 907455","907455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177708","2015-02-05","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps he is taking to help households improve their energy efficiency.","Biography information for Siobhain McDonagh","Siobhain McDonagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 907446","907446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177991","2015-02-05","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-02-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps he is taking to help households improve their energy efficiency.","Biography information for Mrs Siân C. James","Mrs Siân C. James","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 907453","907453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176873","2015-02-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many (a) British-Indian and (b) British-Sikh people were members of the delegation which accompanied the Government trade mission to India in August 2014.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222782","222782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176874","2015-02-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many apprenticeships have been created under the Government Apprentice Scheme in Blyth Valley constituency in each month since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Ronnie Campbell","Mr Ronnie Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222801","222801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176875","2015-02-03","Cabinet Office","2015-01-30","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, which government Ministers attended the World Economic Forum in 2015; and what the cost to the public purse was of each such attendance.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222795","222795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176876","2015-02-04","Cabinet Office","2015-01-30","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether any officials reporting to the Chief Executive of the Civil Service are working to implement or devise policies which could affect the consumption, marketing, pricing, availability or sale of alcohol.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222790","222790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176877","2015-02-03","HM Treasury","2015-01-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to ensure that staff in HM Revenue and Customs' new counter-avoidance directorate have received adequate training to deal with challenges to Accelerated Payment Notices.","Biography information for Mark Field","Mark Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222787","222787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176878","2015-02-03","HM Treasury","2015-01-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether his Department plans to produce a report on its progress in using accelerated payment notices.","Biography information for Mark Field","Mark Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222802","222802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176879","2015-02-03","HM Treasury","2015-01-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many breaches of the minimum wage were reported in each year since 2010 for which records are available in (a) the UK, (b) Scotland, (c) England, (d) Wales and (e) Northern Ireland in the latest period for which figures are available; and how many such cases were (i) taken to court and (ii) led to convictions or penalties.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222805","222805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176880","2015-02-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, who made the decision not to use the super-affirmative procedure for amending the Greater Manchester Combined Authority Order 2011; and on what basis that decision was made.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222804","222804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176881","2015-02-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how he has publicised the consultation on the proposal to amend the constitution of the Greater Manchester Combined Authority.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222791","222791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176882","2015-02-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many compromise agreements his Department has made with departing staff in each year since 2010; and how many such agreements contained confidentiality clauses.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222784","222784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176883","2015-02-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether he has been consulted over the appointment of an interim mayor of Greater Manchester city-region.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222792","222792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176884","2015-02-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many responses he has had to the consultation on the proposal to amend the constitution of the Greater Manchester Combined Authority.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222793","222793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176885","2015-02-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps the Government is taking to improve the rights of leaseholders to hold building management companies to account.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222794","222794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176886","2015-02-04","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he last met the (a) Home Secretary, (b) Foreign Secretary and (c) Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills to discuss cyber security; and what the outcome of those meetings was.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222798","222798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176887","2015-02-04","Cabinet Office","2015-01-30","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, by what process the Government quantifies the severity of cyber-attacks; and what criteria the Government employs to determine its response to such attacks.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222799","222799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176888","2015-02-04","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what progress his Department has made on its work on a cyber-security model to be implemented in its contracts.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222800","222800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176889","2015-02-03","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent progress the Royal Military Police have made in respect of Operation BUTE; and on what date he expects that investigation to conclude.","Biography information for Caroline Dinenage","Caroline Dinenage","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222788","222788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176890","2015-02-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how much the Nuclear Decommissioning Authority paid its staff in (a) performance-related payments and (b) other payments, allowances and benefits in addition to their core salary in each of the last four years; how many and what proportion of officials working for that body received such payments; and what the monetary value of the 20 largest such payments made in each such year was.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222815","222815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176891","2015-02-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how much and what proportion of the Civil Nuclear Police Authority's budget was funded (a) from the public purse and (b) through income recovered from its customers in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222807","222807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176892","2015-02-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the total number of hours, persons employed and costs of reachback support for Nuclear Management Partners at Sellafield in each of the last five years were.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222816","222816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176893","2015-02-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the purpose and function was of the Civil Nuclear Police Authority activities funded by grant-in-aid in the last five years.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222808","222808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176894","2015-02-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, which organisations paid for services from the Civil Nuclear Police Authority in the last financial year.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222809","222809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176895","2015-02-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how much Nuclear Management Partners have received through performance fees or dividend payments from Sellafield Ltd in each year since it was appointed as the parent body organisation for that company.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222817","222817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176896","2015-02-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the definition his Department uses for 'place of worship' is for the purpose of exemption from Energy Performance Certificates.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222789","222789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176897","2015-02-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether his Department has received any applications to carry out fracking in (a) Ealing, Southall constituency, (b) Ealing local authority area and (c) Greater London.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222781","222781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176898","2015-02-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate he has made of how much Nuclear Management Partners will receive in performance fees or dividend payments for the 2014-15 and 2015-16 financial years.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222818","222818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176899","2015-02-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the statement made by the Minister of State in his Department on 16 December 2013, Official Report, column 79WS, what the reason is for the time taken to publish the Triennial Review of the Civil Nuclear Police Authority; and when he plans to publish that review.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222810","222810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176900","2015-02-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 13 January 2015 to Question 219963, how many times the Green Climate Fund board has met during the last 12 months.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222811","222811"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176901","2015-02-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 13 January 2015 to Question 219852, if he will provide a breakdown by category of his Department's expenditure allocated to oil and gas in the last financial year; and of the purposes and functions of that expenditure.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222812","222812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176902","2015-02-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 13 January 2015 to Question 220385, what the purposes and functions are of the Smart Metering Implementation Programme; and whether consideration was given to seeking payment of the costs of that programme from the energy companies.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222813","222813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176903","2015-02-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how much was paid by his Department to its staff in each of the last four years in (a) performance-related payments and (b) other payments, allowances and benefits in addition to their core salary; how many and what proportion of officials received such payments; and what the monetary value of the 10 largest payments made in each such year was.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222814","222814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176904","2015-02-04","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, when the Nuclear Decommissioning Authority is scheduled to next formally review each of its Parent Body Organisation contracts.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222826","222826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176905","2015-02-04","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, when each of the Nuclear Decommissioning Authority's Parent Body Organisation contracts are scheduled for renewal or to reach agreed break points.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222827","222827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176906","2015-02-04","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how much the Nuclear Decommissioning Authority spent in each of the last five years on (a) in-house research and development activities and (b) research and development activities funded directly through its contractors.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222828","222828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176907","2015-02-04","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the support and overhead costs of each of the Nuclear Decommissioning Authority's site licence companies were in each of the last five years; and how much of such costs was spent in each category of expenditure included in those costs.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222829","222829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176908","2015-02-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will make it her policy to implement the Natural Capital Committee's Third Report's (a) recommendations on a 25-year plan to improve and protect natural capital and (b) other recommendations.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222825","222825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176909","2015-02-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what fees her Department has proposed for veterinarians who bid successfully in the tendering process for testing for tuberculosis in cattle.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222775","222775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176910","2015-02-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she has taken to keep veterinarians informed on the timetable of her Department's tendering process for testing cattle for tuberculosis.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222776","222776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176911","2015-02-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the reasons are for the time her Department's tendering process has taken for testing cattle for tuberculosis.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222777","222777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176912","2015-02-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent timetable her Department has set for the tendering process for testing cattle for tuberculosis.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222778","222778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176913","2015-02-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to seek lifting the travel ban on Samar Badawi, the wife of Saudi activist Waleed Abulkhair.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222796","222796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176914","2015-02-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the human rights situation in Saudi Arabia.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222797","222797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176915","2015-02-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations the Government has made to the government of Saudi Arabia in support of the release of Waleed Abulkhair from prison in that country.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222806","222806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176916","2015-02-03","Department of Health","2015-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he has taken to ensure that his Department's 2015-16 tariff proposals do not affect patient access and waiting times.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222783","222783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176917","2015-02-03","Department of Health","2015-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the cost was of backlog maintenance for the NHS estate in England in each level of assessed risk in (a) 2012-13, (b) 2013-14 and (c) 2014-15 to date.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222785","222785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176918","2015-02-03","Home Office","2015-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 27 January 2015 to Question 221195, on radicalism, what proportion of referrals to Channel were for far right concerns.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222780","222780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176919","2015-02-04","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 7 January 2015 to Question 906848, what guidance his Department issues on when Government departments should seek to legislate to establish a legal basis for the sharing of personal data.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222803","222803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176920","2015-02-03","Prime Minister","2015-01-30","To ask the Prime Minister, what (a) private meetings and (b) other engagements he has had with representatives of (i) the Indian government and (ii) Indian private companies since taking up office.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222786","222786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176921","2015-02-03","Department for Transport","2015-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of amending contracts with Highways Agency's contractors to include (a) the compulsory scanning of all domestic animals for micro-chip identification, (b) recording pet identifications and (c) contacting the owners of the pet upon the death of a domestic animal on the road network.","Biography information for Jason McCartney","Jason McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222779","222779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176922","2015-02-04","Department for Transport","2015-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department plans to close the Airdrie Driving Testing Centre.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222824","222824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176923","2015-02-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the long-term sustainability of his plans for a digital service.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222822","222822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176924","2015-02-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what ongoing support his Department offers a jobseeker's allowance claimant who has received a sanction.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222823","222823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176925","2015-02-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will take steps to encourage Work Programme providers to work with housing associations to help tenants boost their employability.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222821","222821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176926","2015-02-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what discussions he has held in 2015 to date with his ministerial colleagues at the Department for Communities and Local Government on the operation of local welfare assistance schemes.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222820","222820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176927","2015-02-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the extent to which the jobseeker's allowance regime facilitates legitimate voluntary work that might boost a jobseeker's skills and experience.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222819","222819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176680","2015-02-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what information his Department holds on the number of people advised by Citizens Advice Bureaux in (a) the UK, (b) England, (c) London, (d) Yorkshire, (e) Kirklees local authority area and (f) Huddersfield constituency in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222635","222635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176682","2015-02-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what information his Department holds on the number of Citizens Advice Bureaux field offices which have (a) opened and (b) closed in (i) the UK, (ii) England, (iii) London, (iv) Yorkshire, (v) Kirklees local authority area and (vi) Huddersfield constituency in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222636","222636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176684","2015-02-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much funding the Government has allocated to Citizens Advice in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222637","222637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176685","2015-02-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what information his Department holds on the number of people who have used Citizens Advice Bureaux in (a) the UK, (b) England, (c) London, (d) Yorkshire, (e) Kirklees local authority area and (f) Huddersfield constituency in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222638","222638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176687","2015-02-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what representations he has received from the management, staff and volunteers of Citizens Advice Bureaux on the effectiveness of Citizens Advice.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222639","222639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176689","2015-02-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the effect of Citizens Advice Bureaux on their users' capability to repay debts.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222640","222640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176691","2015-02-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what information his Department holds on the number of people who have volunteered to work for Citizens Advice Bureaux in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222641","222641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176692","2015-02-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what information his Department holds on the number of paid staff working for Citizens Advice Bureaux in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222642","222642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176694","2015-02-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what criteria his Department uses to assess the effectiveness of Citizens Advice Bureaux.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222643","222643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176696","2015-02-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to support Citizens Advice Bureaux in their recruitment of volunteers.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222644","222644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176698","2015-02-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to support the Citizens Advice Bureaux in retaining their capability and capacity to offer appropriate advice to their users.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222645","222645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176700","2015-02-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what information his Department holds about the number of Citizens Advice Bureaux field offices in (a) the UK, (b) England, (c) London, (d) Yorkshire, (e) Kirklees local authority area and (f) Huddersfield constituency.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222646","222646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176702","2015-02-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to support UK companies bidding for contracts in Turkey.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222698","222698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176704","2015-02-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether any licences have been granted to UAV Engines Ltd since 1 January 2010 for the export of UAV engines or components to (a) the Israeli Defence Force or (b) other elements of Israel’s security forces; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222681","222681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176706","2015-02-03","Cabinet Office","2015-01-29","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the value is of his Department's ICT contracts; and when each such contract is due to end.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222703","222703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176707","2015-02-03","Cabinet Office","2015-01-29","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many (a) desktop computers, (b) laptops and (c) tablet devices there are for each person in his Department.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222701","222701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176708","2015-02-03","HM Treasury","2015-01-29","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make an assessment of the effect of refunding VAT for contracted out of services but not for cloud services on the ability of small businesses to compete for public sector contracts.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222665","222665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176714","2015-02-03","Cabinet Office","2015-01-29","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much his Department has spent on ICT (a) in total; and (b) on average for each person in his Department per person in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222702","222702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176719","2015-02-03","HM Treasury","2015-01-29","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment he has made of (a) levels of bank account switching by customers, (b) trends in bank account switching in the last three years, (c) the average time it takes for customers to switch banks and (d) the process for switching banks and customers' perceptions of the ease or difficulty of so doing.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222656","222656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176721","2015-02-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when the Government plans to consult on ways to increase the borrowing capacity of housing associations in relation to the valuation of properties transferred from local authorities.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222688","222688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176723","2015-02-03","HM Treasury","2015-01-29","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make an assessment of the effect of COS14 VAT rules on public sector procurement of off the shelf software services.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222663","222663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176725","2015-02-03","HM Treasury","2015-01-29","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much VAT was refunded under COS14 rules in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222664","222664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176727","2015-02-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what representations he has received about the decision to withdraw funding for the Local Welfare Assistance scheme.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222699","222699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176730","2015-02-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will direct officials in his Department to meet officials in the Department for Health to discuss giving the Care Quality Commission wider powers than they currently have to undertake inspections of how local authorities commission their care services, even where no specific complaints have been made.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222632","222632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176731","2015-02-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many new homes have been completed in St Austell and Newquay constituency in each of the last five years; and how many of those homes have been affordable housing.","Biography information for Stephen Gilbert","Stephen Gilbert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222669","222669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176732","2015-02-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he plans to take to deregulate housing associations.","Biography information for Dame Rosie Winterton","Ms Rosie Winterton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222666","222666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176733","2015-02-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what support is available to (a) Doncaster local authority area and (b) other local authority areas which are not among the Build pilot areas to accelerate house-building.","Biography information for Dame Rosie Winterton","Ms Rosie Winterton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222667","222667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176734","2015-02-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of refunding VAT for contracted out services on the (a) ability and (b) incentives for local authorities to (i) share software services and (ii) use off the shelf software and Cloud services.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222662","222662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176735","2015-02-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many appeals against planning application refusals by local planning authorities have been (a) upheld and (b) dismissed by the Planning Inspectorate since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Mike Thornton","Mr Michael Thornton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222682","222682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176736","2015-02-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people received access grants from the Local Welfare Assistance fund in (a) 2013 and (b) 2014 in Birmingham.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222723","222723"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176737","2015-02-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many applicants there were for the Mayoral Development Corporation Old Oak Director position.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222747","222747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176738","2015-02-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what recent discussions he has had with the leaders of Greater Manchester's local authorities about the appointment of an interim Mayor of Greater Manchester city-region.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222742","222742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176739","2015-02-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether he has a veto over the appointment of an interim Mayor of Greater Manchester city-region.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222743","222743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176740","2015-02-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he expects an announcement to be made about the appointment of an interim eleventh leader of Greater Manchester city-region.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222744","222744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176741","2015-02-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he expects the Greater Manchester Combined Authority to specify an appointments process for the interim Mayor of Greater Manchester city-region.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222745","222745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176742","2015-02-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when the city-region mayor created by the Greater Manchester devolution agreement will be subject to term limits.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222746","222746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176743","2015-02-03","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, when he expects Phase 2 of Connecting Cumbria to be complete; and what estimate he has made of how many premises in Copeland will receive high speed broadband in that phase.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222689","222689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176744","2015-02-03","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment his Department has made of recent storm damage to buildings and infrastructure relating to Hebrides Range on St Kilda.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Mr Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222740","222740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176745","2015-02-03","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he plans to arrange for buildings pertaining to Hebrides Range on St Kilda, which were damaged by recent high winds, to be repaired.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Mr Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222741","222741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176746","2015-02-03","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the number of military veterans receiving support for (a) mental health and (b) alcohol related issues.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222704","222704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176747","2015-02-02","Department for Education","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much funding her Department has allocated to the training of educational psychologists in each of the last five financial years.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222652","222652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176748","2015-02-02","Department for Education","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 15 January 2015 to Question 220175, for what reasons her Department has decided not to take any proactive steps to reduce the disparity between local authorities in meeting the six-week regulation for visits of children within the first year of a private fostering arrangement.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222651","222651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176749","2015-02-02","Department for Education","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she plans to broaden and escalate the Government’s intervention in Somerset County Council’s Children’s Services.","Biography information for Tessa Munt","Tessa Munt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222679","222679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176750","2015-02-03","Department for Education","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if her Department will issue guidance on removing asbestos insulating board which is vulnerable to disturbance or damage from children.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222726","222726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176751","2015-02-02","Department for Education","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Ofsted and CQC report entitled Evaluation of local areas' readinness for the implementation of the disability and SEN reforms, published on 17 December 2014, page 6, what discussions she has had with the Secretary of State for Health on possible accountability measures to monitor the impact of the SEND reforms.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222713","222713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176752","2015-02-03","Department for Education","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when her Department last reviewed its guidance on assessing the risks from asbestos insulating board accessible to children in schools.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222725","222725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176753","2015-02-02","Department for Education","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Ofsted and CQC report entitled Evaluation of local areas' readinness for the implementation of the disability and SEN reforms, published on 17 December 2014, page 6, whether she plans to introduce accountability measures to monitor the impact of the SEND reforms.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222714","222714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176754","2015-02-03","Department for Education","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many looked after children in each local authority had (a) one, (b) two, (c) three, (d) four, (e) five, (f) six, (g) seven, (h) eight, (i) nine, (j) 10 or more, (k) 20 or more, (l) 30 or more, (m) 40 or more and (n) 50 or more placements in (i) the most recent year for which figures are available and (ii) while they were in care.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222708","222708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176755","2015-02-03","Department for Education","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of the number of former pupils who will be diagnosed with mesothelioma from asbestos exposure at school during the 1960s and 1970s.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222728","222728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176756","2015-02-03","Department for Education","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if her Department will adopt and implement environmental asbestos fibre board for schools.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222727","222727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176757","2015-02-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the level of gas consumption by (a) consumers and (b) all gas users was in each month of 2014.","Biography information for Tom Greatrex","Tom Greatrex","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222722","222722"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176758","2015-02-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, when he plans to publish an update to the sub-national total final electricity consumption statistics.","Biography information for Tom Greatrex","Tom Greatrex","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222721","222721"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176759","2015-02-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate he has made of the average cost to domestic consumers per GWh of (a) gas and (b) electricity in each month of 2014.","Biography information for Tom Greatrex","Tom Greatrex","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222720","222720"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176760","2015-02-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if he will make it his policy to include trade unions representing the offshore workforce in the North Sea Taskforce to be led by the Oil and Gas Authority.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222633","222633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176761","2015-02-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what progress she has made on implementing the Government's timber procurement policy for central government departments which requires the purchase of only legally felled and sustainably produced timber and wood products.","Biography information for Neil Parish","Neil Parish","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222648","222648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176762","2015-02-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of (a) the comparative rate of food price inflation in (i) the UK, (ii) France and (iii) Germany between 2003 and 2015 and (b) the reasons for differences between those inflation rates in that period.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222657","222657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176763","2015-02-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the oral Answer of 29 January 2015, Official Report, column 996, when she plans to publish her Department's estimate of the percentage reduction in badger numbers achieved in both pilot cull areas as a result of last year's cull.","Biography information for Andrew George","Andrew George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222686","222686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176764","2015-02-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the oral Answer of 29 January 2015, Official Report, column 996, what steps her Department took to ensure that if pilot culls had achieved the target of 70 per cent reduction in badger numbers in (a) 2013 and (b) 2014.","Biography information for Andrew George","Andrew George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222685","222685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176765","2015-02-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the oral Answer of 29 January 2015, Official Report, column 996, what percentage reduction in badger numbers was achieved in each of the two 2014 pilot culls.","Biography information for Andrew George","Andrew George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222687","222687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176766","2015-02-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the report of the Dogs Trust entitled, The Puppy Smuggling Scandal, published on 16 November 2014, what assessment she has made of the implications for her policies of the recommendations in that report which relate specifically to her Department; and what timetable it has for the implementation of those recommendations.","Biography information for Neil Parish","Neil Parish","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222676","222676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176767","2015-02-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate she has made of the total area of (a) England and (b) Wales covered by groundwater protection zones (i) 1, (ii) 2 and (iii) 3.","Biography information for Tom Greatrex","Tom Greatrex","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222700","222700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176768","2015-02-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, for what reasons small and medium-sized enterprises are exempted from the provisions of the draft B Single Use Carrier Bags Charges (England) Order 2015; and if she will bring forward a revised draft Order omitting that exemption.","Biography information for Stephen Gilbert","Stephen Gilbert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222668","222668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176769","2015-02-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how her Department defines the term active farmer for the purposes of applications for basic farm payments under the reformed CAP; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Baroness McIntosh of Pickering","Miss Anne McIntosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222673","222673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176770","2015-02-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent steps his Department has taken to tackle the persecution of Christians in (a) Africa and (b) the Middle East.","Biography information for Dr Alasdair McDonnell","Dr Alasdair McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222675","222675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176771","2015-02-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many (a) UK and (b) locally-engaged personnel are working for the UK Government in Yemen.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222649","222649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176772","2015-02-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what estimate he has made of the number of British passport holders in Yemen.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222650","222650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176773","2015-02-03","Department of Health","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his assessment is of the contribution made by (a) the Care Quality Commission and (b) Monitor to (i) safeguarding and (ii) raising standards in healthcare.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222655","222655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176774","2015-02-03","Department of Health","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether further discussions are planned between NHS England and the pharmaceutical industry before drugs are removed from the Cancer Drugs Fund list on 12 March 2015.","Biography information for Annette Brooke","Annette Brooke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222670","222670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176775","2015-02-03","Department of Health","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of breast cancer patients who will be affected by the removal of (a) eribulin, (b) lapatinib, and (c) everolimus from the Cancer Drugs Fund list on 12 March 2015.","Biography information for Annette Brooke","Annette Brooke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222671","222671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176776","2015-02-03","Department of Health","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he expects the Meningitis B vaccine to be made available on the NHS.","Biography information for Mr Gerry Sutcliffe","Mr Gerry Sutcliffe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222696","222696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176777","2015-02-02","Department of Health","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that patients do not allow the extraction of their data under care.data in order to avoid exclusions from bowel screening, e-referrals and similar services.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222677","222677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176778","2015-02-03","Department of Health","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what quantity of the cancer drug Immucyst to be used in bacillus Calmette-Guérin cancer treatment have been obtained by the NHS; and when it was received.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222697","222697"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176779","2015-02-02","Department of Health","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many legal cases have been initiated that involve treatment for trigeminal neuralgia given to patients at the Salford radiotherapy satellite of the Christie NHS Foundation Trust.","Biography information for Tessa Munt","Tessa Munt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222678","222678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176780","2015-02-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to raise awareness of carbon monoxide poisoning in homes.","Biography information for Annette Brooke","Annette Brooke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222711","222711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176781","2015-02-03","Department of Health","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether joint committees of NHS England and clinical commissioning groups are permitted to deviate from national service specifications for specialised services.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222695","222695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176782","2015-02-03","Department of Health","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what criteria his Department has set for the distribution of limited doses of the cancer drug ImmuCyst to be used in Bacillus Calmette-Guerin cancer treatment.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222709","222709"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176783","2015-02-03","Department of Health","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when NHS England will publish details of the co-commissioning of specialised services.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222693","222693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176784","2015-02-03","Department of Health","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether NHS England will remain the sole budget-holder and accountable commissioner for all specialised services.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222694","222694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176785","2015-02-03","Department of Health","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to establish the safety of unlicensed versions of the cancer drug ImmuCyst being used in Bacillus Calmette-Guerin cancer treatment.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222710","222710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176786","2015-02-02","Department of Health","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many NHS trusts have reported patient incidents involving stereotactic radiosurgery or stereotactic radiotherapy; what the nature was of each such incident; and what kind of radiotherapy machine was involved in each such incident.","Biography information for Tessa Munt","Tessa Munt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222680","222680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176787","2015-02-02","Department of Health","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much his Department has paid in debt repayments in respect of NHS PFI projects in the last three years.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222683","222683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176788","2015-02-02","Department of Health","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many staff are employed by each NHS England regional headquarters.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222684","222684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176789","2015-02-03","Department of Health","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress his Department has made in price negotiations with the manufacturer of the meningitis B vaccine.","Biography information for Mr Gerry Sutcliffe","Mr Gerry Sutcliffe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222734","222734"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176790","2015-02-02","Department of Health","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions his Department has had with the Food Standards Agency on implementing the recommendations in the efficiency review carried out by the National Audit Office in 2013.","Biography information for Neil Parish","Neil Parish","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222712","222712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176791","2015-02-03","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of people prosecuted for child neglect were sentenced to jail terms of ten years or more in the most recent year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222707","222707"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176792","2015-02-03","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people were (a) cautioned and (b) prosecuted for child neglect in the most recent year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222706","222706"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176793","2015-02-02","Home Office","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the timescale and process will be for her Department's response to its consultation on the codes of practice relating to the acquisition and retention of data; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222659","222659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176794","2015-02-02","Home Office","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she plans to publish all responses received to her Department's consultation on the codes of practice relating to the acquisition and retention of data.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222660","222660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176795","2015-02-02","Home Office","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the timescale and process will be for public discussion of the Communications Data and Interception review conducted by David Anderson QC; and what opportunities will arise for parliamentary scrutiny of those conclusions.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222658","222658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176796","2015-02-03","Home Office","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many British nationals were subject to (a) regulatory fines, (b) civil penalties or (c) criminal penalties because of their involvement with the proceeds of crime arising from international crude oil theft in each year for which records are available.","Biography information for Stephen Barclay","Stephen Barclay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222653","222653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176797","2015-02-03","Department for International Development","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment the Government has made of financial links between crude oil theft in Nigeria and (a) Boko Haram and (b) wider instability in that country.","Biography information for Stephen Barclay","Stephen Barclay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222654","222654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176798","2015-02-03","Department for International Development","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether the Government received or has had access to the report on crude oil theft in Nigeria, prepared by a US Administration delegation sent to Nigeria by President Obama in December 2013.","Biography information for Stephen Barclay","Stephen Barclay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222674","222674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176799","2015-02-03","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average value was of a confiscation order for drug-related crimes in (a) 2012-13 and (b) 2013-14.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222730","222730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176800","2015-02-03","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many confiscation orders were issued for drug-related crimes in (a) 2012-13 and (b) 2013-14.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222731","222731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176801","2015-02-03","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many confiscation orders were issued in (a) 2012-13 and (b) 2013-14.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222732","222732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176802","2015-02-03","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of offenders convicted in (a) 2012-13 and (b) 2013-14 were convicted for what drug-related crimes.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222733","222733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176803","2015-02-02","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average amount recovered through confiscation orders for drug-related crimes was in (a) 2012-13 and (b) 2013-14.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222715","222715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176804","2015-02-02","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many drug-related confiscation orders were issued for (a) £0 to £1,000, (b) £1,001 to £5,000, (c) £5,001 to £10,000, (d) £10,001 to £20,000, (e) £20,001 to £50,000, (f) £50,001 to £100,000, (g) £100,001 to £500,000, (h) £500,001 to £1 million, (i) £1 million to £5 million and (j) more than £5 million in (i) 2012-13 and (ii) 2013-14.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222716","222716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176805","2015-02-03","Speaker's Committee for the Independent Parliamentary Standards Authority","2015-01-29","To ask the hon. Member for Broxbourne, representing the Speaker's Committee for the Independent Parliamentary Standards Authority, if the Independent Parliamentary Standards Authority will consistently differentiate between (a) total staffing and constituency office costs and (b) other claims by hon. Members on its website and in its publications.","Biography information for Mr David Winnick","Mr David Winnick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222672","222672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176806","2015-02-04","Department for Transport","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many people have been killed or seriously injured in accidents involving mobility scooters in each of the last five years; and how many of the people so killed or seriously injured were driving the scooter.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222748","222748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176807","2015-02-03","Department for Transport","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the cost was of the St John's Thameslink scheme; what that scheme was designed to achieve; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Clive Efford","Clive Efford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222735","222735"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176808","2015-02-03","Department for Transport","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if Thameslink trains will use the new rail lines at St John's following the completion of the scheme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Clive Efford","Clive Efford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222736","222736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176809","2015-02-03","Department for Transport","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 26 January 2015 to Question 221618, on what date the 12-carriage peak-time services listed will begin to operate; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Clive Efford","Clive Efford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222737","222737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176810","2015-02-03","Department for Transport","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 26 January 2015 to Question 221670, how many eight-carriage fixed-set Thameslink trains will be purchased for the Wimbledon link to replace the 12-carriage trains in the original plans; what the savings will be arising from that purchase; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Clive Efford","Clive Efford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222738","222738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176811","2015-02-03","Department for Transport","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 26 January 2015 to Question 221654, if he will place in the Library a map showing the points along the rail lines where Thameslink services would interfere with the timetable for Cannon Street services; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Clive Efford","Clive Efford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222739","222739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176812","2015-02-02","Department for Transport","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will place in the Library an updated copy of the franchise payment profile for all train operating companies until 2023.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222661","222661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176813","2015-02-03","Department for Transport","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment his Department has made of the effect on the number of accidents of road speed limits in built up areas.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222691","222691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176814","2015-02-03","Department for Transport","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment his Department has made of the effect on walking and cycling rates of the Active Travel (Wales) Act 2013; and what plans he has to bring forward legislative proposals similar to that Act.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222690","222690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176815","2015-02-02","Department for Transport","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans he has to continue with Victoria services via Lewisham following the completion of the Thameslink scheme at London Bridge.","Biography information for Clive Efford","Clive Efford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222717","222717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176816","2015-02-03","Wales Office","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what discussions his Department has had with the Welsh Government on who has responsibility for asbestos policy in Welsh schools.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222724","222724"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176817","2015-02-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many veterans are in receipt of (a) jobseekers allowance and (b) employment and support allowance.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222705","222705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176818","2015-02-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether any targets for the sanction referrals for labour market decision makers are based on the number of sanctions applied.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame M. Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222692","222692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176819","2015-02-03","Department for Education","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of young people are not in education, employment or training aged 16, 17, 18 and 19 to 24 in (i) Tower Hamlets, (ii) England and (iii) the UK.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222634","222634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176820","2015-02-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he plans to reply to the letters to him dated 1 December 2014 and 2 January 2015 from the right hon. member for Manchester, Gorton with regard to Mr B Wise.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222647","222647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176821","2015-02-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what proportion of apprenticeship starts have been at (a) Level 2, (b) Level 3 and (c) Level 4 in (i) Tower Hamlets, (ii) London and (iii) the UK in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222771","222771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176822","2015-02-05","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to ensure consumers are aware of their rights when they receive poor service from parcel delivery firms.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222750","222750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176823","2015-02-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many apprenticeship starts have been made by young people aged (a) between 16 and 18, (b) between 19 and 24 and (c) 25 years and above living in (i) Tower Hamlets, (ii) London and (iii) the UK in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222773","222773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176824","2015-02-02","HM Treasury","2015-01-29","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the CBI's People and Prosperity Report, published in September 2014, if he will increase the UK's capital allowances regime in line with other G7 economies in order to increase long-term investment.","Biography information for Ian Paisley","Ian Paisley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222760","222760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176825","2015-02-02","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will launch an inquiry into the future of local newspapers; and if he will take steps to prevent further closures of such newspapers.","Biography information for Ian Paisley","Ian Paisley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222758","222758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176826","2015-02-02","Department for Education","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to improve levels of child literacy in low-income families; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Ian Paisley","Ian Paisley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222756","222756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176827","2015-02-03","Department for Education","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment she has made of the average cost of transport to school or college for 16 to 18 year olds.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222774","222774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176828","2015-02-02","Department for Education","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many looked-after children in each local authority were in a foster care placement on 31 March (a) 2013 and (b) 2014; how many such children in each local authority were in a foster care placement with a relative or friend (i) inside and (ii) outside the authority boundary on each date; how many such children in each local authority were under (A) an interim and (B) a full court order on each date; and how many such children in each local authority area were looked after under a voluntary agreement under section 20 of the Children Act 1989 on each such date.","Biography information for Alan Johnson","Alan Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222762","222762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176829","2015-02-02","Department for Education","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, by what means her Department assessed the extra costs incurred in maintaining and refurbishing the school stock because of the presence of asbestos in its Property Data Survey Programme.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222718","222718"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176830","2015-02-02","Department for Education","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will discuss the outcome of her Department's review of asbestos policy for schools with the Minister for Education and Skills in the Welsh Government when that review is complete.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222729","222729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176831","2015-02-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to tackle the illegal importation of puppies to the UK from Eastern Europe.","Biography information for Ian Paisley","Ian Paisley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222759","222759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176832","2015-02-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations the Government has made to the Egyptian government about the death of Shaimaa El-Sabbagh; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222764","222764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176833","2015-02-02","Department of Health","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will publish in full the financial interests of Tim Kelsey, senior responsible owner of the care.data programme which relate to health data.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222719","222719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176834","2015-02-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people receiving personal independence payments have undergone an intervention to review their entitlement.","Biography information for Roger Williams","Roger Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222766","222766"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176835","2015-02-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people with movement disorders have applied for personal independence payment.","Biography information for Roger Williams","Roger Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222767","222767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176836","2015-02-02","Department of Health","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will commission or conduct research on the links between diabetes and early dementia.","Biography information for Ian Paisley","Ian Paisley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222757","222757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176837","2015-02-02","Department of Health","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will provide additional funding to increase the availability of prescription drugs for diabetes.","Biography information for Ian Paisley","Ian Paisley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222753","222753"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176838","2015-02-02","Home Office","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will launch an inquiry into the reasons for, and implications for her policies of, the recent increase in domestic violence cases in the UK.","Biography information for Ian Paisley","Ian Paisley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222755","222755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176839","2015-02-03","Home Office","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department has plans to give financial support, as part of the Prevent programme, to organisations which work with school-aged young people who have been identified as at risk of extremism.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222768","222768"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176840","2015-02-03","Home Office","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proactive programmes her Department has put in place to make contact with potential extremists since 26 November 2014.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222769","222769"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176841","2015-02-03","Home Office","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many crimes in total have been recorded in (a) Elmbridge and (b) Surrey in each month since April 2014; and how many police officers were employed in these areas during those months.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222763","222763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176842","2015-02-03","Home Office","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which Minister in her Department has lead responsibility for overseeing the changes to the Prevent programme announced in November 2014.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222765","222765"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176843","2015-02-03","Home Office","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what training her Department plans to provide to (a) teachers and (b) headteachers to assist them to carry out the obligations placed on them by the provisions of the Counter-Terrorism and Security Bill.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222770","222770"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176844","2015-02-02","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to tackle insurance fraud known as crash for cash.","Biography information for Ian Paisley","Ian Paisley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222754","222754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176845","2015-02-02","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many confiscation orders were issued for (a) £0-£1,000, (b) £1,001-£5,000, (c) £5,001-£10,000, (d) £10,001-£20,000, (e) £20,001-£50,000, (f) £50,001-£100,000, (g) £100,001-£500,000, (h) £500,001-£1 million, (i) £1 million-£5 million and (j) more than £5 million in (i) 2012-13 and (ii) 2013-14.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222761","222761"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176846","2015-02-05","Department for Transport","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will take steps to encourage local authorities to make greater use of part-time 20mph zones that are in force during times of greater need and not on a 24 hour basis; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222749","222749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176847","2015-02-05","Department for Transport","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he expects the M62 between East Yorkshire and Leeds to be subject to no roadworks, lane closures and temporary speed restrictions; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222751","222751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176848","2015-02-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate his Department has made of the (a) number and (b) proportion of residents in Tower Hamlets who will receive universal credit after its roll out on 2 March 2015.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222772","222772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177637","2015-02-04","Department for International Development","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will make it her policy that Ministers continue to sign off large projects.","Biography information for Andrew Bridgen","Andrew Bridgen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 907433","907433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177638","2015-02-04","Department for International Development","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assistance her Department has provided to reform the security sector, the judiciary and the prison system and to upholding the rule of law in Ethiopia to support that country in meeting its international obligations in these areas.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 907439","907439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177639","2015-02-04","Department for International Development","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to help refugees fleeing conflict in South Sudan.","Biography information for Stephen Mosley","Stephen Mosley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 907437","907437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177640","2015-02-04","Department for International Development","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to monitor the cost-effectiveness of its spending.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 907435","907435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177641","2015-02-04","Department for International Development","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent progress has been made on negotiations to agree the Sustainable Development Goals.","Biography information for Graeme Morrice","Graeme Morrice","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 907438","907438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177642","2015-02-04","Department for International Development","2015-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what the UK has contributed to the Green Climate Fund.","Biography information for David Mowat","David Mowat","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 907436","907436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176318","2015-02-02","Attorney General","2015-01-28","To ask the Attorney General, how many rape complainants have been prosecuted for (a) perverting the course of justice and (b) wasting police time in each criminal justice area in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222375","222375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176319","2015-02-02","Attorney General","2015-01-28","To ask the Attorney General, how many private prosecutions have been instigated against rape complainants in the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222376","222376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176320","2015-02-02","Attorney General","2015-01-28","To ask the Attorney General, how many staff in the Law Officers' Departments have been recruited through employment or recruitment agencies in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222517","222517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176321","2015-02-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to page 8 of Growth is our Business: A Strategy for Professional and Business Services, published in July 2013, what the outcome was of the repeat of the regional outreach consultations, planned to take place in the latter part of 2013; and what steps his Department took in response to that consultation.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222513","222513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176322","2015-02-02","Deputy Prime Minister","2015-01-28","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, how many people have received a fixed penalty notice for failing to register on the electoral register.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222479","222479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176323","2015-02-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will conduct an evaluation of the progress of City Deals in (a) England and (b) Scotland; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Iain McKenzie","Iain McKenzie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222498","222498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176324","2015-02-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what progress his Department has made with pilot projects to assist people with mental health conditions return to work.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222451","222451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176325","2015-02-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 27 January 2015 to Question 221347, how much UK funding of research and development directed towards the oil and gas sector since 2010 has been provided by the Government, its agencies and non-departmental public bodies; and what proportion that amount represents of all Government research and development funding in that period.","Biography information for Mike Weir","Mr Mike Weir","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222502","222502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176326","2015-02-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what his Department's communications budget has been for each financial year from 2010-11 to 2014-15.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222563","222563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176327","2015-02-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what his Department's advertising budget was in each financial year from 2010-11 to 2014-15.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222566","222566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176328","2015-02-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many trade missions have been completed by each of the Government's Business Ambassadors in the last 12 months; on what dates each such visit took place; and to which countries those Ambassadors travelled on each such occasion.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222560","222560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176329","2015-02-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the value was of UK (a) exports to and (b) imports from Ireland in each year from 1985 for which data is available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222618","222618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176330","2015-02-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what discussions he and officials in his Department have had with relevant stakeholders in relation to the closure of the JTI Gallahers factory in Ballymena since October 2014; and what steps he has taken as a consequence of those discussions.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222359","222359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176331","2015-02-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department is taking to prevent the sale online of counterfeit goods.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222456","222456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176332","2015-02-02","Cabinet Office","2015-01-28","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 18 December 2014 to the hon. Member for Mid Sussex to Question 218376, when he plans to publish the curriculum and reading list.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222382","222382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176333","2015-02-02","Cabinet Office","2015-01-28","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether his Department provides guidance to the civil service on the (a) number of days of training that should be available to each civil servant and (b) training budget that should be available per full-time equivalent civil servant.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222385","222385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176334","2015-02-02","Cabinet Office","2015-01-28","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what his Department's advertising budget was in each financial year from 2010-11 to 2014-15.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222567","222567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176335","2015-02-02","Cabinet Office","2015-01-28","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what his Department's communications budget has been for each financial year from 2010-11 to 2014-15.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222564","222564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176336","2015-02-02","Cabinet Office","2015-01-28","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 28 January 2015 to Question 221825, what estimate his Department has made of the number and proportion of people aged 16 to 18 who have had an unknown educational status in London in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222508","222508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176337","2015-02-02","Cabinet Office","2015-01-28","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the rate of youth unemployment as a proportion of the overall rate of unemployment was in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222452","222452"
