"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429147","2015-11-23","Wales Office","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what estimate he has made of his Department's expected underspend against Departmental Expenditure Limits in 2015-16; what his Department's forecast is of total Annually Managed Expenditure in 2015-16; and what that forecast was at the time of the (a) Summer Budget 2015 and (b) March Budget 2015.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16914","16914"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429148","2015-11-20","Women and Equalities","2015-11-18","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what steps her Department has taken to embed the Family Test into its policy making.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16801","16801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429149","2015-11-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of claimants on jobseeker's allowance have registered as having a mental health condition.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16844","16844"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429150","2015-11-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what monitoring his Department carries out on changes in the number of people on jobseeker's allowance registered as having a mental health condition; and what change there has been in such numbers since 2010.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16845","16845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429151","2015-11-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department has taken to embed the Family Test into its policy making.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16800","16800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429152","2015-11-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what support his Department makes available for people with mental health conditions who claim jobseeker's allowance in getting them back into the workplace.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16846","16846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429153","2015-11-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to tackle workplace bullying.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16820","16820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429154","2015-11-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make an estimate of the number of days of work lost because of bullying in the workplace in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16821","16821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429155","2015-11-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the study entitled 'First, do no harm': are disability assessments associated with adverse trends in mental health? A longitudinal ecological study, published in November 2015 in the Journal of Epidemiology and Community Health.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16822","16822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429156","2015-11-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the reasons were for the recent changes in the proportion of resolvable  Freedom of Information requests whose answers were fully withheld.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16829","16829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429157","2015-11-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 2 November 2015 to Question 13828, what other benefits will be available to Syrian immigrants; and what assessment he has made of the effect the payment of such benefits will have on local authorities (a) in general and (b) with regards to the housing of Syrian migrants under the Vulnerable Persons Relocation Scheme.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16760","16760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429158","2015-11-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether it is his policy that the day of the week on which claimants are asked to sign on for jobseekers allowance should be varied.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16774","16774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429159","2015-11-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much his Department spent on winter fuel payments for UK citizens living in (a) Cyprus, (b) France, (c) Gibraltar, (d) Greece, (e) Malta, (f) Portugal and (g) Spain in 2014-15.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16925","16925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429160","2015-11-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when his Department's review of guidance relating to the eligibility of children with Type 1 diabetes for Disability Living Allowance was initiated; and what conclusion that review reached.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16926","16926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429161","2015-11-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to his oral contribution of 20 June 2011, Official Report, column 52, on state pensions for women, what meetings he has had on the transitional arrangements referred to (a) between 20 June 2011 and 7 May 2015 and (b) since 8 May 2015.","Biography information for Nick Thomas-Symonds","Nick Thomas-Symonds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16900","16900"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429162","2015-11-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to his oral contribution of 20 June 2011, Official Report, column 52, on state pensions for women, whether he plans to make an announcement of transitional provisions prior to the introduction of the single-tier state pension.","Biography information for Nick Thomas-Symonds","Nick Thomas-Symonds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16901","16901"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429379","2015-11-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with the governments of British Overseas Territories with financial centres on central registers of beneficial ownership.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 902319","902319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431833","2015-11-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his French counterpart on the ISIL attacks in Paris and the implications of those attacks for the Government's foreign policy.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 902323","902323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431834","2015-11-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he plans to take to ensure that potential breaches of international humanitarian law by the Saudi-led coalition in Yemen are investigated.","Biography information for Callum McCaig","Callum McCaig","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 902325","902325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431835","2015-11-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his counterparts in the EU, Africa and the Middle East on diplomatic steps to tackle the refugee crisis in the Mediterranean.","Biography information for Wendy Morton","Wendy Morton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 902321","902321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431836","2015-11-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the progress of negotiations to reform the EU and the UK's relationship with the EU.","Biography information for Rebecca Harris","Rebecca Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 902320","902320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431837","2015-11-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent diplomatic steps he has taken to promote peace in Somalia.","Biography information for Chris Heaton-Harris","Chris Heaton-Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 902324","902324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428629","2015-11-19","Department for Education","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of the numbers of 16 to 24 year olds who have turned down training or further education for transport reasons in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16578","16578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428630","2015-11-19","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the effect of withdrawal of ESOL Plus mandated funding on the ability of refugees in the UK to access ESOL courses.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16584","16584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428631","2015-11-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether his Department plans to measure the (a) educational, (b) labour market and (c) societal outcomes of student opportunity allocation funding using individual-based data on a national level.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16612","16612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428632","2015-11-20","HM Treasury","2015-11-17","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to prevent local high street bank branches from closing.","Biography information for Chris Davies","Chris Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16629","16629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428634","2015-11-20","Cabinet Office","2015-11-17","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what progress the Government has made on increasing the level of employment in (a) North Lincolnshire, (b) East Yorkshire and (c) England since 2010.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16628","16628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428635","2015-11-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment the Government has made of the effect on the likelihood of people's reemployment of their prior length of absence from work; and what steps the Government is taking to address that matter.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16623","16623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428636","2015-11-19","HM Treasury","2015-11-17","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans he has to encourage investment in improvement of the environment as part of the Northern Powerhouse initiative.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16588","16588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428637","2015-11-20","HM Treasury","2015-11-17","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what his policy is on the taxation of travel expenses for councillors in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Sammy Wilson","Sammy Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16597","16597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428638","2015-11-19","HM Treasury","2015-11-17","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to support greater diversification in forms of lending in the UK banking sector.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16624","16624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428639","2015-11-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what statutory obligations are placed on local authorities to have an accurate assessment of the (a) capacity, (b) location and (c) other aspects of local utility infrastructure.","Biography information for Mrs Maria Miller","Mrs Maria Miller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16611","16611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428640","2015-11-19","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what recent assessment he has made of the legality of private car park companies charging for overstaying.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16577","16577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428641","2015-11-19","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what plans he has to improve the environment as part of the Northern Powerhouse initiative.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16585","16585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428642","2015-11-19","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether he plans to increase access to green space as part of the Northern Powerhouse initiative.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16586","16586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428643","2015-11-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the change in the number of firefighter posts was in Essex Fire and Rescue Service in 2013-14.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16600","16600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428644","2015-11-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the change in the number of firefighter posts was in Hertfordshire Fire and Rescue Service in 2013-14.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16601","16601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428645","2015-11-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the change in the number of firefighter posts was in Bedfordshire Fire and Rescue Service in 2013-14.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16599","16599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428646","2015-11-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the change in the number of firefighter posts was in Cambridgeshire Fire and Rescue Service in 2013-14.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16602","16602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428647","2015-11-19","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether he plans to redirect proceeds from the National Lottery away from the Big Lottery Fund to fulfil his Department's existing commitments to fund the arts, heritage and sport.","Biography information for Gavin Robinson","Gavin Robinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16544","16544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428649","2015-11-20","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether his Department plans to reduce the Big Lottery Fund budget for Scotland.","Biography information for Owen Thompson","Owen Thompson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16638","16638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428650","2015-11-20","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions his Department has had with the voluntary sector in Scotland on the level of funding for Scotland's Big Lottery Fund.","Biography information for Owen Thompson","Owen Thompson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16639","16639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428651","2015-11-19","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what proportion of national lottery sales income has been allocated to the Big Lottery Fund budget for Scotland in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Owen Thompson","Owen Thompson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16630","16630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428652","2015-11-19","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, in what instances special or additional pension provision has been made for part-time military personnel in the last 20 years.","Biography information for Gavin Robinson","Gavin Robinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16614","16614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428653","2015-11-20","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what proportion of the files held at Swadlincote that are subject to the Public Records Act 1958 have been (a) assessed by and (b) released to the National Archive.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16554","16554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428654","2015-11-19","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether a pension was provided to (a) full and (b) part-time members of the Ulster Defence Regiment who latterly served in the Home Battalions of the Royal Irish Regiment.","Biography information for Gavin Robinson","Gavin Robinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16581","16581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428655","2015-11-19","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department plans to provide a pension to part-time soldiers who served in the Ulster Defence Regiment.","Biography information for Gavin Robinson","Gavin Robinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16582","16582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428656","2015-11-19","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 16 November 2015 to Question 15947, on the Veterans Advisory and Pensions Committees, how long he expects the matter to be under consideration.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16565","16565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428657","2015-11-20","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many files held at Swadlincote his Department has made available to the (a) Historical Enquiries Team and (b) Da Silva Review.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16556","16556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428658","2015-11-20","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what his policy is on declassifying and transferring historical files relating to Northern Ireland held at Swadlincote to the National Archive under the 30-year rule.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16555","16555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428659","2015-11-19","Department for Education","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the level of support available to help families with disabled children find appropriate play opportunities.","Biography information for John Glen","John Glen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16592","16592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428660","2015-11-19","Cabinet Office","2015-11-17","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many pupils are known to be (a) victims, (b) perpetrators of domestic assaults; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen McPartland","Stephen McPartland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16620","16620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428661","2015-11-19","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if she will specify the comparable operators whose costs would be taken into account prior to the Opex reopeners for the contract for difference relating to Hinkley Point C power station being triggered 15 and 25 years after the first reactor start date.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16617","16617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428662","2015-11-20","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate she has made of the effect that the offshore wind industry has on stimulating investment in the north of England.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16627","16627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428663","2015-11-19","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what circumstances would constitute a political shutdown of the proposed Hinkley Point C power station by the EU or international competent authority which would trigger a payment to the operators of that power station.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16616","16616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428664","2015-11-20","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps her Department has taken in response to the provisional report of the Competition and Markets Authority's findings on the energy market; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16606","16606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428665","2015-11-19","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what specific changes are needed to her Department's policies to ensure that the UK meets the EU target of 15 per cent of energy to be sourced from renewable sources before 2020; and what the timetable is for implementing each of those changes.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16546","16546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428666","2015-11-19","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether her Department has received evidence on the effect of the feed-in tariff review on jobs in the solar industry.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16547","16547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428667","2015-11-20","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what cost savings her Department is planning to make in the current financial year.","Biography information for Mr Peter Bone","Mr Peter Bone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16559","16559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428668","2015-11-19","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 3 November 2015 to Question 14118, when she plans to respond to the consultation on the feed-in tariff review.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16569","16569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428669","2015-11-19","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the (a) volume, (b) gross capital and (c) gross revenue costs of planned purchases of renewable energy is from other European countries.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16545","16545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428671","2015-11-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what measures she proposes to introduce to regulate commercial fishermen catching sea bass for the period from 1 January to 30 June 2016.","Biography information for Mrs Sheryll Murray","Mrs Sheryll Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16561","16561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428672","2015-11-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what proposed measures are being introduced for the fishing of sea bass by commercial fishermen in the period from 1 July to 31 December 2016.","Biography information for Mrs Sheryll Murray","Mrs Sheryll Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16562","16562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428673","2015-11-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what changes she proposes to introduce to the regulation of recreational sea anglers who capture sea bass for the period from 1 January to 30 June 2016.","Biography information for Mrs Sheryll Murray","Mrs Sheryll Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16563","16563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428674","2015-11-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what changes she proposes to introduce to the regulation of recreational sea anglers who capture sea bass for the period from 1 July to 31 December 2016.","Biography information for Mrs Sheryll Murray","Mrs Sheryll Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16564","16564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428675","2015-11-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the prevalence of bovine TB was in each (a) month and (b) county from 1996 to 2008.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16548","16548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428676","2015-11-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many horses were exported for slaughter in each of the last 10 financial years.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16615","16615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428678","2015-11-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to establish a central database of horse movement as required by the Equine Identification Regulations by 1 July 2016.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16593","16593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428680","2015-11-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to prevent animal crime in relation to the import and export of horses before the implementation of the Equine Identification Regulations.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16594","16594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428681","2015-11-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to (a) simplify and (b) increase the effectiveness of regulatory standards on trade in horses.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16595","16595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428682","2015-11-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions she has had with the (a) Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government and (b) Chancellor of the Exchequer on improving the environment as part of the Northern Powerhouse initiative.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16587","16587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428683","2015-11-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of freedom of religion and belief in Bangladesh; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16622","16622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428684","2015-11-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how the Government plans to use its position on the UN Security Council to facilitate diplomatic negotiations on protecting civilians in Syria.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16557","16557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428685","2015-11-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when his Department plans to make an announcement regarding resettlement of the British Indian Ocean Territory by Chagos islanders.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16549","16549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428686","2015-11-19","Department of Health","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of the number and accessibility of pharmacy facilities; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16575","16575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428687","2015-11-19","Department of Health","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Answer of 24 March 2015 to Question 227804, if his Department plans to commission further research on (a) patterns of long-term prescription of dependency-forming medicines and (b) the scale of addiction to benzodiazepines, z drugs and other such medicines.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16566","16566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428688","2015-11-19","Department of Health","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Answer of 11 March 2015 to Question 226385, how many local authorities supported by PHE are developing withdrawal services for people affected by addiction to prescription benzodiazepine and drug tranquilisers.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16567","16567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428689","2015-11-20","Department of Health","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what modelling his Department has undertaken of the effect on adult social care of different funding allocations for such services.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16604","16604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428690","2015-11-19","Department of Health","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many complaints about day centres for adults with learning disabilities his Department has received since the establishment of the Care Quality Commission.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16589","16589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428691","2015-11-19","Department of Health","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of adults with learning disabilities using day centres which are not regulated by the Care Quality Commission.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16590","16590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428692","2015-11-19","Department of Health","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he plans to extend the remit of the Care Quality Commission to include the regulation of all day centres; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16591","16591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428693","2015-11-20","Department of Health","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he has considered referring the junior doctors' contract dispute to ACAS.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16598","16598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428694","2015-11-19","Department of Health","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of compliance by doctors with the four-week recommended maximum prescribing period for benzodiazepines and z drugs since 2011.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16618","16618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428695","2015-11-20","Home Office","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what funding her Department plans to allocate to domestic and sexual violence support services after April 2016; and for how long she plans for that funding to be available.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16626","16626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428696","2015-11-20","Home Office","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps the Government is taking to ratify the Council of Europe's Istanbul Convention on Preventing and Combating Violence against Women and Domestic Violence.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16621","16621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428698","2015-11-19","Home Office","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what provisions are in place to safeguard the welfare of pregnant women in Yarl's Wood Immigration Removal Centre.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16596","16596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428699","2015-11-20","Home Office","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people from (a) EU and (b) non-EU countries who have been classified as homeless have been returned to their home countries in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16607","16607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428700","2015-11-19","Home Office","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what progress the National Group on Sexual Violence Against Children and Vulnerable People has made on establishing a Child Sexual Exploitation Response Unit; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen McPartland","Stephen McPartland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16619","16619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428701","2015-11-20","Home Office","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will review the number of counter-terrorism officials in the West Midlands; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16603","16603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428703","2015-11-19","Home Office","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many women held in Yarl's Wood Immigration Removal Centre have legal representation.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16576","16576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428704","2015-11-19","Home Office","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of victims of human trafficking from (a) Benin, (b) Nigeria, (c) Uganda and (d) Zimbabwe who applied for asylum were successful in their application between 2010 and 2015.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16583","16583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428705","2015-11-19","Department of Health","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his Department's policy is on testing detainees for infectious diseases such as TB.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16550","16550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428706","2015-11-19","Home Office","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many women taken to hospital from Yarl's Wood Immigration Removal Centre have been handcuffed in transit in each of the last six months.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16551","16551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428707","2015-11-19","Home Office","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many detainees held in Yarl's Wood Immigration Removal Centre (a) claim that they are victims of human trafficking and (b) have been identified by the National Referral Mechanism as victims of human trafficking.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16552","16552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428708","2015-11-19","Home Office","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many women detained in Yarl's Wood Immigration Removal Centre went on hunger strike in 2015.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16553","16553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428709","2015-11-19","Department for International Development","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether her Department is planning to publish an LGBT Theory of Change.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16568","16568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428710","2015-11-20","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 3 November 2015 to Question 14066, what accountability mechanisms are in place for the Criminal Cases Review Commission; and if he will meet the hon. Member for Sefton Central to discuss the case of James Thompson.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16560","16560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428711","2015-11-20","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prosecutions and convictions have been obtained under sections 60 and 79 of the New Roads and Street Works Act 1991 since that Act came into force.","Biography information for Mrs Maria Miller","Mrs Maria Miller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16609","16609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428712","2015-11-19","Home Office","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what arrangements are in place for the Government and the Northern Ireland Executive to cooperate to counter the Islamic terrorist threat and the potential utilisation by such terrorists of the land border between Northern Ireland and the Republic of Ireland.","Biography information for Ian Paisley","Ian Paisley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16571","16571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428713","2015-11-19","Northern Ireland Office","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, whether proposals to expand the Security Service include the expansion of its facilities and additional recruitment in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Ian Paisley","Ian Paisley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16572","16572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428714","2015-11-19","Northern Ireland Office","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what discussions she has had with the Chancellor of the Exchequer on how Northern Ireland can benefit from contributing to the Northern Powerhouse.","Biography information for Ian Paisley","Ian Paisley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16573","16573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428715","2015-11-20","Scotland Office","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for the Department for Culture, Media and Sport on the level of funding for the Big Lottery Fund.","Biography information for Owen Thompson","Owen Thompson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16640","16640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428717","2015-11-20","Department for Transport","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, for what reasons section 80 of the New Roads and Street Works Act 1991 has not been brought into force.","Biography information for Mrs Maria Miller","Mrs Maria Miller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16610","16610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428718","2015-11-20","Department for Transport","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what investment in transport services the Government plans to make in (a) St Helens North constituency and (b) Merseyside as part of the Northern Powerhouse initiative.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16605","16605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428721","2015-11-19","Department for Transport","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many train services through Neston have been cancelled since August 2015; and what the reason was for the cancellation in each such case.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16574","16574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428722","2015-11-19","Department for Transport","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will extend free bus travel for people with disabilities to include peak hours.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16579","16579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428723","2015-11-19","Department for Transport","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what guidance he provides to local authorities on the enforcement of the prohibition on private hire vehicles plying for hire; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16580","16580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428724","2015-11-19","Department for Transport","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans he has to ensure a more reliable train service is provided to Neston.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16570","16570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428725","2015-11-20","Department for Transport","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what representations his Department received from the Mayor of London on the Transport for London Bill.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16558","16558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428728","2015-11-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what reports he has received of claimants receiving overlapping payments of both universal credit and housing benefit; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16608","16608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428730","2015-11-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to page three of the document Universal Credit: increasing the childcare offer, published by his Department in December 2014, whether his Department remains on course to introduce childcare support into universal credit at 85 per cent of costs in April 2016.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16613","16613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428731","2015-11-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if his Department will conduct a peer review into the death of Alan McCardle in Slough.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16625","16625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428742","2015-11-20","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of introducing statutory regulations of the funeral industry.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16680","16680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428743","2015-11-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what progress has been made towards a resolution of the Scottish Power cashback mis-selling dispute since his meeting in July 2015 with the CEO of the Insolvency Service.","Biography information for Richard Arkless","Richard  Arkless","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16713","16713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428744","2015-11-20","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the current provision of skills required by the digital economy; and what steps he is taking to ensure that training delivered under the apprenticeship levy is geared towards high-value high-skilled jobs.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16689","16689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428745","2015-11-20","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether businesses will be permitted to allocate their apprenticeship-levied funds to small and medium-sized enterprises and other business in their supply chain; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16690","16690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428746","2015-11-20","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the likely effect of the apprenticeship levy on existing professional training and digital skills initiatives provided by the digital technology industry.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16705","16705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428747","2015-11-20","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will issue a response to the Federation of Small Businesses report, entitled Reassured, optimised, transformed: driving digital small business, published in September 2015.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16736","16736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428748","2015-11-19","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many apprenticeship starts there have been in each year since 1997.","Biography information for James Heappey","James Heappey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16673","16673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428749","2015-11-20","Cabinet Office","2015-11-17","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what (a) the amount of any underspend expected against departmental expenditure limits in the current fiscal year and (b) his Department's latest forecast of total annually managed expenditure spend for this year is; and what the forecasts were for those sums at the time of the Summer Budget 2015 and March Budget 2015.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16738","16738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428750","2015-11-20","Cabinet Office","2015-11-17","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of a fundraising preference service on the work of the charity sector.","Biography information for Dr Tania Mathias","Dr Tania Mathias","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16683","16683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428751","2015-11-20","Cabinet Office","2015-11-17","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps he is taking to protect the personal details of those registered with the Government Gateway service from hacking; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Tania Mathias","Dr Tania Mathias","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16682","16682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428752","2015-11-20","HM Treasury","2015-11-17","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many and what value of projects received guarantees through the UK Guarantees Scheme (a) in 2015 and (b) since that scheme's launch.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16730","16730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428753","2015-11-20","HM Treasury","2015-11-17","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will estimate the annual change in tax revenue from extending the national living wage to those aged between 18 and 25.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16700","16700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428754","2015-11-20","HM Treasury","2015-11-17","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the document, Fixing the Foundations: Creating a more prosperous nation, Cm 9098, published in July 2015, if he will publish his Department's analysis linking changes to tax credits with increased productivity.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16701","16701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428755","2015-11-20","HM Treasury","2015-11-17","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he expects to sign off in full the business case for universal credit.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16693","16693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428756","2015-11-20","HM Treasury","2015-11-17","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the document, Fixing the Foundations: Creating a more prosperous nation, Cm 9098, published in July 2015, if he will publish his Department's analysis linking the introduction of a Youth Obligation for 18 to 25 year olds on universal credit with increased productivity.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16702","16702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428757","2015-11-19","HM Treasury","2015-11-17","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with the Northern Ireland Executive on tax credits since 25 October.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16663","16663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428758","2015-11-20","HM Treasury","2015-11-17","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department is taking to embed the family test into its policy making.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16711","16711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428759","2015-11-19","HM Treasury","2015-11-17","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what his estimate is of revenue lost to the Exchequer through fuel laundering in Northern Ireland in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16637","16637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428760","2015-11-20","HM Treasury","2015-11-17","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many and what value of projects received investment through the Infrastructure Investment Forum (a) in 2015 and (b) since the Forum's launch.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16739","16739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428761","2015-11-19","HM Treasury","2015-11-17","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what his policy is on raising the upper trivial commutation limit for pensions above 30,000.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16666","16666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428762","2015-11-19","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what guidance his Department publishes to local authorities and housing associations on providing a safe means of exit for disabled residents in the event of an emergency.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16714","16714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428763","2015-11-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, through what channels his Department plans to disburse the 3.2 million payment from the Fire and Rescue Authorities to private landlords for smoke and carbon dioxide alarms after the introduction of the Smoke and Carbon Monoxide Alarm (England) Regulations 2015.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16737","16737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428764","2015-11-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he plans to appoint the Chair of the review of the localisation of council tax benefit; and by what process he plans for that Chair and other people working on that review work to be selected.","Biography information for Ms Karen Buck","Ms Karen Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16641","16641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428765","2015-11-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will place in the Library the minutes of the meeting of the Council Tax Partnership Forum in June 2015.","Biography information for Ms Karen Buck","Ms Karen Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16645","16645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428766","2015-11-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the reason is for the time taken to publish the terms of reference of the review of the localisation of council tax benefit.","Biography information for Ms Karen Buck","Ms Karen Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16642","16642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428767","2015-11-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many staff are currently working on the review of the localisation of council tax benefit; and whether he plans for further appointments to be made to this team.","Biography information for Ms Karen Buck","Ms Karen Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16643","16643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428768","2015-11-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will place in the Library a copy of the terms of reference of the Council Tax Partnership Forum.","Biography information for Ms Karen Buck","Ms Karen Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16644","16644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428769","2015-11-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much his Department provided in Homelessness Prevention Grant to each local authority in London in (a) 2012-13, (b) 2013-14, (c) 2014-15 and (d) 2015-16.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16726","16726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428770","2015-11-19","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 16 November 2015 to Question 15873, on broadband: Cheshire, if he will take steps to  bring the planned coverage of Eddisbury in line with the Cheshire average.","Biography information for Antoinette Sandbach","Antoinette Sandbach","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16734","16734"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428771","2015-11-19","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that public opinion is taken into account in its input to the BBC Charter review.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16633","16633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428772","2015-11-19","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many community projects have benefited from monies allocated by Scotland's Big Lottery Fund in the last five years.","Biography information for Owen Thompson","Owen Thompson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16631","16631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428773","2015-11-19","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the likely effect of redundancies in the UK steel industry on the proportion of defence procurement that arises from UK businesses.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16653","16653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428774","2015-11-20","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when his Department expects to know how much of the Joint Security Fund announced by the Chancellor of the Exchequer in July 2015 will be allocated to his Department.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16647","16647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428775","2015-11-19","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he plans for UK personnel to train at or otherwise attend the new General Atomics unmanned aircraft business park being built in North Dakota.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16740","16740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428776","2015-11-19","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether UK Reapers have been made available for use by the US or other coalition partners in Syria for operations since January 2015.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16741","16741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428777","2015-11-19","Department for Education","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many pupils eligible for free school meals took up a place at each university in each year since 2005-06.","Biography information for Suella Braverman","Suella Fernandes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16670","16670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428778","2015-11-20","Department for Education","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 16 November 2015 to Question 15281, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of the number of teachers trained in the last 10 years; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16706","16706"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428779","2015-11-19","Department for Education","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 12 November to Question 14860, whether all of the providers approved by her Department to provide baseline assessment for primary schools reached the qualifying 10 per cent threshold for providers by the 30 April 2015 deadline.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16662","16662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428780","2015-11-20","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether the agreement signed with China to fund Hinckley Point C nuclear reactor includes funding from China for (a) decommissioning costs and (b) emergency clean-up costs.","Biography information for Dr Tania Mathias","Dr Tania Mathias","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16727","16727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428781","2015-11-20","Department of Health","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether British expatriates who pay income tax in the UK will be charged for medical treatment in the UK.","Biography information for Dr Tania Mathias","Dr Tania Mathias","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16728","16728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428782","2015-11-20","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what her Department's spending on (a) temporary agency staff, (b) consultants, (c) non-payroll staff, (d) administration and (e) marketing and advertising was in (i) 2014-15 prices and (ii) as a share of her Department's total budget in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16707","16707"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428783","2015-11-20","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what her Department's expected underspend is against departmental expenditure limits in the current fiscal year; and what her Department's latest forecast of total AME spend is for this year compared to forecasts at the time of the (a) Summer Budget 2015 and (b) March Budget 2015.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16708","16708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428784","2015-11-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much support from EU agricultural funding has been awarded to UK organic food producers in each of the last five years.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16720","16720"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428785","2015-11-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when she plans to publish her Department's new code of practice on the use of fox snares.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16699","16699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428786","2015-11-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when she will publish the Joint Hen Harrier Recovery Plan.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16704","16704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428787","2015-11-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what her policy is on utilising the skills of animal welfare charities and voluntary organisations to monitor CCTV in slaughterhouses.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16655","16655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428788","2015-11-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to embed the Family Test into its policy making.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16681","16681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428789","2015-11-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many of the (a) core recommendations and (b) specific recommendations of his Department's report entitled Children in Military Custody, published in June 2012, the Israeli government has implemented.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16735","16735"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428790","2015-11-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the implications for the Falkland Islands of the results of the recent Argentinian presidential election.","Biography information for Antoinette Sandbach","Antoinette Sandbach","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16661","16661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428791","2015-11-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the UK contribution to the European External Action Service has been in each year since its creation; and what proportion of the European External Action Service's overall budget the UK has contributed in each such year.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16664","16664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428792","2015-11-20","Department of Health","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent review his Department has conducted into the adequacy of suicide prevention support for (a) men and (b) women; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16703","16703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428793","2015-11-19","Department of Health","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the appropriateness of the use of amalgam in dental fillings.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16715","16715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428794","2015-11-20","Department of Health","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients in (a) St Helens North constituency, (b) Merseyside and (c) the UK were admitted to mental health hospitals outside of their local authority area in the last five years.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16709","16709"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428795","2015-11-19","Department of Health","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many student midwives were in receipt of a bursary in each of the last 10 years for which figures are available; what the average bursary paid to a student midwife was in each of those years; and what the total cost to the public purse in bursaries paid to student midwives was in each such year.","Biography information for Maria Caulfield","Maria Caulfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16671","16671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428796","2015-11-19","Department of Health","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps have been taken to encourage the implementation of improvement interventions relating to chronic kidney disease since April 2015.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16742","16742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428797","2015-11-19","Department of Health","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans his Department has to improve the level of knowledge and awareness amongst GPs of acute kidney injury; and who he plans will lead those initiatives.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16743","16743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428798","2015-11-20","Department of Health","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer given by the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Care Quality during Oral Questions on 17 November 2015 on the establishment of a working party to examine issues regarding the availability of off-patent, repurposed drugs, when the working party was established; what the working party's scope and terms of reference are; which organisations and individuals have been invited to join the working party; and when the next meeting of the working party will be convened.","Biography information for Nick Thomas-Symonds","Nick Thomas-Symonds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16729","16729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428799","2015-11-19","Department of Health","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make an assessment of the quality and rigour of checks made by locum agencies of the character and credentials of staff to be provided to the NHS or social services; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Oliver Heald","Sir Oliver Heald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16660","16660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428800","2015-11-19","Department of Health","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what checks locum agencies are required to make when they sub-contract the provision of staff to other locum agencies for temporary workers in the NHS or social services; what steps are taken to ensure proper checks are made on the quality and character of such staff; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Oliver Heald","Sir Oliver Heald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16659","16659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428801","2015-11-20","Department of Health","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many children in each parliamentary constituency are diagnosed with ADHD.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16725","16725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428802","2015-11-20","Department of Health","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what financial support his Department has provided to the National Suicide Prevention Alliance in each of the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16697","16697"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428803","2015-11-20","Department of Health","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to embed the Family Test into its policy making.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16698","16698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428804","2015-11-20","Department of Health","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that men make use of mental health services when they need them; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16694","16694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428805","2015-12-01","Department of Health","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of progress in the urgent and emergency care vanguard run by South Devon and Torbay System Resilience Group.","Biography information for Anne Marie Morris","Anne Marie Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16731","16731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428806","2015-12-01","Department of Health","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to develop a strategy for rural healthcare.","Biography information for Anne Marie Morris","Anne Marie Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16732","16732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428807","2015-12-01","Department of Health","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether there are any vanguards in rural areas.","Biography information for Anne Marie Morris","Anne Marie Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16733","16733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428808","2015-11-20","Department of Health","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress has been made on implementing the aspirations in NHS England's report entitled, The Future in Mind, published in October 2012.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16651","16651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428809","2015-11-20","Department of Health","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with Ministers in the Department of Education on the provision of specialist mental health services for children and young people who have been victims of (a) child sexual exploitation, (b) bereavement and (c) abuse.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16652","16652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428810","2015-11-20","Department of Health","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the cost to the NHS of NHS mental health patients being treated in non-NHS institutions has been in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16648","16648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428811","2015-11-19","Department of Health","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the total population of student midwives in England was in the latest year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Maria Caulfield","Maria Caulfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16654","16654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428812","2015-11-20","Department of Health","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with Ministers in the Department for Work and Pensions on the effect of sanctions on the mental health of people who have been so sanctioned.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16649","16649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428813","2015-11-20","Department of Health","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress has been made in preparation for the introduction of waiting time targets for child and adolescent mental health services; and when he plans for those waiting times to come into effect.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16650","16650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428814","2015-11-19","Department of Health","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the total cost was to his Department of training student midwives in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Maria Caulfield","Maria Caulfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16632","16632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428815","2015-11-20","Home Office","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of immigration detainees who are (a) foreign national offenders convicted of immigration offences, (b) foreign national offenders convicted of non-immigration offences and (c) other detainees were held in immigration detention for (i) 28 days or fewer, (ii) over 28 days but fewer than four months and (iii) over four months in the last year.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16675","16675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428816","2015-11-20","Home Office","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of people held in immigration detention are (a) foreign national offenders convicted of immigration related offences, (b) foreign national offenders convicted of other offences and (c) non-foreign nationals.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16676","16676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428817","2015-11-20","Home Office","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to embed the Family Test into its policy making.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16710","16710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428818","2015-11-19","Home Office","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to her Statement of 16 November 2015, Official Report, columns 379 to 382, what proportion of the new security officers announced in that Statement she plans will be based in Scotland.","Biography information for Richard Arkless","Richard  Arkless","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16634","16634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428819","2015-11-20","Home Office","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, for what purposes her Department used the income it raised from visa applications in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Michelle Thomson","Michelle  Thomson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16686","16686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428820","2015-11-20","Home Office","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the average amount people spent on visa applications before being granted entry to the UK in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Michelle Thomson","Michelle  Thomson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16687","16687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428821","2015-11-20","Home Office","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, for what reason her Department no longer publishes accounts of the revenue stream from visa services previously published by the UK Border Agency.","Biography information for Michelle Thomson","Michelle  Thomson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16684","16684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428822","2015-11-20","Home Office","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much revenue her Department has raised from each category of visa in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Michelle Thomson","Michelle  Thomson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16685","16685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428823","2015-11-19","Home Office","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent discussions she has had with her Irish counterpart on steps to counter terrorist threats.","Biography information for Tom Elliott","Tom Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16668","16668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428824","2015-11-19","Cabinet Office","2015-11-17","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, for what reason a representative of Northern Ireland was not present at the COBR meeting on 15 November 2015.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16667","16667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428825","2015-11-19","Home Office","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assistance the Government has given to (a) Kent Police, (b) Kent County Council, (c) other operational organisations and (d) businesses to cover costs incurred during the implementation of Operation Stack in Summer 2015.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16665","16665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428826","2015-11-20","House of Commons Commission","2015-11-17","To ask the hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington representing the House of Commons Commission, how many incidents of (a) hacking, (b) viruses and (c) data breaches were reported to the Parliamentary Digital Service in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16688","16688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428827","2015-11-20","House of Commons Commission","2015-11-17","To ask the hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington representing the House of Commons Commission, what steps the Parliamentary Digital Service is taking to protect constituency casework data.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16678","16678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428828","2015-11-19","House of Commons Commission","2015-11-17","To ask the hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington representing the House of Commons Commission, if he will provide an update on whether there are plans for a review of security protocols for the Parliamentary Estate and what communication the Serjeant at Arms office has had with relevant government departments on increasing the security of the House and the safety of staff.","Biography information for Richard Arkless","Richard  Arkless","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16656","16656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428829","2015-11-19","Department for International Development","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much her Department has spent on (a) temporary agency staff, (b) consultants, (c) non-payroll staff, (d) administration and (e) marketing and advertising in real terms in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16657","16657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428830","2015-11-20","Department for International Development","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to embed the Family Test into its policy making.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16712","16712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428831","2015-11-19","Department for International Development","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what (a) the amount of any underspend expected against departmental expenditure limits in the current fiscal year and (b) her Department's latest forecast of total annually managed expenditure spend for this year is; and what the forecasts were for those sums at the time of the Summer Budget 2015 and March Budget 2015.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16658","16658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428832","2015-11-20","Department for International Development","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to support refugees from Iran; and what recent assessment she has made of the safety of Iranian refuges in Iraq.","Biography information for Dr Tania Mathias","Dr Tania Mathias","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16691","16691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428833","2015-11-19","Northern Ireland Office","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what discussions she has had with the Northern Ireland executive about (a) the licensing of road hauliers and (b) tackling transportation of illicit fuel.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16635","16635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428834","2015-11-19","HM Treasury","2015-11-17","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment has been made of the effectiveness of cross border co-operation in reducing the level of fuel laundering.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16636","16636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428835","2015-11-20","Department for Transport","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether a security review has been initiated for the purpose of strengthening port security between Northern Ireland and Scotland.","Biography information for Richard Arkless","Richard  Arkless","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16646","16646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428836","2015-11-19","Scotland Office","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what recent discussions he has had with the (a) Scottish Government and (b) Scottish FA on strengthening security at Scottish stadiums and sporting events.","Biography information for Richard Arkless","Richard  Arkless","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16672","16672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428837","2015-11-19","Department for Transport","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many children have died in road accidents since 2010-11; and if he will estimate what proportion of those children were from households in the lowest income decile.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16674","16674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428838","2015-11-19","Department for Transport","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions he has had with his counterparts in the Northern Ireland Executive on the Airports Commission: Final report, published July 2015.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16724","16724"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428839","2015-11-19","Department for Transport","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the set of proposals sent to his Department during the summer from local authorities, industry bodies and others about a long term alternative to Operation Stack.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16669","16669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428840","2015-11-19","Department for Transport","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he intends to publish the Office for Road and Rail's first Highways England Monitor.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16723","16723"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428841","2015-11-19","Department for Transport","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what guidance his Department has published on the use of plastic bags to contain liquids as passengers pass through aviation security.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16716","16716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428842","2015-11-19","Department for Transport","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what guidance his Department has published for the aviation industry on the definition of liquid.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16717","16717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428843","2015-11-19","Department for Transport","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what guidance his Department has published on the size of plastic bags used to carry liquids through airport security.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16718","16718"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428844","2015-11-19","Department for Transport","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what variations his Department allows between security measures applied at airports.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16719","16719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428845","2015-11-19","Department for Transport","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 16 November 2015 to Question 16052, what steps he is taking to ensure that the two Skoda vehicles tested were representative of the affected models and manufacturers from the Volkswagen Group; and what steps were taken to validate the effectiveness of the test procedure for the wider programme.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16721","16721"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428846","2015-11-19","Department for Transport","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 16 November 2015 to Question 16052, if he will estimate the number of vehicles likely to be tested; and what criteria is being used to decide which models will be tested.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16722","16722"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428847","2015-11-20","Department for Transport","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the total annual consumption of wifi data on trains operated by each franchise; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16677","16677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428848","2015-11-20","Department for Transport","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what progress has been made on the Quicksilver project to build out wifi and mobile infrastructure alongside rail lines; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16679","16679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428849","2015-11-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he expects the business case for universal credit to be signed off in full.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16692","16692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428850","2015-11-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of disability living allowance applications for children diagnosed with ADHD have been rejected in each of the last five financial years.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16696","16696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428851","2015-11-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many children in each parliamentary constituency and in receipt of disability living allowance are diagnosed with hyperkinetic syndrome.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16695","16695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431472","2015-11-23","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent assessment he has made of the cost effectiveness of the Trident programme over the last five years.","Biography information for Owen Thompson","Owen Thompson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 902278","902278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/432032","2015-11-25","Northern Ireland Office","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what recent assessment she has made of the security situation in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Sir Henry Bellingham","Mr Henry Bellingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 902254","902254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/432117","2015-11-25","Northern Ireland Office","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what discussions she has had with Cabinet colleagues on income tax assignment to Northern Ireland; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Graham Allen","Mr Graham Allen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 902252","902252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/432118","2015-11-25","Northern Ireland Office","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what steps the Government is taking to tackle low pay in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 902256","902256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/432119","2015-11-25","Northern Ireland Office","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what discussions she has had with Cabinet colleagues on ensuring that Northern Ireland benefits from the Government's planned expansion of the intelligence agencies.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 902248","902248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/432120","2015-11-25","Northern Ireland Office","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what representations she has received on support for charities which provide sexual health advice and services in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 902249","902249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/432121","2015-11-25","Northern Ireland Office","2015-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what recent assessment she has made of the political situation in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Jenny Chapman","Jenny Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 902253","902253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428284","2015-11-18","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he plans to take to ensure that high-speed broadband provision can meet the likely demand for such provision by 2020 of creative and digital companies in geographic clusters.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16353","16353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428289","2015-11-18","Home Office","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the potential effect of proposed changes to Tier 2 visas on the recruitment of people with specific skills from overseas to the video games industry.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16352","16352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428290","2015-11-18","Home Office","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will raise the issue of transport of assault rifles and semi-automatic machine guns into and across the EU at the next Home Affairs European Council; and whether she has raised the issue with Europol.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16433","16433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428292","2015-11-18","Prime Minister","2015-11-16","To ask the Prime Minister, what discussions he has had with his counterparts at the G20 in Turkey on support provided to ISIS by nationals of Saudi Arabia and Qatar.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16431","16431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428293","2015-11-18","Prime Minister","2015-11-16","To ask the Prime Minister, what assessment he has made of the evidence provided to the G20 summit in Turkey by President Putin of Russia that funding for ISIS activities has come from countries within the G20.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16432","16432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428294","2015-11-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to support initiatives to increase hedgehog numbers.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16499","16499"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428296","2015-11-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his Saudi Arabian counterpart on (a) support given by nationals of Saudi Arabia to ISIS and (b) ways to stop such assistance.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16418","16418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428298","2015-11-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 13 November 2015 to Question 15120, on Western Sahara: human rights, whether he discussed reports of intimidation, harassment and kidnapping of human rights defenders in the Occupied Territories of Western Sahara during the visit of King Mohamed VI.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16509","16509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428299","2015-11-18","HM Treasury","2015-11-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the total amount received by the Treasury in profit from the Crown Estate was in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16419","16419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428302","2015-11-18","Department of Health","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential financial benefits to the NHS of increased utilisation of biosimilar medicines.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16399","16399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428303","2015-11-18","Department of Health","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to raise awareness of biosimilar medicines amongst NHS healthcare professionals.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16400","16400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428305","2015-11-18","Department of Health","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to support the uptake of (a) biosimilar products and (b) other innovative and clinically beneficial forms of medicine.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16408","16408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428307","2015-11-19","Department of Health","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of information maintained by the NHS to enable his Department to assess the reasons why women choose to have a BRCA1/2 test.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16389","16389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428308","2015-11-19","Department of Health","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will publish data on molecular genetic test activity rates in 2012-13 and each subsequent year.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16390","16390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428309","2015-11-19","Department of Health","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will require a UK Genetics Testing Network to audit Clinical Commissioning Policy: Genetic Testing for BRCA1/2 Mutations, published by NHS England in 2014.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16391","16391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428316","2015-11-19","HM Treasury","2015-11-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the spending reductions agreed between his Department and the Department for Transport will affect Barnett consequentials.","Biography information for Drew Hendry","Drew Hendry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16327","16327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428318","2015-11-19","Department for Transport","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what effect the spending reductions agreed between his Department and HM Treasury will have on the (a) Driver and Vehicle Standards Agency, (b) Driver and Vehicle Licensing Agency, (c) Maritime and Coastguard Agency and (d) Vehicle Certification Agency.","Biography information for Drew Hendry","Drew Hendry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16328","16328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428319","2015-11-20","Department for Transport","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what effect the spending reductions agreed between his Department and HM Treasury will have on investment in (a) road, (b) rail, (c) air, (d) ports and ferry services, (e) active and sustainable travel and (f) freight facilities.","Biography information for Drew Hendry","Drew Hendry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16329","16329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428320","2015-11-20","Department for Transport","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department plans to introduce or increase any revenue raising streams to complement the departmental spending reductions agreed with HM Treasury.","Biography information for Drew Hendry","Drew Hendry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16330","16330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428321","2015-11-23","Department for Transport","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether (a) his Department and (b) its agencies plan to review their estates as a result of spending reductions agreed with HM Treasury.","Biography information for Drew Hendry","Drew Hendry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16331","16331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428327","2015-11-18","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of adult education courses in helping people into work.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16320","16320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428329","2015-11-18","HM Treasury","2015-11-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the tax revenue that may be received from the Point of Consumption Tax on online betting and gaming.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16373","16373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428331","2015-11-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans her Department has to renew its funding for the National Wildlife Crime Unit after March 2016.","Biography information for Gerald Jones","Gerald Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16385","16385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428332","2015-11-19","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps her Department is taking to improve the energy efficiency of homes; and whether any of the National Infrastructure Committee's funding will be available for use to increase home energy efficiency.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16366","16366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428333","2015-11-18","Home Office","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the effect of her Department's miscalculation of the amount of funding available for West Midlands Police on the adequacy of the provision of policing in Birmingham; and what steps she is taking to ensure effective policing in that city.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16360","16360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428335","2015-11-19","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the effect of increasing spending on the science capital commitment on UK productivity.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16489","16489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428336","2015-11-19","HM Treasury","2015-11-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the increased tax revenue from extending the National Living Wage to those aged 18 to 25.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16466","16466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428338","2015-11-19","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions he has had with industry representatives on the Universal Service Obligation announced by the Prime Minister on 7 November 2015; and what representations he has received from such representatives since.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16478","16478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428340","2015-11-19","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to the Prime Minister's announcement of 7 November 2015 on broadband access, what discussions he has had with Ofcom on a Universal Service Obligation for broadband; and whether Ofcom were aware of the obligation before it was announced.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16510","16510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428341","2015-11-19","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to the Prime Minister's announcement of 7 November 2015 on broadband access, what public funding has been assigned for the delivery of the Universal Service Obligation for broadband; and whether he plans to publish this information as part of the comprehensive spending review.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16511","16511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428342","2015-11-19","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to the Prime Minister's announcement of 7 November 2015 on broadband access, whether the Government will consult on the Universal Service Obligation for broadband.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16512","16512"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428344","2015-11-19","Department for Transport","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with whom did the Driver and Vehicle Licensing Agency share licence data in 2014-15; and what payments were received for such data sharing.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16479","16479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428347","2015-11-18","HM Treasury","2015-11-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many staff of the Financial Conduct Authority and the Financial Services Authority worked on money laundering enforcement in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16376","16376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428348","2015-11-18","HM Treasury","2015-11-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, which companies were prosecuted by the Financial Conduct Authority or the Financial Services Authority for issues relating to money laundering in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16375","16375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428349","2015-11-19","HM Treasury","2015-11-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many (a) investigations and (b) enforcement actions into money laundering offences have been commenced by the Financial Conduct Authority and the Financial Services Authority in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16394","16394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428350","2015-11-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what progress her Department has made towards the targets for protecting peat set out in the Natural Environment White Paper of 2011 since the publication of the last implementation update report in October 2014.","Biography information for Richard Benyon","Richard Benyon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16344","16344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428351","2015-11-19","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what guidance his Department provides to housing associations on the proportion of their new build properties that must be capable of adaptation.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16469","16469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428352","2015-11-19","HM Treasury","2015-11-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that an approach supply of finance to productive investment is available to help increase productivity.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16397","16397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428353","2015-11-19","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the effect of the provision of high-speed broadband infrastructure on productivity.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16395","16395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428354","2015-11-19","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department is taking to improve the UK's productivity.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16396","16396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428355","2015-11-19","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, for what reasons the number of prisoners being released on Home Detention Curfews in Devon decreased between 2011 and 2014.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16339","16339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428356","2015-11-19","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners released on a Home Detention Curfew in Devon broke their curfew conditions between 2011 and 2014.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16340","16340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428357","2015-11-19","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners released under a Home Detention Curfew in Devon were returned to prison after breaking the conditions of such a curfew between 2011 and 2014.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16341","16341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428358","2015-11-18","Department of Health","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to improve the assessment of medicines for rarer cancers with small patient populations.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16497","16497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428359","2015-11-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the conduct of the recent elections in Burma.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16398","16398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428360","2015-11-19","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what recent discussions she has had with her European counterparts about minimum EPC standards for the private rented sector.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16463","16463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428361","2015-11-19","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what recent discussions she has had with local authorities about minimum EPC standards for the private rented sector.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16464","16464"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428362","2015-11-19","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what recent discussions she has had with the cavity wall insulation industry about minimum EPC standards in the private rented sector.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16465","16465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428363","2015-11-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will take steps to ensure that universal credit claimants are not sanctioned in the period between accepting an offer of employment and starting employment.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16361","16361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428364","2015-11-19","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what his plans are for the Tranche 3 a Typhoon aircraft; and how many such aircraft are in storage.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16476","16476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428365","2015-11-19","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the current status is of the purchase Tranche 3 b Typhoon aircraft; and how many such aircraft his Department plans to purchase.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16473","16473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428366","2015-11-18","Department for International Development","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what support her Department is providing to aid agencies and international partners to prepare Syrian refugee camps for winter.","Biography information for Dawn Butler","Dawn Butler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16498","16498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428367","2015-11-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations the British High Commission in Colombo has received from (a) the Tamil National Alliance and (b) Tamil civil society groups on the treatment of Tamil political prisoners in Sri Lanka.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16378","16378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428368","2015-11-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his Sri Lankan counterpart on the application of the Prevention of Terrorism Act 1978 in Sri Lanka.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16355","16355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428369","2015-11-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of reports that Tamil political prisoners have been on hunger strike in Sri Lanka; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16356","16356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428370","2015-11-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his Sri Lankan counterpart on the detention of Tamil political prisoners in Sri Lanka.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16357","16357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428371","2015-11-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the (a) human rights situation in Sri Lanka and (b) detention of Tamil political prisoners in that country.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16358","16358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428372","2015-11-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether 18 to 21 year olds who live in supported accommodation will be able to claim the housing element of universal credit when they move out of supported accommodation.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16318","16318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428373","2015-11-18","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether she has given consideration to re-classifying electricity storage vessels to enable distribution network operators to utilise such vessels without paying generation charges.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16370","16370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428374","2015-11-18","Northern Ireland Office","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what discussions she has had with the Secretary of State for Defence on the release of documents relating to Northern Ireland held at Swadlincote under the 30-year rule.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16335","16335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428375","2015-11-19","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the implications are for the (a) PEACE and (b) INTERREG IVA programmes in (i) the UK and (ii) Northern Ireland of a UK decision to leave the EU.","Biography information for Dr Alasdair McDonnell","Dr Alasdair McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16321","16321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428376","2015-11-19","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what representations she has made to energy companies to ensure they pass on reductions in the wholesale price of gas and electricity to the consumer.","Biography information for Wayne David","Wayne David","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16468","16468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428377","2015-11-18","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans his Department has to hold national events to commemorate the 100th anniversary of the founding of the RAF in 2018.","Biography information for Edward Argar","Edward Argar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16345","16345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428378","2015-11-18","HM Treasury","2015-11-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of the cost to HM Revenue and Customs of administering and enforcing self-employed registration for students in full-time education earning less than the Personal Allowance.","Biography information for Ms Nusrat Ghani","Nusrat Ghani","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16434","16434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428379","2015-11-18","HM Treasury","2015-11-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of the potential benefits of removing the obligation to register as self-employed for students in full-time education earning less than the standard personal allowance.","Biography information for Ms Nusrat Ghani","Nusrat Ghani","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16423","16423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428380","2015-11-18","HM Treasury","2015-11-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps the Government is taking to reduce the indebtedness of people aged 18 to 25.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16529","16529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428381","2015-11-18","Cabinet Office","2015-11-16","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what information his Department holds on the average debt of young people aged 18 to 25.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16530","16530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428382","2015-11-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Indian counterpart on the treatment of Muslims and Christians in India.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16532","16532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428383","2015-11-18","Home Office","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions she has had with her French counterpart on the possible introduction of fingerprinting at Schengen zone borders.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16533","16533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428384","2015-11-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions she has had with the (a) NFU and (b) other farming bodies on the effect of herbicides on reducing crop yields.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16543","16543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428385","2015-11-18","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many people were recruited to the (a) army, (b) Royal Air Force, (c) Royal Navy and (d) reserve forces in Northern Ireland in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16528","16528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428386","2015-11-18","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will take steps to reduce Islamist culture at HM Prison Whitemoor.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16526","16526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428387","2015-11-18","Department for Transport","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he plans to reach a decision on the possible expansion of Heathrow Airport.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16527","16527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428388","2015-11-18","Department of Health","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people were diagnosed with pneumococcal pneumonia in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16522","16522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428389","2015-11-18","Department of Health","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of when new, cheap forms of blood cancer tests are likely to be made available on the NHS.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16523","16523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428390","2015-11-18","Department of Health","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will promulgate official advice to pregnant women not to drink alcohol.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16524","16524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428391","2015-11-18","Department of Health","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make Translarna available on the NHS to treat Duchenne Muscular Dystrophy.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16534","16534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428392","2015-11-18","Department of Health","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to monitor and control eye surgery.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16535","16535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428393","2015-11-18","Department of Health","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people have had corrective laser eye surgery in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16536","16536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428394","2015-11-18","Department of Health","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people have had (a) successful and (b) unsuccessful laser eye surgery in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16537","16537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428395","2015-11-18","Department of Health","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to raise awareness of the risks of parents sharing a bed with their baby.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16538","16538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428396","2015-11-18","Department of Health","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will review NHS diabetes dietary guidelines.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16539","16539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428397","2015-11-18","Department of Health","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that (a) adults and (b) children undertake appropriate health checks to prevent diabetes complications.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16540","16540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428398","2015-11-18","Department of Health","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that (a) an appropriate number of podiatrists work in the NHS and (b) such podiatrists are appropriately trained.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16541","16541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428399","2015-11-18","Department of Health","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he plans for 3D heart imaging to identify blocked arteries to be available on the NHS.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16542","16542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428400","2015-11-18","Department of Health","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what educational and health programmes are (a) in place and (b) planned to reduce the incidence of sexually transmitted disease.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16525","16525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428401","2015-11-18","Department of Health","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what mandatory requirements are in place to ensure that care home staff are well trained.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16515","16515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428402","2015-11-18","Department of Health","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people were diagnosed with complex regional pain syndrome in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16516","16516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428403","2015-11-18","Cabinet Office","2015-11-16","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many women were diagnosed with breast cancer in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16517","16517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428404","2015-11-18","Department of Health","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will commission an independent five-year review of provision for diabetes.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16518","16518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428405","2015-11-18","Department of Health","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will commission structural education courses to prevent diabetes, in line with NICE guidance.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16519","16519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428406","2015-11-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is planning to enable more people aged over 50 to gain employment.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16531","16531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428407","2015-11-19","Department of Health","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 23 March 2015 to Question 227900, how much of the 250 million additional funding that was committed has been spent; and how many children and young people with mental health problems this funding has supported.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16520","16520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428408","2015-11-19","Department of Health","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 23 March 2015 to Question 227900, why people are counted only once during the year regardless of how many times they were in hospital; and whether he plans to change this counting method.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16521","16521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428409","2015-11-19","Department of Health","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many children were admitted to adult inpatient mental health wards in 2014-15.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16486","16486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428410","2015-11-19","Department of Health","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many specialist mental health centres for those with drug and alcohol addiction were funded by NHS England in each of the last three years; and how many people each such centre supported.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16485","16485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428411","2015-11-19","Department of Health","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the oral contribution of the Minister for Community and Social Care of 14 October 2015, Official Report, column 464, how many veterans the 10 mental health teams have supported in each year since they were opened.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16504","16504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428412","2015-11-18","Department for Transport","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what mitigation work is planned for Chicklade as part of the plans to dual the A303 at Stonehenge.","Biography information for Dr Andrew Murrison","Dr Andrew Murrison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16374","16374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428413","2015-11-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answers of the 24 June 2015 to Questions 4118 and 4121 and the statement of the Minister for Europe of 10 November 2015, Official Report, column 239, in which he stated that 'roughly like 40 per cent of the people from elsewhere in the EU who live in the UK are in receipt of benefits or tax credits of some sort,' how this figure was calculated; how many EU citizens have been in the UK for less than four years; and of those people how many have made individual claims for tax credits.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16392","16392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428414","2015-11-19","Department of Health","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the availability of medicines which treat patients with chronic myeloid leukaemia who are resistant or intolerant to tyrosine kinase inhibitor therapies.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16337","16337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428415","2015-11-18","Department for Education","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many pupils have been suspended from school for having committed domestic assaults in each year since 2012; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen McPartland","Stephen McPartland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16347","16347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428416","2015-11-18","Cabinet Office","2015-11-16","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many students in higher and further education have been recorded as victims of domestic assaults in each year since 2012.","Biography information for Stephen McPartland","Stephen McPartland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16348","16348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428417","2015-11-18","Department for Transport","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to section 32(1) of the Pilotage Act 1987, what plans he has to bring forward legislative proposals to maintain pilotage standards in areas where harbour authorities now have the power to impose compulsory pilotage upon shipping.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16452","16452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428418","2015-11-19","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the cost of using external agencies for recruitment to senior Civil Service posts in his Department in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16475","16475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428419","2015-11-18","Cabinet Office","2015-11-16","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much his Department spent in legal costs on the Information Rights Tribunal case on the Reducing Regulation Sub-Committee Freedom of Information request.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16447","16447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428420","2015-11-18","Cabinet Office","2015-11-16","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, on how many occasions the Reducing Regulation Sub-Committee has met.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16359","16359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428421","2015-11-19","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the cost of using external agencies for recruitment to senior Civil Service posts in his Department in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16474","16474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428422","2015-11-19","Department of Health","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the cost of using external agencies for recruitment to senior Civil Service posts in his Department in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16477","16477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428423","2015-11-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what estimate he has made of the cost of using external agencies for recruitment of Senior Civil posts in his Department in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16484","16484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428424","2015-11-19","Home Office","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 3 November 2015 to Question 13442, what proportion of case workers in her Department received Keeping Children Safe Tier 3 training in 2014.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16326","16326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428425","2015-11-18","Department of Health","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Answer of 9 January 2015 to Question 219449, what progress has been made in improving wheelchair services following the NHS England review.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16448","16448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428426","2015-11-18","Department of Health","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he plans to take to ensure that people with rare neuromuscular conditions in Sheffield, Heeley constituency have access to the appropriate wheelchair for their condition.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16411","16411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428427","2015-11-19","Home Office","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what technical consultancy was provided to her Department to help produce the draft Investigatory Powers Bill; and how much was spent from the public purse on such consultancy.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16393","16393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428428","2015-11-19","Scotland Office","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, whether the Government plans to table amendments to the Scotland Bill in the House of Lords.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16324","16324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428429","2015-11-18","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many inmates are able to access education at HM Prison Holloway each day.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16371","16371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428430","2015-11-18","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisons do not accommodate workshops.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16430","16430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428431","2015-11-18","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many workshop placements were delivered in prisons for (a) women and (b) men in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16429","16429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428432","2015-11-18","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how he plans to assess whether prisoners identified as having poor English and mathematics skills make progress prior to their release.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16426","16426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428433","2015-11-18","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the quality of educational facilities in HM Prison Holloway; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16425","16425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428434","2015-11-18","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the reoffending rate is of ex-offenders who were granted release on temporary licence to undertake (a) voluntary work, (b) paid work or (c) an educational course.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16427","16427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428435","2015-11-18","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what revenue accrued through deductions and levies on the earnings of prisoners in each year since 2011.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16428","16428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428436","2015-11-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether she has had discussions with the Chancellor of the Exchequer on the effect of tax credits on farmers.","Biography information for Nick Smith","Nick Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16317","16317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428437","2015-11-18","Department for International Development","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the cost effectiveness of (a) cataract surgery, (b) correction of refractive error, (c) interventions against trachoma and (d) other public health interventions.","Biography information for Mr Nick Hurd","Mr Nick Hurd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16415","16415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428438","2015-11-18","Department for International Development","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assumptions her Department has made on (a) global levels of avoidable blindness and low vision and (b) projected levels of those problems in 2020 in planning its work.","Biography information for Mr Nick Hurd","Mr Nick Hurd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16414","16414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428439","2015-11-18","Department for International Development","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the cost effectiveness of her Department's programmes to help reduce the incidence of avoidable blindness and low vision.","Biography information for Mr Nick Hurd","Mr Nick Hurd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16413","16413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428440","2015-11-18","Department for International Development","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department has taken to help reduce the incidence of avoidable blindness and low vision since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Nick Hurd","Mr Nick Hurd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16412","16412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428441","2015-11-18","Department for International Development","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what information her Department holds on the global cost of lost economic activity due to blindness and low vision.","Biography information for Mr Nick Hurd","Mr Nick Hurd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16409","16409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428442","2015-11-18","Department for International Development","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assistance her Department is providing to countries which have not yet developed a national eye care plan.","Biography information for Mr Nick Hurd","Mr Nick Hurd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16410","16410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428443","2015-11-19","Department of Health","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what support his Department is providing to the Care Quality Commission for improving the quality of food in care and nursing homes.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16322","16322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428444","2015-11-19","Department of Health","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to reduce poor nutrition among elderly people (a) in general and (b) in nursing and care homes.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16323","16323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428445","2015-11-19","Department of Health","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking in response to the finding of research by P. Zainotto et al, forecasting obesity to 2010, published in 2006, that around 97 per cent of obese children come from families where at least one parent is obese or overweight.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16325","16325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428446","2015-11-19","Department of Health","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he plans to take to improve understanding of palliative and end-of-life care in nursing and care homes.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16387","16387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428447","2015-11-19","Department of Health","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of (a) the prevalence of child obesity and (b) whether there is a correlation between child obesity and deprivation; and what steps his Department is taking to address that issue.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16386","16386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428448","2015-11-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of people who have died within a week of being notified of a benefit sanction in the last 12 months; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16354","16354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428449","2015-11-18","Department of Health","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department has taken to enable people with limited English to access healthcare services.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16453","16453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428450","2015-11-18","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department has taken to give refugees settled in the UK opportunities to improve their English language skills.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16369","16369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428451","2015-11-18","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the effect on community cohesion of the withdrawal of ESOL Plus Mandation funding.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16456","16456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428452","2015-11-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the contribution of the Minister of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Office, the hon. Member for East Devon, of 22 October 2015, Official Report, column 1264, what training was provided to the election observers supported by Government funding referred to in that contribution.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16332","16332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428453","2015-11-18","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the effect of the withdrawal of ESOL Plus Mandation funding on attainment levels of children whose parents participated in or were eligible for ESOL courses.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16458","16458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428454","2015-11-18","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department has taken to ensure that the skills of ESOL tutors are not lost following the withdrawal of ESOL Plus Mandation funding.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16459","16459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428455","2015-11-18","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent representations he has received on the Action for ESOL Manifestos.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16460","16460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428456","2015-11-18","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assistance his Department is providing to help businesses to employ migrants with in-demand skills but poor English language skills.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16462","16462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428457","2015-11-18","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assistance his Department provides to local authorities and housing associations for English language courses following the withdrawal of ESOL Plus Mandation funding.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16457","16457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428458","2015-11-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment his Department has made on the effect of the withdrawal of ESOL plus mandation funding ESOL on employment prospects for refugees.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16454","16454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428459","2015-11-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department has taken to ensure that claimants with limited English are referred to a structured programme to improve their English skills.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16455","16455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428460","2015-11-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the withdrawal of ESOL funding on levels of poverty.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16461","16461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428461","2015-11-19","Home Office","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many Syrian refugees have been admitted to the UK since September 2015 in each region; and how many she plans to admit by the end of 2016.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16513","16513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428462","2015-11-19","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of changes to his Department's policies on (a) the provision of secure colleges, (b) prohibiting prisoners from receiving books, (c) the sale of HM Courts and Tribunal Service, (d) Saudi prison contracts and (e) the timetable for the tender for criminal defence work.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16336","16336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428463","2015-11-18","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much each (a) county council, (b) Metropolitan district, (c) London borough and (d) unitary authority (i) spent on (A) education and (B) all services in 2009-10 and (ii) budgeted to spend on both such categories of services in 2015-16.","Biography information for Jo Cox","Jo Cox","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16416","16416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428464","2015-11-18","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much each (a) county council, (b) Metropolitan district, (c) London borough and (d) unitary authority (i) spent on social services in 2009-10 and (ii) budgeted to spend on such services in 2015-16.","Biography information for Jo Cox","Jo Cox","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16417","16417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428465","2015-11-19","Church Commissioners","2015-11-16","To ask the right hon. Member for Meriden, representing the Church Commissioners, for what reason the Church Commissioners have not released land for the construction of a primary school, in accordance with previous legal undertakings, at the Paston Reserve urban extension in Peterborough; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stewart Jackson","Mr Stewart Jackson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16388","16388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428466","2015-11-19","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will encourage the International Organisation of Securities Commissions to bring global listing rules in line with those set out in the European Non-Financial Reporting Directive.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16506","16506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428467","2015-11-19","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what progress he has made in transposing the European Non-Financial Reporting Directive into UK law; and whether there will be additional reporting requirements.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16505","16505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428468","2015-11-18","Cabinet Office","2015-11-16","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will include a commitment to extend the Open Contracting Principles to cover climate and development finance in the third National Action Plan.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16493","16493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428469","2015-11-19","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what discussions she has had with ministerial colleagues on a cross-departmental approach to moving to low carbon energy sources.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16467","16467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428470","2015-11-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 22 June 2015 to Question HL381, what steps he has taken following allegations of breaches of bribery and corruption laws by Soco International in Virunga National Park; what guidance his Department provides on the exploration of natural resources by UK listed companies operating in national parks and UNESCO wold heritage sites; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16492","16492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428471","2015-11-19","Department for International Development","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is taking to ensure UK support for energy in developing countries is directed towards low carbon technologies.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16508","16508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428472","2015-11-19","Home Office","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to paragraph 8.1 of Transparency in Supply Chains etc: A practical guide, published by her Department on 29 October 2015, if she will provide a central database of slavery and human trafficking statements published by each organisation.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16507","16507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428473","2015-11-18","Department of Health","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of fixing recoverable costs in medical negligence cases to a maximum of 250,000 on a claimant's ability to pursue a case.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16421","16421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428474","2015-11-18","Department of Health","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of fixing recoverable costs in medical negligence cases to a maximum of 250,000 on the accountability of the NHS to the public.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16422","16422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428475","2015-11-18","Department of Health","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of medical negligence cases which may be affected by the Government's proposals to introduce fixed recoverable costs in cases worth up to (a) 10,000, (b) 25,000, (c) 50,000, (d) 100,000 and (e) 250,000; and what the average saving he hopes to secure at each level is.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16420","16420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428476","2015-11-18","Department of Health","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether reducing incidents of negligent care will be the primary focus of the Government's proposed package of reforms aimed at reducing costs in medical negligence litigation.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16435","16435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428477","2015-11-18","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will review compensation payments to armed forces veterans who served prior to 1987 and have contracted mesothelioma as a result of being exposed to asbestos while under military orders.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16351","16351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428478","2015-11-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent steps the Government has taken to advance peace talks in Israel and the Palestinian territories.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16491","16491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428479","2015-11-18","Department of Health","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will promote the development of a pharmacist-led common ailments service to reduce winter pressures on A&E departments and GP practices.","Biography information for Alex Chalk","Alex Chalk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16349","16349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428480","2015-11-19","Home Office","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the number of Palestinians is who have applied for visit visas for the UK in each month since November 2013; and how many such applications were successful for each of those months.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16338","16338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428481","2015-11-18","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether her Department has considered the potential contribution that sustainable fuels can make to supporting the decarbonisation of the UK economy.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16319","16319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428482","2015-11-18","HM Treasury","2015-11-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent progress there has been in holding to account directors responsible for promoting, managing and supervising Connaught Asset Management.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16380","16380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428483","2015-11-18","HM Treasury","2015-11-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of steps taken to hold to account companies and directors responsible for promoting and managing the affairs of Connaught Asset Management.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16382","16382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428484","2015-11-18","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what legislative provision exists to ensure that directors responsible for misconduct can be appropriately dealt with.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16381","16381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428485","2015-11-18","Home Office","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what regulations on prior knowledge of English apply to applicants for Tier 4 visas where the student's principal purpose in entering the UK is to study English as a foreign language.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16379","16379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428486","2015-11-19","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what plans he has to revise the agreement reached with the National Housing Federation on right to buy to remove references to almshouses in the table of discretionary sales.","Biography information for Will Quince","Will Quince","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16364","16364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428487","2015-11-19","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what plans he has to revise the agreement reached with the National Housing Federation on right to buy to expressly state that almshouse licensees will not have the right to buy.","Biography information for Will Quince","Will Quince","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16363","16363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428488","2015-11-18","Department for Transport","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effects on traffic flow and congestion of the omission of the planned Junction 7 from the M61; and what representations his Department has received on how to mitigate those effects.","Biography information for Chris Green","Chris Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16383","16383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428489","2015-11-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what progress she has made on meeting the recovery target for construction and demolition waste in the Waste Framework Directive, 2008/98/EC; and what further steps she is taking to meet that target.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16365","16365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428490","2015-11-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate she has made of the number of animals exported to (a) EU member states and (b) countries outside the EU in the last year.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16514","16514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428491","2015-11-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many dog attacks have been recorded in the last two years.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16488","16488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428492","2015-11-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many prosecutions there have been for owning a dog banned under the Dangerous Dogs Act 1991 in each of the last two years.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16503","16503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428493","2015-11-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of child maintenance cases in the 1993 and 2003 legacy schemes which were in receipt of regular ongoing maintenance being paid to the non-resident or receiving parent and which were subject to forced closure did not migrate to the 2012 Child Maintenance Scheme.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16443","16443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428494","2015-11-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many child maintenance cases used Family Based Arrangements since 2010; and what proportion in each scheme has (a) resulted in regular maintenance and (b) broken down, resulting in the use of the collection service, in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16444","16444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428495","2015-11-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many complaints  relating to the implementation of charging for the 2012 statutory maintenance scheme have been received by (a) the Child Maintenance Service and (b) Child Maintenance Options.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16446","16446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428496","2015-11-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of child maintenance cases resulted in complaints in the (a) 2012 Child Maintenance Scheme, (b) 1993 legacy scheme and (c) 2003 legacy scheme; and what proportion of complaints were upheld in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16445","16445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428497","2015-11-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of child maintenance cases transitioned from the legacy child maintenance schemes to collection and payment under the 2012 scheme in (a) Northern Ireland and (b) the rest of the UK.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16440","16440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428498","2015-11-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the value was of child maintenance payments made to receiving parents under each scheme and each type of payment arrangement in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16441","16441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428499","2015-11-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much the Child Maintenance Service has collected in charges since their introduction.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16442","16442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428500","2015-11-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the total cost to the public purse was of repayments made following the Manual Process 217 computer errors in child maintenance collection.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16377","16377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428502","2015-11-18","Department for International Development","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much her Department has spent on election observation (a) in real terms and (b) as a proportion of her Department's budget since 2010.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16449","16449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428503","2015-11-18","Department for Education","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of looked-after children have received at least five GCSEs at grades A*-C in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16362","16362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428504","2015-11-18","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what proportion of in-home displays need to remain in operation after installation for the smart metering implementation programme to have the potential to deliver overall economic benefit for customers and energy providers.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16346","16346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428505","2015-11-18","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the effect of the proposed merger of O2 and Three on the competitive functioning of the mobile telecommunications industry.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16450","16450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428506","2015-11-18","HM Treasury","2015-11-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to deliver a faster payments infrastructure.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16451","16451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428507","2015-11-18","HM Treasury","2015-11-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of the availability of bank accounts for (a) crowd funding and (b) digital currency businesses.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16372","16372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428508","2015-11-19","Department for Education","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the benefits of teaching first aid in schools on public health outcomes.","Biography information for Anne-Marie Trevelyan","Mrs Anne-Marie Trevelyan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16471","16471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428509","2015-11-19","Department of Health","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the role of first aid in (a) public health prevention strategies, (b) reducing the number of deaths, injuries and disabilities and (c) reducing pressures on A&E and other emergency services.","Biography information for Anne-Marie Trevelyan","Mrs Anne-Marie Trevelyan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16470","16470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428510","2015-11-18","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, in what ways the UK's military mission in Afghanistan is contributing to the protection of civilian Hazaras.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16333","16333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428511","2015-11-18","HM Treasury","2015-11-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will estimate the number of people who are earning below the lower earnings limit and have more than one employer and do not qualify for national insurance contribution deductions.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16334","16334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428512","2015-11-18","Department of Health","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what level of funding his Department has provided for mental health services in (a) Liverpool, Walton constituency, (b) Merseyside and (c) England in the last three years.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16368","16368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428513","2015-11-18","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when the NATO Members User Group for MQ-9 Reaper drones last met; and whether he attended that meeting.","Biography information for Martin Docherty-Hughes","Martin John Docherty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16342","16342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428514","2015-11-18","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent health and safety checks for civilian personnel have been carried out at Faslane Naval Base.","Biography information for Martin Docherty-Hughes","Martin John Docherty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16343","16343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428515","2015-11-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department is taking to improve the retention of students who have the potential to succeed in higher education but face financial difficulties.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16490","16490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428516","2015-11-18","Home Office","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of women detained in Yarl's Wood Immigration Removal Centre in the last year have (a) attempted to or (b) inflicted harm upon themselves.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16438","16438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428517","2015-11-18","Home Office","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what information she holds on the likely publication date for the independent review of Yarl's Wood, commissioned by Serco.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16500","16500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428518","2015-11-18","Home Office","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many hon. Members have had a request to visit Yarl's Wood Immigration Removal Centre refused in the last 12 months; and on what grounds each such refusal was justified.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16436","16436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428519","2015-11-18","Home Office","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of the officers employed at Yarl's Wood Immigration Removal Centre are male.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16437","16437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428520","2015-11-19","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to Fulfilling our Potential: Teaching Excellence, Social Mobility and Student Choice, CM 9141, what steps he is taking to implement the commitment to double the proportion of students from disadvantaged backgrounds entering higher education by 2020.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16487","16487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428521","2015-11-19","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of (a) long-term skills and employment needs of the digital economy, (b) the role apprenticeships could play in meeting those needs and (c) the role alternative forms of professional training and vocational education could play in meeting those needs; and whether he plans for alternative forms of digital skills development to be supported by the Apprenticeship Levy.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16350","16350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428522","2015-11-19","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will take steps to encourage (a) the training of school children in digital skills before they enter the workforce, (b) graduate schemes on digital skills, (c) improving the digital skills of the workforce of firms in the digital technology industry and (d) other initiatives to promote existing professional training and digital skills initiatives; and whether he plans for such initiatives to be supported by the Apprenticeship Levy.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16367","16367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428523","2015-11-19","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what plans he has for the future of the Student Opportunity Fund.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16384","16384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428524","2015-11-19","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate his Department has made of how many people were recorded as homeless in each county region in the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16483","16483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428525","2015-11-18","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what review his Department has conducted of homelessness in the West Midlands; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16424","16424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428526","2015-11-18","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 16 November 2015 to Question 15658, what the total cost of military operations against ISIS has been in each of the last two years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16495","16495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428527","2015-11-18","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 16 November 2015 to Question 15604, what information her Department holds on the (a) number of petroleum exploration and development licences which have been (i) applied for and (ii) issued in the last 12 months and (b) the location to which such applications and licences apply.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16496","16496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428528","2015-11-19","Department of Health","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) complaints and (b) investigations into complaints made by civil servants against special advisers in his Department there have been in each of the last five years; and how many such (i) complaints and (ii) investigations are outstanding.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16482","16482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428529","2015-11-19","Home Office","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what information her Department holds on the number of (a) arrests for and (b) successful prosecutions of individuals charged with counter-terrorism offences in (i) Coventry and (ii) the West Midlands in each of the last five years; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16480","16480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428530","2015-11-19","Home Office","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) complaints and (b) investigations into complaints made by civil servants against special advisers in her Department there have been in each of the last five years; and how many such (i) complaints and (ii) investigations are outstanding.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16481","16481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428531","2015-11-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 16 November 2015 to Question 15934, what estimate his Department has made of the number of people in receipt of carer's credit in each of the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16494","16494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428532","2015-11-18","Cabinet Office","2015-11-16","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 17 June 2015 to Question 2354, when the review of the enforcement response to bribery and corruption will be published.","Biography information for Lord Davies of Gower","Byron Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16502","16502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428533","2015-11-18","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, when he expects there to be universal access to superfast fibreoptic broadband in Easington constituency.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16401","16401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428534","2015-11-18","HM Treasury","2015-11-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to encourage the growth of stakeholder banks within the UK.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16406","16406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428535","2015-11-18","HM Treasury","2015-11-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the role of stakeholder banks in supporting regional growth.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16407","16407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428536","2015-11-18","Department of Health","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many doctors have requested a certificate of current professional status in 2015.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16405","16405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428537","2015-11-18","Department of Health","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to implement the Infertility Network UK recommendations on access to IVF treatment.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16402","16402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428538","2015-11-18","Department of Health","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many clinical commissioning groups implement in full the Infertility Network UK recommendations on access to IVF treatment.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16403","16403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428539","2015-11-18","Department of Health","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had about a national job profile for Hazardous Area Response Team paramedics.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16404","16404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428540","2015-11-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to the Government of Saudi Arabia on the ending the restrictions on imports of fuel, food and medical supplies to Yemen.","Biography information for Stephen Phillips","Stephen Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16501","16501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428541","2015-11-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to support the establishment of an independent international body to investigate violations of international law in Yemen.","Biography information for Stephen Phillips","Stephen Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16439","16439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428542","2015-11-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to the Colombian government about the FARC prisoners on hunger strike.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16472","16472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428670","2015-11-19","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment she has made of the prospects of a long-term global carbon reduction goal being agreed at the Paris Climate Conference in December 2015.","Biography information for Wendy Morton","Wendy Morton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 902237","902237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428719","2015-11-19","Department for Transport","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect of the proposed expansion of Heathrow Airport on (a) London's air quality and (b) greenhouse gas emission levels.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 902222","902222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429290","2015-11-19","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps she is taking to ensure that smart meters provide the maximum possible benefits for consumers.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 902220","902220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427996","2015-11-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to raise awareness of the right to statutory paternity leave.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16113","16113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427997","2015-11-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, (a) how many and (b) what proportion of the total number of Employment Support Fund claimants were claimants with dyslexia in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16126","16126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427998","2015-11-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to improve the provision of education for and support offered to dyslexic students in higher education outwith the provision of disabled students' allowances.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16127","16127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427999","2015-11-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the number of dyslexic students who will receive disabled students' allowances in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16128","16128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428000","2015-11-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what data his Department holds on the (a) employment rate and (b) income of graduates with dyslexia in comparison with people with dyslexia who did not attend university.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16129","16129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428001","2015-11-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, (a) how many and (b) what proportion of recipients of disabled students' allowances had dyslexia in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16130","16130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428002","2015-11-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of changes to disabled students' allowances on students with dyslexia.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16131","16131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428003","2015-11-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to promote joint work between special needs assessors and disability advisers within universities on ensuring that appropriate support is given and provision made for disabled students and for students with dyslexia.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16133","16133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428004","2015-11-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to ensure that higher education institutions make appropriate provision for disabled students who do not have complex needs.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16134","16134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428005","2015-11-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, (a) how many and (b) what proportion of apprentices who failed to complete their training in the last five years were apprentices with dyslexia.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16135","16135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428006","2015-11-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment his Department has made of the appropriateness of the level of apprenticeship levy funding for (a) SMEs in general and (b) creative industry SMEs.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16140","16140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428007","2015-11-17","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what plans his Department has to assist and promote the UK video games industry in areas outside London.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16141","16141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428008","2015-11-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, for what reasons the matters within his Department's responsibility in Schedule 1 of the draft Wales Bill have been designated as reserved.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16143","16143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428009","2015-11-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what data his Department collects on the (a) number of apprenticeship providers which provide support to apprentices who have been assessed as dyslexic and (b) quality of that support.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16121","16121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428010","2015-11-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many apprentices who have dyslexia have received support from the Access to Work fund in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16122","16122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428011","2015-11-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what guidance his Department gives to apprenticeship providers on supporting apprentices with dyslexia.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16123","16123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428012","2015-11-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to ensure that people with dyslexia obtain functional skills qualifications.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16124","16124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428013","2015-11-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what data his Department collects on the number of apprentices who have dyslexia.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16125","16125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428014","2015-11-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many times he has (a) met and (b) corresponded with a minister of the Welsh Government on the draft Wales Bill in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16148","16148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428015","2015-11-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, by what process his Department identified the areas of policy within its responsibility proposed for reservation in Annex B of the publication Powers for a Purpose: Towards a lasting devolution settlement for Wales, published on 27 February 2015.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16152","16152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428016","2015-11-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many members of the new Construction Leadership Council have been confirmed in their positions; what the roles of those members are; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Oliver Colvile","Oliver Colvile","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16166","16166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428017","2015-11-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, who drafted the terms of reference for the new Construction Leadership Council; how those terms of reference were decided on; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Oliver Colvile","Oliver Colvile","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16167","16167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428018","2015-11-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether the new Construction Leadership Council will assume the responsibilities previously held by the Chief Construction Adviser from November 2015; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Oliver Colvile","Oliver Colvile","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16168","16168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428019","2015-11-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether the terms of reference for the new Construction Leadership Council have been published; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Oliver Colvile","Oliver Colvile","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16169","16169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428020","2015-11-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment he has made of the effect on jobseekers of the requirement to search and apply for jobs within a 90-minute travel radius.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16195","16195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428021","2015-11-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will exempt companies which show a serious and sustained commitment to measurable and successful training from additional application and reporting requirements under the apprenticeship grant scheme.","Biography information for Kwasi  Kwarteng","Kwasi Kwarteng","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16170","16170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428022","2015-11-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much central funding has been provided to further education establishments in (a) London, (b) the London Borough of Lewisham, (c) the London Borough of Southwark and (d) the London Borough of Bromley in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Dowd","Jim Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16214","16214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428023","2015-11-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many students have enrolled on English language courses at further education establishments in (a) London, (b) the London Borough of Lewisham, (c) the London Borough of Southwark and (d) the London Borough of Bromley in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Dowd","Jim Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16215","16215"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428024","2015-11-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many students have enrolled at further education establishments in (a) London, (b) the London Borough of Lewisham, (c) the London Borough of Southwark and (d) the London Borough of Bromley in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Dowd","Jim Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16216","16216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428025","2015-11-18","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much funding his Department will make available to support the retraining of workers recently made redundant by Cleveland Potash.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16315","16315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428026","2015-11-18","HM Treasury","2015-11-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many (a) employees and (b) companies have participated in the shares for rights scheme under section 31 of the Growth and Infrastructure Act 2013.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16316","16316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428027","2015-11-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if his Department will fund the NextGen Skills Academy higher apprenticeships in order better to support games employers.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16302","16302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428028","2015-11-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what guidance his Department gives to local authorities on the statutory minimum level for a local authority trading standards service.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16306","16306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428029","2015-11-17","Cabinet Office","2015-11-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether his Department was consulted by HM Treasury before the Government announced its intention to exclude subsidised renewable energy generation by community energy organisations from eligibility for social investment tax relief.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16118","16118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428030","2015-11-17","Cabinet Office","2015-11-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what progress the Government has made on developing a right to mutualise within the public sector; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16119","16119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428031","2015-11-17","Cabinet Office","2015-11-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what plans the Government has for the funding of the Commissioning Academy over the next five years.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16120","16120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428032","2015-11-18","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the effect of changes to business rate relief on the charity sector.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16162","16162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428033","2015-11-18","Cabinet Office","2015-11-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment he has made of the effect of raising the minimum wage on the capacity of charities to deliver public services.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16163","16163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428034","2015-11-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will ensure that any agreement on a central registry of beneficial ownership in Montserrat includes access for the public with legitimate reason.","Biography information for Dame Margaret Hodge","Margaret Hodge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16077","16077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428035","2015-11-18","HM Treasury","2015-11-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps the Government is taking to ensure parents using employer childcare voucher schemes are informed of the planned introduction of the tax free childcare scheme.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16158","16158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428036","2015-11-17","HM Treasury","2015-11-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with representatives from the Icelandic government on debt owed to (a) UK taxpayers and (b) the public purse by Icelandic banks.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16100","16100"
