"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11883","2013-07-08","Ministry of Justice","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many individuals held in young offenders institutions have been convicted of further crimes for their behaviour since entering the establishment in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Stephen Gilbert","Stephen Gilbert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163767","163767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11884","2013-07-08","Ministry of Justice","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people currently held in the secure children's estate are of no fixed abode.","Biography information for Stephen Gilbert","Stephen Gilbert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163768","163768"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11885","2013-07-08","Ministry of Justice","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people currently held in a secure training centre have been convicted of further crimes for their behaviour since entering the establishment in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Stephen Gilbert","Stephen Gilbert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163769","163769"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11910","2013-07-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people between 16 and 25 years old in (a) Sheffield and (b) each Sheffield parliamentary constituency have been claiming jobseeker's allowance for two years or more in each month since May 2010.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163954","163954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11911","2013-07-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in (a) Sheffield and (b) each Sheffield parliamentary constituency have been unemployed for two years or more in each month since May 2010.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164009","164009"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/13364","2013-07-09","Home Office","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will bring forward legislative proposals to make over-the-counter retail sales of cannabis seed illegal; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Roger Gale","Sir Roger Gale","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163719","163719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/138","2013-07-05","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, which bodies are responsible for carrying out the work previously done by regional resilience forums.","Biography information for Lord Beith","Sir Alan Beith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163745","163745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/141","2013-07-05","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, in which industries increased trade and investment with China in 2013 is being sought.","Biography information for Mr Frank Roy","Mr Frank Roy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163864","163864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/24","2013-07-05","Department of Health","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what safety assessment he has made of recent research by Professor Seralini at the University of Caen on the toxic effect of the consumption of Monsanto's Roundup-resistant NK103 maize on animal and human health.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163735","163735"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/413","2013-07-09","Deputy Prime Minister","2013-07-03","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what recent discussions he has had with his ministerial colleagues on improving social mobility.","Biography information for Andrea Leadsom","Andrea Leadsom","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163802","163802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5432","2013-07-05","Ministry of Justice","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department has taken to ensure that client choice in relation to legal aid is still available.","Biography information for Mr Mike Hancock","Mr Mike Hancock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163730","163730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5433","2013-07-05","Ministry of Justice","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the potential effect that residency tests for civil legal aid will have on (a) victims of human trafficking, (b) victims of domestic violence and (c) babies under 12 months old.","Biography information for Mr Mike Hancock","Mr Mike Hancock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163731","163731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5590","2013-07-05","Department of Health","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the indicators set out in the Quality and Outcomes Framework in providing incentives to GPs to tackle obesity; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163722","163722"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5591","2013-07-05","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he has taken to ensure that the UK is in future classed as an Innovation Leader, as opposed to an Innovation Follower in the European Commission Innovation Union Scoreboard; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163723","163723"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5592","2013-07-05","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will make it his policy to raise public spending on research and development to 0.7 per cent of GDP, in line with the current EU average, by 2020; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163724","163724"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5593","2013-07-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what estimate he has made of the number of nuclear warheads possessed by Israel; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163762","163762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5594","2013-07-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what estimate he has made of the number of (a) British citizens and (b) people categorised for purposes of evacuation as entitled persons living in Israel.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163763","163763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5595","2013-07-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many officials in his Department are engaged in the promotion of measures to reduce noise; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164036","164036"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5596","2013-07-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what progress has been made on issuing a Protected Geographical Indication for the Colchester Oyster; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164037","164037"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5597","2013-07-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he has taken to promote the Noise Strategy since May 2007; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164038","164038"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5659","2013-07-05","Wales Office","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills on the proposal of the Farmers' Union of Wales that a total ban on the sale of Chinese lanterns be introduced.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163839","163839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5660","2013-07-08","Wales Office","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how many people have taken up jobs as a result of the Jobs Summit held in Newport in February 2013.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164108","164108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5661","2013-07-08","Wales Office","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what analysis his Department has made of which services are available through the medium of Welsh on www.gov.uk/Cymraeg; and what discussions he has with ministerial colleagues on those services on that website not currently provided in Welsh.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164094","164094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5662","2013-07-08","Wales Office","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what advice the Wales Office Big Society Advisory Forum has given to his Department to date.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164095","164095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5663","2013-07-08","Ministry of Justice","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he plans to make it possible to pay fines on the Government website www.gov.uk/Cymraeg through the medium of Welsh.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164096","164096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58","2013-07-05","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many (a) single-pensioner households in York and (b) two-pensioner households in York have received Warm Front assistance in each year since the inception of that scheme; and what the average spend was on each of those households.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163874","163874"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5898","2013-07-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, for how many years the provision of a six day universal service after any privatisation of Royal Mail will continue; and if he will bring forward legislative proposals to guarantee future universal service provision.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163721","163721"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5899","2013-07-15","Home Office","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people are currently on the sex offenders register; and what estimate she has made of the number of sex offenders in the UK who are not subject to the sex offenders register because their convictions took place prior to the implementation of the Sex Offenders Act 1997.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163733","163733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/59","2013-07-05","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate the UK Statistics Authority has made of the number of young people aged 16 to 24 in York in (a) training, (b) employment and (c) education in each year since 1995-96.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163899","163899"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5900","2013-07-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much the Chief Executive of Royal Mail was paid in 2012-13; and what percentage change in his salary there was between (a) 2011-12 and (b) 2012-13.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163856","163856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5901","2013-07-15","Department of Health","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he has taken steps to implement recommendation 6 of the Murrison Report, A Better Deal for Military Amputees, calling for the National Institute for Health and Care Excellence to be tasked with the production of national guidelines for prosthetic prescription and rehabilitation for all amputees including provision for military amputees.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163857","163857"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5902","2013-07-15","Department of Health","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of recommendation 3 of the Murrison Report, A Better Deal for Military Amputees, published 2011; and if he will adopt this recommendation as his policy.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164035","164035"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60","2013-07-05","Department for Transport","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much his Department has spent on concessionary bus travel for pensioners (a) in England and (b) in the City of York in each year since 2004-05.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163881","163881"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6059","2013-07-08","Northern Ireland Office","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what assessment she has made of the findings of the report by HM Inspectorate of Constabulary on the Historical Enquiries Team; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164100","164100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6060","2013-07-08","Northern Ireland Office","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what discussions she has had with the Chief Constable of the Police Service of Northern Ireland regarding the report by HM Inspectorate of Constabulary on the Historical Enquiries Team.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164101","164101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/61","2013-07-05","Cabinet Office","2013-07-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many businesses there were in (a) York Central constituency and (b) City of York local authority area in each year since 1995-96.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163895","163895"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6186","2013-07-05","Ministry of Defence","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many serving members of the (a) Royal Air Force, (b) Royal Navy and (c) Army have asked for voluntary early release, at each base located in Wales; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163828","163828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6187","2013-07-05","Ministry of Defence","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the cost of relocating 71 (IR) Squadron to RAF Wittering; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163829","163829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6188","2013-07-05","Ministry of Defence","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent discussions he has had with the Welsh Government on negotiating a reduction in rent at RAF St. Athan for 71 (IR) Squadron; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163830","163830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6189","2013-07-05","Ministry of Defence","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) civilians and (b) serving military personnel are employed by the (i) Royal Air Force, (ii) Royal Navy and (iii) Army in Wales; where they are located; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163831","163831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6190","2013-07-05","Ministry of Defence","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the effect of the proposed relocation of 71 (IR) Squadron from RAF St. Athan to RAF Wittering on his Department's footprint in Wales; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163833","163833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6211","2013-07-05","Department of Health","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions he has had with Organización Nacional de Trasplantes regarding organ donation rates in Spain.","Biography information for Glyn Davies","Glyn Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163734","163734"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6212","2013-07-05","Department of Health","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what (a) assessment he has made and (b) reports he has received on the effect of dedicated transplant co-ordinators situated in hospitals on the rate of organ donation.","Biography information for Glyn Davies","Glyn Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163738","163738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6213","2013-07-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what progress the Chalara Control Plan has made on (a) reducing the rate of spread and (b) developing resistance to the disease in the native UK ash tree population; and what management guidance his Department has offered to land owners with trees showing signs of the fungus.","Biography information for Glyn Davies","Glyn Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163739","163739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6214","2013-07-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what guidance his Department issues to farmers relating to the prophylactic use of antibiotics in (a) poultry farming and (b) all other types of farming.","Biography information for Glyn Davies","Glyn Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163740","163740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6215","2013-07-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on forests of the spread of phytophthora ramorum in the larch tree population; what steps he is taking to prevent the spread of phytophthora ramorum; and what recent discussions he has had with his counterpart in the Welsh Government on this issue.","Biography information for Glyn Davies","Glyn Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163741","163741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6216","2013-07-05","Department of Health","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that the intensive care units exist to (a) receive, (b) maintain and (c) make full use of all organs donated by organ donors.","Biography information for Glyn Davies","Glyn Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163742","163742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6217","2013-07-05","Department of Health","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what change there has been in organ donation rates in England since the Organ Donation Taskforce reported.","Biography information for Glyn Davies","Glyn Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163743","163743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6218","2013-07-05","Department of Health","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what (a) assessment he has made and (b) reports he has received on whether a change to a presumed consent system of organ donation will increase levels of donation.","Biography information for Glyn Davies","Glyn Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163744","163744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6219","2013-07-05","Department of Health","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average age of an organ donor was in each year from 2000.","Biography information for Glyn Davies","Glyn Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163837","163837"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6288","2013-07-05","Department of Health","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the differences in the availability of (a) intrauterine insemination and (b) in vitro fertilisation across NHS trusts in England.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164070","164070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6289","2013-07-05","Department of Health","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will review the National Institute for Health and Care Excellence recommendations for fertility treatment.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164071","164071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6290","2013-07-05","Department of Health","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that fertility treatment is consistent across the NHS.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164072","164072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6481","2013-07-10","Department for Transport","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with organisations involved in the recent completion of high speed rail projects in (a) France, (b) Germany and (c) Spain.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164031","164031"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6482","2013-07-10","Department for Transport","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what methodology was used to estimate the cost of the High Speed 2 project; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164032","164032"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6483","2013-07-10","Ministry of Defence","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will estimate the cost of his proposed reforms to the Army reservist system.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164033","164033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6484","2013-07-10","HM Treasury","2013-07-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will estimate the financial effects of proposed European Commission regulations of interchange fees on (a) debit cardholders, (b) credit cardholders and (c) small businesses.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164034","164034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6485","2013-07-05","Department of Health","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will assess the progress and development of the new national urgent lung allocation system for cystic fibrosis patients.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164039","164039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6486","2013-07-05","Department of Health","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what representations he has received on the use of interventional lung assist devices in transplants for cystic fibrosis patients.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164040","164040"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6770","2013-07-05","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much funding his Department allocated for youth work in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12 and (c) 2012-13; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164073","164073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6771","2013-07-05","Cabinet Office","2013-07-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much funding his Department allocated for youth work in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12 and (c) 2012-13; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164074","164074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6772","2013-07-05","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much funding his Department allocated for youth work in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12 and (c) 2012-13; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164075","164075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6773","2013-07-05","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how much funding her Department allocated for youth work in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12 and (c) 2012-13; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164076","164076"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6774","2013-07-05","Department for Education","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much funding his Department allocated for youth work in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12 and (c) 2012-13; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164077","164077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6775","2013-07-05","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how much funding his Department allocated for youth work in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12 and (c) 2012-13; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164078","164078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6776","2013-07-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much funding his Department allocated for youth work in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12 and (c) 2012-13; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164079","164079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6777","2013-07-05","Women and Equalities","2013-07-03","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, how much funding the Government Equalities Office allocated for youth work in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12 and (c) 2012-13; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164080","164080"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6778","2013-07-05","Department of Health","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much funding his Department allocated for youth work in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12 and (c) 2012-13; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164081","164081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6779","2013-07-05","Home Office","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much funding her Department allocated for youth work in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12 and (c) 2012-13; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164082","164082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6780","2013-07-05","Ministry of Justice","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much funding his Department allocated for youth work in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12 and (c) 2012-13; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164083","164083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6781","2013-07-05","Northern Ireland Office","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how much funding her Department allocated for youth work in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12 and (c) 2012-13; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164084","164084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6782","2013-07-05","Scotland Office","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how much funding his Department allocated for youth work in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12 and (c) 2012-13; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164085","164085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6783","2013-07-05","Department for Transport","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much funding his Department allocated for youth work in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12 and (c) 2012-13; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164086","164086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6784","2013-07-05","HM Treasury","2013-07-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much funding his Department allocated for youth work in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12 and (c) 2012-13; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164087","164087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6785","2013-07-05","Wales Office","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how much funding his Department allocated for youth work in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12 and (c) 2012-13; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164088","164088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6786","2013-07-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much funding his Department allocated for youth work in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12 and (c) 2012-13; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164089","164089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6787","2013-07-08","Department of Health","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much non-capital funding he provided in England for hospices in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12 and (c) 2012-13; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164120","164120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6788","2013-07-08","Department of Health","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients (a) in total and (b) in each NHS trust in England waited for more than (i) four, (ii) eight, (iii) 12 and (iv) 16 hours in accident and emergency departments in (A) 2010-11, (B) 2011-12 and (C) 2012-13; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164121","164121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6789","2013-07-08","Department of Health","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients in (a) total and (b) in each NHS trust in London accident and emergency departments waited for more than (i) four, (ii) eight, (iii) 12 and (iv) 16 hours in (A) 2010-11, (B) 2011-12 and (C) 2012-13; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164122","164122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7009","2013-07-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of people in (a) Warrington and (b) Warrington North constituency who are employed on zero hours contracts; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163947","163947"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7010","2013-07-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in Warrington have participated in the Work Programme since its inception; and how many such participants have found (a) part-time and (b) full-time jobs through that programme.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164013","164013"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7096","2013-07-08","HM Treasury","2013-07-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the introduction of ex-ante position limits for agricultural futures and options markets.","Biography information for Dr Alasdair McDonnell","Dr Alasdair McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163850","163850"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7097","2013-07-08","Northern Ireland Office","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what steps she plans to take to ensure that determinations made by the Parades Commission are accepted by all parties and organisations in Northern Ireland and that decisions are supported by the rule of law.","Biography information for Dr Alasdair McDonnell","Dr Alasdair McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164029","164029"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7121","2013-07-08","Home Office","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) nail bars and (b) cannabis factories have been investigated by the police in relation to human trafficking in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Peter Bone","Mr Peter Bone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163772","163772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7122","2013-07-08","Attorney General","2013-07-03","To ask the Attorney General, how many prosecutions there have been for human trafficking in relation to (a) nail bars and (b) cannabis factories in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Peter Bone","Mr Peter Bone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163773","163773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7123","2013-07-08","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the number of nail bar businesses in the UK.","Biography information for Mr Peter Bone","Mr Peter Bone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163774","163774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7210","2013-07-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many Social Fund budgeting loan applications to pay for funeral expenses have been (a) received and (b) awarded; and what the total cost of the awards was in each month since May 2012.","Biography information for Baroness Burt of Solihull","Lorely Burt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163855","163855"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7536","2013-07-08","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if she will publish details of the technical amendments that she has been discussing with the Scottish Government to the Royal Charter to ensure it is operable in Scotland; which of those such amendments are still to be agreed; which of those amendments it is anticipated will not be agreed by the time the Privy Council is due to meet in July 2013; and for what reasons any such amendments will not be agreed by such time.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164019","164019"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7537","2013-07-08","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether she expects to conclude discussions with the Scottish Government on the amendments to the cross-party Royal Charter, which was debated in the House on 18 March 2013, by the time the Privy Council is due to meet in July 2013.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164020","164020"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7538","2013-07-08","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, when she expects to conclude discussions with the Scottish Government on the technical amendments to the cross-party Royal Charter, which was debated in the House on 18 March 2013.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164021","164021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7539","2013-07-08","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, when she plans to answer Question 160538, tabled on 12 June 2013 for answer on 20 June 2013.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164022","164022"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7627","2013-07-08","Department of Health","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment his Department has made of the standard of care reviews conducted on in-patients with learning disabilities and autism.","Biography information for Frank Dobson","Frank Dobson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164090","164090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7628","2013-07-08","Department of Health","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he has taken to ensure the independence of those professionals who conduct care reviews of the in-patients with learning disabilities and autism.","Biography information for Frank Dobson","Frank Dobson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164091","164091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7629","2013-07-08","Department of Health","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of the in-patients with learning disabilities and autism whose care has recently been reviewed have been recommended to (a) move into the community and (b) remain as in-patients.","Biography information for Frank Dobson","Frank Dobson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164092","164092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7630","2013-07-08","Department of Health","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many former patients of Winterbourne View Hospital have been moved to community-based settings within 20 miles of their original family homes.","Biography information for Frank Dobson","Frank Dobson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164093","164093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7647","2013-07-05","Ministry of Defence","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the title Shropshire Yeomanry is to be maintained by the Royal Mercian and Lancastrian Yeomanry following completion of the Reserves in the Future Force 2020 process.","Biography information for David Wright","David Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163989","163989"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7648","2013-07-05","Ministry of Defence","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what change will be made to the capacity and function of the current B Squadron Royal Mercian and Lancastrian Yeomanry base at Dawley Bank in Telford.","Biography information for David Wright","David Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163967","163967"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7649","2013-07-05","Ministry of Defence","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will outline the personnel profile for the Royal Mercian and Lancastrian Yeomanry based at Dawley Bank, Telford (a) before and (b) upon completion of the Reserves in the Future Force 2020 process.","Biography information for David Wright","David Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163990","163990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7731","2013-07-05","Home Office","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) police officers and (b) police community support officers there were in Northamptonshire police force area in (i) 2010, (ii) 2011, (iii) 2012 and (iv) 2013.","Biography information for Andy Sawford","Andy Sawford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163757","163757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/80","2013-07-08","Cabinet Office","2013-07-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, for what reasons he has not yet published the Positive for Youth, One Year On progress report due in December 2012.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163781","163781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8035","2013-07-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to Regulation 12D(5) and (7) of the Housing Benefit Regulations 2006, for what reasons the 13 weeks protection rule is not being replicated under universal credit; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163952","163952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8036","2013-07-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to Regulations 12D(5) and (7) of the Housing Benefit Regulations 2006, what estimate he has made of the number of households affected by the omission from universal credit of the 13 weeks' protection.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164008","164008"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8037","2013-07-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he plans to take to improve job outcomes for employment and support allowance claimants referred to the Work Programme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164111","164111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8038","2013-07-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, which individuals he plans to nominate for membership of the advisory group of the new health and work assessment and advisory service; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164113","164113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/81","2013-07-08","Cabinet Office","2013-07-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what responsibility his Department will retain for the UK Youth Parliament; and what projected grants payments there are from his or any successor department.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163782","163782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/811","2013-07-05","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what the value of sales of National Lottery scratch cards has been in Northern Ireland in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163732","163732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8198","2013-07-08","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what volume of the Energy Company Obligation market has been secured through the brokerage auction to date.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163779","163779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8199","2013-07-08","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the average subsidy is that a household with installations completed has received under the Carbon Emissions Reduction Obligation element of the Energy Company Obligation.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163785","163785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/82","2013-07-08","Cabinet Office","2013-07-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when the Youth Action Group last met; and if he will  publish the minutes.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163783","163783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8200","2013-07-08","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many of the energy companies that are legally obligated to deliver the Energy Company Obligation are not providing (a) Green Deal assessments and (b) Green Deal packages.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163843","163843"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8201","2013-07-08","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, when he plans to publish a revised impact assessment of the Energy Company Obligation.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163786","163786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8202","2013-07-08","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what successor scheme the Government plans to introduce when the Energy Company Obligation ends in March 2015.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163787","163787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/83","2013-07-08","Cabinet Office","2013-07-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what his plans are for the future of the inter-departmental Youth Action Group; and who will chair it.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163784","163784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8333","2013-07-08","Department of Health","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the terms of reference are for the investigation by Dr Bill Kirkup into the University Hospitals of Morecambe Bay NHS Foundation Trust; and when he expects the investigation to commence.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163845","163845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8334","2013-07-08","Department of Health","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when the Kirkup investigation into the involvement of Jimmy Savile at Broadmoor Hospital will report; and who will receive this report.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163770","163770"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8419","2013-07-08","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what progress has been made by the Advance Manufacturing Supply Chain initiative; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Ben Wallace","Mr Ben Wallace","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163949","163949"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8756","2013-07-08","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent meetings he has had with private sector companies to discuss investment and the potential privatisation of Royal Mail.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163950","163950"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8757","2013-07-08","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent meetings he has had with hedge funds and venture capitalist companies on the potential privatisation of Royal Mail.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163951","163951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/926","2013-07-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what safety assessment he has made of the recent findings by the European Food Safety Authority's scientists of a potentially harmful hidden viral gene in 54 of 86 genetically modified crops commercialised to date in the US.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163736","163736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/927","2013-07-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will list all parliamentary constituencies ranked in order of rurality.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163737","163737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/929","2013-07-05","Northern Ireland Office","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how much her Department has spent on hospitality at (a) Hillsborough Castle, (b) Stormont and (c) other venues in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163725","163725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/930","2013-07-05","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to ensure Gypsy and Traveller sites are not placed in (a) rural villages and (b) other inappropriate locations.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163726","163726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/931","2013-07-05","Ministry of Justice","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the averge length of time a member of the publicly-funded criminal bar waits for payment of invoiced funds; and what the longest length of time such a member has had to wait for payment in the last three years.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163727","163727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/932","2013-07-05","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to protect greenbelt land from inappropriate and unsustainable development.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163728","163728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9329","2013-07-08","Department of Health","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average waiting time in accident and emergency was in (a) Barnsley Hospital NHS Foundation Trust area and (b) England in each of the last four (i) quarters and (ii) years.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163960","163960"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/933","2013-07-05","HM Treasury","2013-07-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether his proposals on the new national funding formula for schools will include early years education for those under five years old.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163729","163729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9330","2013-07-08","HM Treasury","2013-07-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many businesses in (a) Barnsley Central constituency, (b) Barnsley, (c) South Yorkshire and (d) England have qualified for the increased levels of small business rate relief since 2010.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163961","163961"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9331","2013-07-08","Department of Health","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average waiting time for an operation in (a) Barnsley Hospital NHS Foundation Trust area and (b) England was in each of the last four (i) quarters and (ii) years.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163962","163962"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9332","2013-07-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many new homes in (a) Barnsley Central constituency, (b) Barnsley and (c) South Yorkshire have qualified for the New Homes Bonus (NHB) to date; how much funding has been given to Barnsley Metropolitan Borough Council under the NHB to date; and what estimate he has made of the number of new houses built in (i) Barnsley Central constituency, (ii) Barnsley and (iii) South Yorkshire as a result of the NHB.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163963","163963"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9333","2013-07-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment his Department made of the potential costs to local councils of changes to permitted developments for householders.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163946","163946"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9334","2013-07-05","Department for Transport","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many new drivers in (a) Barnsley Central constituency, (b) South Yorkshire and (c) England took the Pass Plus training course in each of the last five years; what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of Pass Plus in preventing accidents among new drivers; and what steps his Department is taking to encourage drivers to take Pass Plus after their driving tests.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164057","164057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/934","2013-07-05","Home Office","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, for which classes of young people who are (a) UK citizens and (b) EU nationals resident temporarily in the UK those looking after them are not liable for Disclosure and Barring Service checks; and what the reasons are for any differences in such a policy based upon the nationality of the young people concerned.","Biography information for Lord Blunkett","Mr David Blunkett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163746","163746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/935","2013-07-05","Deputy Prime Minister","2013-07-03","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, how many visits he has made to (a) Scotland, (b) Wales and (c) Northern Ireland in an official capacity in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163747","163747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/936","2013-07-05","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of his Department's communications with small businesses; what discussions he has had with small businesses and small businesses' organisations on the effectiveness of his Department's communications with small businesses; and what steps he plans to take to improve the effectiveness of his Department's communications with small businesses.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163752","163752"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/937","2013-07-05","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what the value of national lottery ticket sales in Northern Ireland has been in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163753","163753"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/938","2013-07-05","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of Royal Mail employees' views on his proposed employee share scheme.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163754","163754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9380","2013-07-05","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the retained duty fire fighting system in the Mid Bedfordshire constituency.","Biography information for Ms Nadine Dorries","Nadine Dorries","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164050","164050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9381","2013-07-05","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to prevent reductions in the pensions of retained system firefighters.","Biography information for Ms Nadine Dorries","Nadine Dorries","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164049","164049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/939","2013-07-05","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what guarantees and safeguards he has put in place to protect the pensions scheme of (a) past workers and (b) present workers at Royal Mail.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163755","163755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/940","2013-07-05","Department for Education","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children in (a) Hampshire and (b) England have been denied access to school meals as a direct result of failure to pay outstanding meal fees in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Steve Brine","Steve Brine","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163756","163756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/941","2013-07-05","Deputy Prime Minister","2013-07-03","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what his assessment is of the last meeting of the British Irish Council.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163758","163758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942","2013-07-05","Northern Ireland Office","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what discussions she has held with the Northern Ireland Executive on the Investment Conference to be held in Northern Ireland in October 2013.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163759","163759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943","2013-07-05","Northern Ireland Office","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, which people have received hospitality from her Department at (a) Hillsborough Castle, (b) Stormont and (c) other venues in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163760","163760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944","2013-07-08","HM Treasury","2013-07-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to Investing in Britain's Future, Cm 8669, published June 2013, how much will be spent on infrastructure development in each region of the UK.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163775","163775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/945","2013-07-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the UK's allocation from the EU CAP budget (a) will be in each of the next five years and (b) was in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163776","163776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/946","2013-07-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what arguments he used to justify an increase in the UK's share of the EU CAP Budget.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163777","163777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/947","2013-07-08","HM Treasury","2013-07-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent discussions he has held with RBS regarding staffing levels in Ulster Bank.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163778","163778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9471","2013-07-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the roll-out of the household benefit cap in Bromley, Croydon, Enfield and Haringey; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sarah Teather","Sarah Teather","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164023","164023"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9472","2013-07-08","Ministry of Justice","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the (a) average and (b) range of time it has taken the Legal Aid Agency to make a decision following an application for exceptional case funding has been since 1 April 2013.","Biography information for Sarah Teather","Sarah Teather","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 164007","164007"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/948","2013-07-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many families have been helped through the Troubled Families programme involving children with (a) truanting problems and (b) mental health problems.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163780","163780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/949","2013-07-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 17 June 2013, Official Report, columns 488-9W, on Occupied Territories, what information his Department holds on how many occasions Israel has provided disaggregated statistics to the OECD for areas Israel occupied since 1967; and on how many occasions the OECD has requested such disaggregated data.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163844","163844"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/950","2013-07-08","Attorney General","2013-07-03","To ask the Attorney General, in what proportion of prosecutions where the Crown Prosecution Service has sought for the defendant to be remanded in prison, has such an application has been refused in (a) Kettering, (b) Northamptonshire and (c) England in the last three years.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163846","163846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9506","2013-07-08","Department of Health","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what representations (a) he and (b) his Department received regarding University Hospitals Morecambe Bay NHS Trust prior to May 2010.","Biography information for David Morris","David Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163959","163959"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/951","2013-07-08","Deputy Prime Minister","2013-07-03","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to prevent disqualified candidates appearing on a ballot paper.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163847","163847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/952","2013-07-08","HM Treasury","2013-07-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent discussions he has held with the Northern Ireland Finance Minister regarding the recently announced job losses at Ulster Bank.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163765","163765"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/953","2013-07-08","HM Treasury","2013-07-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether his Department's ongoing review of Ulster Bank will address the (a) company's redundancy plans and (b) retention of services in rural areas.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163771","163771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/954","2013-07-05","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many local authorities have utilised the general power of competence created by section 1 of the Localism Act 2011 to date; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Graham Allen","Mr Graham Allen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163834","163834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/955","2013-07-05","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the Government's proposed privatisation of Royal Mail on households in rural communities.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163835","163835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/956","2013-07-05","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to Construction 2025 Industrial Strategy: government and industry in partnership, published on 2 July 2013, for what reasons the issue of blacklisting in the construction sector was not included in the strategy; and if he will ensure that this issue is considered in any further discussions between government and industry on the future shape of the construction sector labour market.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163836","163836"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/957","2013-07-05","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many (a) letters and (b) parcels were delivered by Royal Mail in each year for which data is available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163838","163838"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/958","2013-07-05","Home Office","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much the Independent Police Complaints Commission spent on investigating complaints into the actions of each police force in each of the last three years for which figures are available; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163841","163841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/959","2013-07-08","Department of Health","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) colorectal excision, (b) breast excision, (c) hip replacement, (d) knee replacement, (e) inguinal hernia repair, (f) cholecystectomy and (g) open excision of the prostate procedures were carried out in England among people aged 65 and over in (i) 2001-02 and (ii) 2011-12 by (A) primary care trust area of responsibility and (B) current clinical commissioning group area of responsibility.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163848","163848"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/960","2013-07-05","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 2 July 2013, Official Report, column 583W, on post offices: Rhyl, what plans he has to dispose of the Rhyl Crown Post Office building.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163842","163842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/961","2013-07-08","Department of Health","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) colorectal excision, (b) breast excision, (c) hip replacement, (d) knee replacement, (e) inguinal hernia repair, (f) cholecystectomy and (g) open excision of the prostate procedures were carried out in England among people aged 75 and over in (i) 2001-02 and (ii) 2011-12 by (A) primary care trust area of responsibility and (B) current clinical commissioning group area of responsibility.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163849","163849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/962","2013-07-08","HM Treasury","2013-07-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many vending machines in his Department's premises contain snack foods that are high in calories and low in nutritional value.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163851","163851"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/963","2013-07-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many vending machines in his Department's premises contain snack foods that are high in calories and low in nutritional value.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163852","163852"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/964","2013-07-08","Home Office","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many vending machines in her Department's premises contain snack foods that are high in calories and low in nutritional value.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163853","163853"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/965","2013-07-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 17 June 2013, Official Report, columns 488-9W, on Occupied Territories; what assessment he has made of whether the Government's acceptance of Israeli statistics to the OECD, which do not distinguish between Israel and areas occupied since 1967, is compliant with the UK's international law obligations, including the duty of non-recognition.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163854","163854"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/966","2013-07-12","Deputy Prime Minister","2013-07-03","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what recent discussions he has had on Wave 2 City Deals.","Biography information for Guy Opperman","Guy Opperman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163720","163720"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/967","2013-07-05","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what recent discussions he has had with his ministerial colleagues on the effects of the Warm Homes and Energy Conservation Act 2000 on levels of fuel poverty; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163858","163858"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968","2013-07-05","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much funding his Department allocated to City of York Council for (a) local authority supported capital expenditure in housing stock and (b) major repairs allowance in 2009-10 and in each year since then.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163868","163868"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/969","2013-07-05","Department for Education","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what guidance his Department (a) has issued to schools since May 2010 and (b) plans to issue to schools in the next six months on reducing obesity among people under the age of 16; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163859","163859"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/970","2013-07-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many children in Yorkshire and the Humber were living in (a) absolute and (b) relative poverty in each year since 1995-96.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163869","163869"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/971","2013-07-05","Department of Health","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what comparative assessment he has made of levels of obesity in the UK and other comparable countries; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163860","163860"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/972","2013-07-05","Department for Education","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the gross average salary of a full-time teacher in local authority schools in the City of York was in (a) cash and (b) real terms in each year since 1995-96.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163897","163897"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/973","2013-07-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of (a) children, (b) pensioners and (c) households fell below 60 per cent of contemporary median equivalised income (i) before and (ii) after housing costs between (A) 2007-08 to 2009-10, (B) 2008-09 to 2010-11, (C) 2009-10 to 2011-12 and (D)  2010-11 and 2012-13.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163870","163870"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/974","2013-07-05","Department for Education","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of young people aged (a) 16, (b) 17 and (c) 18 years living in (i) York and (ii) Yorkshire and the Humber were in (A) full-time education and (B) full-time education, employment or training in December 2012.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163898","163898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/975","2013-07-05","Department of Health","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what level of capital expenditure his Department provided for York Teaching Hospital NHS Foundation Trust in each year since 1996-97.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163914","163914"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/976","2013-07-05","Home Office","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average cost of Independent Police Complaints Commission investigations is; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163861","163861"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/977","2013-07-05","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how much her Department spent on sport in (a) Yorkshire and the Humber and (b) City of York local authority area in each year since 2004-05.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163871","163871"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/978","2013-07-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much has been spent specifically for the benefit of biodiversity on the public forest estate in each year since 2004-05.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163872","163872"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/979","2013-07-05","Home Office","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many police officers of each (a) rank and (b) police force have been reprimanded as a result of Independent Police Complaints Commission investigations prompted by complaints in each of the last three years for which information is available.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163862","163862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/980","2013-07-05","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what funding was allocated to York College by the Skills Funding Agency and the Young People's Learning Agency in (a) cash and (b) real terms in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163900","163900"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/981","2013-07-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps (a) his Department and (b) UK Trade and Investment are taking to promote UK exports to, and attract inward investment from, China.","Biography information for Mr Frank Roy","Mr Frank Roy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163863","163863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/982","2013-07-05","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much funding per (a) undergraduate and (b) postgraduate student the Higher Education Funding Council for England allocated to (i) the University of York and (ii) York St John University in each year since 1995-96.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163901","163901"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/983","2013-07-05","Department for Education","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much mainstream grant funding was allocated by the Training and Development Agency for Schools to (a) the University of York and (b) York St John University in each year since 1995-96 in (i) cash terms and (ii) at constant prices.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163902","163902"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/984","2013-07-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how additional funding allocated by his Department to work in China is being spent.","Biography information for Mr Frank Roy","Mr Frank Roy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163865","163865"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/985","2013-07-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what programme of events will be taking place between China and the UK in the next 12 months.","Biography information for Mr Frank Roy","Mr Frank Roy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163866","163866"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/986","2013-07-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what proportion of waste collected in City of York was recycled in each year since 2008-09; and what funding his Department provided to City of York Council to increase recycling rates in each of those years.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163873","163873"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/987","2013-07-05","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much capital funding the Government allocated to (a) York College, (b) the University of York and (c) York St John University in each year since 1995-96.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163903","163903"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988","2013-07-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much his Department has spent on flood protection measures in (a) England, (b) Yorkshire and the Humber and (c) the City of York Council area in each year since 1995-96.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163867","163867"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/990","2013-07-05","Cabinet Office","2013-07-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate the UK Statistics Authority has made of the median gross weekly earnings of (a) men, (b) women and (c) all people employed (i) full-time and (ii) part-time in the areas covered by (A) York travel to work area, (B) York Unitary Authority and (C) York Central constituency in each year since 1997 (1) in cash terms and (2) at 2013 prices.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163879","163879"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/991","2013-07-05","Cabinet Office","2013-07-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the average weekly gross earnings of full-time (a) men, (b) women and (c) people in York were in each year since 2006-07 in (i) cash terms and (ii) at constant prices.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163880","163880"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/992","2013-07-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many free NHS sight tests were given to people aged 60 years and over in the North Yorkshire and York Primary Care Trust area in each year since 2004-05; and what estimate he has made of the cost of providing those tests.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163882","163882"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/993","2013-07-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much funding his Department allocated to City of York Council for expenditure on social services for people aged 65 years or over in each year from 2008-09 in (a) cash and (b) real terms.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163883","163883"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/994","2013-07-05","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how much his Department spent on the Warm Front Scheme in York Local Authority Area in each year since the inception of that scheme.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163884","163884"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/995","2013-07-05","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much the Regional Growth Fund has spent in (a) Yorkshire and the Humber and (b) City of York in (i) cash and (ii) real terms in each year since that fund was created.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163885","163885"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9957","2013-07-05","Ministry of Defence","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, to what agency and individual those working at CSO Morwenstow are accountable.","Biography information for Fabian Hamilton","Fabian Hamilton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163748","163748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9958","2013-07-05","Ministry of Defence","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what his plans are for RAF Barford St John over the next (a) 12 months and (b) two years.","Biography information for Fabian Hamilton","Fabian Hamilton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163749","163749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9959","2013-07-05","Ministry of Defence","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) US army, (b) US air force, (c) US navy and US marines, (d) NSA personnel, (e) US contractors, (f) British contractors, (g) British army, (h) British air force, (i) British navy and (j) Ministry of Defence personnel work at CSO Morwenstow.","Biography information for Fabian Hamilton","Fabian Hamilton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163750","163750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/996","2013-07-05","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many businesses were declared bankrupt in (a) York, (b) Yorkshire and the Humber and (c) England in each year since 2008-09.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163886","163886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/997","2013-07-05","Cabinet Office","2013-07-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many full-time equivalent civil servants were employed in the City of York (a) in total and (b) by each government department or agency in each year since 1995-96.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163887","163887"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/998","2013-07-05","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many applications for undergraduate study were made to (a) the University of York, (b) York St John University and (c) all English universities in each year since 2008-09.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163904","163904"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999","2013-07-05","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many young people from York Central constituency (a) applied for and (b) started a degree course in each year since 2008-09.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163905","163905"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10045","2013-07-04","Women and Equalities","2013-07-02","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what consultation has been carried out by her Department with the Equality Commission for Northern Ireland on the provisions of the Marriage (Same Sex Couples) Bill as far as they relate to Northern Ireland; what representations she has received from the Commission on this matter; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163606","163606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10046","2013-07-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what official souvenirs were given to attendees at the conclusion of the G8 Summit at Lough Erne; and what the cost of those souvenirs was.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163607","163607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10047","2013-07-04","Northern Ireland Office","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many staff, of each grade, were employed by her Department in each year since 1998.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163608","163608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10048","2013-07-04","Northern Ireland Office","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what her Department's budget has been in each year since 1998.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163609","163609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10049","2013-07-04","Ministry of Defence","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent research has been carried out by his Department into alternative base sites in the UK for the nuclear deterrent or submarines from HM Naval Base Clyde.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163649","163649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10063","2013-07-09","Home Office","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many closure orders restricting access to premises linked to the exploitation or prostitution of trafficked women have been (a) applied for and (b) obtained from the courts by (i) the Metropolitan Police and (ii) other police forces in the last three years; how many of these have been enforced; what assessment she has made of the amount of statistical data available; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mark Field","Mark Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163626","163626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10376","2013-07-05","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, when the triennial review of the Industry Training Boards for Construction, Engineering Construction and Film Industry Training Boards is expected to be completed.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163708","163708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10393","2013-07-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with the government of Kenya in relation to seeking a resolution over Kenyan public sector pensions.","Biography information for Mary Macleod","Mary Macleod","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163477","163477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10480","2013-07-11","Home Office","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she plans to reply to the letters she has received from the right hon. Member for Tonbridge and Malling dated 14 March, 2 May, 22 May and 26 June 2013 on behalf of his constituent, Mrs Rene Siu-Ling Chung.","Biography information for Sir John Stanley","Sir John Stanley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163686","163686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10587","2013-07-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether his Department owns Rectory Farm adjacent to Wisley Airfield, Surrey; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Paul Beresford","Sir Paul Beresford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163523","163523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10613","2013-07-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many homes containing two or more bedrooms under local authority or housing association control were lying empty in the north of England immediately prior to the introduction of the under-occupancy penalty tax.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame M. Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163603","163603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10614","2013-07-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the number of people required to leave their homes and move into private rented accommodation as a result of the introduction of the under-occupancy penalty in the north of England.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame M. Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163604","163604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10615","2013-07-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many people have been required to leave their homes in the North of England since the introduction of the under occupancy penalty.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame M. Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163599","163599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10630","2013-07-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received on the use of Swedish-made weapons against ethnic minorities in Kachin State, Burma.","Biography information for Mr David Burrowes","Mr David Burrowes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163488","163488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11145","2013-07-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent meetings (a) Ministers and (b) officials of his Department have had with representatives of the shipping industry on the application of European Union directives on (i) collective redundancies and (ii) transfer of undertakings to seafarers.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163415","163415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11146","2013-07-04","Department for Transport","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will take steps to ensure that European Union Directives on (a) collective redundancies and (b) transfer of undertakings are applied to seafarers.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163416","163416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11147","2013-07-04","Department for Transport","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent estimate he has made of the total annual contribution of the container port market to domestic levels of carbon emissions.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163417","163417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11148","2013-07-04","Department for Transport","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will take steps to ensure that European Union directives on (a) protection of employees in the event of employer insolvency, (b) the European Works Council and (c) informing and consulting employees are applied to seafarers.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163418","163418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11149","2013-07-04","Department for Transport","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions (a) Ministers and (b) officials of his Department have had with representatives of the shipping industry regarding the application of European Union legislation to seafarers.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163419","163419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11150","2013-07-04","Department for Transport","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the total carbon emissions from (a) road freight and (b) rail freight were in each year since 1993-94.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163420","163420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11151","2013-07-04","Department for Transport","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change on the annual contribution to carbon emissions from the road transport sector; and what steps he is taking to support an acceleration in modal shift of freight from road to rail as a means of reducing levels of carbon emissions.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163421","163421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11152","2013-07-04","Department for Transport","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what consideration he has given to the recent conclusions of the European Commission's Task Force on Maritime Employment and Competitiveness; and if he has discussed these conclusions with the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163497","163497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11153","2013-07-04","Department for Transport","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what consideration he has given to the recent conclusions of the European Commission's Task Force on Maritime Employment and Competitiveness; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163498","163498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11383","2013-07-08","Department for Education","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many local authorities had a dedicated service to support young runaway children in (a) 2009-10, (b) 2010-11 and (c) 2011-12.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163408","163408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11384","2013-07-08","Department for Education","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many full-time equivalent staff were employed by local authorities to provide direct support to young runaway children in (a) 2009-10, (b) 2010-11 and (c) 2011-12.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163409","163409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11776","2013-07-09","Ministry of Justice","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the estimated cost of the Salvation Army's Trafficking Support Scheme will be in 2013-14; and what the cost of this scheme was in (a) 2011-12 and (b) 2012-13.","Biography information for Dame Eleanor Laing","Mrs Eleanor Laing","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163625","163625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11789","2013-07-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how often people with (a) rheumatoid arthritis, (b) cystic fibrosis and (c) multiple sclerosis were reassessed for employment and support allowance.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163611","163611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11790","2013-07-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people assessed by ESA50 without a face-to-face interview were placed into the (a) support group and (b) work-related activity group in each month from 1 July 2012.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163613","163613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11791","2013-07-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people with (a) rheumatoid arthritis, (b) cystic fibrosis and (c) multiple sclerosis have undergone multiple work capability assessments since its introduction.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163676","163676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11868","2013-07-04","Department for Transport","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the average annual course fees are for deck and engine officer qualifications.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163579","163579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/11881","2013-07-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many Atos assessment centres there are in the UK; and how many have disabled parking facilities.","Biography information for Stephen Gilbert","Stephen Gilbert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163682","163682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/119","2013-07-04","Department for Education","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of graduates from each Russell Group university applied to the Teach First programme in each year since that programme's creation.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163413","163413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/12014","2013-07-05","Home Office","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when the psychoactive substance Benzo Fury or any of its component substances were first identified by her Department's forensic early warning system.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163403","163403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/12015","2013-07-05","Home Office","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much income has been generated by the (a) Late Night Levy and (b) Early Morning Restriction Order to date; and whether she expects the income generated from these two powers to match projections in the Government's impact assessment in the first and second years of operation.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163404","163404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/12016","2013-07-05","Home Office","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she intends to begin consultations on the introduction of full-cost recovery for licence applications under the Licensing Act 2003; and by what date she expects to have implemented full-cost recovery for licence applications.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163513","163513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/12017","2013-07-05","Department of Health","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his policy is on awarding ongoing payments to victms of contaminated blood who are infected with either HIV or hepatitis C stage two; for what reasons such payments are awarded; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163531","163531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/129","2013-07-09","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how much has been allocated for the delivery of the named super connected cities, announced in November 2012 by city; how much has been spent to date by city; and what the expected future spend is by year and by city.","Biography information for Geraint Davies","Geraint Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163623","163623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/143","2013-07-05","Cabinet Office","2013-07-02","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many and what proportion of 18 to 24 year olds have been unemployed for two years or more.","Biography information for Mr David Winnick","Mr David Winnick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163711","163711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/181","2013-07-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much in unspent discretionary housing payments has been returned to the Exchequer by each local authority in Wales in the last five financial years; and what comparative assessment he has made of the proportion of such payments returned by local authorities in (a) Wales and (b) England.","Biography information for Mr Mark Williams","Mr Mark Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163476","163476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/200","2013-07-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to Construction 2025 Industrial Strategy: government and industry in partnership, published on 2 July 2013, what steps he is taking to improve standards in health and safety on smaller projects.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163486","163486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5462","2013-07-05","Ministry of Defence","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 1 July 2013, Official Report, column 401W, on procurement, what the total sum saved through his Department's re-negotiation of contracts is since May 2010.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163709","163709"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5538","2013-07-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the reasons are for the abolition of the UK Advisory Network; and whether he has any plans to offer a replacement or alternative to the businesses that used it.","Biography information for Caroline Nokes","Caroline Nokes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163655","163655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5647","2013-07-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will take steps to introduce a total ban on the sale of Chinese lanterns.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163598","163598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5648","2013-07-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what measurable targets he plans to set for reversing the decline of bees and other pollinators as part of the National Pollinator Strategy.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163698","163698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5649","2013-07-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how he plans to involve (a) the Department for Communities and Local Government and (b) other Government departments in the National Pollinator Strategy.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163699","163699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5650","2013-07-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will take steps to ensure that the UK will lead the way internationally in developing strategies to reverse the decline of bees and other pollinators.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163700","163700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5651","2013-07-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he had with the Israeli Attorney-General in June 2013 on implementing measures to require audio-visual recordings of all interrogations of Palestinian children by the Israeli military and to make these available to the children's lawyers.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163691","163691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5652","2013-07-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he had with the Israeli Attorney-General on putting an end to the Israeli military practice of arresting Palestinian children by night.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163692","163692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5653","2013-07-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he had with the Israeli Attorney-General on ending the Israeli military practice of shackling Palestinian children.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163693","163693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5654","2013-07-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he had with the Israeli Attorney-General on ending the practice of keeping Palestinian children in solitary confinement while in Israeli military custody.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163694","163694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5655","2013-07-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he had with the Israeli Attorney-General on ending the practice of transferring Palestinian children from the West Bank to military custody in Israel.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163695","163695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5656","2013-07-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will ensure that new elements of the National Pollinator Strategy are implemented before the spring of 2014.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163696","163696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5657","2013-07-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans he has to set out a clear timetable for action to reverse bee decline in the UK.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163697","163697"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/5658","2013-07-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the speech of the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State, Lord de Mauley of 28 June 2013, when his Department expects to (a) finish collecting the results of the urgent and comprehensive review of current policy on pollinators, (b) finalise the new National Pollinator Strategy and (c) begin implementing the National Pollinator Strategy.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163707","163707"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6115","2013-07-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the future work programme of the African Union High-level Implementation Panel.","Biography information for Mr William Bain","Mr William Bain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163638","163638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6116","2013-07-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent discussions his Department has had with the Home Office and the devolved administrations on specialist policing support for tackling wildlife crime.","Biography information for Mr William Bain","Mr William Bain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163639","163639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6117","2013-07-04","HM Treasury","2013-07-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the distributional consequences were of payments of pension tax relief in respect of persons on (a) the basic rate of income tax, (b) the higher rate of income tax and (c) the supplementary rate of income tax, by income decile of the population, in each of the last four financial years.","Biography information for Mr William Bain","Mr William Bain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163640","163640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6118","2013-07-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received on the upcoming expiry of the United Nations Mission in the Republic of South Sudan's mandate in that country; and what representations he has made regarding its renewal.","Biography information for Mr William Bain","Mr William Bain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163662","163662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6119","2013-07-04","HM Treasury","2013-07-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the payments were of pension tax relief in respect of persons on (a) the basic rate of income tax, (b) the higher rate of income tax and (c) the supplementary rate of income tax in each of the last four financial years; and what levels of those payments accrued to individuals as categorised by income decile of the population.","Biography information for Mr William Bain","Mr William Bain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163641","163641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6120","2013-07-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate his Department plans to make of any over or underspend of discretionary housing payment allocations by councils in (a) Scotland, (b) England and (c) Wales in 2013-14; what information his Department is seeking from those councils to make that estimate; and how frequently that estimate will be reviewed.","Biography information for Mr William Bain","Mr William Bain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163642","163642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6185","2013-07-04","Ministry of Justice","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what arrangements are in place for expert witnesses to conduct interviews with prisoners in private at Close Supervision Centre HM Prison Woodhill; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163565","163565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6238","2013-07-04","Department for Education","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether his Department has assessed the potential social, educational and economic benefits of supporting play therapy and early intervention at key stage 1.","Biography information for Alec Shelbrooke","Alec Shelbrooke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163650","163650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6285","2013-07-04","Department for Education","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 1 July 2013, Official Report, column 599, on free school meals, if he will set a date for the publication of plans for the future of free school meals under universal credit.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163647","163647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6286","2013-07-04","Department for Education","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 1 July 2013, Official Report, column 599, on free school meals, what assessment he has made of how many and what proportion of families with children in receipt of free school meals are living in poverty.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163645","163645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6287","2013-07-04","Department for Education","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 1 July 2013, Official Report, column 599, on free school meals, what assessment he has made of how many and what proportion of families with children in receipt of free school meals earn more than £135 a week.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163646","163646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6302","2013-07-05","Home Office","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which local authorities have resolved to use powers to regulate lapdancing clubs under the Police and Crime Act 2009.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163402","163402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6478","2013-07-09","Department for Education","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the expected benefits of allowing schools to vary term dates are.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163716","163716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6479","2013-07-09","Department of Health","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent representations he has received regarding the potential for an opt-out organ donation system in the UK as a whole.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163717","163717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6480","2013-07-09","Department for Education","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what representations he has received regarding concerns over proposals to allow schools to vary term dates.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163718","163718"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6538","2013-07-04","Department for Education","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what minimum expectations of delivery he has issued to local authorities on the delivery of youth services.","Biography information for Tristram Hunt","Tristram Hunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163577","163577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6539","2013-07-04","Department for Education","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of funding of and level of spend for youth services.","Biography information for Tristram Hunt","Tristram Hunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163578","163578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6540","2013-07-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will make an assessment of the London Economics report entitled the outcomes associated with the BTEC route of degree level acquisition.","Biography information for Tristram Hunt","Tristram Hunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163569","163569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6768","2013-07-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many (a) rangers, (b) planners, (c) archaeologists, (d) sustainable development advisers and (e) education officers were employed in each national park in England in (i) 2010-11, (ii) 2011-12 and (iii) 2012-13; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163534","163534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/6769","2013-07-05","Department of Health","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many registered nurses there were at each acute hospital trust in London in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12 and (c) 2012-13; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163535","163535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7114","2013-07-05","Ministry of Defence","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the viability of developing housing on his Department's land in Shoeburyness.","Biography information for James Duddridge","James Duddridge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163532","163532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7115","2013-07-05","Ministry of Defence","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what proposals his Department has received to develop housing on its land in Shoeburyness.","Biography information for James Duddridge","James Duddridge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163533","163533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7260","2013-07-04","Ministry of Justice","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what funding he is providing for identified victims of human trafficking after they have exited the Salvation Army Trafficking Support Scheme.","Biography information for Michael Connarty","Michael Connarty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163648","163648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7272","2013-07-04","Ministry of Justice","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many times the RSPCA has achieved a criminal conviction in each of the last 15 years; how many of those convictions were for breaches of the Dangerous Wild Animals Act 1976 in each such year; and what the nature was of each offence, by type.","Biography information for Karl McCartney","Karl McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163563","163563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7273","2013-07-04","Ministry of Justice","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many private prosecutions were brought by the RSPCA (a) in the five years prior to November 2010 and (b) in each year since.","Biography information for Karl McCartney","Karl McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163690","163690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7624","2013-07-05","Department for Transport","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will instruct High Speed 2 Ltd to carry out a feasibility study of Option 8 at Euston Station.","Biography information for Frank Dobson","Frank Dobson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163712","163712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7625","2013-07-05","Department for Transport","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he became aware that High Speed 2 Ltd has not carried out a feasibility study of Option 8 at Euston Station.","Biography information for Frank Dobson","Frank Dobson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163713","163713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7626","2013-07-05","Department of Health","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his Department's latest estimate is of that sum owed to the NHS by foreign patients; and how much of that sum is made up of debts owed by foreign patients treated in private beds in NHS hospitals.","Biography information for Frank Dobson","Frank Dobson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163714","163714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7643","2013-07-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether his Department has conducted any studies into variations in the fees charged by local authorities and utility companies in relation to disabled facilities grants.","Biography information for David Wright","David Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163573","163573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7644","2013-07-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many disabled facilities grants were approved in the last five years in England and Wales.","Biography information for David Wright","David Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163574","163574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7645","2013-07-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what work his Department has done to assess value for money in relation to disabled facilities grants.","Biography information for David Wright","David Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163575","163575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7646","2013-07-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what guidance his Department provided to local authorities on the disabled facilities grant regime; and whether he plans to review such guidance.","Biography information for David Wright","David Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163576","163576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7778","2013-07-05","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the judgement by the Court of Justice of the European Union, in the case VG Wort v Kyocera on 27 June 2013, on his proposal for an exception to copyright for private copying that allows for appropriate compensation to be paid at the point of sale.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163399","163399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7779","2013-07-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that (a) the National Wildlife Crime Unit, (b) the Metropolitan Police Wildlife Crime Unit and (c) other wildlife law enforcement bodies have the necessary resources to tackle wildlife crime effectively.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163400","163400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7797","2013-07-04","Ministry of Defence","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many veterans residing in Halton constituency are in receipt of (a) war pension scheme, (b) armed forces compensation scheme and (c) armed forces pension scheme payments.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163490","163490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7798","2013-07-04","Department of Health","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many care assistants in Halton constituency are on zero hours contracts.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163491","163491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7799","2013-07-04","Department of Health","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many ambulances there were in the North West Ambulance service area in (a) 1 April 1998, (b) 1 April 2010 and (c) 1 April 2012.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163492","163492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7800","2013-07-04","Department of Health","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many dentists there were in Halton constituency in (a) April 1998, (b) April 2010 and (c) April 2012.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163493","163493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7801","2013-07-04","Department of Health","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many GPs there were in Halton constituency in (a) April 1998, (b) April 2010 and (c) April 2012.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163494","163494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7802","2013-07-04","Ministry of Defence","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent estimate he has made of the number of World War Two veterans in (a) Halton constituency, (b) Merseyside and (c) the UK.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163495","163495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7803","2013-07-04","Ministry of Defence","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many reservists there were in Halton constituency in 1 April 2013.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163496","163496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7804","2013-07-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many recycling plants have failed health and safety requirements in each year since 2001.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163528","163528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7805","2013-07-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent estimate he has made of the number of fires at recycling plants since 2001.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163529","163529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7806","2013-07-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether his Department has estimated the average time material is stored at recycling plants before being recycled.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163530","163530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7841","2013-07-05","Prime Minister","2013-07-02","To ask the Prime Minister, what (a) oral and (b) written discussions he has had with the Independent Adviser on Minister's Interests on the appointment of Ian Livingston as Minister for Trade.","Biography information for Ann McKechin","Ann McKechin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163401","163401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/7842","2013-07-04","Prime Minister","2013-07-02","To ask the Prime Minister, what (a) assessment and (b) recommendations the Adviser on Ministers' Interests has made on the scale of shareholdings in British Telecom held by Ian Livingston.","Biography information for Ann McKechin","Ann McKechin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163414","163414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/793","2013-07-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many overpayments were made by the Student Loans Company in error in the 2012-13 financial year.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163412","163412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/794","2013-07-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what processes are in place to scrutinise the (a) efficacy, (b) accuracy and (c) value for money of bids for the Future Cities Project under the auspices of the Technology Strategy Board; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stewart Jackson","Mr Stewart Jackson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163475","163475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795","2013-07-04","Ministry of Defence","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will place in the Library the letter from HM Industrial Pollution Directorate to Lord James Douglas Hamilton in 1990 detailing that debris from demolition work at the air station HMS Merlin was used for infilling purposes between 1944 and 1951.","Biography information for Mr Gordon Brown","Mr Gordon Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163478","163478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/796","2013-07-04","Ministry of Defence","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will place in the Library the paper written in September 1992 from his Department to the Committee on Medical Aspects of radiation in the environment which named the Dalgety Bay area as a site of contamination.","Biography information for Mr Gordon Brown","Mr Gordon Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163479","163479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797","2013-07-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent assessment he has made of whether the Financial Reporting Review Panel's (a) resources and (b) expertise are sufficient to fulfil the Government's commitment to ensure that directors' social and environmental duties have to be covered in company reporting.","Biography information for Martin Horwood","Martin Horwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163482","163482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798","2013-07-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to Construction 2025 Industrial Strategy: government and industry in partnership, published on 2 July 2013, what additional support he plans to provide to businesses to help exploit the export potential of digital and building information modelling capabilities.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163483","163483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/799","2013-07-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to Construction 2025 Industrial Strategy: government and industry in partnership, published on 2 July 2013, how much resource he plans to provide from UK Export Finance Services to major construction firms for the purposes of exporting.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163484","163484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/800","2013-07-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to Construction 2025 Industrial Strategy: government and industry in partnership, published on 2 July 2013, what his expected timescale is for the development of a construction supply chain payment charter.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163485","163485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/801","2013-07-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to Construction 2025 Industrial Strategy: government and industry in partnership, published on 2 July 2013, what protocols and standards he plans to bring forward regarding building information modelling.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163487","163487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/802","2013-07-05","Department of Health","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what involvement Sir David Nicholson had in (a) commissioning and (b) producing the NHS Next Stage Review.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163510","163510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/803","2013-07-05","Department of Health","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Answer of 10 October 2007, Official Report, column 672W, on NHS Next Stage Review, what the final cost of the NHS Next Stage Review was and the costs of the review under each major cost area were.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163511","163511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8031","2013-07-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent representations he has made to the European Union Employment Commissioner on the Commission's current review of health and safety policy; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163405","163405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8032","2013-07-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to reduce occupational ill-health.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163406","163406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8033","2013-07-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what research his Department has commissioned since May 2010 on making workplaces safer; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163407","163407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8034","2013-07-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many fatal accidents occurred in the construction sector in the last year for which figures are available; and how many of the people who were killed were (a) self-employed, (b) employed by firms with fewer than 10 employees and (c) employed by firms with fewer than 50 employees.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163614","163614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/804","2013-07-05","Department of Health","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Answer of 10 October 2007, Official Report, column 672W, on NHS Next Stage Review, how many (a) clinicians, (b) managers and (c) other staff made formal contributions to the NHS Next Stage Review.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163512","163512"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/805","2013-07-05","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if he will list those (a) oil-fired and (b) coal-fired power stations which (i) have been closed during the last five years and (ii) are due to be closed during the next 10 years, together with the reasons for closure in each case.","Biography information for Dr Julian Lewis","Dr Julian Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163514","163514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/806","2013-07-05","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what reductions (a) have occurred over the last five years and (b) are anticipated in the next 10 years in the total electricity generating capacity of the United Kingdom; and to what extent these will be offset by new generating capacity in each period.","Biography information for Dr Julian Lewis","Dr Julian Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163515","163515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/807","2013-07-05","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if he will make it his policy to mothball sufficient power stations (a) already and (b) scheduled to be taken out of service to ensure a strategic reserve generating capacity to (i) prevent power cuts and (ii) meet emergency demands in times of conflict or other crises.","Biography information for Dr Julian Lewis","Dr Julian Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163516","163516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/808","2013-07-05","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether he has identified any power stations, either closed or scheduled for closure, which could be mothballed economically; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Julian Lewis","Dr Julian Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163517","163517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/809","2013-07-05","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether (a) EU and (b) other restrictions on emissions by power stations can be set aside in circumstances of national emergency; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Julian Lewis","Dr Julian Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163518","163518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810","2013-07-04","Church Commissioners","2013-07-02","To ask the Honourable Member for Banbury, representing the Church Commissioners, for what reason prayers are not permitted at civil weddings; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Baroness McIntosh of Pickering","Miss Anne McIntosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163424","163424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/812","2013-07-04","Ministry of Defence","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the maximum decibel noise measurements were from the Shoeburyness explosion site on the morning of 7 June 2013.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163501","163501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/813","2013-07-04","Ministry of Defence","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what munitions were being tested at the Shoeburyness explosion site on the morning of 7 June 2013; and whether the noise exceeded the recommended maximum of noise pollution levels.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163502","163502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/814","2013-07-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will publish a list of meetings held by (a) Ministers and (b) officials in his Department over the last 12 months on Government policy on mandatory public disclosure of voting practices by institutional investors.","Biography information for Peter Aldous","Peter Aldous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163503","163503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/815","2013-07-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what proportion of institutional investors publicly disclosed their voting records in the latest period for which figures are available; how many such disclosures were of (a) summary figures and (b) full breakdowns of voting practices on particular issues at particular companies.","Biography information for Peter Aldous","Peter Aldous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163504","163504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816","2013-07-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what comparative assessment his Department has conducted of the effects in (a) France, (b) the US and (c) other countries of policies on voting disclosure in jurisdictions in which institutional investors are obliged to publicly disclose their voting practices.","Biography information for Peter Aldous","Peter Aldous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163505","163505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/817","2013-07-04","Ministry of Justice","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what plans he has to review the law relating to presumption of death provisions.","Biography information for Baroness McIntosh of Pickering","Miss Anne McIntosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163506","163506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/818","2013-07-04","Ministry of Justice","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what practical assistance is given to those whose loved ones are missing presumed dead.","Biography information for Baroness McIntosh of Pickering","Miss Anne McIntosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163507","163507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/819","2013-07-04","Ministry of Justice","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what arrangements are in place to allow all lines of police enquiry and evidence to be pursued before any decision regarding presumption of death can be made; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Baroness McIntosh of Pickering","Miss Anne McIntosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163508","163508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8194","2013-07-05","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what recommendations his Department has received from the Behavioural Insights Team based in the Cabinet Office on better incentivising domestic and non-domestic retrofit.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163396","163396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8195","2013-07-05","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many companies who secured a contract through eco-brokerage have defaulted on their contractual obligations since July 2012.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163395","163395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8196","2013-07-05","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many cashback vouchers have been (a) issued and (b) paid in each (i) parliamentary constituency and (ii) local authority area by 16 June 2013.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163397","163397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8197","2013-07-05","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many (a) Green Deal assessments and (b) Green Deal plans were completed in each (i) parliamentary constituency and (ii) local authority area by 16 June 2013.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163398","163398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/820","2013-07-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he has had any discussions with senior management of (a) Barclays Bank, (b) RBS Group, (c) HSBC Banking Group and (d) Lloyds Banking Group on the progress that they have made in providing offers of redress to their own customers through the provisions of the Financial Conduct Authority redress scheme for businesses mis-sold interest rate swaps; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Guto Bebb","Guto Bebb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163509","163509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/821","2013-07-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many vending machines in his Department's premises contain snack foods that are high in calories and low in nutritional value.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163524","163524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822","2013-07-05","Ministry of Defence","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many vending machines in his Department's premises contain snack foods that are high in calories and low in nutritional value.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163525","163525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823","2013-07-05","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many vending machines in his Department's premises contain snack foods that are high in calories and low in nutritional value.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163526","163526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/824","2013-07-05","Department for Education","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many vending machines in his Department's premises contain snack foods that are high in calories and low in nutritional value.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163527","163527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/825","2013-07-09","Ministry of Justice","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether he plans to review the provision of the multi-agency public protection regime in the East of England; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stewart Jackson","Mr Stewart Jackson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163542","163542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/826","2013-07-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will list all Twitter accounts for which officials of his Department (a) have had and (b) currently have responsibility for (i) monitoring and (ii) updating.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163543","163543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/827","2013-07-05","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent discussions he has had with the Financial Conduct Authority on the number of businesses offered redress as part of their redress scheme for businesses mis-sold interest rate hedging products; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Guto Bebb","Guto Bebb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163537","163537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828","2013-07-08","Department for Transport","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions he and Ministers of his Department have had with their international counterparts concerning the carriage of polyisobutene; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Sheryll Murray","Sheryll Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163539","163539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829","2013-07-08","Department for Transport","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions he has had with other Bonn convention signatories regarding safeguarding guillemots and other sea birds from oil spills; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Sheryll Murray","Sheryll Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163540","163540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830","2013-07-08","Department for Transport","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions he has had with the International Maritime Organisation about the reclassification of polyisobutene.","Biography information for Mrs Sheryll Murray","Sheryll Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163541","163541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/831","2013-07-04","Department for Education","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which schools in each parliamentary constituency in England will receive funding under the Priority Schools Building Programme in the next three years.","Biography information for Chris Skidmore","Chris Skidmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163583","163583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/832","2013-07-04","Home Office","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent discussions she has had with the Independent Police Complaints Commissioner; when each such meeting took place; what issues were discussed; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163584","163584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/833","2013-07-04","Ministry of Justice","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what Directorate within his Department has policy responsibility for Essex Probation Trust; how many officials of each Civil Service grade are employed within this Directorate; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163585","163585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/834","2013-07-04","Home Office","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) current and (b) former members of the police service (i) currently serve and (ii) served between 2005 and 2012, on the Independent Police Complaints Commission, by police force area; in what capacity they served; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163564","163564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/835","2013-07-04","Ministry of Justice","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps Essex Probation Trust (EPT) (a) have taken and (b) plans to take in each of the next two years to increase its cost-effectiveness; what meetings officials in his Department have had with EPT on this issue; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163586","163586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/836","2013-07-04","Ministry of Justice","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will place in the Library a copy of the response from Essex Probation Trust to each request under the Freedom of Information Act 2000, where the request was agreed to and answered in (a) full and (b) part since October 2011; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163587","163587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/837","2013-07-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many (a) permanent workers, (b) temporary workers and (c) zero-hour contracts there were in the Royal Mail in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163566","163566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838","2013-07-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the average wage is of a Royal Mail employee.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163567","163567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839","2013-07-04","Ministry of Justice","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many staff employed by Essex Probation Trust were (a) suspended and (b) dismissed for misusing the government procurement card in the last 12 months; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163588","163588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/840","2013-07-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many people have been employed by the Royal Mail in each (a) region, (b) county and (c) parliamentary constituency in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163568","163568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/841","2013-07-04","Home Office","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many anti-social behaviour orders were issued (a) nationally and (b) in Peterborough constituency in each of the last five years; and what the rate of breach of anti-social behaviour orders was (i) nationally and (ii) in Peterborough constituency in each such year.","Biography information for Mr Stewart Jackson","Mr Stewart Jackson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163580","163580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8418","2013-07-05","Ministry of Defence","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 1 July 2013, Official Report, column 400W, on Iran, what the assessed and agreed potential liability is to international military services of funds owed to Iran.","Biography information for Mr Ben Wallace","Mr Ben Wallace","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163684","163684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/842","2013-07-04","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what recent assessment he has made of the operation of (a) section 1 and (b) section 2 of the Warm Homes and Energy Conservation Act 2000; what recent representations he has received on the operation of the Act; and what responses he gave to such representations.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163581","163581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843","2013-07-04","Department for Education","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much each school has received under the Academies Capital Maintenance Fund in each year of that fund's operation; and in which parliamentary constituency is each such school based.","Biography information for Chris Skidmore","Chris Skidmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163582","163582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844","2013-07-04","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many (a) written, (b) email and (c) telephone representations he has received on (i) his plans to alleviate fuel poverty in the private rented sector, (ii) the operation of the Warm Homes and Energy Conservation Act 2000 and (iii) the disconnection of (A) gas and (B) electricity supplies in each month since May 2010; how many such representations were from (1) individuals and (2) organisations; if he will place in the Library copies of responses sent to such representations; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163570","163570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/845","2013-07-04","Ministry of Justice","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what information his Department holds on how many members of the public have attended each meeting of the Essex Probation Board in each of the last 12 months for which information is available; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163571","163571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/846","2013-07-04","Home Office","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what research she has commissioned into the level of public confidence in the Independent Police Complaints Commission since May 2010; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163572","163572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/847","2013-07-04","Department for Transport","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to enable Network Rail to be considered a public body for the purposes of auditing by the National Audit Office.","Biography information for Mark Pritchard","Mark Pritchard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163618","163618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/848","2013-07-04","Department for Transport","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to ensure that Network Rail is audited by the National Audit Office; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mark Pritchard","Mark Pritchard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163619","163619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/849","2013-07-04","Department for Transport","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans his Department has to make Network Rail subject to scrutiny by the National Audit Office; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mark Pritchard","Mark Pritchard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163620","163620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850","2013-07-04","Department for Transport","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans his Department has to improve the level of public scrutiny on the performance of Network Rail.","Biography information for Mark Pritchard","Mark Pritchard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163621","163621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851","2013-07-04","HM Treasury","2013-07-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 1 July 2013, Official Report, column 406W, on Financial Services, which activities of Tiuta Plc fell under the supervision of the Financial Services Authority.","Biography information for Guto Bebb","Guto Bebb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163605","163605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8519","2013-07-05","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the number of jobs which have been created or safeguarded by foreign direct investment from other EU countries in (a) total and (b) each NUTS 1 region in each year since 2003.","Biography information for Mr Mike Thornton","Mr Michael Thornton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163615","163615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/852","2013-07-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the total income was from Government services for sub-post offices in each year since 2005.","Biography information for Paul Maynard","Paul Maynard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163637","163637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8520","2013-07-05","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the number of jobs  in each NUTS 1 region which are dependent on trade with the European Union.","Biography information for Mr Mike Thornton","Mr Michael Thornton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163616","163616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8521","2013-07-05","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many businesses in (a) total and (b) each NUTS 1 region conducted trade in (i) services and (ii) goods with other EU countries in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Mr Mike Thornton","Mr Michael Thornton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163617","163617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/853","2013-07-04","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what criteria National Grid would use to determine whether new electricity transmission projects would be constructed overground or underground.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163651","163651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/854","2013-07-04","Ministry of Justice","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent steps Essex Probation Trust (a) has taken and (b) plans to take in each of the next two years to reduce reoffending in (i) Southend-on-Sea and (ii) Essex; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163593","163593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8549","2013-07-04","Prime Minister","2013-07-02","To ask the Prime Minister, with reference to his oral Answer of 27 February 2013, Official Report, column 306, when he will (a) respond to the petition of the hon. Member for Ochil and South Perthshire on food banks and (b) answer the hon. Member's subsequent email correspondence of 27 February 2013 and 12 March 2013 relating to that issue.","Biography information for Gordon Banks","Gordon Banks","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163627","163627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/855","2013-07-04","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many hon. Members wrote to his Department on behalf of constituents about (a) steps taken to alleviate fuel poverty in the private rented sector, (b) the operation of the Warm Homes and Energy Conservation Act 2000 and (c) the disconnection of (i) gas and (ii) electricity supplies in the last 12 months; what the average time taken to reply was; if he will place in the Library a copy of each such reply; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163594","163594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/856","2013-07-04","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what recent discussions (a) he, (b) Ministers in his Department and (c) officials in his Department have had with their counterparts in HM Treasury on the operation of the Warm Homes and Energy Conservation Act 2000; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163595","163595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/857","2013-07-04","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what recent assessment he has made of his Department's progress towards eradicating fuel poverty for all households in England by 2016; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163596","163596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/858","2013-07-04","Department for Education","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 3 June 2013, Official Report, column 1013W, on schools: standards, if he will ask HM Chief Inspector to provide the requested data for May 2010 according to the constituency boundaries that came into force in that month.","Biography information for Chris Skidmore","Chris Skidmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163597","163597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/859","2013-07-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Statement of 1 July 2013, Official Report, columns 24-5W, on planning and Travellers, if he will extend the provisions put in place for greenbelt land to areas designated Areas of Outstanding Natural Beauty; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Sheryll Murray","Sheryll Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163600","163600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860","2013-07-04","HM Treasury","2013-07-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he plans to respond to the Sita Trust report, Sita Trust's Funds Held, submitted in response to his Department's Funds Held challenge.","Biography information for Andrew Bridgen","Andrew Bridgen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163602","163602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8603","2013-07-04","HM Treasury","2013-07-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether savings covered by the terms and limits of the Financial Services Compensation Scheme are protected against (a) ad hoc restrictions of access, (b) bank bail-ins and (c) other forms of expropriation or forced conversion.","Biography information for John Hemming","John Hemming","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163688","163688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8604","2013-07-04","HM Treasury","2013-07-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will instruct National Savings and Investments to make National Savings index-linked savings certificates permanently available to savers with immediate effect.","Biography information for John Hemming","John Hemming","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163689","163689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861","2013-07-04","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many miles of electricity transmission cabling were constructed by National Grid (a) overground and (b) underground in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163652","163652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862","2013-07-04","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the average cost is of installing electricity transmission cables (a) overground via pylons and (b) underground; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163653","163653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/863","2013-07-04","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what representations he has received from the Welsh Government on the intention of Western Powers Distribution to construct electricity pylons between TAN 8 area G in north Carmarthenshire to the national grid located in South Carmarthenshire.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163654","163654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864","2013-07-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when HM Ambassador to the Dominican Republic last discussed the case of Ms Nicole Reyes, a constituent of the hon. Member for Cardiff South and Penarth, with the government of the Dominican Republic.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163667","163667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865","2013-07-05","Department for International Development","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what aid the Government provided (a) directly and (b) via multilateral agencies to support judicial and penal reform in the Dominican Republic in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163668","163668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/866","2013-07-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of employment and support allowance claimants in the work-related activity group are in employment 12 to 18 months after their claim.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163677","163677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867","2013-07-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when he or one of his Ministers last met the (a) Justice Minister and (b) Attorney General of the Dominican Republic.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163669","163669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/868","2013-07-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when HM Ambassador to the Dominican Republic last met the (a) Justice Minister and (b) Attorney General of the Dominican Republic.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163670","163670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/869","2013-07-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when HM Ambassador to the Dominican Republic last met the Dominican Republic's Ambassador to the Court of St. James.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163671","163671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/870","2013-07-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of employment and support allowance claimants found fit for work are in employment 12 to 18 months after their claim.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163678","163678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/871","2013-07-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of employment and support allowance claimants found fit for work flow on to jobseeker's allowance.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163679","163679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/872","2013-07-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of jobseeker's allowance claimants are in employment 12 to 18 months after their claim.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163680","163680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/873","2013-07-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the criteria are for a work programme provider to be eligible for market share shift.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163681","163681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/874","2013-07-04","Ministry of Justice","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will place in the Library a copy of Essex Probation Trust's government procurement card transaction data including (a) the date of transaction, (b) the merchant, (c) the value and (d) a description of each item of expenditure incurred since October 2012; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163589","163589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/875","2013-07-04","Ministry of Justice","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent reports he has received of the morale of probation officers in the Essex Probation Trust area; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163590","163590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/876","2013-07-04","Ministry of Justice","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) males and (b) females in each age group on probation in the Essex Probation Trust area reoffended in each of the last 12 months for which information is available; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163591","163591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/877","2013-07-04","Ministry of Justice","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the 10 most frequent offences committed by (a) males and (b) females in each age group on probation within Essex Probation Trust area were in each of the last 12 months; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163592","163592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/878","2013-07-05","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will review the lessons of the fire at Smethwick on 1-2 July 2013 for the adequacy of current and planned levels of fire and rescue resources nationally.","Biography information for Chris Williamson","Chris Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163610","163610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/879","2013-07-05","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the profit margins were of the Royal Mail in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163685","163685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8794","2013-07-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received on whether draft laws in Burma which are being drafted with the assistance of the Government are being treated as state secrets by the government of Burma; and what the reasons are for such a practice.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163499","163499"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8795","2013-07-04","Department for International Development","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assistance her Department provides to communities impoverished by land confiscation in Burma.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163500","163500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/8796","2013-07-05","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of any change in the level of rent arrears owed to housing associations and local authorities since the introduction of the under-occupancy penalty; and if he will publish statistics on that matter.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163683","163683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/880","2013-07-04","Department for Transport","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect that the introduction of Network Rail's new track access charges for freight operating companies will have on annual rail freight volumes from and to UK ports.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163701","163701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/881","2013-07-04","Department for Transport","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect that Network Rail's introduction of track access charges for freight operating companies will have on annual volumes of freight carried by (a) rail and (b) road.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163702","163702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882","2013-07-04","Department for Transport","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent research he has conducted into the volumes of freight moved (a) to and (b) from container ports in the UK by (i) road and (ii) rail in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163703","163703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/883","2013-07-04","Department for Transport","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to increase multi-modal freight capacity in the UK port sector.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163704","163704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884","2013-07-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent estimate he has made of the number of children in the UK living in poverty; and what steps the Government is taking to substantially reduce child poverty in the near future.","Biography information for Mr David Winnick","Mr David Winnick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163710","163710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885","2013-07-04","Attorney General","2013-07-02","To ask the Attorney General, if he will list all Twitter accounts for which officials of the Law Officers' Departments (a) have had and (b) currently have responsibility for (i) monitoring and (ii) updating.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163544","163544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/886","2013-07-04","Cabinet Office","2013-07-02","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will list all Twitter accounts for which officials of his Department (a) have had and (b) currently have responsibility for (i) monitoring and (ii) updating.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163545","163545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887","2013-07-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will list all Twitter accounts for which officials of his Department (a) have had and (b) currently have responsibility for (i) monitoring and (ii) updating.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163546","163546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/888","2013-07-04","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if she will list all Twitter accounts for which officials of her Department (a) have had and (b) currently have responsibility for (i) monitoring and (ii) updating.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163547","163547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889","2013-07-04","Ministry of Defence","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will list all Twitter accounts for which officials of his Department (a) have had and (b) currently have responsibility for (i) monitoring and (ii) updating.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163548","163548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890","2013-07-04","Department for Education","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will list all Twitter accounts for which officials of his Department (a) have had and (b) currently have responsibility for (i) monitoring and (ii) updating.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163549","163549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/891","2013-07-04","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if he will list all Twitter accounts for which officials of his Department (a) have had and (b) currently have responsibility for (i) monitoring and (ii) updating.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163550","163550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/892","2013-07-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will list all Twitter accounts for which officials of his Department (a) have had and (b) currently have responsibility for (i) monitoring and (ii) updating.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163551","163551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/893","2013-07-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will list all Twitter accounts for which officials of his Department (a) have had and (b) currently have responsibility for (i) monitoring and (ii) updating.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163552","163552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/894","2013-07-04","Department of Health","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will list all Twitter accounts for which officials of his Department (a) have had and (b) currently have responsibility for (i) monitoring and (ii) updating.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163553","163553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/895","2013-07-04","Home Office","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will list all Twitter accounts for which officials of her Department (a) have had and (b) currently have responsibility for (i) monitoring and (ii) updating.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163554","163554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/896","2013-07-04","Department for International Development","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will list all Twitter accounts for which officials of her Department (a) have had and (b) currently have responsibility for (i) monitoring and (ii) updating.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163555","163555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/897","2013-07-04","Ministry of Justice","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will list all Twitter accounts for which officials of his Department (a) have had and (b) currently have responsibility for (i) monitoring and (ii) updating.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163556","163556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/898","2013-07-04","Northern Ireland Office","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, if she will list all Twitter accounts for which officials of her Department (a) have had and (b) currently have responsibility for (i) monitoring and (ii) updating.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163557","163557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/899","2013-07-04","Prime Minister","2013-07-02","To ask the Prime Minister, if he will list all Twitter accounts for which officials of No. 10 Downing Street (a) have had and (b) currently have responsibility for (i) monitoring and (ii) updating.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163558","163558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/900","2013-07-04","Scotland Office","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, if he will list all Twitter accounts for which officials of his Department (a) have had and (b) currently have responsibility for (i) monitoring and (ii) updating.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163559","163559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/901","2013-07-04","HM Treasury","2013-07-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will list all Twitter accounts for which officials of his Department (a) have had and (b) currently have responsibility for (i) monitoring and (ii) updating.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163560","163560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9019","2013-07-05","Ministry of Justice","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what meetings with legal aid consultees he has planned; and if he will make a statement on the response to the consultation.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163519","163519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902","2013-07-04","Wales Office","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, if he will list all Twitter accounts for which officials of his Department (a) have had and (b) currently have responsibility for (i) monitoring and (ii) updating.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163561","163561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9020","2013-07-05","Prime Minister","2013-07-02","To ask the Prime Minister, what human rights issues were raised during his visit to Kazakhstan; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163520","163520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9021","2013-07-05","Ministry of Justice","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will list all meetings he and Ministers have held as part of the legal aid consultation; and on what dates these meetings took place.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163521","163521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9022","2013-07-05","Ministry of Justice","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will list all submissions received in response to his recent consultation on legal aid changes and ensure that they are all published.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163522","163522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/903","2013-07-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will list all Twitter accounts for which officials of his Department (a) have had and (b) currently have responsibility for (i) monitoring and (ii) updating.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163562","163562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9038","2013-07-09","Department of Health","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential effects of teaching first aid in schools on public health and reducing unnecessary accident and emergency admissions.","Biography information for Anne Marie Morris","Anne Marie Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163410","163410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9039","2013-07-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the number of businesses which have secured funding under the Start-Up Loans scheme to date.","Biography information for Anne Marie Morris","Anne Marie Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163687","163687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904","2013-07-09","HM Treasury","2013-07-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the region and financial year breakdown is of the infrastructure investment contained within his Department's Investing in Britain's Future document, published in July 2013.","Biography information for Geraint Davies","Geraint Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163622","163622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/905","2013-07-09","Department for Transport","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what his policy is on increasing the provision of rail services via Open Access train operating company providers on (a) the East Coast Mainline and (b) other rail routes; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stewart Jackson","Mr Stewart Jackson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163624","163624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/906","2013-07-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent estimate he has made of the number of British citizens residing permanently in the Dominican Republic.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163628","163628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9063","2013-07-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to the Palestinian Authority on its use of maps depicting a State of Palestine replacing Israel.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163422","163422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9064","2013-07-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to the Palestinian Authority about reports that PA TV has broadcast a video calling on Palestinians to raise flags over all Israeli cities and villages.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163423","163423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/907","2013-07-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of judicial processes in the Dominican Republic; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163629","163629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/908","2013-07-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many times the Government has intervened to make representations on behalf of British citizens detained in the Dominican Republic in the last 10 years.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163630","163630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909","2013-07-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many British citizens are currently detained following conviction in the Dominican Republic; and what the average length of sentence is.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163631","163631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/910","2013-07-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many British citizens are currently detained awaiting trial in the Dominican Republic.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163632","163632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/911","2013-07-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many incidents have been reported to his Department of milk infected by tuberculosis (TB) since May 2010; and for what reasons his Department bans the sale of milk known to be infected by TB.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163633","163633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/912","2013-07-04","Prime Minister","2013-07-02","To ask the Prime Minister, what matters in respect of Pakistan's continued possession of nuclear weapons he discussed with his Pakistani counterpart during his recent visit to Pakistan.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163634","163634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/913","2013-07-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, which Government products and services have been (a) added to and (b) removed from the range available at post offices since May 2010.","Biography information for Paul Maynard","Paul Maynard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163635","163635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/914","2013-07-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the financial effect of changes to the range of Government products and services available at post offices; and what the effect on Post Office incomes of this change has been since May 2010.","Biography information for Paul Maynard","Paul Maynard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163636","163636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/915","2013-07-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many respite hours per week parents with children who (a) are autistic, (b) have cerebral palsy and (c) have spina bifida are entitled to.","Biography information for Mr Tom Clarke","Mr Tom Clarke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163659","163659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/916","2013-07-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, which body or authority ultimately determines whether a parent receives any respite hours when coping with a child who has spina bifida.","Biography information for Mr Tom Clarke","Mr Tom Clarke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163660","163660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/917","2013-07-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, which body or authority ultimately determines whether a parent receives any respite hours when coping with a child who has cerebral palsy.","Biography information for Mr Tom Clarke","Mr Tom Clarke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163661","163661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/918","2013-07-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when his Department decided to sell for human consumption beef known to be infected by bovine TB; how much revenue has been earned from such sales to date; and for what reasons such meat is not labelled as having bovine TB.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163663","163663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/919","2013-07-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what progress he has made following the Portas Review on promoting the inclusion of the high street in neighbourhood plans.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163664","163664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/920","2013-07-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what progress he has made following the Portas Review on running a high profile campaign to get people involved in neighbourhood plans.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163665","163665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/921","2013-07-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what progress he has made following the Portas Review on introducing a public register of high street landlords.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163666","163666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/922","2013-07-04","Department for Transport","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions his Department has had with Network Rail regarding freight capacity at UK ports.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163705","163705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/923","2013-07-04","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of local authorities' capacity to match-fund the further £250 million in funding for superfast broadband which has been proposed for 2015.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163643","163643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/924","2013-07-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the average (a) time taken to open the post upon receipt of a letter and (b) time to process and action a letter for Companies House was in each of the last eight quarters; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163644","163644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/925","2013-07-04","Department for Transport","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what proportion of (a) passenger and (b) freight services shifted from road to rail in each year since 1993-94.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163706","163706"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/928","2013-07-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what guidance his Department plans to issue to staff in Jobcentre Plus on advice they can give to unemployed people who are in financial difficulties and are in the seven-day waiting period for jobseeker's allowance on assistance they can access.","Biography information for Mr David Winnick","Mr David Winnick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163715","163715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9325","2013-07-05","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what recent estimate he has made of the number of people sleeping rough in (a) Barnsley Central constituency, (b) South Yorkshire, (c) England and (d) the UK.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163672","163672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9326","2013-07-05","Department for Transport","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many speeding offences have been committed in (a) Barnsley Central constituency and (b) South Yorkshire in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163673","163673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9327","2013-07-05","Department of Health","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he is considering adopting a cap-based solution to the nursery milk scheme.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163674","163674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9328","2013-07-05","HM Treasury","2013-07-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the number of businesses in Barnsley Central constituency who will receive the £2,000 enterprise allowance.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163675","163675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/95","2013-07-09","Department of Health","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions his Department has had with (a) other Government departments, (b) industry representatives, (c) health stakeholders and (d) others on the efficacy of a future policy of fortification of flour with folic acid; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stewart Jackson","Mr Stewart Jackson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163411","163411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9552","2013-07-04","Department for International Development","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how the Government plans to address the endemic nature of corruption through use of the development budget in countries lacking transparency.","Biography information for Naomi Long","Naomi Long","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163656","163656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9553","2013-07-04","Department for International Development","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assistance the Government provides to ethnic Rohingya from Burma who have fled to Bangladesh.","Biography information for Naomi Long","Naomi Long","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163657","163657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9554","2013-07-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what information the Government has relating to the involvement of the (a) Arakan Liberation Party and (b) Rakhine National Development Party in inciting, organising and carrying out attacks against ethnic Rohingya in Burma.","Biography information for Naomi Long","Naomi Long","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163658","163658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9688","2013-07-04","Department for International Development","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether her recent commitment, at the Nutrition for Growth Summit, to increase funding for nutrition specific interventions by eight per cent between 2013 and 2020 will include activities and programmes that focus on water, sanitation and hygiene; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Jim Dobbin","Jim Dobbin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163480","163480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9689","2013-07-04","Department for International Development","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how the financial commitment made at the recent Nutrition for Growth Summit of increased funding of eight per cent between 2013 and 2020 will be broken down across her Department's programmes; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Jim Dobbin","Jim Dobbin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163481","163481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9761","2013-07-05","Department for Transport","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what funding has been allocated to Bikeability cycle training as a result of decisions announced in Spending Round 2013, Cm 8639.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163536","163536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9762","2013-07-08","Cabinet Office","2013-07-02","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many British citizens reside in other EU countries (a) by country and (b) by status of their residence (working, studying or retired).","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163538","163538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9763","2013-07-04","Home Office","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to review the guidance on the standard of English language required by spousal visa applicants.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163601","163601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9764","2013-07-05","Home Office","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many new psychoactive substances were identified by her Department's forensic early warning system at the Glastonbury Festival in (a) 2013, (b) 2012 and (c) 2011.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163612","163612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/9780","2013-07-04","Department for Transport","2013-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many cycling (a) fatalities and (b) serious injuries occurred among (i) adults and (ii) children in each of the last three years; and what proportion of such (A) adults and (B) children was wearing helmets.","Biography information for Annette Brooke","Annette Brooke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163489","163489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10118","2013-07-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how the compliance commitments made in the June 2013 G8 Summit communiqué will be monitored.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163169","163169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10119","2013-07-03","HM Treasury","2013-07-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many unannounced minimum wage inspections were carried out by HM Revenue and Customs on companies located in (a) Newcastle Upon Tyne North constituency, (b) the North East and (c) England in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163197","163197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10120","2013-07-04","HM Treasury","2013-07-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he plans to take to ensure that the Overseas Territories comply with the standards of beneficial ownership agreed at the June 2013 G8 Summit; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163209","163209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10121","2013-07-04","HM Treasury","2013-07-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment he has made of the potential use of VAT avoidance schemes in the public sector; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163225","163225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10122","2013-07-04","HM Treasury","2013-07-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment he has made of the number of NHS trusts in England receiving professional advice on reducing their VAT liability; what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Health on this issue; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163226","163226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10123","2013-07-03","HM Treasury","2013-07-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many notices of minimum wage underpayments were issued by HM Revenue and Customs to companies located in (a) Newcastle Upon Tyne North constituency, (b) the North East and (c) England in each of the last five years; and how many such companies (i) paid within 14 days, (ii) paid within 28 days and (iii) took their case to appeal.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163199","163199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10124","2013-07-03","HM Treasury","2013-07-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many complaints regarding minimum wage non-compliance were received by HM Revenue and Customs regarding companies located in (a) Newcastle Upon Tyne North constituency, (b) the North East and (c) England in each of the last five years; and what proportion of these complaints resulted in prosecutions.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163200","163200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10137","2013-07-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his Palestinian counterpart about Palestinian Authority Television broadcasting songs identifying Israeli cities as Palestinian.","Biography information for Mr James Clappison","Mr James Clappison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163265","163265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10138","2013-07-03","Department for International Development","2013-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much aid her Department contributes annually to (a) Palestinian Authority Television (PATV) and (b) the PATV programme, For You.","Biography information for Mr James Clappison","Mr James Clappison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163266","163266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10202","2013-07-04","Ministry of Justice","2013-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the proposed timescale for identification of the specific site for the North Wales prison is.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163224","163224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10203","2013-07-04","Ministry of Justice","2013-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the total budget is for the North Wales prison project.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163229","163229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10204","2013-07-04","Ministry of Justice","2013-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when work will commence on the building of the new prison in North Wales.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163260","163260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10333","2013-07-05","HM Treasury","2013-07-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when the Government plans to publish the response to the consultation on Alcohol Fraud: legislative measures to tackle existing and emerging threats to the UK alcohol duty regime.","Biography information for Dan Rogerson","Dan Rogerson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163337","163337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10334","2013-07-05","HM Treasury","2013-07-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what legislative proposals the Government plans to bring forward to tackle alcohol duty fraud.","Biography information for Dan Rogerson","Dan Rogerson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163338","163338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10335","2013-07-05","HM Treasury","2013-07-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will publish each response received to the consultation on Alcohol Fraud: legislative measures to tackle existing and emerging threats to the UK alcohol duty regime.","Biography information for Dan Rogerson","Dan Rogerson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163339","163339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10336","2013-07-12","Cabinet Office","2013-07-01","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the fertility rate was in (a) England, (b) each region of England and (c) each local authority area in each year since 2001.","Biography information for Dan Rogerson","Dan Rogerson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163341","163341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10372","2013-07-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether unemployed people aged between 18 and 24 enrolled on the Government's traineeship programme will be eligible to claim jobseeker's allowance for the duration of their traineeship.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163263","163263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10373","2013-07-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate his Department has made of how many young people aged between 18 and 24 will enrol on a traineeship in the academic year 2013-14.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163317","163317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10374","2013-07-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much funding from its apprenticeship and adult skills budget he expects his Department to allocate for the delivery of traineeships in the academic year 2013-14.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163318","163318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10375","2013-07-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Statement by the Chancellor of the Exchequer of 26 June 2013, Official Report, column 315, on the Spending Review, what additional resources his Department plans to provide for the delivery of ESOL provision for jobseekers in receipt of benefit.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163319","163319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10611","2013-07-03","Department for Transport","2013-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 18 June 2013, Official Report, column 593W, on shipping: crew, if he will take steps to ensure that indicative projections of UK seafarer (a) officer and (b) rating numbers appear in the 2013 edition of his Department's annual UK seafarer statistics.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame M. Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163190","163190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/10612","2013-07-03","Department for Transport","2013-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 18 June 2013, Official Report, column 593W, on shipping: crew, for what reasons data on indicative projections of seafarer numbers did not appear in the 2012 edition of his Department's annual UK seafarer statistics; and for what reasons indicative projections of the number of UK seafarers based on current recruitment and retention rates in the industry were not contained in that document.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame M. Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 163191","163191"
