"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755674","2017-09-06","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what plans she has made to replace EU funding to the UK creative sector once the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7069","7069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755675","2017-09-06","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, if she will bring forward proposals to ensure more women are encouraged into sport.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7082","7082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755676","2017-09-06","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how much her Department has contributed to the Digital Scotland Superfast Broadband programme; and what other support her Department has given to the rollout of superfast broadband in Scotland.","Biography information for John Lamont","John Lamont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7202","7202"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755677","2017-09-06","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how many properties in Berwickshire, Roxburgh and Selkirk are estimated not to have access to superfast broadband services.","Biography information for John Lamont","John Lamont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7141","7141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755678","2017-09-06","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how much has been spent on all consultancy services by the Big Lottery Fund in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7227","7227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755679","2017-09-06","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how much has been spent on all consultancy services by the Big Lottery Fund in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7228","7228"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755680","2017-09-06","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how many civil servants are employed by the Big Lottery Fund in each pay scale.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7229","7229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755681","2017-09-06","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how many civil servants are employed by the Big Lottery Fund.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7230","7230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755682","2017-09-06","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how much the Big Lottery Fund has spent on HR consultancy in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7233","7233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755683","2017-09-06","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how much the Big Lottery Fund has spent on HR consultancy in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7234","7234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755684","2017-09-06","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps her Department is taking to ensure competition among providers where fibre optic broadband is rolled out.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7310","7310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755685","2017-09-06","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions she has had with her EU counterparts on long-term broadcast access to the EU for Ofcom-licensed broadcasters based in the UK after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Vicky Ford","Vicky Ford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7298","7298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755686","2017-09-06","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how she plans to keep Parliament informed about the merger of Sky with 21st Century Fox before making her decision on that merger; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7334","7334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755687","2017-09-06","Ministry of Defence","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he plans to make a final decision on the relocation of (a) 614 RAF Auxiliary Squadron, (b) University of Wales Air Squadron, (c) 2300 Air Cadets Squadron, (d) Regional Rehabilitation Unit for Wales and the Midlands and (e) the Band of the Prince of Wales; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7240","7240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755688","2017-09-06","Ministry of Defence","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 27 June 2017 to Question 275, on RAF St Athan, when he plans to publish the impact assessment of (a) 614 RAF Auxiliary Squadron, (b) University of Wales Air Squadron, (c) 2300 Air Cadets Squadron, (d) Regional Rehabilitation Unit for Wales and the Midlands and (e) the Band of the Prince of Wales; and if he will place a copy of that impact assessment in the Library.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7241","7241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755689","2017-09-06","Ministry of Defence","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department has conducted an assessment of the potential effect of the relocation of No. 4 School of Technical Training at St Athan to RAF Cosford on the local economy; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7242","7242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755690","2017-09-06","Ministry of Defence","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 27 June 2017 to Question 275, on RAF St Athan, which organisations will be consulted as part of the impact assessment on the relocation of (a) 614 RAF Auxiliary Squadron, (b) University of Wales Air Squadron, (c) 2300 Air Cadets Squadron, (d) Regional Rehabilitation Unit for Wales and the Midlands and (e) the Band of the Prince of Wales; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7243","7243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755691","2017-09-06","Ministry of Defence","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many aircraft are currently in service on the Queen Elizabeth-class aircraft carrier.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7159","7159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755692","2017-09-06","Ministry of Defence","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the current difference is between the number of serving RAF personnel and the full-time military trained strength of the RAF.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7169","7169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755693","2017-09-06","Ministry of Defence","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps were taken to implement the recommendation set out in para 2.23 of the 2006 Deepcut Review.","Biography information for Douglas Ross","Douglas Ross","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7191","7191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755694","2017-09-06","Ministry of Defence","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will establish a permanent memorial to British servicemen and women who lost their lives in Palestine during the lead-up to Israel's independence.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7073","7073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755695","2017-09-06","Ministry of Defence","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the proportion of time RAF service personnel spend on their military duties at RAF Northolt.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6858","6858"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755696","2017-09-06","Ministry of Defence","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of whether any (a) military or (b) civil aeronautical regulations are currently being breached at RAF Northolt.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6859","6859"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755697","2017-09-06","Ministry of Defence","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the risk to local buildings from larger commercial aircraft using RAF Northolt.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6860","6860"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755698","2017-09-06","Ministry of Defence","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many new Army recruits who joined the Army since January 2017 held a degree level qualification on entry.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6913","6913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755699","2017-09-06","Ministry of Defence","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many new Army recruits who joined the Army since January 2017 held A-level qualifications on entry.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6914","6914"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755700","2017-09-06","Ministry of Defence","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many new Army recruits who joined the Army since January 2017 were from the lowest socio-economic groups.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6915","6915"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755701","2017-09-06","Ministry of Defence","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many new Army recruits who joined the Army since January 2017 were aged between 16 and 24.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6916","6916"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755702","2017-09-06","Ministry of Defence","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many new Army recruits who joined the Army since January 2017 were (a) male and (b) female.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6917","6917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755703","2017-09-06","Ministry of Defence","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many new Army recruits who joined the Army since January 2017 held five GCSEs at Grade A* to C.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6918","6918"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755704","2017-09-06","Ministry of Defence","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 18 July 2017 to Question 4377, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the Abertillery Reserve Centre on recruitment to the armed forces.","Biography information for Nick Smith","Nick Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6957","6957"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755705","2017-09-06","Ministry of Defence","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans he has to deploy Royal Navy ships to the Black Sea for training exercises.","Biography information for Mark Pritchard","Mark Pritchard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6950","6950"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755706","2017-09-06","Ministry of Defence","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the value was of his Department's spend with UK industry in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6942","6942"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755707","2017-09-06","Ministry of Defence","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he has received representations from Aircraft Carrier Alliance prime contractors on utilising a similar procurement model as that to be used to build the planned Royal Fleet Auxiliary Fleet Solid Support ships.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6943","6943"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755708","2017-09-07","Ministry of Defence","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate his Department has made of the total cost to the public purse of the Queen Elizabeth-class aircraft carriers.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6988","6988"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755709","2017-09-07","Ministry of Defence","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 20 July 2017 to Question 5260, on the Navy, whether the personnel numbers targets have changed from SDSR 2015 for each Service; and what the personnel targets are for each Service by 2025.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7013","7013"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755710","2017-09-07","Ministry of Defence","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many P-8 Poseidon Maritime Patrol Aircraft will be purchased.","Biography information for Wayne David","Wayne David","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6994","6994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755711","2017-09-07","Ministry of Defence","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the new P-8 Poseidon Maritime Patrol Aircraft are planned to provide 24-hour cover for the UK's nuclear deterrent and aircraft carriers.","Biography information for Wayne David","Wayne David","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6995","6995"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755712","2017-09-06","Ministry of Defence","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what financial support is currently available for veterans charities to apply for.","Biography information for Ross Thomson","Ross Thomson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7405","7405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755713","2017-09-06","Ministry of Defence","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of when the UK will end its codified role in EU military unification after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Iain Stewart","Iain Stewart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7383","7383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755714","2017-09-06","Department for Education","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans her Department has to introduce the legislative proposals for the establishment of a Sharia-compliant alternative finance product based on the Takaful model before September 2018.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7482","7482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755715","2017-09-06","Department for Education","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what progress her Department has made on the establishment of a Sharia-compliant alternative finance product based on the Takaful model.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7483","7483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755716","2017-09-06","Department for Education","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether the Government plans to include domestic violence and violence against women in the schools curriculum in England and Wales.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7460","7460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755717","2017-09-06","Department for Education","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will revise the home-to-school travel and transport statutory guidance to reduce the mileage thresholds beyond which free transport is provided for pupils.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7467","7467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755718","2017-09-07","Department for Education","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when she expects to set out her plans to implement the recommendations in Sir Adrian Smith's review of post-16 mathematics, published on 20 July 2017.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6990","6990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755719","2017-09-07","Department for Education","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many teachers of the deaf were employed by each unitary and county council in England in each of the last five academic years.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6999","6999"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755720","2017-09-07","Department for Education","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether her Department holds data on the number of rejected EHCP applications in the London Borough of Brent in 2015-16.","Biography information for Dawn Butler","Dawn Butler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7016","7016"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755721","2017-09-06","Department for Education","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to her Oral Statement of 17 July 2017, Official Report, column 565, what savings will be made from healthy pupils capital to increase core schools funding in 2019-20.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6947","6947"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755722","2017-09-06","Department for Education","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to page 49 of the Social Mobility Commission's report, Time for Change: an assessment of government policies on social mobility 1997-2017, published on 28 June 2017, what assessment she has made of the level of (a) retention and (b) graduate outcomes among students from disadvantaged backgrounds.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6879","6879"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755723","2017-09-06","Department for Education","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to page 48 of the Social Mobility Commission's report, Time for Change: an assessment of government policies on social mobility 1997-2017, published on 28 June 2017, what assessment she has made of that report's recommendation to introduce effective incentives to attract and retain good quality teachers in the schools that need them most.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6880","6880"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755724","2017-09-06","Department for Education","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to pages 45-46 of the Social Mobility Commission's report, Time for Change: an assessment of government policies on social mobility 1997-2017, published on 28 June 2017, what assessment she has made of the effect of the focus on evaluating pupils' learning of core content through examinations on levels of stress and anxiety among students.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6881","6881"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755725","2017-09-06","Department for Education","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to page 77 of the Social Mobility Commission's report, Time for Change: an assessment of government policies on social mobility 1997-2017, published on 28 June 2017, what recent assessment she has made of the effect of the increase in the reliance on formal qualifications in some professions on the accessibility of those professions to people from disadvantaged backgrounds.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6882","6882"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755726","2017-09-06","Department for Education","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to pages 77-78 of the Social Mobility Commission's report, Time for Change: an assessment of government policies on social mobility 1997-2017, published on 28 June 2017, what recent assessment she has made of the effect of (a) internships, (b) unpaid internships and (c) unadvertised internships on the accessibility of some jobs to people from disadvantaged backgrounds.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6883","6883"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755727","2017-09-06","Department for Education","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether her Department plans to introduce a disabled student's allowance for students in further education.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6954","6954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755728","2017-09-11","Department for Education","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many teachers have been disciplined under section 406 of the Education Act 1996 in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6982","6982"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755729","2017-09-06","Department for Education","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to page 61 of the Social Mobility Commission's report, Time for Change: an assessment of government policies on social mobility 1997-2017, published on 28 June 2017, what assessment she has made of the effect on the confidence of young people leaving compulsory education of a failure rate for English and mathematics GCSE resits higher than 75 per cent.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6885","6885"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755730","2017-09-06","Department for Education","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to pages 45-46 of the Social Mobility Commission's report, Time for Change: an assessment of government policies on social mobility 1997-2017, published on 28 June 2017, what assessment she has made of the effect of incentives for teachers to maximise test scores within a narrower curriculum on opportunities for social and emotional learning which are accessible to all children.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6886","6886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755731","2017-09-06","Department for Education","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to pages 45-46 of the Social Mobility Commission's report, Time for Change: an assessment of government policies on social mobility 1997-2017, published on 28 June 2017, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of resources available to schools for social and emotional learning activities.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6887","6887"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755732","2017-09-06","Department for Education","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to pages 45-46 of the Social Mobility Commission's report, Time for Change: an assessment of government policies on social mobility 1997-2017, published on 28 June 2017, what assessment she has made of the effect on social mobility of the increase in extra-curricular social and emotional activities where there is a cost attached for parents.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6888","6888"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755733","2017-09-06","Department for Education","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to page 38 of the Social Mobility Commission's report, Time for Change: an assessment of government policies on social mobility 1997-2017, published on 28 June 2017, what assessment she has made of the effect of social geographic isolation on social mobility.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6889","6889"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755734","2017-09-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to page 18 of the Social Mobility Commission's report, Time for Change: an assessment of government policies on social mobility 1997-2017, published on 28 June 2017, what assessment he has made of the effect of poor housing conditions on child development.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6890","6890"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755735","2017-09-06","Department for Education","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to page 18 of the Social Mobility Commission's report, Time for Change: an assessment of government policies on social mobility 1997-2017, published on 28 June 2017, what assessment she has made of the effect on social mobility of changes to funding of programmes that are aimed at parents.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6891","6891"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755736","2017-09-06","Department for Education","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to page 27 of the Social Mobility Commission's report, Time for Change: an assessment of government policies on social mobility 1997-2017, published on 28 June 2017, what assessment she has made of the effect of a wide range of choices for parents on the uptake of vouchers for parenting programmes.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6892","6892"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755737","2017-09-06","Department for Education","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to pages 25-26 of the Social Mobility Commission's report, Time for Change: an assessment of government policies on social mobility 1997-2017, published on 28 June 2017, what assessment she has made of the effect of the level of pay on the number of qualified professionals in the childcare sector.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6893","6893"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755738","2017-09-06","Department for Education","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to page 27 of the Social Mobility Commission's report, Time for Change: an assessment of government policies on social mobility 1997-2017, published on 28 June 2017, what assessment she has made of the effect of the level of resources available to local authorities on their allocation of funding to parenting programmes.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6894","6894"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755739","2017-09-06","Department for Education","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to page 24 of the Social Mobility Commission's report, Time for Change: an assessment of government policies on social mobility 1997-2017, published on 28 June 2017, what steps she is taking to ensure the provision of quality childcare places when the free childcare entitlement increases to 30 hours per week.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6895","6895"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755740","2017-09-06","Department for Education","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to page 25 of the Social Mobility Commission's report, Time for Change: an assessment of government policies on social mobility 1997-2017, published on 28 June 2017, what assessment she has made of the consistency in the range of available qualifications for early years professionals.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6896","6896"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755741","2017-09-06","Department for Education","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to page 23 of the Social Mobility Commission's report, Time for Change: an assessment of government policies on social mobility 1997-2017, published on 28 June 2017, what assessment she has made of the reasons for the relatively low demand for subsidised childcare among the most disadvantaged families.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6897","6897"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755742","2017-09-06","Department for Education","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans she has to ensure girls are encouraged into sport.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7083","7083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755743","2017-09-06","Department for Education","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Answers of 21 April 2017 to Questions 70502 and 70503, on apprentices: Parliament, how much has been paid by the House of Commons and by hon. Members of the House of Commons and Members of the House of Lords.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7075","7075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755744","2017-09-06","Department for Education","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many schools in England currently teach cooking; and how many of those are (a) academies and (b) free schools.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7128","7128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755745","2017-09-06","Department for Education","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Social Mobility Commission Report, Time for Change: an assessment of government policies on social mobility 1997-2017, what steps she is taking to improve teacher retention and continuing professional development.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7212","7212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755746","2017-09-06","Department for Education","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of the number of families unable to access 30 hours free childcare allowance as their chosen registered childminder is a relative.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7190","7190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755747","2017-09-06","Department for Education","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many three and four-year olds benefited from the early years pupil premium in (a) 2016-17 and (b) 2015-16.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7132","7132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755748","2017-09-06","Department for Education","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the take-up rate for early education entitlement in 2016 was for eligible (a) two and (b) three and four-year olds.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7133","7133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755749","2017-09-06","Department for Education","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the total expenditure on the early years pupil premium was in (a) 2016-17 and (b) 2015-16.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7134","7134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755750","2017-09-06","Department for Education","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, for what reasons some universities are limited on the number of students that can be admitted in one academic year for degrees such as medicine.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7222","7222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755751","2017-09-07","Department for Education","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much of the education capital budget was allocated to (a) free schools, (b) academies and (c) maintained schools in each year since 2009-10; and how much is forecast to be spent on each of these school groups for the next three fiscal years.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7208","7208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755752","2017-09-06","Department for Education","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what arrangements are in place in the apprenticeships service account system in relation to payments made through (a) the apprenticeships levy and (b) co-investments to ensure that funding levels for apprenticeships are not negatively affected by macro-economic trends in wage levels.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7213","7213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755753","2017-09-06","Department for Education","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what training is available for teachers to handle or report hate crime in schools.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7203","7203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755754","2017-09-06","Department for Education","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to encourage more young people to work towards a career in the healthcare professions.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7223","7223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755755","2017-09-06","Department for Education","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much her Department has spent on drug education and awareness in schools in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7263","7263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755756","2017-09-07","Department for Education","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and which heads of multi-academy trusts earn more than £150,000 per annum.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7379","7379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755757","2017-09-06","Department for Education","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to page 6 of the Education Policy Institute report, Closing the gap? Trends in educational attainment and disadvantage, published in August 2017, if she will make an assessment of the implications for her policies of the findings that at current trends we estimate that it would take around 50 years for the disadvantage gap to close completely by the time pupils take their GCSEs; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7272","7272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755758","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will bring forward proposals to ensure that sufficient people train as nurses to address any shortfall in NHS nurse provision.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7317","7317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755759","2017-09-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps are being taken at ports to tackle illegal smuggling of puppies and other animals into the UK.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7280","7280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755760","2017-09-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many prosecutions have occurred or proceedings commenced as the result of seizure of illegally imported puppies taken into Dogs Trust's care via its puppy pilot quarantine scheme since the start of that initiative.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7281","7281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755761","2017-09-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will publish the outcome of his Animal Welfare Team's voluntary survey of police forces, local authorities and social landlords on measures to address dog control and to reduce dog attacks in England.","Biography information for Nicky Morgan","Nicky Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7324","7324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755762","2017-09-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what bilateral agreements (a) have been negotiated and (b) are being planned with (i) Spain, (ii) Iceland and (iii) other EU countries with major fishing fleets to address the potential consequences of the UK's withdrawal from the London Fisheries Convention.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7323","7323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755763","2017-09-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to improve measures to prevent the illegal importation of underage puppies after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7268","7268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755764","2017-09-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the introduction of the 5 pence carrier bag charge on the number of carrier bags issued by retailers.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7244","7244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755765","2017-09-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what environmental projects have benefited from the introduction of the 5 pence carrier bag charge.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7245","7245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755766","2017-09-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that national trails are properly signposted.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7246","7246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755767","2017-09-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to promote the use of national trails.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7247","7247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755768","2017-09-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much was allocated to the National Parks in each year since 2010; and how much is projected to be spent in each year up to 2020.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7248","7248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755769","2017-09-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what proportion of food consumed in the UK was imported in each year since 2007.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7103","7103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755770","2017-09-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether his Department has undertaken an impact assessment of the effect on the UK agricultural sector of the UK leaving the single market.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6872","6872"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755771","2017-09-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps the Government plans to take to protect the status of Scottish whisky as a premium product in exports to the US after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for John McNally","John McNally","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6971","6971"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755772","2017-09-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with Welsh Government Ministers on the future of farm subsidies after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6969","6969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755773","2017-09-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to improve the labelling of meat and other animal products to help consumers make an informed decision about welfare standards.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7413","7413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755774","2017-09-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans he has to combine the 25 Year Plan for the Environment with the 25 Year Plan for Food and Farming; whether there will be an opportunity for consultation prior to or after the publication of any individual or combined plan; and whether any such individual or combined plan will apply to England only.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7363","7363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755775","2017-09-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to stop the domestic ivory market.","Biography information for Mims Davies","Mims Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7408","7408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755776","2017-09-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answers of 25 July 2017 to Questions 5342, 5394, 5395 and 5396, what the reasons are for the time taken by the Environment Agency to deal with the site operated by Rowan Oak Waste at Shaw Road in Dudley.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7399","7399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755777","2017-09-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate the Government has made of the change in the level of harmful emissions, such as PM2.5, as a result of more people using wood-burning stoves and chimneys in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7396","7396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755778","2017-09-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the most recent Forestry Commission production forecast is.","Biography information for Jo Churchill","Jo Churchill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7503","7503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755779","2017-09-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he has made an assessment of the potential merits of helping establish a Forest School in Suffolk; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jo Churchill","Jo Churchill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7504","7504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755780","2017-09-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the report, published by the Russian LGBT network on 31 July 2017, on the widespread detention and torture of LGBT people in the North Caucasus republic of Chechnya.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7516","7516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755781","2017-09-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had over the summer recess with the Iranian authorities about the persecution of religious minorities in that country.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7412","7412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755782","2017-09-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his Iranian counterpart on the persecution of Christians and other religious and ethnic minorities in that country.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7404","7404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755783","2017-09-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to investigate the disappearance in Turkey of Gary Burns.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7422","7422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755784","2017-09-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with the Canadian Government on the practice of seal hunting.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7358","7358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755785","2017-09-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his Department has made an assessment of the potential effect on the UK's projection of soft power of the UK leaving (a) Horizon 2020, (b) the Erasmus Plus programme, (c) Marie Sklodowska-Curie actions and (d) Creative Europe; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7344","7344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755786","2017-09-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the likely extent of the continuing use of the English language in European institutions after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7461","7461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755787","2017-09-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations the Government has made to the Burmese authorities on the prison sentence handed down to Niranjan Rasalingham; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Paul Scully","Paul Scully","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6952","6952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755788","2017-09-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the Answer of 2 March 2017 to Question 65626, whether the Government plans to continue to provide quarterly updates to the House on military action against ISIL in Syria during the 2017 Parliament.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7011","7011"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755789","2017-09-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to the Government of Iran on that Government's treatment of Christians.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7009","7009"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755790","2017-09-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what estimate his Department made prior to the EU referendum being held of the administrative and travel costs of renegotiating the UK's membership with the EU.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6987","6987"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755791","2017-09-07","Department for International Trade","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what advice on human rights is given to UK companies doing business in China.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7006","7006"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755792","2017-09-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many UK-based staff of his Department there were in (a) 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012, (d) 2013, (e) 2014, (f) 2015, (g) 2016 and (h) 2017.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7018","7018"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755793","2017-09-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he or his officials have had with the Turkish Government about that country's customs agreement with the EU.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7097","7097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755794","2017-09-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 25 July 2017 to Question 5166, on Mexico: missing persons, what response was provided by the Mexican authorities; if his Department will seek an update on actions taken since the subject was discussed; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7196","7196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755795","2017-09-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, on which date a Minister from his Department last visited the Republic of Tanzania; and what issues were discussed during that visit.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7198","7198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755796","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his Department spends per capita on mental health per year in (a) England and (b) York.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7118","7118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755797","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much the NHS has spent on respiratory medicines in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7167","7167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755798","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many applications there have been for entry to 2017-18 degree courses for (a) physiotherapy, (b) midwifery, (c) occupational therapy,(d) speech and language therapy, (e) dietetics, (f) podiatry, (g) diagnostic radiography, (h) therapeutic radiography, (i) paramedic science, (j) prosthetics and orthotics, (k) orthoptics, (l) art therapy, (m) drama therapy and (n) music therapy.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7168","7168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755799","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps are being taken to improve definitions of myalgic encephalomyelitis for diagnosis.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7179","7179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755800","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what training is provided for doctors to help them treat patients with myalgic encephalomyelitis.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7180","7180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755801","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients received NHS treatment for myalgic encephalomyelitis in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7181","7181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755802","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much funding is provided each year for research into myalgic encephalomyelitis.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7182","7182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755803","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) parents and (b) children have received treatments under the £290 million funding announced in January 2016 for perinatal mental health.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7137","7137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755804","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much of the £290 million funding announced in January 2016 for perinatal mental health has been allocated; and if he will provide a full breakdown of the allocations from that fund made to date.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7136","7136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755805","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the recommended caseload for a community psychiatric nurse is.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7150","7150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755806","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average turnover rate is for community psychiatric nurses.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7151","7151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755807","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department has taken to enact the UK Strategy for Rare Diseases in England.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7170","7170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755808","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients the NHS is treating for multiple sclerosis.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7178","7178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755809","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average waiting time is for (a) a mental health assessment and (b) mental health treatment in (i) England and (ii) York.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7120","7120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755810","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what comparative assessment he has made of the level of staffing available for mental health services in (a) York and (b) England.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7119","7119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755811","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the rate of complete immunisation is for children under the age of four.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7130","7130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755812","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many parents in each year since 2010 have been placed on the family nurse partnership programme.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7131","7131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755813","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people in (a) York Central constituency and (b) the Vale of York Clinical Commissioning Group have been affected by contaminated blood.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7121","7121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755814","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether health visitors are required to (a) inform parents of their entitlement to Healthy Start vouchers and (b) assist them through the application process.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7122","7122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755815","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information on healthy eating is given to parents alongside Healthy Start vouchers.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7123","7123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755816","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what changes have been made to the NHS' cyber security following the cyber attack in May 2017.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7028","7028"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755817","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans his Department has for a specialist drug treatment and recovery pilot programme in the North East.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7238","7238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755818","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much the NHS has spent on healthcare for patients who have been unable to leave hospital due to a lack of adequate adapted housing in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7239","7239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755819","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent steps his Department has taken to ensure that adequate numbers of junior doctors are being trained.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7224","7224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755820","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the latest statistical bulletin published by the Office for National Statistics on deaths related to drug poisoning, what steps he is taking to address the disproportionately high drug mortality rate in the North East.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7218","7218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755821","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, for what reasons his Department is ruling out adding chronic conditions such as cystic fibrosis to the prescription charges exemption list.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7220","7220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755822","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many full-time equivalent occupational therapists working in mental health the NHS has employed in each year since 2006-07.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr  Dan Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7302","7302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755823","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many full-time equivalent physiotherapists working in mental health the NHS has employed in each year since 2006-07.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr  Dan Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7303","7303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755824","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many full-time equivalent social workers working in mental health the NHS has employed in each year since 2006-07.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr  Dan Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7304","7304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755825","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his Department's policy is on its officials engaging with representatives of the tobacco industry.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7335","7335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755826","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many full-time equivalent psychologists have been employed by the NHS in each year since 2006-07.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr  Dan Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7305","7305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755827","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many full-time equivalent psychiatrists have been employed by the NHS in each year since 2006-07.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr  Dan Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7306","7306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755828","2017-09-07","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect on patient care of the requirements for routine outpatient clinics working out of a hospital to advise patients that any prescription must be brought to a regular GP to issue an FP10 prescription to then be taken to a pharmacy.","Biography information for Heidi Allen","Heidi Allen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7381","7381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755829","2017-09-07","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what advice his Department gave to Doncaster and Bassetlaw Hospital Trust on myth busting in public communications during the purdah period of the 2017 General Election..","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7382","7382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755830","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many full-time equivalent mental health nurses have been employed by the NHS in each year since 2006-07.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr  Dan Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7307","7307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755831","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will bring forward proposals to ensure that the 101 and 111 services are accessible to people who suffer from deafness by facilitating the use of text by means of a registration form such as with the 999 service.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7320","7320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755832","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to simplify the continuing health care application process.","Biography information for Richard Benyon","Richard Benyon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7293","7293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755833","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many families seeking continuing healthcare pay for legal support.","Biography information for Richard Benyon","Richard Benyon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7294","7294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755834","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to support the development and growth of smaller and non-London medical schools.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7288","7288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755835","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the official period is for the retention of patient documents.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6870","6870"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755836","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many breaches of guidance on mixed-sex sleeping arrangements occurred in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Sir David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7054","7054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755837","2017-09-07","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps are being taken to fill vacancies in the NHS.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7004","7004"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755838","2017-09-07","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people are in receipt of NHS continuing healthcare in each (a) parliamentary constituency and (b) clinical commissioning group.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6991","6991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755839","2017-09-07","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his Department is doing to improve access to gluten-free food for people with coeliac disease.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6996","6996"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755840","2017-09-07","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his Department is doing to improve recognition of coeliac disease by primary care health services.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6997","6997"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755841","2017-09-07","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he plans to maintain gluten-free prescriptions on the NHS.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6998","6998"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755842","2017-09-07","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to improve the rates of early intervention in treating eating disorders in England.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7010","7010"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755843","2017-09-07","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many continence nurses were employed by each of the 135 acute non-specialist NHS trusts at (a) 31 July 2016 and (b) 31 July 2017.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7002","7002"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755844","2017-09-07","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure all new mothers' mental health problems are identified as early as possible.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr  Dan Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7014","7014"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755845","2017-09-07","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Answer of 8 March 2017 to Question 66737, when he plans to introduce legislative proposals to give single parents with children born through surrogacy the same rights as couples.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6968","6968"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755846","2017-09-07","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make an assessment of the effectiveness of mental health advice given by health care professionals during the antenatal period.","Biography information for Gavin Robinson","Gavin Robinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6974","6974"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755847","2017-09-12","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when the outcome of consultation on expansion of undergraduate medical education will be announced.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6980","6980"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755848","2017-09-12","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what criteria are used to decide where to establish new medical schools.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6981","6981"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755849","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when data obtained by his Department and arms-length bodies from UCAS on the number and profile of applications for entry to medical and nursing courses in 2017-18, specifically by subject, profession and geographical spread, will be released.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7465","7465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755850","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make it his policy to exempt NHS staff from hospital car parking charges when they are at work.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7466","7466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755851","2017-09-07","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he plans to lay before Parliament a remedial order to allow single parents to apply for a parental order following surrogacy.","Biography information for Wayne David","Wayne David","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7451","7451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755852","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, who his Department approached to advise on the membership of the Infected Blood Reference Group; how many (a) people and (b) organisations were invited to attend that group; how many (i) people and (ii) campaigners are members of that group; and if he will publish correspondence which invited members to join that group.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7443","7443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755853","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many meetings the Infected Blood Reference Group has held since its creation; which dates that group met; and if he will publish the minutes of the meetings of that group.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7444","7444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755854","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the size of the training and development budget was for health visitors in England in each of the last five years for which data is available.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7447","7447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755855","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to introduce an equivalent access and waiting time standard for people over 19-years of age who have an eating disorder to that which is in place for people under the age of 19 with such a disorder.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7485","7485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755856","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of recent trends in the (a) size of health visitors' caseloads and (b) duration of each home visit undertaken by health visitors.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7477","7477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755858","2017-09-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether the Government has undertaken an assessment of the potential effect on health of the increase in the use of domestic wood burning stoves and chimneys.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7481","7481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755859","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the level of the take-up of Healthy Start vouchers.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7493","7493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755860","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with Cabinet colleagues on ensuring that UK citizens who (a) are on dialysis and (b) otherwise require healthcare under the European Health Insurance Card system to be arranged for them in the EU before they can travel will be able to continue to receive such care after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7355","7355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755861","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the Government has learned from the implementation of the Mental Health (Care and Treatment) (Scotland) Act 2003; and whether such lessons will influence the future shape of mental health legislation in England and Wales.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7369","7369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755862","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the Government has learned from the implementation of recent changes to mental health and mental capacity legislation in Northern Ireland; and whether such changes will influence the future shape of mental health legislation in England and Wales.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7370","7370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755863","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans the Government has to act upon the recommendations made by the Royal College of Obstetricians and Gynaecologists' report, Each Baby Counts, published in June 2017, to improve maternity care.","Biography information for Mims Davies","Mims Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7417","7417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755864","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect of the relative cost of housing compared with wages in (a) Oxford and (b) Oxfordshire on the ability of Oxford University Hospitals NHS Foundation Trust to recruit nursing staff on a starting salary.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7432","7432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755865","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average starting salary for a nurse is in (a) Oxford city, (b) Oxfordshire and (c) Oxford West and Abingdon constituency.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7433","7433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755866","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that mothers are properly supported following childbirth with their (a) general and (b) mental health.","Biography information for Mims Davies","Mims Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7407","7407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755867","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what effect data for Q1 2017-18 published by NHS England on the access and waiting time standard for people under-19 years of age with eating disorders has on the Government's assessment of its progress against the targets set out in that standard; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7487","7487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755868","2017-09-07","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what her policy is on transactions involving substances listed in Part 3 of Schedule 1A to the Poisons Act 1972 which may be used both as an explosive precursor and as an offensive weapon.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7517","7517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755869","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make an assessment of the merits of introducing a state-funded national resilience programme to provide people with counselling and support in the aftermath of a terrorist attack or other traumatic event.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7402","7402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755870","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what mechanisms are in place to ensure that automated facial recognition software in use by police forces is independently tested for racial accuracy biases.","Biography information for Sir Edward Davey","Sir Edward Davey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7425","7425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755871","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which independent oversight mechanism is responsible for overseeing the police's use of automated facial recognition technology.","Biography information for Sir Edward Davey","Sir Edward Davey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7426","7426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755872","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many visa applications have been received by UK Visas and Immigration in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sir Edward Davey","Sir Edward Davey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7416","7416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755873","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many children have lost a parent to domestic violence in each of the last five years; and what steps have been taken to mitigate the effect of domestic violence on children.","Biography information for Mims Davies","Mims Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7419","7419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755874","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the Government's policy is on (a) continuing membership of the European Health Insurance Card scheme and (b) establishing similar arrangements to those which obtain under that scheme after the UK leaves the EU; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7368","7368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755875","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will publish the value of contracts awarded by her Department and its arms-length bodies to McKinsey & Co in each year since 2013.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7392","7392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755876","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will publish the value of contracts awarded by her Department and its arms-length bodies to McKinsey & Co in each year from 2010 to 2013.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7393","7393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755877","2017-09-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether his Department plans to use GPS tracking or similar monitoring when imposing restraining orders.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7394","7394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755878","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what guidance her Department provides for its caseworkers on (a) the timescale for, (b) the use of discretion in assessing and (c) assessment of the minimum income in applications for spouses to join someone with a legal right to live in the UK, including the timescale, the assessment of minimum income and the application of discretion.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7341","7341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755879","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what her Department's definition of a complex case is with regard to immigration cases; and how the decision is taken for a case not to be subject to the timescale of six months for an immigration decision.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7342","7342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755880","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what guidance her Department uses for assessments of humanitarian protection after refugees have been in the UK for five years; and what that guidance advises on the (a) retention of documents, (b) time to be taken for the process and (c) criteria by which decisions should be made; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7343","7343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755881","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that the Knowledge of Language and Life in the UK test is being correctly used in (a) Bristol and (b) elsewhere.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7340","7340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755882","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she has plans to change the English language requirement for spouse visa applications; and if she will make statement.","Biography information for Judith Cummins","Judith Cummins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7457","7457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755883","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent discussions she has had with the head of the Gangmasters and Labour Abuse Authority (GLAA) on tackling modern slavery in the UK; and what programmes of work her Department undertakes in cooperation with the GLAA.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7476","7476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755884","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications her Department received for refugee family reunion visas on the basis of exceptional compelling compassionate circumstances outside the immigration rules for each country and year since 2010.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7448","7448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755885","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many refugee family reunion visas were granted on the basis of exceptional compelling compassionate circumstances outside the immigration rules for each country and year since 2010.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7449","7449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755886","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many Thai citizens were approved to visit the UK and failed to return to Thailand in 2016.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7445","7445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755887","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when the Biometrics Strategy, due to be published in 2013, will be released.","Biography information for Sir Edward Davey","Sir Edward Davey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7438","7438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755888","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to reduce the number of deaths from illegal drug use in the North East.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7468","7468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755889","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to reduce knife crime.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6949","6949"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755890","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Annual Statistics of Scientific Procedures on Living Animals Great Britain 2015, published by her Department on 20 July 2017, if she will take steps to reduce the breeding and dispatch of animals in the UK and make greater use of cryopreservation to maintain established lines of genetically altered animals for research purposes.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6958","6958"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755891","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she plans to commence the appointment process for the second Independent Anti-Slavery Commissioner; and what criteria will be used to assess applicants.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6955","6955"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755892","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make it a requirement that the recommendations of the Independent Police Complaints Commission following a domestic homicide are binding on all agencies.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6899","6899"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755893","2017-09-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether his Department plans to review the penalties for breach of a restraining order where that order was issued following proven domestic violence.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6902","6902"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755894","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will require police and crime commissioners to report annually on (a) prevention, (b) investigation and (c) post-conviction protection of victims of domestic violence.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6910","6910"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755895","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans she has to review and improve processes of investigation of rape allegations.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6907","6907"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755896","2017-09-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) claims were made to the Criminal Injuries Compensation Authority and (b) such claims were successful in each of the last two years.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6908","6908"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755897","2017-09-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether he plans to bring forward legislative proposals to amend section 41 of the Youth Justice and Criminal Evidence Act 1999 to limit the cross-examination of rape victims about their sexual history.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6905","6905"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755898","2017-09-06","Department for Education","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what progress the Government has made on achieving its aims set out in action 28 of its 2016 to 2020 Strategy on Violence Against Women and Girls.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6946","6946"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755899","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions she has had with FIFA and UEFA on Holocaust education in football clubs.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6939","6939"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755900","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions she has had with FIFA and UEFA on programmes to tackle racism and discrimination in football.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6940","6940"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755901","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions she has had with her European counterparts on racism and discrimination in the Champions League or the Europa League.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6941","6941"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755902","2017-09-07","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the reported figures are on knife crime in each of the last five years in (a) Calderdale, (b) Kirklees, (c) Bradford, (d) Leeds and (e) Wakefield.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7015","7015"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755903","2017-09-07","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much compensation was paid to police officers by (a) Lancashire, (b) Greater Manchester, (c) Cumbria, (d) Merseyside and (e) Cheshire Constabulary in each month between 1 January 2016 and 30 June 2017; how many officers received compensation from each constabulary listed; how much was paid to each police officer; and what the reason was for each award.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7001","7001"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755904","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many asylum support applications are processed within the Government's target times.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7031","7031"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755905","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many asylum seekers fall into destitution or homelessness during the process of their application for refuge in the UK.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7032","7032"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755906","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many section 98 applications submitted from asylum seekers before 3pm receive a reply on the same day.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7033","7033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755907","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many section 95 support applications from asylum seekers are dealt with within 14 days.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7034","7034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755908","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many civil servants process asylum applications; and how many have done so in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7036","7036"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755909","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many straightforward asylum applications are completed within six months.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7035","7035"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755910","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applicants for British citizenship have been waiting three years or more to have their application granted.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6871","6871"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755911","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to page 40 of the Mayor's Office of Policing and Crime's report, The London Knife Crime Strategy, published in June 2017, what assessment she has made of the need for legislative proposals to introduce new knife crime-related community orders.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6877","6877"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755912","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the operation of the contract with Sitel UK for UK Visas and Immigration since its entry into force on 1 June 2017.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6868","6868"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755913","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 20 July 2017 to Question 5241, how many applicants who have paid for her Department's Priority Service have not received a response within the 60 days' time standard in each month for the last five years.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6865","6865"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755914","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 25 July 2017 to Question 5865, whether applicants for settled status will need to have resided legally for a continuous period of five years within the meaning of Article 16(1) and Article 16(2) of the EU Free Movement Directive 2004/38/EC.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6866","6866"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755915","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 25 July 2017 to Question 5865, whether people who currently qualify under the derogation in Article 17 of the EU Free Movement Directive 2004/38/EC will qualify for settled status subject to the same criteria.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6867","6867"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755916","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many visitor visas have been refused to Malawians who wish to visit the UK in each year since 2010.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7351","7351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755917","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions she has had with (a) the Scottish Government and (b) the Scotland-Malawi Partnership on the issue of visitor visas to Malawians.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7349","7349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755918","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many asylum applications from Zimbabwean nationals have been (a) received, (b) granted and (c) refused in each year since 2008.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7352","7352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755919","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many visitor visas have been granted in each year since 2010 to Malawians wishing to visit the UK.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7354","7354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755920","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans her Department has to ensure that it will have the capacity efficiently to process short-term work visas for EU residents in the creative industries wishing to do project work in the UK after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7330","7330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755921","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if her Department will review the UK's drugs policy and take steps to evaluate the effectiveness of the Misuse of Drugs Act 1971.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7217","7217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755922","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made on the effectiveness of its drugs policy on (a) reducing harm, (b) drug related deaths and (c) improving community safety.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7219","7219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755923","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what experiments accounted for the 50 per cent increase in 2016 in the number of experiments on new world monkeys, marmosets and tamarins.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7205","7205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755924","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, for what reasons her Department has blacklisted citizenship applications from applicants who took the TOEIC test through companies accused of fraudulent activities; when those applicants were defrauded by those companies; and what steps she is taking to ensure that those applicants can still apply with an alternative proof of their level of English being of the required standard to process their application fairly.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7221","7221"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755925","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Government's policy paper entitled The United Kingdom's exit from the European Union: safeguarding the position of EU citizens living in the UK and UK nationals living in the EU, published on 26 June 2017, whether the application fees for the various status' announced in that policy paper will be set following consultation; and whether EU citizens will be required to pay such fees each time they transition from one status to another status such as from temporary status to settled status.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7251","7251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755926","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to paragraph 6 of the Government's policy paper entitled The United Kingdom's exit from the European Union: safeguarding the position of EU citizens living in the UK and UK nationals living in the EU, published on 26 June 2017, whether the criteria for whether a person is a qualifying EU citizen will be set out in primary or secondary legislation.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7252","7252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755927","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to paragraph 6 of the Government's policy paper entitled The United Kingdom's exit from the European Union: safeguarding the position of EU citizens living in the UK and UK nationals living in the EU, published on 26 June 2017, what the definition is of five years continuous residence.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7253","7253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755928","2017-09-07","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many times police officers requested permission for squad cars to pursue a moped in (a) 2015 and (b) 2016; and on how many occasions such permission was denied by senior police officers.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7276","7276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755929","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 13 July 2017 to Question 3762, on public buildings: fire prevention, whether her Department collects information on the number of fire and rescue service officers deployed to inspect and audit buildings under the Regulatory Reform (Fire Safety) Order 2005.","Biography information for Chris Williamson","Chris Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7270","7270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755930","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what representations she has received from the creative industries about the provision of cultural and educational permits to EU residents after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7059","7059"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755931","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what breeds of dogs were used in the 325 experiments (basic and applied research) listed in the Annual Statistics of Scientific Procedures on Living Animals, Great Britain 2016, as being carried out on other breeds; and what those dogs were used for.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7085","7085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755932","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the Government is doing to reduce the number of dogs used in experiments on living animals.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7086","7086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755933","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what percentage of settlement visas were processed within 12 weeks in each year since 2005.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7116","7116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755934","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications for settlement visas were received in each year since 2005; and what average time was taken to process such applications.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7114","7114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755935","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications for settlement visas were received using the priority service in each year since 2005; and what average time was taken to process such applications.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7115","7115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755936","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what resources her Department has made available to police forces around the UK to deal with scrambler bikes.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7174","7174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755937","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what resources her Department has made available to Merseyside Police to deal with scrambler bikes.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7171","7171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755938","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what advice her Department gives to local police forces on pursuing people on scrambler bikes.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7172","7172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755939","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what measures her Department is taking to keep scrambler bikes off the streets.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7173","7173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755940","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of settlement visas using the priority service were processed within 12 weeks (a) in each year since 2005 and (b) for each quarter of the last two years.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7117","7117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755941","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she expects to be able to announce the cut-off date for EU citizens to qualify for settled status or temporary status.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7161","7161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755942","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she expects to be able to announce the package of benefits, pensions, healthcare, economic and other rights EU citizens will maintain under the new immigration status.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7162","7162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755943","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans she has to review the minimum income requirements for non-EEA family members.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7163","7163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755944","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how long she expects a decision on settled status to take once an application has been submitted; and whether there will be a maximum waiting limit for such a decision.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7164","7164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755945","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will publish the latest performance data for the 101 service.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7200","7200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755946","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many asylum applications have been (a) granted and (b) refused to Afghan nationals in each year since 2010.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7197","7197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755947","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many transit visas the Government has issued during the last three years in the UK fishing sector.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7192","7192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755948","2017-09-06","House of Commons Commission","2017-09-04","To ask the right hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington, representing the House of Commons Commission, with reference to the Answers of 21 April 2017 to Questions 70502 and 70503, on apprentices: Parliament, whether the House of Commons has declared a levy payment since May 2017.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7074","7074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755949","2017-09-06","House of Commons Commission","2017-09-04","To ask the right hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington, representing the House of Commons Commission, what steps have been taken to ensure the use of British materials in the refurbishment of the Elizabeth Tower and its machinery.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7409","7409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755950","2017-09-06","Department for International Development","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what support the UK has given to the people of (a) Sierra Leone and (b) Freetown after recent flooding.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7446","7446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755951","2017-09-06","Department for International Development","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what discussions her Department has had with the Gangmasters and Labour Abuse Authority on steps to tackle modern slavery.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7478","7478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755952","2017-09-06","Department for International Development","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to support children in countries that benefit from UK aid to have access to high-quality childcare; and what plans she has to support an increase in nursery quality in those countries so that all children are prepared and ready for school at age five.","Biography information for Chris Williamson","Chris Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7500","7500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755953","2017-09-06","Department for International Development","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much her Department spends on combatting modern slavery each year.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7135","7135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755954","2017-09-06","Department for International Development","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what resources her Department has made available to help Sierra Leone in the aftermath of recent flooding and mudslides in that country.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7289","7289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755955","2017-09-06","Department for International Development","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps the Government is taking to work closely with disability-focused organisations to improve the effectiveness of the UK's efforts to enhance access to education for disabled girls in developing countries.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7322","7322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755956","2017-09-06","Department for International Development","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to help meet the aims of Sustainable Development Goal 4.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7321","7321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755957","2017-09-07","Department for International Development","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the recent rise in malaria cases in Delhi, India; and what support her Department is providing to tackle malaria in (a) India and (b) Asia.","Biography information for Paul Scully","Paul Scully","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6979","6979"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755958","2017-09-07","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when he plans to publish the outcome of the consultation on dangerous driving proposals which closed in February 2016.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7005","7005"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755959","2017-09-07","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many appeals against decisions on (a) personal independence payment and (b) employment and support allowance were heard at (i) Blackburn, (ii) Blackpool, (iii) Burnley, (iv) Lancaster and (v) Preston Magistrates' Court in each month between 1 January 2016 and 31 July 2017; and on how many occasions at each venue in each of these months regarding (A) personal independence payment and (B) employment and support allowance hearings were adjourned.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7000","7000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755960","2017-09-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many reports of (a) anti-Semitism, (b) Islamophobia, (c) racism and (d) homophobia by prisoners have been received in the last two years.","Biography information for Ellie Reeves","Ellie Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7019","7019"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755961","2017-09-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what occupational training is available for prisoners; what the criteria are for subscribing to such training; and to what degree any training is oversubscribed.","Biography information for Ellie Reeves","Ellie Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7022","7022"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755962","2017-09-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether there is a national curriculum for prison education.","Biography information for Ellie Reeves","Ellie Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7023","7023"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755963","2017-09-07","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the target time is for the Criminal Injuries Compensation Authority to assess a claim.","Biography information for Meg Hillier","Meg Hillier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7017","7017"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755964","2017-09-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much has been spent on education services in prisons over the last two years.","Biography information for Ellie Reeves","Ellie Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7021","7021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755965","2017-09-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether people convicted for hate crimes receive anti-racist or other relevant education as part of their rehabilitation.","Biography information for Ellie Reeves","Ellie Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7020","7020"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755966","2017-09-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the amount spent on legal fees relating to challenges to tribunal fees since 2013.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7026","7026"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755967","2017-09-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much Civil Service time has been spent on legal challenges to tribunal fees in each year since 2013.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7025","7025"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755968","2017-09-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department has taken to ensure that all prisoners are able to open a bank account.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6933","6933"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755969","2017-09-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners (a) had and (b) have not had a bank account in each year since 2010.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6934","6934"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755970","2017-09-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners have left prison without a bank account in each year since 2010.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6935","6935"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755971","2017-09-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment his Department has made of the effect on the rehabilitation of prisoners of not having a bank account.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6936","6936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755972","2017-09-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what training his Department provides to prison officers to assist prisoners in the opening of bank accounts.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6937","6937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755973","2017-09-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what discussions his Department has had with banks, building societies and savings co-operatives on the introduction of a scheme to help offenders open bank accounts.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6938","6938"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755974","2017-09-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will review the effectiveness of short prison sentences and seek alternatives such as community sentences, electronic tagging and home curfew.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6948","6948"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755975","2017-09-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what information his Department holds on the number of rape victims who were cross-examined about their sexual history during cases tried in the last three years.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6909","6909"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755976","2017-09-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to ensure that changed names or the addresses of victims of domestic violence or abuse are not provided in court-related documents provided to the perpetrator of that violence or abuse.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6911","6911"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755977","2017-09-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to ensure that victims of domestic violence or abuse and their alleged perpetrators shall both have legal representation to avoid direct contact in court proceedings.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6912","6912"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755978","2017-09-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether he will take steps to allow victims of domestic violence or abuse to give evidence either by video link or to be recorded at a separate time to the cross-examination of the accused.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6903","6903"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755979","2017-09-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people convicted of offences of violence against women and girls have been ordered to pay compensation into the Victim Surcharge Fund in each of the last three years; and how many of those offenders (a) paid in full, (b) paid in part and (c) failed to pay.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6904","6904"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755980","2017-09-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how long a victim has following a finding of guilt to make a claim to the Criminal Injuries Compensation Authority.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6900","6900"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755981","2017-09-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether a victim who is aged 16 or under at the time of an offence is eligible to make a claim to the Criminal Injuries Compensation Authority.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6901","6901"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755982","2017-09-07","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many British sign language court interpreters are available in each region in England.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6977","6977"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755983","2017-09-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he plans to take to ensure that victims of domestic violence or abuse are not cross-examined by the alleged perpetrator in a criminal, civil or family court.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6898","6898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755984","2017-09-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what support is provided to prisoners who have an addiction to new psychoactive substances.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6919","6919"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755985","2017-09-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the increase in the use of new psychoactive substances in prisons on reoffending rates.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6920","6920"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755986","2017-09-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many new psychoactive substances have been confiscated in each prison in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6921","6921"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755987","2017-09-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what discussions he has had with the Prisons and Probation Ombudsman on deaths of prisoners in custody as both a direct and indirect result of new psychoactive substances.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6922","6922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755988","2017-09-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many dogs trained to detect new psychoactive substances are deployed at each prison.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6923","6923"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755989","2017-09-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners have undergone mandatory testing for new psychoactive substances since the introduction of testing for such substances.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6924","6924"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755990","2017-09-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will take steps to expand drug testing from substances listed for testing to substances that fall under the definition of a psychoactive substance.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6925","6925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755991","2017-09-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether additional funding is available to prisons to prevent further increases in the use of new psychoactive substances.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6926","6926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755992","2017-09-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what training is provided to prison officers to identify and deal with prisoners' use of new psychoactive substances.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6927","6927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755993","2017-09-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 14 July 2017 to Question 3452, on prisons: education, what oversight is conducted into induction programmes in prisons; and how those programmes are quality assessed.","Biography information for Ellie Reeves","Ellie Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7279","7279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755994","2017-09-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department is taking to help prisons to increase levels of (a) drugs testing and (b) searches for mobile phones.","Biography information for Vicky Ford","Vicky Ford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7299","7299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755995","2017-09-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to address violence in HM Prison Chelmsford.","Biography information for Vicky Ford","Vicky Ford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7300","7300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755996","2017-09-07","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will seek to quash convictions for child prostitution of any victim of child abuse.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7373","7373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755997","2017-09-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many members of staff have been employed in each young offenders institution in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7254","7254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755998","2017-09-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the overall budget has been for each prison operated by (a) HM Prison Service and (b) each prison operator in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7255","7255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/755999","2017-09-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many members of staff have been employed in each prison operated by (a) HM Prison Service and (b) each private prison operator in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7256","7256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756000","2017-09-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many members of staff have been employed in each open prison in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7257","7257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756001","2017-09-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many members of staff have been employed in each women's prison in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7258","7258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756002","2017-09-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many members of staff have been employed in each high security prison in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7259","7259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756003","2017-09-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what plans he has to review sentence levels for driving offences.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7193","7193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756004","2017-09-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many discharge grants were paid in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Will Quince","Will Quince","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7081","7081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756005","2017-09-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much, including administration costs, was spent on the Discharge Grant Scheme in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Will Quince","Will Quince","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7080","7080"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756006","2017-09-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of (a) male and (b) female prisons contains prisoners identified as transgender.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7088","7088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756007","2017-09-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many investigations into the deaths of transgender prisoners the Prisons and Probation Ombudsman investigated in each year since 1997-98.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7087","7087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756008","2017-09-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many complaints related to black and ethnic minority equality issues in prisons the Prisons and Probation Ombudsman received in each year since 1997-98; and what proportion of the estimated black and ethnic minority prison population made a complaint in each year.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7089","7089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756009","2017-09-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many complaints relating to prisons the Prisons and Probation Ombudsman received in each year since 1997-98; and what proportion of the prison population made a complaint in each year.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7090","7090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756010","2017-09-06","Attorney General","2017-09-04","To ask the Attorney General, how many court cases the Government has defended since 2010; and what the cost to the public purse was of each such case.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7101","7101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756011","2017-09-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been found guilty of offences under section 22 of the Gender Recognition Act 2004 in each year since 2004-05; and how many were fined the maximum amount stipulated for that offence.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7091","7091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756012","2017-09-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average length of time taken was in each year since 2004-05 to transfer transgender prisoners who (a) did and (b) did not have a gender recognition certificate to prisons which correspond to the gender they identify as having.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7442","7442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756013","2017-09-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will take steps to ensure that actual bodily harm and grievous bodily harm in a domestic setting are included in sentencing guidelines as an aggravating factor.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7459","7459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756014","2017-09-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many complaints related to transgender equality issues in prisons the Prisons and Probation Ombudsman received in each year since 1997-98; and what those figures represent as a proportion of the estimated transgender prisoner population in each of those years.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7390","7390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756015","2017-09-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether the fact that a child has witnessed domestic violence is taken into account when a family court makes directions in child contact proceedings.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7395","7395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756016","2017-09-06","Northern Ireland Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, with reference to the case Smyth 2017 No. 038954 on legal recognition for humanist marriages in Northern Ireland, what effect the absence of a Northern Ireland Executive has on the Government of Northern Ireland's authority to continue to contest that case; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7486","7486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756017","2017-09-06","Northern Ireland Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what information the Government holds on how much the (a) Department of Finance and Registrar General's Office and (b) Office of the Northern Ireland Attorney General have spent contesting case Smyth 2017 No. 038954 on legal recognition of humanist marriages in Northern Ireland at the (i) High Court and (ii) Court of Appeal.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7484","7484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756018","2017-09-07","Prime Minister","2017-09-04","To ask the Prime Minister, what discussions she has had with the devolved administrations on the terms of reference of an inquiry into the contaminated blood scandal; and if she will publish all correspondence with devolved administrations on that inquiry.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7209","7209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756019","2017-09-06","Prime Minister","2017-09-04","To ask the Prime Minister, on what date she plans to respond to the letter of 12 July 2017 from the hon. Member for Glasgow East inviting her to visit Glasgow.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7296","7296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756020","2017-09-06","Scotland Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what discussions he has had with representatives of the Scottish hospitality sector on the effect of restricted freedom of movement after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7297","7297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756021","2017-09-06","Scotland Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what plans the Government has to deliver an ultra deep water port on the East Coast of Scotland.","Biography information for Andrew Bowie","Andrew Bowie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7194","7194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756022","2017-09-07","Scotland Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, (a) on which date he last met representatives of Citizens Advice Scotland and (b) what issues were discussed.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6983","6983"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756023","2017-09-07","Scotland Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, on which date he last visited a food bank.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6984","6984"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756024","2017-09-07","Scotland Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, whether he plans to visit a food bank in the month of September 2017.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6985","6985"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756025","2017-09-06","Scotland Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, pursuant to the Answer of 17 July 2017 to Question 3978, what the differences were in the advertisements aimed at the different genders.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7439","7439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756026","2017-09-06","Scotland Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, pursuant to the Answer of 17 July 2017 to Question 3978, what age ranges were targeted by his social media spending.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7440","7440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756027","2017-09-06","Scotland Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, whether he has had discussions with the Home Secretary on the visa process for the issue of visas to Malawians visiting the UK; and what representations he has received on that process.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7353","7353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756028","2017-09-06","Department for Transport","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what cost-benefit analysis he has made of the High Speed 2 rolling stock procurement of a (a) mixed fleet of classic compatible and captive and (b) single fleet of classic compatible trains.","Biography information for Iain Stewart","Iain Stewart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7384","7384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756029","2017-09-06","Department for Transport","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to increase the use of electric bicycles as an alternative to commuting by car.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7411","7411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756030","2017-09-06","Department for Transport","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps the Government is taking to promote the use of cycle paths.","Biography information for Mims Davies","Mims Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7420","7420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756031","2017-09-06","Department for Transport","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps the Government is taking to encourage people to use public transport in order to reduce congestion and its associated effect on air quality.","Biography information for Mims Davies","Mims Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7418","7418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756032","2017-09-06","HM Treasury","2017-09-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment has been made of the treatment of electric vehicles with a list price of more than £40,000 under the new vehicle excise duty system on the uptake of electric vehicles.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7434","7434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756033","2017-09-06","Department for Transport","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps the Government is taking to monitor speed limits and ensure that they are appropriate.","Biography information for Mims Davies","Mims Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7424","7424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756034","2017-09-06","Department for Transport","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the impact of interpreting into UK law the EU directives on operator licensing on (a) community transport providers and (b) isolated individuals and rural communities.","Biography information for Mr Ranil Jayawardena","Mr Ranil Jayawardena","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7450","7450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756035","2017-09-07","Department for Transport","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how he plans to ensure the reliability of services for passengers on the East Midlands franchise during the period when the InterCity125 trains are overhauled in 2019 to 2020 as planned in the franchise consultation released on 20 July 2017.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7515","7515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756036","2017-09-07","Department for Transport","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to work with the rail franchises to ensure greater reliability for passengers.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6978","6978"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756037","2017-09-06","Department for Transport","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to his oral statement of 5 July 2017, Official Report, column 153WH, when his Department plans to publish the (a) terms of reference and (b) names of the chair and members of the working party on working conditions in the private hire industry.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6953","6953"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756038","2017-09-06","Department for Transport","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect of the absence of an air quality strategy on the draft national policy statement on airports.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6960","6960"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756039","2017-09-07","Department for Transport","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans he has to lift the ban on flights from the UK to Sharm el-Sheikh, Egypt.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6992","6992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756040","2017-09-07","Department for Transport","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment he has made of safety on international flights to Sharm el-Sheikh.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6993","6993"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756041","2017-09-06","Department for Transport","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the consultation document on East Midlands rail franchise, published in July 2017, whether his Department has considered the effect on the local economy of an increase in the number of fast trains from London to London Luton Airport to four an hour.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Mr Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6862","6862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756042","2017-09-06","Department for Transport","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether consultation on the East Midlands rail franchise will take into account the volume of air passengers at London Luton Airport; and what assessment he has made of the (a) economic, (b) social and (c) environmental merits of improved rail services related to that franchise to that airport.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Mr Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6861","6861"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756043","2017-09-06","Department for Transport","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will implement the recommendation in Appendix 5 of the Gibb Report on electrification of the Uckfield line.","Biography information for Tom Tugendhat","Tom Tugendhat","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7199","7199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756044","2017-09-06","Department for Transport","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department plans to establish minimum requirements which all local authorities must abide by when granting licenses to taxi or private hire vehicle drivers.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7183","7183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756045","2017-09-06","Department for Transport","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if his Department plans to establish a national database of registered taxi and private hire vehicles in conjunction with the DVLA and police.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7184","7184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756046","2017-09-06","Department for Transport","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with the Scottish Government about improvement to the A1.","Biography information for John Lamont","John Lamont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7142","7142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756047","2017-09-06","Department for Transport","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans his Department has to reduce the speed limit for heavy goods vehicles from 56 miles per hour.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7152","7152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756048","2017-09-06","Department for Transport","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions his Department had with the Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs before the announcement of a ban on petrol and diesel vehicles by 2040.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7176","7176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756049","2017-09-06","Department for Transport","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the average cost is of dealing with a fatal road traffic accident on an A road.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7084","7084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756050","2017-09-06","Department for Transport","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if his Department will be launching a New Stations Fund 3.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7109","7109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756051","2017-09-06","Department for Transport","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what funding will be available to York Railway Station to handle HS2 services.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7110","7110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756052","2017-09-06","Department for Transport","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of York Railway Station's capacity to handle HS2 services.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7111","7111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756053","2017-09-06","Department for Transport","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department will be launching a further Better Bus Area programme.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7108","7108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756054","2017-09-06","Department for Transport","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he will announce successful applications to the Highways Maintenance Challenge Fund 2a.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7107","7107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756055","2017-09-06","Department for Transport","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will introduce proposals to make available a free bus pass for people at the age of 60.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7333","7333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756056","2017-09-06","Department for Transport","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the Answer of 20 April 2017 to Question 70178, how much of the £175 million allocated to local highways authorities will be spent on improving road safety on the A19.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7235","7235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756057","2017-09-06","Department for Transport","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the capital spend on transport was per head of population in (a) the North East, (b) Northumberland and (c) Wansbeck constituency in the last 12 months for which figures are available.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7225","7225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756058","2017-09-07","Department for Transport","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what information his Department holds on the (a) number and (b) nature of road traffic incidents recorded at the junction of Harwich Road and the A120 east of Colchester and at Pellens Corner nearby over the last 12 months; and how many times the ambulance service has been required to attend those incidents.","Biography information for Sir Bernard Jenkin","Mr Bernard Jenkin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7374","7374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756059","2017-09-07","Department for Transport","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many Northern Rail trains on the Harrogate line in the last 12 months had two carriages.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7372","7372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756060","2017-09-07","Department for Transport","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the (a) effect on passengers and (b) extent of airlines overbooking flights; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7378","7378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756061","2017-09-06","Wales Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what representations he has made to the Department for Exiting the European Union on continuation of interreg funding for Wales in partnership with Ireland.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7156","7156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756062","2017-09-06","Wales Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport on increasing participation rates of Welsh children in sport.","Biography information for Tonia Antoniazzi","Tonia Antoniazzi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6931","6931"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756063","2017-09-06","Wales Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Health on the adequacy of provision of sport in (a) Gower constituency and (b) Wales to tackle mental health issues in primary school-aged children.","Biography information for Tonia Antoniazzi","Tonia Antoniazzi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6932","6932"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756064","2017-09-06","Women and Equalities","2017-09-04","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, whether she plans to discuss with the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport better representation of women's sport on terrestrial television.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7318","7318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756065","2017-09-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to ensure minimal disruption in the regularity in which claimants in Hull will receive income from their benefits prior to the introduction there of universal credit in 2018.","Biography information for Emma Hardy","Emma Hardy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7316","7316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756066","2017-09-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many breaches of data protection there have been in his Department in each year since 2010; and to which parts of his Department's work those breaches relate.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7291","7291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756067","2017-09-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment his Department made of public transport provision for former Cwmbran Pension Centre staff whose posts will be relocated to North Cardiff.","Biography information for Nick Thomas-Symonds","Nick Thomas-Symonds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7286","7286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756068","2017-09-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the closure of Cwmbran Pension Centre on local communities.","Biography information for Nick Thomas-Symonds","Nick Thomas-Symonds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7287","7287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756069","2017-09-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to increase the proportion of people diagnosed with autism who are in full-time or part-time work.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7308","7308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756070","2017-09-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what consultation was undertaken with staff at Cwmbran Pension Centre before the decision to relocate those staff to North Cardiff.","Biography information for Nick Thomas-Symonds","Nick Thomas-Symonds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7285","7285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756071","2017-09-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many benefits appeals are received by his Department on the basis of correspondence not having been received.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7283","7283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756072","2017-09-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many men and women in the most recent year for which data are available died before they reached state pension age.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7284","7284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756073","2017-09-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many complaints his Department has (a) received and (b) investigated in the last 12 months in each region from women born in the 1950s and affected by changes in state pension age; what criteria are used to determine whether a complaint is investigated; how many such investigations have been completed; and what the anticipated (i) timescale and (ii) cost is of each such investigation under way.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7309","7309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756074","2017-09-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether private sector contractors have any role in the processing of outbound correspondence from his Department.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7282","7282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756075","2017-09-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many sanctions have been issued to claimants who have a registered mental health illness in the last 12 months.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7348","7348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756076","2017-09-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to inform current benefit claimants in Kingston upon Hull West and Hessle constituency that they are entitled to an advance payment to switching to universal credit.","Biography information for Emma Hardy","Emma Hardy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7326","7326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756077","2017-09-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of claimants in Kingston upon Hull West and Hessle constituency who will wait more than 11 weeks to receive any payment from universal credit following its introduction there in 2018.","Biography information for Emma Hardy","Emma Hardy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7329","7329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756078","2017-09-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of claimants in Kingston upon Hull West and Hessle constituency who will wait more than six weeks to receive any payment from universal credit following its introduction there in 2018.","Biography information for Emma Hardy","Emma Hardy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7328","7328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756079","2017-09-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of people in Hull who will claim universal credit when it is introduced there in 2018.","Biography information for Emma Hardy","Emma Hardy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7327","7327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756080","2017-09-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of claimants accessing jobcentre services are (a) long-term unemployed, (b) identified as having additional support needs and (c) identified as having additional employment skills or training needs; what steps his Department has taken to review the needs of long-term unemployed and other claimants with identified needs; and what additional support his Department plans to provide to such claimants as a result of planned jobcentre closures.","Biography information for Lesley Laird","Lesley Laird","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7273","7273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756081","2017-09-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment his Department has made of the effectiveness of regional corporate hubs or shared premises as part of the planned changes to jobcentres.","Biography information for Lesley Laird","Lesley Laird","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7274","7274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756082","2017-09-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the evidential basis is for the jobcentre services in Scotland meeting the Government's criteria of three miles or 20 minutes radius travel distance for claimants to reach a jobcentre; what modes of transport his Department used in its assessment of travel time; what consultation his Department has carried out with claimants affected by proposed jobcentre closures; and what additional support or funding his Department plans to provide to claimants with additional travel costs.","Biography information for Lesley Laird","Lesley Laird","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7275","7275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756083","2017-09-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he plans to respond to the letter of 7 July 2017 from the hon. Member for Glasgow East on the proposed closure of Easterhouse and Parkhead Jobcentres.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7271","7271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756084","2017-09-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, for what reasons there is a seven-day waiting period for universal credit; and what assessment he has made of the effect of that waiting period on a claimant's wellbeing.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7269","7269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756085","2017-09-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what his Department's policy is on paying benefits to claimants who do not have a bank account.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7262","7262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756086","2017-09-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessments have been made of poverty rates among women aged 60 to 62.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7207","7207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756087","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people with Parkinson's disease have been sectioned under the Mental Health Act 1983 in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7143","7143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756088","2017-09-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average length of time is that a jobcentre work coach has available to spend with each claimant at each appointment.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7125","7125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756089","2017-09-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many completed repeat assessments there have been of people with (a) Parkinson's disease, (b) multiple sclerosis, (c) motor neurone disease, (d) rheumatoid arthritis and (e) cystic fibrosis, by year of repeat assessment, since the introduction of personal independence payments in 2013; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7144","7144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756090","2017-09-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people with (a) cystic fibrosis, (b) rheumatoid arthritis, (c) motor neurone disease, (d) multiple sclerosis and (e) Parkinson's disease have qualified for (i) income-related employment and support allowance and (ii) income-related jobseeker's allowance since 2008; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7145","7145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756091","2017-09-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many women over the age of 60 claim jobseeker's allowance at (a) Bridgend Jobcentre and (b) Porthcawl Jobcentre; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7146","7146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756092","2017-09-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many universal credit starts since 1 April 2017 were by recipients of employment and support allowance.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7138","7138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756093","2017-09-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people with Parkinson's disease have had employment and support allowance cancelled after 12 months without undergoing a work capability assessment; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7147","7147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756094","2017-09-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many (a) staff are deployed to respond to complaints received from women born in the 1950s affected by the change to the state pension age and (b) additional staff have been employed to respond to those complaints in each of the last 12 months; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7148","7148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756095","2017-09-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, on what date his Department opened an investigation into complaints made by women born in the 1950s affected by the changes to the state pension age; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7149","7149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756096","2017-09-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what progress has been made towards introducing personalised and tailored employment support for disabled people who are looking for work.","Biography information for Heidi Allen","Heidi Allen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7106","7106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756097","2017-09-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the introduction of universal credit on the take-up of higher education for full-time disabled students.","Biography information for Heidi Allen","Heidi Allen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7105","7105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756098","2017-09-06","Department for Education","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether all families in receipt of universal credit are entitled to free school meals.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7124","7124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756099","2017-09-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many universal credit starts since 1 April 2017 were by individuals with an outstanding employment and support appeal.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7139","7139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756100","2017-09-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of constituents in Gower have had their personal independence payments overturned as a result of (a) mandatory reconsideration and (b) an appeal hearing in each year for which data is available.","Biography information for Tonia Antoniazzi","Tonia Antoniazzi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6928","6928"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756101","2017-09-06","Cabinet Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many and what proportion of constituents in Gower worked in the public sector in each year for which data is available.","Biography information for Tonia Antoniazzi","Tonia Antoniazzi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6929","6929"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756102","2017-09-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if the Government will make an assessment of the findings of the London School of Economics Centre for the Analysis of Social Exclusion report, Does Money Affect Children's Outcome: An Update, published in July 2017.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6878","6878"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756103","2017-09-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps the Government is taking to seek a solution to the problem of hidden costs and charges in pension schemes.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6875","6875"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756104","2017-09-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans the Government has to prevent the practice of pension scheme providers using percentage figures to communicate fees and charges to consumers.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6876","6876"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756105","2017-09-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to page 71 of the Social Mobility Commission's report, Time for Change: an assessment of government policies on social mobility 1997-2017, published on 28 June 2017, what assessment he has made of the effect of welfare reforms and policies encouraging labour market flexibility on (a) rates of labour force participation, (b) job quality, (c) productivity and (d) worker progression.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6884","6884"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756106","2017-09-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the potential future costs of providing transitional financial support for WASPI women until they reach the state pension age.","Biography information for Julian Knight","Julian Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6951","6951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756107","2017-09-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department has taken to ensure that people with a learning disability who are in receipt of jobseeker's allowance have access to additional specialist employment support.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6961","6961"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756108","2017-09-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department takes to ensure that employers have access to the skills and knowledge necessary to employ someone with a learning disability.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6962","6962"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756109","2017-09-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment he has made of the effect of personal independence payments on retention of employment among people with a learning disability.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6963","6963"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756110","2017-09-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to increase employment opportunities for people with a learning disability in (a) the public sector and (b) the wider economy.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6964","6964"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756111","2017-09-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment his Department has made of the costs and benefits of increasing the employment rate of people with a learning disability.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6965","6965"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756112","2017-09-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether he has made an assessment of the effect of jobcentre and Jobcentre Plus closures on the ability of jobcentre users to access job opportunities.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6966","6966"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756113","2017-09-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment was carried out prior to jobcentre and Jobcentre Plus closures on the potential effect of such closures on the levels of (a) poverty and (b) unemployment in the affected areas.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6967","6967"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756114","2017-09-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, (a) on which date he last met Citizens Advice Scotland and (b) what issues were discussed during that meeting.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6986","6986"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756115","2017-09-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Minister for Employment's oral contribution of 19 July 2017, Official Report, column 823, whether trade unions have been informed that no job losses will result from the proposed closure of jobcentres in Scotland; and how many additional staff will be recruited as front line staff and work coaches.","Biography information for Lesley Laird","Lesley Laird","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6975","6975"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756116","2017-09-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he plans to publish the equality impact assessment on jobcentre closures in Scotland; and if he will place a copy of that assessment in the Library.","Biography information for Lesley Laird","Lesley Laird","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6976","6976"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756117","2017-09-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many applicants for (a) employment and support allowance and (b) personal independence payment in North West England requested that their assessments be recorded in the most recent 12 months for which data is available.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7007","7007"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756118","2017-09-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Answer of 5 April 2017 to Question 69482, on work capability assessments, when he expects the results of the pilot to test audio recording of personal independence payment face-to-face assessments to be published.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7003","7003"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756119","2017-09-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much his Department has spent on contracts for delivering work capability assessments in the last year.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7027","7027"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756120","2017-09-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether frontline staff of his Department are required to inform new universal credit claimants of the availability of advance payments of that credit during their waiting period to receive payments of that credit.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7497","7497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756121","2017-09-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of applications for short-term benefit advance were successful in the most recent 12 months for which data is available; and what reasons were given to those people who made such unsuccessful applications in that period.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7498","7498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756122","2017-09-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 17 July 2017 to Question 4515, what assessment he has made of potential transport difficulties experienced by claimants travelling to a different jobcentre from the one they currently attend; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Mrs Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7518","7518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756123","2017-09-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 17 July 2017 to Question 4515, if he will publish the equality analysis referred to; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Mrs Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7519","7519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756124","2017-09-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 17 July 2017 to Question 4515, what estimate his Department has made of the number of claimants living outside Liverpool, Riverside who will be directed to jobcentres in Liverpool, Riverside; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Mrs Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7520","7520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756125","2017-09-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 17 July 2017 to Question 4515, what estimate his Department has made of the number of Liverpool, Riverside  residents who will be directed to different jobcentres than those they currently attend; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Mrs Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7521","7521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756126","2017-09-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many mandatory reconsiderations have taken place for each type of benefit and tax credit; and how many of those reconsiderations overturned the original decision in each of the last 24 months.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7543","7543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756127","2017-09-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many appeals have taken place for each type of benefit and tax credit; and how many of those appeals overturned the original decision in each of the last 24 months.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7544","7544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756128","2017-09-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much additional funding was allocated for loans to compensate full-time disabled students for the loss of access to employment and support allowance since the introduction of universal credit.","Biography information for Heidi Allen","Heidi Allen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7545","7545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756129","2017-09-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to help universal credit claimants avoid getting into debt.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7441","7441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756130","2017-09-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether he plans to undertake an assessment of reasons for the increase in the number of employment and support allowance and personal independence payment appeals in the year ending March 2017.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7480","7480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756131","2017-09-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether there is an older claimant champion employed at (a) Bridgend and (b) Porthcawl Jobcentre; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7474","7474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756132","2017-09-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, which conditions are included within the movement disorders disability category Stat-Xplore sub group; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7475","7475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756133","2017-09-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many applications have been made for alternative payment arrangements under universal credit; and what the outcomes were of those applications.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7494","7494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756134","2017-09-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effect of his Department's policy on the requirement for a current tenancy agreement to be dated within the previous three months on the ability of claimants to successfully claim their full universal credit entitlement.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7495","7495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756135","2017-09-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the (a) total cost incurred by claimants and (b) average cost incurred by each claimant has been of calls to the universal credit helpline in each of the most recent 12 months for which data is available.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7496","7496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756136","2017-09-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what progress his Department has made on enabling new benefit claimants to submit their supporting documents electronically via a secure online portal.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7491","7491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756137","2017-09-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many benefit claimants have taken up the option of signing on by post in each of the last three years; and under what circumstances that option has been exercised by those claimants.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7492","7492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756138","2017-09-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many single homeless people have accessed the main homelessness duty in England in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Sir Edward Davey","Sir Edward Davey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7435","7435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756139","2017-09-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many people in England are currently classified as having intentionally made themselves homeless.","Biography information for Sir Edward Davey","Sir Edward Davey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7436","7436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756140","2017-09-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many people in England had their application to the main homelessness duty refused in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Sir Edward Davey","Sir Edward Davey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7437","7437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756141","2017-09-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many families with children aged below the school leaving age are in receipt of the bereavement support payment; and how many such families have children below the age of (a) 11 and (b) five.","Biography information for Sir Edward Davey","Sir Edward Davey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7427","7427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756142","2017-09-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many families are in receipt of the new bereavement support payment.","Biography information for Sir Edward Davey","Sir Edward Davey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7428","7428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756143","2017-09-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many families without children aged below the school leaving age are in receipt of the bereavement support payment.","Biography information for Sir Edward Davey","Sir Edward Davey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7429","7429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756144","2017-09-06","Department for Transport","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many people are classed as ineligible for a blue badge disabled parking permit and have been awarded 12 points in the planning and following a journey activity of the personal independence payment.","Biography information for Sir Edward Davey","Sir Edward Davey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7430","7430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756145","2017-09-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of claimants had to wait more than 6 weeks before receiving their first payment since universal credit was introduced.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7431","7431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756146","2017-09-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether he plans to make the universal credit helpline free of charge.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7410","7410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756147","2017-09-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many full-time disabled students received disability living allowance or personal independence payment and were in the work-related activity group for income-related employment and support allowance in (a) 2015-16 and (b) 2016-17.","Biography information for Heidi Allen","Heidi Allen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7397","7397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756148","2017-09-06","Department for Education","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the oral Answer of the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Work and Pensions of 6 July 2017, Official Report, column 1297, on the number of people over 60-years old who started apprenticeships, how many of those people were (a) men and (b) women.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7386","7386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756149","2017-09-06","Department for Education","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the oral Answer of the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Work and Pensions of 6 July 2017, Official Report, column 1297, on the number of people over 60-years old who started apprenticeships, what steps her Department is taking to promote apprenticeships for women over 59-years old.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7387","7387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756150","2017-09-06","Department for Education","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the oral contribution of the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Work and Pensions of 5 July 2017, Official Report, column 143WH, on apprenticeships opportunities, how many women over 59-years old her Department estimates will start apprenticeships in each year to 2020-21.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7388","7388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756151","2017-09-06","Department for Education","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the oral contribution of the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Work and Pensions of 5 July 2017, Official Report, column 143WH, on apprenticeships opportunities, how many women over 59-years started apprenticeships in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7389","7389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756152","2017-09-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, on what evidence the decision was taken by his Department to mandate the migration of 65 to 69 year-olds from disability living allowance to personal independence payment.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7356","7356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756153","2017-09-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people aged 65 to 69 have been moved from disability living allowance to personal independence payment.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7357","7357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756154","2017-09-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the potential financial effect on people aged between 65 and 69 who, when mandated to migrate from disability living allowance to personal independence payment, may lose entitlement to mobility elements due to the different criteria of those benefits.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7362","7362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756155","2017-09-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether he plans to introduce a new duty on energy companies to set out a timetable to reduce the number of people on prepayment meters.","Biography information for Patricia Gibson","Patricia Gibson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7400","7400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756156","2017-09-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether he has made an assessment of the potential merits of including low-income families with young children in the core group of those eligible for the Warm Home Discount.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7489","7489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756157","2017-09-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many meetings his Department has had with representatives of the care sector on the payment of sleep-in shifts for care workers.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7452","7452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756158","2017-09-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will publish a position paper on the future of the Competition and Markets Authority and its role in investigating multinational mergers after the UK leaves the EU; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7456","7456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756159","2017-09-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what information his Department holds on how much British steel will be used by BMW to manufacture the e-Mini at Cowley.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7522","7522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756160","2017-09-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what representations he has made to BMW on the use of British steel to construct the e-Mini at Cowley.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7524","7524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756161","2017-09-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate his Department has made of the total revenue generated from the investment by small businesses in the life sciences sector in research and development for 2016-17.","Biography information for Jo Churchill","Jo Churchill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7501","7501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756162","2017-09-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions he has had with the Scottish Government about protecting the Scotch whisky industry when the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7061","7061"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756163","2017-09-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when he plans to publish his Department's paper, Future Capabilities of the UK Steel Sector.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7012","7012"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756164","2017-09-07","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what recent steps she has taken to improve broadband coverage in Gower constituency.","Biography information for Tonia Antoniazzi","Tonia Antoniazzi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6970","6970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756165","2017-09-06","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether her Department has undertaken an impact assessment of the effect on the UK tech sector of the UK leaving the single market.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6873","6873"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756166","2017-09-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of extending the remit of the Groceries Code Adjudicator to cover support for small businesses and farmers that supply supermarkets.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6863","6863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756167","2017-09-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when his Department plans to publish its response to its call for evidence on extending the remit of the Groceries Code Adjudicator.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6864","6864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756168","2017-09-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions he has had with Cabinet colleagues about protecting the Scotch whisky industry when the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7060","7060"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756169","2017-09-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when he will publish the Green Growth Plan.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7070","7070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756170","2017-09-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the Government's policy is for carbon capture and storage.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7071","7071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756171","2017-09-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what discussions his Department had with the Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs before the announcement of a ban on petrol and diesel vehicles by 2040.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7175","7175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756172","2017-09-06","Department for Education","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to page 38 of the Social Mobility Commission Report, Time for Change: an assessment of government policies on social mobility 1997-2017, what assessment she has made of the effect of (a) economic and (b) geographic isolation on social mobility.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7216","7216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756173","2017-09-07","HM Treasury","2017-09-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment the Government has made of the effect of closure of ATMs in rural areas on the economies and communities of those areas.","Biography information for Jamie Stone","Jamie Stone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7371","7371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756174","2017-09-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of providing the Scotch whisky industry with a sectoral deal to promote its competitiveness and growth.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7338","7338"
