"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041285","2019-01-16","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether he plans to publish the Cairncross Review before 31 January 2018.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208215","208215"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041286","2019-01-17","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 20 November 2018 to Question 189764 on Ministry of Justice: Research, if he will publish the central record of his Department's externally commissioned social research.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208324","208324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041287","2019-01-17","Treasury","2019-01-14","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of trends in the level of business rates on the financial viability of small music venues.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208216","208216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041288","2019-01-17","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many hours of education on average each week young people received in each secure training centre in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208325","208325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041289","2019-01-16","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many incidents of segregation have occurred at each secure institution that holds children in each of the last five years for which information is available.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208326","208326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041290","2019-01-16","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many incidents of segregation have occurred at each secure institution that holds children by each ethnic group in each of the last five years for which information is available.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208327","208327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041291","2019-01-16","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many compensation claims were won by prisoners for loss or damage to their property held by the prison service in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208328","208328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041292","2019-01-16","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what research his Department has commissioned on the routes which are used to bring contraband into prisons.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208329","208329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041293","2019-01-17","Treasury","2019-01-14","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether (a) he has and (b) officials of his Department have met with (i) his and (ii) their counterparts in the Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport to discuss extending business rates relief to small music venues.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208217","208217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041294","2019-01-16","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the highest hourly rate paid for legal advice was by (a) his Department and (b) each of his Department's arms length bodies in 2018.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208330","208330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041295","2019-01-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the highest hourly rate paid for legal advice was by (a) his Department and (b) each of his Department's arms length bodies in 2018.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208331","208331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041296","2019-01-16","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what the highest hourly rate paid for legal advice was by (a) his Department and (b) each of his Department's arms length bodies in 2018.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208332","208332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041297","2019-01-16","Department for Education","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the highest hourly rate paid for legal advice was by (a) his Department and (b) each of his Department's arms length bodies in 2018.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208333","208333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041298","2019-01-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the highest hourly rate paid for legal advice was by (a) his Department and (b) each of his Department's arms length bodies in 2018.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208334","208334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041299","2019-01-16","Department for Education","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the highest hourly rate paid for legal advice was by (a) his Department and (b) each of his Department's arms length bodies in 2018.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208335","208335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041300","2019-01-16","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what the highest hourly rate paid for legal advice was by (a) his Department and (b) each of his Department's arms length bodies in 2018.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208336","208336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041301","2019-01-17","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of the 20  November 2018 to Question 191955 on Forensic Science: Misconduct, what steps are being taken to establish how many civil and family court cases may have been affected by manipulation; and what steps the police plan to take to determine whether such manipulation took place.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208337","208337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041302","2019-01-16","Department for International Development","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what the highest hourly rate paid for legal advice was by (a) her Department and (b) each of her Department's arms length bodies in 2018.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208338","208338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041303","2019-01-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to increase plastic reprocessing in the UK.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208239","208239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041304","2019-01-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to reduce the amount of waste that the UK exports.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208240","208240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041305","2019-01-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make an assessment of the effect of Prescription Ordering Direct services' ability to deny or delay repeat prescription requests from patients with lifelong or long-term illnesses or diseases for whom their GP has always previously and continues to prescribe such medication on the health of such patients.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208241","208241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041306","2019-01-17","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to Answer of 11 January 2019 to Question 206287 on Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government: Oral Questions, for what reason the Government decided to transfer responsibility for children's services to the Department for Education.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208218","208218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041307","2019-01-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his Brazilian counterpart on LGBT+ rights in that country.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208219","208219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041308","2019-01-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of effect on Guatemala of that country's withdrawal from the International Commission Against Impunity in Guatemala.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208220","208220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041309","2019-01-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his Chinese counterpart on the recent bilateral discussions with the North Korean leader.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208221","208221"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041310","2019-01-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his counterpart in the Philippines on the safety of human rights defenders in that country.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208222","208222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041311","2019-01-17","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps the Civil and Family Courts Service is taking to identify cases where decisions were taken on the basis of forensic testing provided by (a) Randox and (b) Trimega.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208339","208339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041312","2019-01-17","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department is taking to provide public information on the right of people to apply for a C650 Application notice to vary or set aside an order in relation to children as a result of the manipulation of forensic tests.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208340","208340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041313","2019-01-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to reduce NHS waiting times in (a) Oxfordshire and (b) England.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208341","208341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041314","2019-01-17","Home Office","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether it remains his Department's policy to consider an asylum-seeker's claim for asylum less favourably if that person did not claim asylum in the first safe country they reached; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208342","208342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041315","2019-01-17","Home Office","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps his is taking to ensure a smooth transition in the transfer of asylum accommodation contracts; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208242","208242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041316","2019-01-17","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, when he plans to respond to the request made in November 2018 by hon. Members representing Birmingham to meet to discuss his instruction to Birmingham City Council prohibiting further access to its reserves.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208199","208199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041317","2019-01-16","Treasury","2019-01-14","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 19 December 2018 to Question 203920 on Customs, what completion dates have been set for the contracts for the (a) development and (b) upgrade of IT systems in relation to customs declarations at British ports.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208243","208243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041318","2019-01-16","Department for Transport","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will publish the assessments that the Government has commissioned since the 2016 EU referendum on the effect of additional customs checks at Dover of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208244","208244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041319","2019-01-16","Treasury","2019-01-14","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 29 October 2018 to Question 185078 on Revenue and Customs: Blockchain, what assessment he has made of the (a)  time and (b) cost resources required to be allocated by HMRC to produce blockchain solutions to facilitate (a) Authorised Economic Operator status, (b) Rules of Origin certification, (c) the Single Administrative Document and (d) standard import and export declarations.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208245","208245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041320","2019-01-16","Treasury","2019-01-14","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of the use of Blockchain technology on tackling the illegal traffic of goods across the border between (a) Northern Ireland and the Republic of Ireland and (b) Northern Ireland and the rest of the UK after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208246","208246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041321","2019-01-16","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate his Department has made of the number and proportion of female prisoners in England and Wales who committed an offence to support the drug use of someone else for which they received a prison sentence in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208343","208343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041322","2019-01-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what information his Department holds on which UK-supplied military equipment has been used by Turkey in Syria.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208344","208344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041323","2019-01-17","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether UK-supplied military equipment has been used by Israel in the Occupied Palestinian Territories since February 2018.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208345","208345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041324","2019-01-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans his Department has to restore regular reporting of mental health spend to the NHS Dashboard.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208247","208247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041325","2019-01-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, for what reason there is no reference to maternal postnatal checks in the NHS Long Term Plan, and what plans his Department has to introduce such checks for new mothers.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208248","208248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041326","2019-01-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to page 38 of his Department's document of 5 November 2018, Prevention is better than cure, our vision to help you live well for longer, what progress he is making on considering the best available evidence of what a health in all policies approach could look like.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208249","208249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041327","2019-01-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to  paragraph 2.3 of the NHS Long Term Plan, published in January 2019, what funding he plans to provide to the NHS to deliver the new commitments for action to improve prevention.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208250","208250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041328","2019-01-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to his speech at the Charity Commission's annual meeting on 7 January 2017, The shared society, what steps the Government has taken to reduce mental health stigma since July 2016.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208251","208251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041329","2019-01-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the letter to him of 27 September 2018 from Marom UK on Marom Budapest and its community centre Aurora, what response he has made to that letter.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208346","208346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041330","2019-01-16","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what post-legislative scrutiny of the Sexual Offences Act 2003 the Government has undertaken; and when he plans to review Section 21 of that Act.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208347","208347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041331","2019-01-17","House of Commons Commission","2019-01-14","To ask the right hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington, representing the House of Commons Commission, how much money is now owed by (a) hon. Members and (b) former hon Members for unpaid catering and hospitality bills at the House of Commons (i) in total, and (ii) as a proportion of the turnover of catering and hospitality in the House of Commons; and what steps the Commission is taking to ensure the collection of those debts.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208188","208188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041332","2019-01-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the (a) level of violence and (b) number of arrests currently occurring in Sudan.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208189","208189"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041333","2019-01-17","Home Office","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how long it is taking on average to process applications made by EU nationals to the pilot EU settled status scheme.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208223","208223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041334","2019-01-17","Treasury","2019-01-14","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the oral contribution on the motion on Section 13(1)(b) of the European Union (Withdrawal) Act 2018 on 10 January 2019, Official Report, Column 574, what technology proposals the Government has received on establishing a frictionless border between the UK and the EU.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208348","208348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041335","2019-01-17","Treasury","2019-01-14","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the oral contribution on the motion on Section 13(1)(b) of the European Union (Withdrawal) Act 2018 on 10th January 2019, Official Report, Column 574, whether he has received expert advice on the feasibility of technology solutions to create a frictionless border in Northern Ireland whilst facilitating a different customs arrangement between the UK and the EU than exists at present.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208349","208349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041336","2019-01-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many child and adolescent mental health in-patient beds there were in England in each year from 2009 to 2018 inclusive.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr Dan Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208252","208252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041337","2019-01-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many child and adolescent mental health in-patient beds there were in London in each year from 2009 to 2018 inclusive.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr Dan Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208253","208253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041338","2019-01-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many child and adolescent mental health in-patient beds there have been in Norfolk and Suffolk in each year from 2009 to 2018 inclusive.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr Dan Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208254","208254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041339","2019-01-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government on reducing rates of drug dependency among homeless people; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr Dan Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208255","208255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041340","2019-01-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government on reducing rates of alcohol dependency among homeless people; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr Dan Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208256","208256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041341","2019-01-16","Department for International Development","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what discussions she has had with the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care on facilitating health professionals in England to travel to low and middle income countries to provide healthcare education and training; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr Dan Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208257","208257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041342","2019-01-16","Department for International Development","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is taking to improve mental health provision in low and middle income countries.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr Dan Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208258","208258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041343","2019-01-17","Cabinet Office","2019-01-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, which government strategic suppliers have provided living wills.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208200","208200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041345","2019-01-17","Treasury","2019-01-14","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many candidates in addition to Bill Dodwell were interviewed for the role of Tax Director of the Office of Tax Simplification.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208201","208201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041346","2019-01-16","Treasury","2019-01-14","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to his Department's press release entitled The Chancellor and the Office of Tax Simplification announce Bill Dodwell as new Tax Director, published on gov.uk on 10 January 2019, whether the newly appointed Tax Director of the Office of Tax Simplification was approached about the role while he was still under contract with Deloitte.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208202","208202"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041347","2019-01-17","Cabinet Office","2019-01-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when the previous holder of the role of Crown Representative to Small and Medium-sized Enterprises left that role.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208203","208203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041348","2019-01-17","Cabinet Office","2019-01-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether the military planners sent to Departments to prepare for the UK leaving the EU without a deal are answerable to the Ministers of those Departments.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208204","208204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041349","2019-01-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 11 January 2019 to Question 206400 on Beverage Containers: Recycling, if he will (a) set a target for recycling over 90 percent of drinks containers of all shapes as suggested in the Scottish consultation and (b) make an assessment of the need for a deposit return system that includes containers of all shapes, sizes and materials to achieve such a target.","Biography information for Steve Double","Steve Double","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208351","208351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041350","2019-01-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations the UK Government is making and to whom on behalf of British citizens who travelled to Syria for humanitarian, personal or religious reasons and have subsequently been trapped within Daesh territory.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208352","208352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041351","2019-01-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 11 January 2019 to Question 206400 on Beverage Containers: Recycling, what assessment he has made of (a) the effectiveness of deposit return systems in operation in other countries; and (b) the merits of the Norwegian environmental tax on recyclable plastic bottles.","Biography information for Steve Double","Steve Double","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208353","208353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041352","2019-01-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how much his Department is spending on a public information campaign to prepare people for the potential effects of the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Jo Swinson","Jo Swinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208224","208224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041353","2019-01-17","Department for International Development","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much her Department is spending on a public information campaign to prepare people for the potential effects of the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Jo Swinson","Jo Swinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208259","208259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041354","2019-01-17","Home Office","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to Answer of 10 December 2018 to Question 198924 on Immigration: EU Nationals, which private sector organisations could be involved in the use of the data.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208354","208354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041355","2019-01-17","Department for Education","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether schools in Scotland receive funding from his Department for English children who attend those schools.","Biography information for Anne-Marie Trevelyan","Anne-Marie Trevelyan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208355","208355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041356","2019-01-17","Home Office","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to Answer of 27 November 2018 to Question 181253 on Deportation: Windrush Generation; what evidence he has sought to inform his decision not to make a specific attempt to inform those 49 people of the existence of the Windrush Taskforce; if he will make it his policy to attempt to inform them; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208260","208260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041357","2019-01-17","Home Office","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment he has made of trends in the level of unsolved crime in (a) Coventry, (b) the West Midlands and (c) the UK.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208190","208190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041358","2019-01-16","Department for Education","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the average waiting time was for a child to be assessed for an Education, Health and Care Plan after receiving a diagnosis of autism spectrum disorder in (a) the London Borough of Lewisham, (b) London and (c) England in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208356","208356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041359","2019-01-17","Treasury","2019-01-14","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the announcement that the Peterlee HMRC office closure will be delayed, which other HMRC offices will have their closures delayed; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208357","208357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041360","2019-01-17","Department for Education","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to increase the number of men working in early years education.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208191","208191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041361","2019-01-17","Home Office","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether any changes have been made to the operational roll-out of Operation Gull in Northern Ireland as an Immigration Enforcement intelligence led operation in the past two months.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208205","208205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041362","2019-01-17","Treasury","2019-01-14","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer,  when the most recent meeting was held under the auspices of the Border Delivery Group with ports and airports in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208206","208206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041363","2019-01-17","Home Office","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate his Department has made of the total number of alcohol-related crimes committed in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208192","208192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041364","2019-01-17","Department for Education","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the effect on the public purse of replacing university maintenance grants with larger maintenance loans in every year since that change was introduced in 2016-17.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208358","208358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041365","2019-01-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has held with representatives of the Government of Thailand on the political situation in that country.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208193","208193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041366","2019-01-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate her Department has made of the number of applications for carer's allowance by individuals whose dependent has no recourse to public funds which have not been approved in (a) Lewisham Deptford constituency, (b) the London Borough of Lewisham and (c) London in each year of the last five years.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208359","208359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041367","2019-01-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment his Department has made of trends in the number of migrants attempting to cross the Mediterranean from Libya.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208194","208194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041368","2019-01-17","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many officials in his Department are assigned to work on fire safety and issues related to the Grenfell Tower fire.","Biography information for Sarah Jones","Sarah Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208360","208360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041369","2019-01-17","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what conclusions he has made on the extent of non-ACM flammable cladding in high rise buildings following the Government’s recent research on that subject.","Biography information for Sarah Jones","Sarah Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208361","208361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041370","2019-01-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he has taken to ensure the continued supply of medical food in the event of the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208261","208261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041371","2019-01-17","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, when the findings of the Government's commissioned research into non-ACM flammable cladding will be published.","Biography information for Sarah Jones","Sarah Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208362","208362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041372","2019-01-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of medical food supplies in the event of the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208262","208262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041373","2019-01-17","Home Office","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what information his Department holds on the number of fires involving buildings below 18 metres in height that were (i) clad and (ii) insulated with combustible building materials in each year for which information is available.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208263","208263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041375","2019-01-17","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether his Department has made an assessment of the future difficulties that may potentially arise from the ban on combustible cladding when buildings are subject to change of use, such as a non-residential building changing to a multi-occupancy dwelling.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208264","208264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041376","2019-01-17","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2019-01-14","To ask the hon. Member for Houghton and Sunderland South, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what recent discussions the Electoral Commission has had with the Minister for the Cabinet Office on the investigatory powers of the Electoral Commission.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208265","208265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041377","2019-01-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the Indonesian Government on the escalation of violence in West Papua at the end of 2018 and the beginning of 2019.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208364","208364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041378","2019-01-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department plans to review the 2010 Equality Act to ensure that there are sufficient protections for people who have mental ill health.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208266","208266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041379","2019-01-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether the Government has plans to respond to the report entitled, Review of Survivor Benefits in Occupational Pension Schemes, published in June 2014.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208267","208267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041380","2019-01-17","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, for what reason the Press Recognition Panel was added to his Ministerial responsibilities; and what assessment he has made of the effect of that decision on the work of the Panel.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208225","208225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041381","2019-01-17","Department for Transport","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 189742 to Question 189742 on Motorcycles: Safety, when he plans to publish the refreshed Road Safety Statement.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208365","208365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041382","2019-01-17","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what his Department's policy is on challenging incursions into Gibraltar Territorial Waters by Spanish state vessels.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208207","208207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041383","2019-01-17","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what actions UK (a) armed forces units and (b) vessels are permitted to take in order to challenge incursions into Gibraltar Territorial Waters by Spanish state vessels.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208208","208208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041384","2019-01-17","Department for Transport","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 10 January 2019 to Question 205973 on Airports: Unmanned Air Vehicles, what consultations the Government undertook prior to implementing the 400 ft height and 1 km radius exclusion zone on the use of drones adjacent to airports.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208366","208366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041385","2019-01-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the average length of time is from submission of an application under the renewable heat incentive scheme for the installation of a biomass boiler to a final decision being made on that application.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208367","208367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041386","2019-01-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many outstanding decision notices on applications under the renewable heat incentive scheme for the installation of a biomass boiler there are in (a) Scotland and (b) Kilmarnock and Loudoun constituency.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208368","208368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041387","2019-01-17","Treasury","2019-01-14","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much has been spent on designing the commemorative 50p coin to mark the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208268","208268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041388","2019-01-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how much his Department spent on gifts for members of the Royal Family to disburse in each year since 2009.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208209","208209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041389","2019-01-17","Treasury","2019-01-14","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans the Royal Mint have for the commemorative 50p coin to mark the UK leaving the EU in the event that the date of the UK leaving the EU is postponed.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208269","208269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041390","2019-01-17","Cabinet Office","2019-01-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much his Department spent on gifts for members of the Royal Family to disburse in each year since 2009.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208226","208226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041391","2019-01-17","Cabinet Office","2019-01-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, which (a) towns or cities and (b) other bodies have sought permission from his Department to use the word Royal in a proposed name since 1 January 2014; and which of those requests for permission have been (i) approved and (ii) refused.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208227","208227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041392","2019-01-17","Cabinet Office","2019-01-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what criteria his Department apply when determining whether to grant permission to an external body seeking to use the word Royal in a proposed name.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208228","208228"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041393","2019-01-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what discussions she has had with Plumbing Pensions (UK) Ltd on its decision to issue section 75 employer debt notices to employers who have participated in the Plumbing & Mechanical Services (UK) Industry Pension Scheme and according to that scheme’s records have triggered a section 75 employer debt; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208369","208369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041394","2019-01-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many ESA50 forms were issued by her Department to residents of Bristol South constituency in each month from June to November 2017.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208370","208370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041395","2019-01-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many ESA50 forms were returned to her Department by residents of Bristol South constituency in each month from June to November 2017.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208371","208371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041396","2019-01-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate her Department has made of the number of businesses affected by the issuing of section 75 employer debt notices by Plumbing Pensions (UK) Ltd to employers who have participated in the Plumbing & Mechanical Services (UK) Industry Pension Scheme and according to that scheme’s records have triggered a section 75 employer debts; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208372","208372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041397","2019-01-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many UC50 forms were issued by her Department to residents of Bristol South constituency in each month from June to November 2018.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208373","208373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041398","2019-01-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many UC50 forms were returned to her Department by residents of Bristol South constituency in each month from June to November 2018.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208374","208374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041399","2019-01-16","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will publish the in-year spending for the programmes listed in the Defence Equipment Plan 2017 as (a) Ajax, (b) Apache CSP, (c) Astute Boats 4-7, (d) Brimstone 2 Integration, (e) Brimstone CSP, (f) BVRAAM on Lightning II, (g) FASGW(H)/Sea Venom, (h) FASGW(L)/Martlet, (i) Sea Ceptor Type 23, (j) Sea Ceptor Type 26, (k) Spear Cap 3, (l) SRAAM Sustainment (MG1), (m) SRAAM Sustainment (MG2), (n) Core Production Capability, (o) Dreadnought, (p) Lightning II, (q) Marshall, (r) New Style of IT (Deployed), (s) P-8A Poseidon, (t) Protector, (u) QE Carriers, (v) Sky Sabre, (w) Tide-class Tanker, (x) Type 26 Frigate, (y) Meteor Integration (Typhoon), (z) Meteor Integration (Typhoon), (i) Brimstone 2 Integration (Typhoon) and (ii) Warrior CSP; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208229","208229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041400","2019-01-16","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will publish the in-year spending for the programmes listed in the Defence Equipment Plan 2018 as (a) Ajax, (b) Apache CSP, (c) Brimstone CSP, (d) BVRAAM on Lightning II, (e) FASGW(H)/Sea Venom, (f) FASGW(L)/Martlet, (g) Sea Ceptor Type 23, (h) Sea Ceptor Type 26, (i) Spear Cap 3, (j) ASRAAM Sustainment (MG1), (k) ASRAAM Sustainment (MG2), (l) Lightning II, (m) Marshall, (n) P-8A Poseidon, (o) Protector, (p) QE Carriers, (q) Sky Sabre, (r) Tide-class Tanker, (s) Type 26 Frigate, (t) Meteor Integration (Typhoon), (u) Meteor Integration (Typhoon), (v) Brimstone 2 Integration (Typhoon), (w) Warrior CSP (x) Dreadnought  (y) Astute Boats 4-7 (z) Core Production Capability; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208230","208230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041401","2019-01-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what proportion of children aged five had at least one missing, decayed or filled tooth in each of the last eight years .","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208231","208231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041402","2019-01-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if the Office for Product Safety and Standards will investigate the manufacture, importation and installation of notice boards in schools, colleges and universities that are not fire safe compliant with European BS EN 13501 class B standard; and if he will publish the results of that investigation.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208195","208195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041403","2019-01-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if the Health and Safety Executive will undertake an investigation to determine whether notice boards in workplaces including schools, colleges, universities and care homes meet fire safety standards; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208196","208196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041404","2019-01-17","Department for Education","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will conduct a comparative fire risk assessment of school notice boards which meet European BS EN 13501 (a) class B and (b) class E standard; and if he will publish the results of that assessment.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208197","208197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041405","2019-01-16","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, who the 11 organisations are that Victim Support will be working with to provide support for those bereaved by murder and manslaughter.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208270","208270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041406","2019-01-17","Treasury","2019-01-14","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether it is his Department’s policy to provide additional fiscal support to providers of public services should their costs change as a result of the UK leaving the EU without a deal and if (a) such inflationary effects have not been compensated by the Treasury and (b) the funding commitments referred to in response to Question 206791 have been deployed in full.","Biography information for Kirsty Blackman","Kirsty Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208271","208271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041407","2019-01-16","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many staff at (a) HM Inspectorate of Prisons, (b) HM Inspectorate of Probation, (c) HM Prison Service, (d) HM Prison and Probation Service and (e) Prison Service Pay Review body that work (i) inside and (ii) outside Greater London are paid at a rate below the London Living Wage.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208375","208375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041408","2019-01-16","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many staff at (a) HM Inspectorate of Prisons, (b) HM Inspectorate of Probation, (c) HM Prison Service, (d) HM Prison and Probation Service and (e) Prison Service Pay Review body that work (i) inside and (ii) outside Greater London are paid at a rate below the Real Living Wage.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208376","208376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041409","2019-01-17","Wales Office","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what discussions his Department had with the Prime Minister's office on the content of the Prime Minister's Brexit speech in Stoke-on-Trent on 14 January 2019.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208210","208210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041410","2019-01-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many staff at (a) Care Quality Commission, (b) Health Education England, (c) Health Research Authority, (d) Medicines and Healthcare Products Regulatory Agency and (e) NHS England that work (i) inside and (ii) outside Greater London are paid at a rate below the London Living Wage.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208377","208377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041411","2019-01-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many staff at (a) Care Quality Commission, (b) Health Education England, (c) Health Research Authority, (d) Medicines and Healthcare Products Regulatory Agency and (e) NHS England that work (i) inside and (ii) outside Greater London are paid at a rate below the Real Living Wage.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208378","208378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041412","2019-01-16","Cabinet Office","2019-01-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many staff at the (a) Boundary Commission for England, (b) Boundary Commission for Northern Ireland, (c) Crown Commercial Service, (d) Government Property Agency and (e) Privy Council Office (i) inside and (ii) outside Greater London are paid at a rate below the London Living Wage.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208379","208379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041413","2019-01-16","Cabinet Office","2019-01-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many staff at the (a) Boundary Commission for England, (b) Boundary Commission for Northern Ireland, (c) Crown Commercial Service, (d) Government Property Agency and (e) Privy Council Office (i) inside and (ii) outside Greater London are paid at a rate below the Real Living Wage.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208380","208380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041414","2019-01-16","Treasury","2019-01-14","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, when HMRC plans to reach an agreement with the Roadchef Employee Benefit Trust on outstanding tax issues.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208381","208381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041415","2019-01-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many staff at (a) Companies House, (b) the Insolvency Service, (c) the Intellectual Property Service (d) the Met Office and (e) the UK Space Agency (i) inside and (ii) outside Greater London are paid at a rate below the London Living Wage.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208382","208382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041416","2019-01-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many staff at (a) Companies House, (b) the Insolvency Service , (c) the Intellectual Property Service, (d) the Met Office and (e) the UK Space Agency (i) inside and (ii) outside Greater London are paid at a rate below the Real Living Wage.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208383","208383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041417","2019-01-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what proportion of the NHS England budget was spent on business rates in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208384","208384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041418","2019-01-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much his Department has spent on (a) taxis, (b) first class train tickets and (c) business class air travel in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208385","208385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041419","2019-01-16","Home Office","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much his Department has spent on (a) taxis, (b) first class train tickets and (c) business class air travel in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208386","208386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041420","2019-01-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how much his Department has spent on (a) taxis, (b) first class train tickets and (c) business class air travel in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208387","208387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041421","2019-01-16","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how much his Department has spent on (a) taxis, (b) first class train tickets and (c) business class air travel in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208388","208388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041422","2019-01-17","Department for Transport","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the status is of the application made under the Access for All programme in relation to Goring and Streatley station.","Biography information for John Howell","John Howell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208272","208272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041423","2019-01-16","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how much private (a) schools and (b) hospitals claimed in business rate relief in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208389","208389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041424","2019-01-16","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how many staff at (a) Arts Council England, (b) Big Lottery Fund, (c) the British Film Institute, (d) the British Library and (e) the British Museum (i) inside and (ii) outside Greater London are paid at a rate below the London Living Wage.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208390","208390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041425","2019-01-16","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether his Department plans to publish updated guidance on Traveller accommodation needs assessments following the withdrawal of the 2007 guidance in 2016.","Biography information for Lee Rowley","Lee Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208391","208391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041426","2019-01-16","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how many staff at (a) Arts Council England, (b) Big Lottery Fund, (c) the British Film Institute, (d) the British Library and (e) the British Museum (i) inside and (ii) outside Greater London are paid at a rate below the Real Living Wage.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208392","208392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041427","2019-01-16","Home Office","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many children have been (a) transferred to the UK and (b) allocated a place but not yet been transferred to the UK under section 67 of the Immigration Act 2016.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208393","208393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041428","2019-01-16","Home Office","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the timetable is for the UK to fulfill its commitment on transferring 480 children to the UK under section 67 of the Immigration Act 2016.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208394","208394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041429","2019-01-16","Home Office","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many offers of placements his Department has received from local authorities with the capacity to look after unaccompanied asylum-seeking children.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208395","208395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041430","2019-01-16","Department for Transport","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent steps the (a) Government and (b) DVLA has taken to ensure that people over 70 are assessed to ensure safety when driving.","Biography information for Lesley Laird","Lesley Laird","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208396","208396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041431","2019-01-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps she is taking to celebrate the achievements of people with learning disabilities and autism (a) in employment and (b) outside of employment.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Mitchell","Mr Andrew Mitchell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208211","208211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041432","2019-01-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will urgently introduce regional parity of financial support for victims of the infected blood scandal.","Biography information for Paul Girvan","Paul Girvan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208397","208397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041433","2019-01-16","Department for Education","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many staff at the (a) Education and Skills Funding Agency, (b) Equality and Human Rights Commission, (c) Standards and Testing Agency, (d) Student Loans Company and (e) Teaching Regulation Agency (i) inside and (ii) outside Greater London are paid at a rate below the London Living Wage.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208398","208398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041434","2019-01-16","Department for Education","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many staff at the (a) Education and Skills Funding Agency, (b) Equality and Human Rights Commission, (c) Standards and Testing Agency, (d) Student Loans Company and (e) Teaching Regulation Agency (i) inside and (ii) outside Greater London are paid at a rate below the Real Living Wage.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208399","208399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041435","2019-01-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care,whether it is his policy that the responsibility for the delivery of compensation to victims of the infected blood scandal lies with his Department due to that scandal having occurred prior to the establishment of devolved departments of health.","Biography information for Paul Girvan","Paul Girvan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208400","208400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041436","2019-01-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate his Department has made of the number of children who have been diagnosed with autism in (a) Lewisham Deptford constituency, (b) the London Borough of Lewisham and (c) London in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208401","208401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041437","2019-01-16","Department for Education","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether his Department has made an assessment of the effects of overcrowded living conditions on children with special educational needs.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208402","208402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041438","2019-01-16","Northern Ireland Office","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, whether it is the Government's policy that victims in Northern Ireland of the infected blood scandal deserve as a matter of urgency the same financial recognition as those in Scotland, England and Wales due to the scandal having taken place under direct rule; and if she will meet representatives from Haemophilia Northern Ireland to discuss their concerns.","Biography information for Paul Girvan","Paul Girvan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208403","208403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041439","2019-01-16","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department plans to take to resolve the matter of around £25 million a year being allocated from the public purse to rent disused, derelict and abandoned married quarters.","Biography information for Scott Mann","Scott Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208404","208404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041440","2019-01-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what estimate his Department has made of the number of British citizens who have died abroad as a result of (a) murder and (b) manslaughter in each year since 2000.","Biography information for Hannah Bardell","Hannah Bardell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208405","208405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041441","2019-01-16","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will take steps to honour and commemorate the 30 British soldiers who died in Germany in 1921 and 1922 while implementing conditions of the Treaty of Versailles and who lie in unmarked graves in Opole in Poland by asking the Commonwealth War Graves Commission to undertake the marking of their graves.","Biography information for Scott Mann","Scott Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208406","208406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041442","2019-01-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many staff at the (a) Agriculture and Horticulture Development Board, (b) Animal and Plant Health Agency, (c) Centre for Environment, Fisheries and Aquaculture Science, (d) Rural Payments Agency and (e) Veterinary Medicines Doctorate (i) inside and (ii) outside Greater London are paid at a rate below the London Living Wage.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208407","208407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041443","2019-01-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what criteria his Department uses to determine the allocation of fishing opportunities.","Biography information for Scott Mann","Scott Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208408","208408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041444","2019-01-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what data her Department holds on the reasons given for non-attendance by sanctioned claimants of (a) jobseekers allowance and (b) employment support allowance in (i) Lewisham Deptford constituency, (ii) the London Borough of Lewisham and (iii) London in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208409","208409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041445","2019-01-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment the Government has made of the effect of changes to the Nutrient Profile Model on the likely intake of Vitamin D and calcium by children and young adults.","Biography information for Scott Mann","Scott Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208410","208410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041446","2019-01-16","Department for International Development","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many staff at the (a) Commonwealth Scholarship Commission in the UK, (b) Independent Commission for Aid Impact and (c) Government Equalities Office that work (i) inside and (ii) outside Greater London are paid at a rate below the London Living Wage.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208411","208411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041447","2019-01-16","Department for International Development","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many staff at the (a) Commonwealth Scholarship Commission in the UK, (b) Independent Commission for Aid Impact and (c) Government Equalities Office that work (i) inside and (ii) outside Greater London are paid at a rate below the Real Living Wage.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208412","208412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041448","2019-01-17","Department for Education","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many students aged 16 to 19 are eligible for (a) free school meals and (b) free meals in further education.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208413","208413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041449","2019-01-16","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he has taken to upgrade the existing runway and install new Arrestor Beds to comply with military aeronautical authority regulations at RAF Northolt; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208184","208184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041450","2019-01-17","Home Office","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Government's white paper on The UK’s future skills-based immigration system, published in December 2018, whether he plans to introduce a second immigration Bill to implement the proposals contained in that White Paper.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208426","208426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041451","2019-01-17","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether units in the Royal Navy or Royal Marines receive regular training in the use and operation of paintball weapons.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208212","208212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041452","2019-01-16","Treasury","2019-01-14","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what funding allocation Scotland will receive as a result of Barnett formula determinations on spending in preparation for the UK leaving the EU without a withdrawal agreement.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208273","208273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041453","2019-01-16","Department for Transport","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 16 April 2018 to Question 134899 on Motor Vehicles: Lighting, whether the review of the technical requirements been published.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208414","208414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041454","2019-01-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Answer of 9 January 2019 to Question 205829, Children; Maintenance, how many non-compliant parents were disqualified from holding or obtaining a UK passport in (a) 2016, (b) 2017 and (c) 2018.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208213","208213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041455","2019-01-16","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what recent discussions has his Department has with the Local Government Association on funding for local authorities.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208274","208274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041456","2019-01-16","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that (a) tenants of social housing feel safe and (b) people carrying out antisocial behaviour are reprimanded.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208275","208275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041457","2019-01-16","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to help people with mobility issues to find properties that meet their needs.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208276","208276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041458","2019-01-16","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether his Department takes steps to tackle the use of drugs in social housing; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208277","208277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041459","2019-01-16","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to provide support to families affected by domestic abuse.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208278","208278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041460","2019-01-16","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether his Department has a policy of replacing fire alarms every few years in its properties.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208279","208279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041461","2019-01-16","Department for Education","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether his Department is taking steps to provide counselling for students in schools.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208280","208280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041462","2019-01-16","Department for Education","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to help provide classes for students with special needs in the schools of their choice.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208281","208281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041463","2019-01-16","Department for Education","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much money was paid back from student loan repayments in each of the last three years.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208282","208282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041464","2019-01-16","Department for Education","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many students have taken up apprenticeships in each region in each of the last three years.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208283","208283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041465","2019-01-16","Department for Education","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many students did not get a grade 9-4 in their GCSE results in the 2017-18 academic year.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208284","208284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041466","2019-01-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the safety of escape rooms in the UK following deaths in a Polish escape room on 6 January 2019.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208427","208427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041467","2019-01-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans his Department has to support the Northumbrian lamb industry in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal and tariffs on its products are imposed.","Biography information for Anne-Marie Trevelyan","Anne-Marie Trevelyan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208415","208415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041468","2019-01-16","Home Office","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what advice he provides operators of escape rooms on fire safety and evacuation procedures in the event of a fire in locked rooms.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208428","208428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041469","2019-01-16","Home Office","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what advice he has provided to fire authorities on fire safety in escape rooms.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208429","208429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041470","2019-01-17","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Written Statement on 29 November 2018 on Grenfell update, HCWS1126, how much money his Department has allocated to support local authorities in undertaking emergency remedial work to remediate unsafe aluminium composite material cladding.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208285","208285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041471","2019-01-17","Home Office","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications for permanent residence documents by EU Citizens exercising treaty rights as self-sufficient people or students have been refused on the grounds of the applicant not having comprehensive sickness insurance.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208416","208416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041472","2019-01-16","Department for Transport","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans his Department has for the onward cascade and transfer of rolling stock between train operators in the event that there are delays to the delivery and introduction of new trains.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208286","208286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041473","2019-01-16","Department for Transport","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect on performance of the number of new trains planned to be introduced across the rail network between 2019 and 2021.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208287","208287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041474","2019-01-16","Department for Transport","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what meetings his Department has held with freight operating companies on the potential need for additional freight services from Folkestone, Dover and other ports in the south of England.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208288","208288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041475","2019-01-16","Department for Transport","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, (a) how much his Department has spent and (b) what progress his Department has made on the introduction of smart ticketing technology across the railway in (a) 2016 (b) 2017 and (c) 2018.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208289","208289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041476","2019-01-17","Home Office","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, on what grounds the requirement for an EU Citizen to hold comprehensive sickness insurance while exercising their treaty rights as a self-sufficient person or student may be waived in respect of applications for permanent residence documents.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208417","208417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041477","2019-01-17","Treasury","2019-01-14","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many (a) large and (b)medium-sized companies have used HMRC's profit diversion compliance facility in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208290","208290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041478","2019-01-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what specific consideration is given to the effect of (a) PTSD and (b) other mental health issues when assessing the needs of veterans.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208418","208418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041479","2019-01-16","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what criteria his Department used to select the prisons included in the 10 Prison Programme.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208419","208419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041480","2019-01-17","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether military planners have been seconded to other Departments to prepare for the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208420","208420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041481","2019-01-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many staff in his Department are working on his Department’s plans for the UK to leave the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208421","208421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041482","2019-01-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations his Department has made to the Government of Turkey on its international obligations to maintain human rights.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208291","208291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041483","2019-01-17","Northern Ireland Office","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what estimate her Department has made of the amount of funding Northern Ireland has received from (a) grants from the EU and (b) loans from the European Investment Bank since 1998.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208292","208292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041484","2019-01-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate it has made of the amount of money spent by businesses in the 4th Quarter of 2018 on preparing for leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208422","208422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041485","2019-01-17","Wales Office","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how many meetings he has had with the First Minister of Wales since the Welsh Assembly voted to reject the Withdrawal Agreement on 4 December 2018.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208423","208423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041486","2019-01-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to page 51 of the NHS Long Term Plan, when his Department plans to (a) start and (b) complete the roll-out the new CAMHS model for 0-25-year olds.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208293","208293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041487","2019-01-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to page 51 of the NHS Long Term Plan, how what estimate he has made of the cost of the roll-out of the new CAMHS model for 0-25-year olds.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208294","208294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041488","2019-01-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 11 January 2018 to Question 206308 on Pregnancy: Mental Health Services, what funding his Departmental will make available for the expansion in perinatal services under the NHS Long Term Plan.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208295","208295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041635","2019-01-17","Department for Education","2019-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the recommendations in the November 2018 report of the All-Party Parliamentary Group for International Students entitled A Sustainable future for international students in the UK, what plans his Department has to set an international student growth strategy focused on recruitment and student experience.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208880","208880"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039550","2019-01-15","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many non-disclosure agreements his Department entered into in 2006.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207554","207554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039551","2019-01-15","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many non-disclosure agreements his Department entered into in 2007.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207570","207570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039552","2019-01-15","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many non-disclosure agreements his Department entered into in 2008.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207571","207571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039553","2019-01-15","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many non-disclosure agreements his Department entered into in 2009.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207572","207572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039554","2019-01-15","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many non-disclosure agreements his Department entered into in 2010.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207573","207573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039555","2019-01-15","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many non-disclosure agreements his Department entered into in 2011.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207574","207574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039556","2019-01-15","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many non-disclosure agreements his Department entered into in 2012.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207575","207575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039557","2019-01-15","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many non-disclosure agreements his Department entered into in 2005.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207576","207576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039558","2019-01-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to page 6 of the NHS Long-Term Plan, whether the right of every patient to have an online digital GP consultation will be added to the NHS constitution.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207577","207577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039559","2019-01-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to page 6 of the NHS Long-Term Plan, what estimate has he made of the proportion of online GP consultations that will be carried out by private providers that do not currently provide NHS services.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207578","207578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039560","2019-01-15","Department for Transport","2019-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the report entitled, Southern Rail Link to Heathrow Market Sounding, published by his Department in December 2018, what progress his Department has made on the publication of a (a) process and (b) timeframe in relation to the (i) development and (ii) completion of a Southern Rail Link to Heathrow.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207579","207579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039561","2019-01-15","Department for Transport","2019-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with the Chancellor of the Exchequer on funding for the next stage of development of the Southern Rail Link to Heathrow.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207580","207580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039562","2019-01-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the number of patients who have (a) used Immunotherapy treatments under the NHS and (b) had Immunotherapy treatments ended after two years in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207581","207581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039563","2019-01-15","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many young offenders have been kept in solitary confinement for 22 hours a day in each Young Offenders Institution in the last month for which figures are available.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207582","207582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039564","2019-01-15","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of young offenders in each Young Offenders Institution were allowed (a) weekly visits, (b) a visit every two weeks and (c) more than one visit a week in the last calendar month for which figures are available.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207583","207583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039565","2019-01-16","Department for Transport","2019-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to his Department's news story, Government confirms £173.5 million funding to improve transport in Leeds, published on 21 April 2017, whether that funding can be spent beyond April 2021 on a specific transport project that has already commenced.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207602","207602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039566","2019-01-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate his Department has made of the cost to local authorities of the collection and disposal of packaging waste.","Biography information for Anna McMorrin","Anna McMorrin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207603","207603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039567","2019-01-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when his Department plans to publish its consultation on introducing consistent recyclable packaging material funded by Extended Producer Responsibility.","Biography information for Anna McMorrin","Anna McMorrin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207604","207604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039568","2019-01-15","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2019-01-11","To ask the hon. Member for Houghton and Sunderland South, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, pursuant to the Answer of 7 January 2019 to Question 203928 and the Answer of 8 January 2019 to Question 205307, on Political Parties, Elections and Referendums Act 2000: Fines, if the Speaker's Committee will undertake a review of whether it is an appropriate and proportionate enforcement policy practice by the Electoral Commission for a political party to be fined £6,000 for submitting a quarterly reporting one day after the deadline.","Biography information for Luke Hall","Luke Hall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207584","207584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039569","2019-01-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the security, justice and reconciliation Programme in Iraq assists in the prosecution of individuals in Iraq’s criminal and counter-terrorism courts.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207540","207540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039570","2019-01-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the effectiveness of the Overseas Security and Justice Assistance assessment made in respect of the Security, Justice and Reconciliation Programme in Iraq; and if he will lay that assessment before Parliament.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207541","207541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039571","2019-01-16","Home Office","2019-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the number of home visits that the police have made to registered sex offenders in the last 12 months for which figures are available.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207585","207585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039572","2019-01-15","Department for Transport","2019-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department plans to review the law governing the maximum power of undipped headlights on motor vehicles.","Biography information for Jamie Stone","Jamie Stone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207605","207605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039573","2019-01-15","Department for Transport","2019-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department plans to review the law on adding additional headlights to vehicles.","Biography information for Jamie Stone","Jamie Stone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207606","207606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039574","2019-01-16","Home Office","2019-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 7 January 2019  to Question 203400, whether he has met the NPCC Brexit Implementation Team on contingency planning for the UK leaving the EU without a deal in his capacity as Secretary of State.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207586","207586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039575","2019-01-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what guidance her Department has given to Jobcentre staff on EEA Nationals’ entitlement to universal credit.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207587","207587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039576","2019-01-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what guidance her Department has issued to Jobcentre staff on when it is appropriate to ask that an EEA national sit a habitual residency test when applying for universal credit.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207588","207588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039577","2019-01-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of EEA national applicants have been refused universal credit in each year for which information is available.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207589","207589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039578","2019-01-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of EEA National universal credit applicants have been asked to sit a habitual residency test in each year for which information is available.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207590","207590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039579","2019-01-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether any other Givernment Departments are informed when EEA nationals are unable to pass the Habitual Residency Test to facilitate (a) changes in immigration status and (b) other consequences.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207591","207591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039580","2019-01-16","Department for Education","2019-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment his Department has made of the level of preparedness of schools in response to the risk of cyber attacks.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207555","207555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039581","2019-01-16","Home Office","2019-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 10 January to Question 206043 on Undocumented Migrants: Boats, for what reason his Department does not routinely publish that data; and if he will make it his policy to publish that data routinely.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207607","207607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039582","2019-01-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to (a) reduce the number of child soldiers and (b) prevent the recruitment of new child soldiers.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207556","207556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039583","2019-01-16","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what estimate his Department has made of the number of football stadiums in the UK nominated for designation as assets of community value under the Localism Act 2011 that have been judged by a local authority not to meet the test for being such an asset.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207557","207557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039584","2019-01-16","Home Office","2019-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what requests for additional funding his Department has received from the NPCC Brexit Contingency Planning Team for the safety net model to be implemented in readiness for the UK leaving the EU; and how much additional funding that equates to for each police force area.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207608","207608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039585","2019-01-16","Department for International Trade","2019-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, pursuant to the Answer of 10 January to Question 205795 on Department for International Trade: Brexit, when his Department plans to publish the data transparency releases referred to in that answer.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207542","207542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039586","2019-01-16","Department for Education","2019-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to raise awareness of alternatives to higher education among school leavers.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207558","207558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039587","2019-01-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 10 January to Question 205797 on Department of Health and Social Care: Brexit, when his Department plans to publish the data transparency releases referred to in that answer.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207543","207543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039588","2019-01-15","Cabinet Office","2019-01-11","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 10 January to Question 205794 on Cabinet Office: Brexit, when his Department plans to publish the data transparency releases referred to in that answer.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207544","207544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039589","2019-01-15","Treasury","2019-01-11","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 10 January to Question 205796 on Treasury: Brexit, when his Department plans to publish the data transparency releases referred to in that answer.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207545","207545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039590","2019-01-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to involve people with learning disabilities and autism in the development of mandatory training for NHS staff.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207559","207559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039591","2019-01-16","Home Office","2019-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) officers and (b) staff from (i) police forces, (ii) the National Crime Agency and (iii) the national Criminal Records Office are staffing the Brexit Contingency Planning team; and what assumptions have been made on the number of police officers needed to respond to the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207609","207609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039592","2019-01-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many cases her Department has passed to the Jointly Managed Engagement Team for HMRC to clarify earnings with employers where there has been a dispute reported through RTI in each month since 2016.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207610","207610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039593","2019-01-16","Treasury","2019-01-11","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much money from the public purse has been (a) spent and (b) allocated for preparations for the UK leaving the EU without a deal to date; how much of that funding has been made by way of ministerial direction; and for what functions that funding has been allocated.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207546","207546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039594","2019-01-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much money his Department has allocated for preparations for the UK leaving the EU without a deal to date; how much of that funding has been made by way of ministerial direction; and for what functions that funding has been allocated.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207547","207547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039595","2019-01-16","Northern Ireland Office","2019-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how much money his Department has allocated for preparations for the UK leaving the EU without a deal to date; how much of that funding has been made by way of ministerial direction; and for what functions that funding has been allocated.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207548","207548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039596","2019-01-15","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 2 November 2018 to Question 185063 on armed forces: coroners, what the timetable is for the consultation on whether to publish those protocols; and if his Department will publish the pre-Section 104 Order protocols between the Ministry of Justice, the Ministry of Defence, the Scottish Government and the Chief Coroner on dealing with military deaths in Scotland separately.","Biography information for Martin Docherty-Hughes","Martin Docherty-Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207592","207592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039597","2019-01-15","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence he will publish more details on the timescale and implementation for the Defence Policy Board as set out in his Department’s report on the Modernising Defence Programme in December 2018; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Martin Docherty-Hughes","Martin Docherty-Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207593","207593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039598","2019-01-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how much money his Department has allocated for preparations for the UK leaving the EU without a deal to date; how much of that funding has been made by way of ministerial direction; and for what functions that funding has been allocated.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207549","207549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039599","2019-01-16","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much money his Department has allocated for preparations for the UK leaving the EU without a deal to date; how much of that funding has been made by way of ministerial direction; and for what functions that funding has been allocated.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207550","207550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039600","2019-01-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much money her Department has allocated for preparations for the UK leaving the EU without a deal to date; how much of that funding has been made by way of ministerial direction; and for what functions that funding has been allocated.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207551","207551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039601","2019-01-15","Home Office","2019-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much money his Department has allocated for preparations for the UK leaving the EU without a deal to date; how much of that funding has been made by way of ministerial direction; and for what functions that funding has been allocated.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207552","207552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039602","2019-01-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much money his Department has allocated for preparations for the UK leaving the EU without a deal to date; how much of that funding has been made by way of ministerial direction; and for what functions that funding has been allocated.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207553","207553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039603","2019-01-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with French authorities on travel by migrants and asylum-seekers across the English Channel.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207560","207560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039604","2019-01-15","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how much money his Department has allocated for preparations for the UK leaving the EU without a deal to date; how much of that funding has been made by way of ministerial direction; and for what functions that funding has been allocated.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207561","207561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039605","2019-01-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions has he had with his counterpart in (a) Morocco, (b) Algeria and (c) Libya about migrants and asylum-seekers crossing the Mediterranean.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207562","207562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039606","2019-01-15","Department for Education","2019-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much money his Department has allocated for preparations for the UK leaving the EU without a deal to date; how much of that funding has been made by way of ministerial direction; and for what functions that funding has been allocated.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207563","207563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039607","2019-01-15","Scotland Office","2019-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how much money his Department has allocated for preparations for the UK leaving the EU without a deal to date; how much of that funding has been made by way of ministerial direction; and for what functions that funding has been allocated.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207564","207564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039608","2019-01-15","Wales Office","2019-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how much money his Department has allocated for preparations for the UK leaving the EU without a deal to date; how much of that funding has been made by way of ministerial direction; and for what functions that funding has been allocated.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207565","207565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039609","2019-01-16","Department for Education","2019-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, for what reason the funding allocation for the early years pupil premium in the dedicated schools grant has fallen from £50.0 million in 2015-16 to £28.1 million in 2019-20 while the hourly rate has remained 53p.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207611","207611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039610","2019-01-16","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent assessment he has made of the re-offending rate in relation to prison sentences of (a) less than six months and (b) more than six months.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207566","207566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039611","2019-01-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment he has made of the number of prisoners who have reported a drug or alcohol misuse problem upon arrival at prison in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207567","207567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039612","2019-01-16","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the number and proportion of prisoners serving sentences of less than six months who are homeless upon release in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207568","207568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039613","2019-01-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure the forthcoming social care green paper will address social care provision for adults of working age with a disability.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207569","207569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039614","2019-01-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people requested a mandatory reconsideration for (a) universal credit and (b) PIP in 2018; and how many of those mandatory reconsiderations resulted in changed outcomes.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207594","207594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039615","2019-01-15","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many non-disclosure agreements his Department entered into in 2013.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207595","207595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039616","2019-01-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many families (a) will and (b) will not be exempt from the two-child tax credit cap in (i) Motherwell and Wishaw, (ii) North Lanarkshire and (iii) Scotland.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207596","207596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039617","2019-01-15","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many non-disclosure agreements his Department entered into in 2014.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207597","207597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039618","2019-01-15","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many non-disclosure agreements his Department entered into in 2015.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207598","207598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039619","2019-01-15","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many non-disclosure agreements his Department entered into in 2016.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207599","207599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039620","2019-01-15","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many non-disclosure agreements his Department entered into in 2017.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207600","207600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039621","2019-01-15","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many non-disclosure agreements his Department entered into in 2018.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207601","207601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039622","2019-01-15","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the effect on the prison estate of the resources allocated to the 10 Prisons Programme.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207612","207612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039623","2019-01-15","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the number of staff shortages by prison in the wider prison estate resulting from resources being deployed as part of the 10 Prisons Programme.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207613","207613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039624","2019-01-15","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what discussions he has had with the Chancellor of the Exchequer on additional funding to roll-out the 10 Prisons Programme throughout the prison estate.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207614","207614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038854","2019-01-10","Department for Transport","2019-01-10","What steps he is taking to ensure the compliance of foreign-registered vehicles with UK laws and regulations.","Biography information for Andrew Selous","Andrew Selous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 908489","908489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038855","2019-01-10","Department for Transport","2019-01-10","If he will support Transport for London to increase the number of step-free access underground stations in London.","Biography information for Emma Dent Coad","Emma Dent Coad","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 908490","908490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038856","2019-01-10","Department for Transport","2019-01-10","What steps he is taking to ensure the preparedness of his Department in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Kirsty Blackman","Kirsty Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 908491","908491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038857","2019-01-10","Department for Transport","2019-01-10","What due diligence was undertaken by his Department in advance of its award of a contract to Seaborne Freight.","Biography information for Meg Hillier","Meg Hillier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 908493","908493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038858","2019-01-10","Department for Transport","2019-01-10","What recent assessment he has made of trends in the number of bus journeys in England.","Biography information for Karen Lee","Karen Lee","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 908494","908494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038859","2019-01-10","Department for Transport","2019-01-10","What recent discussions he has had with the Scottish Government on the proposal to merge British Transport Police in Scotland with Police Scotland.","Biography information for Hugh Gaffney","Hugh Gaffney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 908495","908495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038936","2019-01-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the effect on the financial circumstances of universal credit claimants who receive their wages on a fixed day each month and therefore have multiple pay days during an assessment period; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Nick Smith","Nick Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207176","207176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038938","2019-01-15","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the number of people who have been granted legal aid in welfare cases in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207160","207160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038941","2019-01-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions he has had with Cabinet colleagues on reducing the cost of hormone replacement therapy for patients who pay multiple prescription charges for medication with more than one ingredient.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207273","207273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038942","2019-01-15","Home Office","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many police officers were employed by North Wales Police in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207161","207161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038943","2019-01-15","Attorney General","2019-01-10","To ask the Attorney General, how many people have been appointed as Queen's Counsel in Northern Ireland in the last three years.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207162","207162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038944","2019-01-10","Department for Transport","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department is taking steps to ensure that legal action is pursued against Volkswagen executives regarding that company's emissions scandal.","Biography information for Nick Smith","Nick Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207177","207177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038945","2019-01-15","Home Office","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, further to his oral statement of 7 January 2019 on Migrant Crossings, Official Report column 85, whether asylum seekers arriving on the Kent Coast since 1 October 2018 have had their applications for asylum processed using standard procedures.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207208","207208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038946","2019-01-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he has a target for increasing the early stage diagnosis rate for pancreatic cancer in the lifetime of this Parliament.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207163","207163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038947","2019-01-15","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to Prime Minister’s Office file PREM 19/3076, whether the UK is legally obliged to supply Saudi Arabia with aircraft parts under the Al Yamamah arms deal.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207274","207274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038948","2019-01-14","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the (a) rate of (b) average amount paid in Required Hours Addition allowance was to prison governors in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207209","207209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038949","2019-01-14","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the number of prison governors claiming the Required Hours Addition allowance without completing the required training.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207210","207210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038950","2019-01-14","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to ensure that all Required Hours Addition claimants have completed the required training; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207211","207211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038951","2019-01-15","Home Office","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what funds his Department has spent on advertisements promoting online passport applications in each of the last three years; and what funds he plans to spend on promoting online passport applications in the next financial year.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207212","207212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038952","2019-01-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if his Department will publish correspondence with (a) NHS England and (b) NHS Improvement on any (i) assessment and (b) analysis that indicates a funding shortfall of more than £1 billion in 2019-20.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207213","207213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038953","2019-01-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has made a recent assessment of the effect on the human rights of (a) the Nubian people and (b) other political dissenters of the Egyptian Government's alleged persecution of those people; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207214","207214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038954","2019-01-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many protesters have been reported to have been (a) detained, (b) tortured and (c) killed by Sudanese authorities since demonstrations began on 19 December 2018; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207146","207146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038955","2019-01-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his Sudanese counterpart on the Sudanese authorities' response to the protests in that country.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207147","207147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038956","2019-01-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what effect the (a) response of the Government of Sudan to the recent protests in that country and (b) Troika government's statement published on 8 January 2019 will have on the UK-Sudan Strategic Dialogue due to take place in 2019.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207148","207148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038957","2019-01-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what joint programmes on security are ongoing between the UK Government and the Government of Sudan.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207149","207149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038958","2019-01-14","House of Commons Commission","2019-01-10","To ask the right hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington, representing the House of Commons Commission, what recent assessment the Commission has made of the efficiency of call-handling procedures in the House of Commons Pass Office.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207164","207164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038959","2019-01-14","Cabinet Office","2019-01-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people currently work in the civil contingencies secretariat.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207215","207215"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038960","2019-01-14","Cabinet Office","2019-01-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the civil contingencies secretariat budget was for (a) 2016-17, (b) 2017-18 and (c) 2018-19.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207216","207216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038961","2019-01-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many calls to 111 were abandoned in each month in 2018.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207217","207217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038962","2019-01-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of income from private patients at each NHS Trust for each of the last ten years for which records are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207218","207218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038963","2019-01-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the number of nurses employed in the NHS per head of population for each of the last ten years for which records are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207219","207219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038964","2019-01-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the number of vacancies in the NHS by 2030 based upon workforce assumptions in the NHS Long Term Plan.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207220","207220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038965","2019-01-15","Treasury","2019-01-10","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to his Department's announcement entitled New pound coin goes global with rollout to British overseas nations, published on 6 January 2019, if he will list which authority in each of the Overseas Territories and Crown Dependencies that will be responsible for commissioning new £1 coins.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207221","207221"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038966","2019-01-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many reindeer in how many consignments and from which countries were imported into the UK in 2018; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207150","207150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038967","2019-01-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many reindeer in how many consignments and to which countries were exported from the UK in 2018; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207152","207152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038968","2019-01-15","Department for International Development","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent discussions she has had with her counterparts in (a) the G20 and (b) the G7 on addressing malnutrition since the publication of the 2018 Global Nutrition Report.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207222","207222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038969","2019-01-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent discussions she has had with the Secretary of State for Justice on improving access to employment for ex-offenders.","Biography information for Chris Elmore","Chris Elmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207275","207275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038970","2019-01-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many work coaches currently work in UK prisons on a full-time basis.","Biography information for Chris Elmore","Chris Elmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207276","207276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038971","2019-01-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment she has made of the effectiveness of policies to help former prisoners find employment.","Biography information for Chris Elmore","Chris Elmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207277","207277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038972","2019-01-14","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent assessment he has made of trends in the number of female offenders who have been unable to enter employment upon leaving prison.","Biography information for Chris Elmore","Chris Elmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207278","207278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038973","2019-01-14","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many female offenders who have received more than one custodial sentence since 2010 were unemployed when they re-offended.","Biography information for Chris Elmore","Chris Elmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207279","207279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038974","2019-01-14","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, in which European Union member states do British citizens have to register their details with the Government upon moving to that country.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207280","207280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038975","2019-01-14","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what the financial costs are for a British citizen to acquire a permanent resident permit or the equivalent of such document in each European Union member state.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207281","207281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038976","2019-01-14","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what are the financial costs for a British citizen to become a citizen of each European Union member state.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207282","207282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038977","2019-01-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to involve people with learning disabilities and autism in the development of mandatory training for NHS staff.","Biography information for Marsha De Cordova","Marsha De Cordova","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207283","207283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038978","2019-01-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether mandatory training for NHS staff on learning disability and autism will involve people with learning disabilities and autism.","Biography information for Marsha De Cordova","Marsha De Cordova","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207284","207284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038979","2019-01-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to reduce waiting times for (a) NHS treatment in A&E, (b) routine operations, and (c) cancer care.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207285","207285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038980","2019-01-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure services funded by the NHS uphold national learning disability improvement standards; and whether he plans to bring forward measures to ensure compliance with those standards.","Biography information for Marsha De Cordova","Marsha De Cordova","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207286","207286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038981","2019-01-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what oversight his Department will give to services funded by the NHS in relation to the implementation of national learning disability improvement standards.","Biography information for Marsha De Cordova","Marsha De Cordova","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207287","207287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038982","2019-01-14","Treasury","2019-01-10","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether his Department has plans to assess the eligibility of music venues for discounted business rates.","Biography information for Mr Edward Vaizey","Mr Edward Vaizey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207178","207178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038983","2019-01-14","Home Office","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when he plans to publish details of the Windrush compensation scheme following the Government's consultation on that scheme.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207288","207288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038984","2019-01-15","Department for Transport","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment his Department has made of the potential effect of the UK leaving the EU without a deal on traffic levels around Portsmouth International Port.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207289","207289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038985","2019-01-15","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many outstanding cases his Department is currently dealing with on disputes over applications for war pensions.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207153","207153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038986","2019-01-15","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to he Answer of 9 January 2019 to Question 205256 on Housing: Regeneration, if he will create a fund for land clearance and the demolition of low quality, high void rate housing in circumstances whereby local authorities develop plans for housing regeneration.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207223","207223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038987","2019-01-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the answer of 9 January 2019 to Question 205254 on Universal Credit: Support for Mortgage Interest, if she will ensure the rules in relation to support for mortgage interest loans mean that the 39 week waiting period is not reset when a claimant receives any income.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207224","207224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038988","2019-01-14","Treasury","2019-01-10","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much money has been raised for the public purse from vehicle excise duties from the Greater London Authority area in each year for which information is available; and what assessment he has made of the potential merits of devolving the proceeds of vehicle excise duties raised in the Greater London Authority area to London local authorities.","Biography information for Julia Lopez","Julia Lopez","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207290","207290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038989","2019-01-14","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether the funding allocated to Wales out of the UK Shared Prosperity fund will be as a result of a (a) pre-allocation or (b) competitive bidding process.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207291","207291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038990","2019-01-14","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether funding allocated from the UK Shared Prosperity Fund will be restricted to  specific funding streams and policy goals.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207292","207292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038991","2019-01-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference paragraph 1 of page 114 of the NHS Long-Term Plan, when he plans to (a) revoke the National Health Service (Procurement, Patient Choice and Competition) (No 2) Regulations 2013 and (b) exclude the NHS from the Public Contract Regulations.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207225","207225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038992","2019-01-15","Department for International Development","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to support internally displaced peoples in northern Nigeria.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207154","207154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038993","2019-01-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when he plans to respond to the letter from the right hon. Member for North Norfolk of 26 July 2018 in relation to Dr Chris Day.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207165","207165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038994","2019-01-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to include people with (a) learning disabilities and (b) autism in the development of mandatory training for NHS staff.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207226","207226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038995","2019-01-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether mandatory training on learning disability and autism will include people with (a) learning disabilities and (b) autism.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207227","207227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038996","2019-01-15","Department for Education","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate his Department has made of the number of people that have completed an adult education course in (a) Coventry, (b) the West Midlands and (c) the UK in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207155","207155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038997","2019-01-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to (a) monitor and (b) ensure that services funded by the NHS are compliant with national learning disability improvement standards.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207228","207228"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038998","2019-01-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when he plans to respond to the letter from the right hon. Member for North Norfolk and the hon. Member for Ellesmore Port and Neston of 17 December 2018, in relation to Dr Chris Day.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207179","207179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038999","2019-01-14","Cabinet Office","2019-01-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether Gypsy and Irish Traveller communities are classified as being specific communities in need of supported participation with the 2021 census; and what steps he plans to put in place to ensure census liaison staff reach those communities.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207229","207229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039000","2019-01-14","Cabinet Office","2019-01-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether the Roma will be classified as a specific community in need of supported participation in the 2021 census, and what steps his Department is taking to ensure that census liaison staff reach those communities.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207230","207230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039001","2019-01-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the availability of essential epilepsy medicines imported from the EU in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207180","207180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039002","2019-01-15","Department for Education","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate his Department has made of the total cost to the public purse of teacher training bursaries awarded in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207156","207156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039003","2019-01-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he plans to exclude epilepsy medications from the Serious Shortage Protocol for medicines; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207181","207181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039004","2019-01-14","Treasury","2019-01-10","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people have live savings accounts under the Help to Save scheme in (a) the UK and (b) Preseli Pembrokeshire at 31 December 2018.","Biography information for Stephen Crabb","Stephen Crabb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207182","207182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039005","2019-01-15","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what discussions his Department has had with the Home Office to ensure that non-UK EU residents in the process of seeking settled status will be able to access local authority-provided services while they are waiting for conferment of that status.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207293","207293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039006","2019-01-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what discussions she has had with the Home Secretary on ensuring that EU citizens in the process of seeking settled status in the UK will continue to be able to access social security benefits while awaiting the outcome of their application.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207294","207294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039007","2019-01-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people have put their Type 2 diabetes into remission and stopped taking medication for their condition in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207183","207183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039008","2019-01-15","Department for Transport","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate his department has made of the cost to the public purse of creating a national database of all licensed taxi and PHV drivers, vehicles and operator, as recommended by the September 2018 report of the Task and Finish Group on Taxi and Private Hire Vehicle Licensing; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207157","207157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039009","2019-01-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people under 21 years old have developed Type 2 diabetes in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207184","207184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039010","2019-01-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many NHS prescriptons have been issued for patients to use medical cannabis since 1 November 2018.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207185","207185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039011","2019-01-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the effect on health of sweeteners used in foods as an alternative to sugar.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207186","207186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039012","2019-01-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information his Department holds on the number of NHS Trusts with crowdfunding pages; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207231","207231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039013","2019-01-15","Department for Education","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to his oral contribution of 17 December 2018, Official Report Column 509, if he will place in the Library a copy of the 30 November 2018 presentation by the Institute for Apprenticeships at Exeter College citing the projected £500 million overspend on the apprenticeship levy budget.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207232","207232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039014","2019-01-15","Department for Education","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 18 December 2018 to Question 202058 on apprentices: finance, by what means his Department controls expenditure in a demand-led apprenticeship programme; and what steps his Department is taking to prevent an overspend in each of the next three years.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207233","207233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039015","2019-01-15","Department for Education","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to support schools in educating students about the dangers of knife crime.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207166","207166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039016","2019-01-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many NHS prescriptions have been honoured at a pharmacy for patients to use medical cannabis since 1 November 2018.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207187","207187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039017","2019-01-14","Cabinet Office","2019-01-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the Places for Growth Programme in identifying the potential for relocating government offices to Southampton.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207295","207295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039018","2019-01-14","Cabinet Office","2019-01-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what progress has been made on implementing the Places for Growth programme.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207296","207296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039019","2019-01-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to his Department’s report entitled, Air quality: explaining air pollution – at a glance, published on 22 May 2018, for what reason emissions of ammonia have increased since 2013.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207297","207297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039020","2019-01-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effect of the use of winter tyres on roads on air quality.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207298","207298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039021","2019-01-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many observers the Government sent to the recent election in the Democratic Republic of Congo; and when those observers are expected to report back on the fairness of that election.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207158","207158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039022","2019-01-15","Home Office","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many cessation of international protection decisions by nationality of applicant have been made by the UK under Article 11 and  Article 17 of Directive 2011/95/EU in 2018.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207234","207234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039023","2019-01-15","Home Office","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many withdrawal of international protection decisions were made by the UK by nationality of applicant under Article 14 and Article 19 o f Directive 2011/95/EU in  2018.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207235","207235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039024","2019-01-15","Home Office","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average duration of the asylum procedure at first instance is in the UK.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207236","207236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039025","2019-01-15","Home Office","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average time was for a decision to be made on an application for asylum in the UK for (a) Syrian nationals, (b) Afghan nationals and (c) Iraqi nationals in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207237","207237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039026","2019-01-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the current uptake of winter 2018-19's influenza vaccination among those who are eligible for free treatment.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207188","207188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039027","2019-01-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many applications for universal credit have been made in the Welsh language.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207167","207167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039028","2019-01-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether Erwinase will be available for the treatment for children with acute lymphoblastic leukaemia between January 2019 and March 2019; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207238","207238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039029","2019-01-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the number of (a) prescriptions issued and (b) patients that use medical cannabis in the next 12 months.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207189","207189"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039030","2019-01-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the effect of delaying the managed migration aspect of universal credit on the ability to make a universal credit application in Welsh.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207168","207168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039031","2019-01-14","Department for International Development","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will make it her policy to allocate additional funding at the 6th replenishment of the Global Fund in October 2019.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207299","207299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039032","2019-01-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what proportion of the cost of training a student midwife is paid by (a) the student, (b) his Department and (c) other sources.","Biography information for Gareth Snell","Gareth Snell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207300","207300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039033","2019-01-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the Ministerial Statement of 12 December 2018 on NHS Overseas Charging Regulations Review 2017, HCWS1174, what assessment was made of the needs of (a) pregnant women and (b) new mothers in that review.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207239","207239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039034","2019-01-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the Written Statement of 12 December 2018 on NHS Overseas Charging Regulations Review 2017, HCWS1174, what discussions he held with (a) healthcare professionals, (b) non-governmental organisations and (c) others with an expertise in maternity care as part of that review.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207240","207240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039035","2019-01-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions (a) he, (b) Ministers in his Department and (c) officials in his Department with NHS Trusts on implementing adequate measures to ensure access to medical cannabis for patients.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207190","207190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039036","2019-01-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate his Department has made of the number of patients that were denied access to medicinal cannabis by their (a) NHS trust, (b) GP and (c) neurologist.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207191","207191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039037","2019-01-14","Department for Education","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much was paid in (a) tuition fee loans and (b) maintenance loans with respect to students undertaking undergraduate midwifery courses (a) in total and (b) on average per student midwife in each academic year since 2016-17; and what estimate his Department has made of the proportion of such loans that will be repaid by people who received them.","Biography information for Gareth Snell","Gareth Snell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207301","207301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039038","2019-01-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment he has made of the effectiveness of NHS and medical professionals body guidelines on the prescription of medical cannabis.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207192","207192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039039","2019-01-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment he has made of the effectiveness of hospital trusts in implementing the law change of 1 November 2018 to ensure patients that might benefit from medical cannabis are able to.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207193","207193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039040","2019-01-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many times (a) he, (b) Ministers in his Department and (c) officials in his Department have met with Bedrocan.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207194","207194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039041","2019-01-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many times (a) he, (b) Ministers in his Department and (c) officials in his Department have met with Tilray.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207195","207195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039042","2019-01-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many times (a) he, (b) Ministers in his Department and (c) officials in his Department have met with GW Pharmaceuticals.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207196","207196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039043","2019-01-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many times (a) he, (b) Ministers in his Department and (c) officials in his Department have met with Aphria.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207197","207197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039044","2019-01-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the Weybridge fire incident report, published by NHS Property Services in May 2018, whether recommendations 4a. and 5a. have been implemented.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207241","207241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039045","2019-01-14","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will make an assessment of the accuracy of allegations (a) of approximately £500,000 being spent inefficiently by Crawley Borough Council on a recent IT project and (b) that freedom of information requests by residents on that subject have not been fully responded to; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207242","207242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039046","2019-01-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many student midwives were in receipt of a bursary in each academic year since 2016-17; what the average bursary paid to a student midwife was in each of those years; and what the total cost of those bursaries was to his Department in each of those years.","Biography information for Gareth Snell","Gareth Snell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207302","207302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039047","2019-01-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the average cost to the NHS has been of employing a midwife on a full-time basis in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Gareth Snell","Gareth Snell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207303","207303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039048","2019-01-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many babies were born in (a) an obstetric unit, (b) a midwifery unit situated alongside an obstetric unit, (c) a standalone midwifery unit, (d) at home, (e) in another setting in the most recent period for which information is available.","Biography information for Gareth Snell","Gareth Snell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207304","207304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039049","2019-01-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information his Department holds on the reasons that midwives have provided for leaving NHS employment in each of the last five years for which information is available.","Biography information for Gareth Snell","Gareth Snell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207305","207305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039050","2019-01-15","Department for Education","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions he has had with educational psychologists on the effect of reception baseline assessments on infant mental health.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207169","207169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039051","2019-01-15","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, for what reason the consultation on the UK Shared Prosperity Fund has been postponed; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207151","207151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039052","2019-01-15","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 10 September 2018 to Question 170708 and the Written Statement of 24 July 2018 on Local Growth, HLWS898, if he will publish the proposed timeline for the consultation on the Shared Prosperity Fund.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207170","207170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039053","2019-01-15","Department for International Trade","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many free trade agreements to which the UK is a party through its EU membership will be rolled over in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal on 30 March 2019; and which countries those agreements will be with.","Biography information for Kirsty Blackman","Kirsty Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207243","207243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039054","2019-01-15","Department for International Trade","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether the UK has secured an agreement with Turkey to continue trading after 30 March 2019 on the same terms on which it currently trades with that country; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Kirsty Blackman","Kirsty Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207244","207244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039055","2019-01-15","Cabinet Office","2019-01-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what guidance his Department issues to Government Departments on their (a) responsibilities and (b) obligations in relation to answers to (i) written and (ii) oral Parliamentary Questions.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207198","207198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039056","2019-01-15","Cabinet Office","2019-01-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office,  what guidance his Department has issued to Government Departments in relation to the transfer to another Department of (a) written and (b) oral Parliamentary Questions to another Government Department to answer.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207199","207199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039057","2019-01-14","Department for Transport","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to ensure the implementation of the (a) recommendations and (b) learning points set out in the Rail Accident Report: Collision at London Waterloo,15 August 2017, published the Rail Accident Investigation Branch in November 2018.","Biography information for Laura Smith","Laura Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207306","207306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039058","2019-01-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 1 November 2018 to Question 185101 on Universal Credit: Telephone Services, if she will publish the (a) supportive lines and (b) agent led processes used by universal credit call centre staff, in addition to the Digital Channel Product.","Biography information for Danielle Rowley","Danielle Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207307","207307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039059","2019-01-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the average level of sugar content in baby food products available in the UK.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207200","207200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039060","2019-01-15","Treasury","2019-01-10","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the effect on the amount of customs revenue accruing to the public purse of (a) leaving the EU, (b) leaving the EU without a deal and (b) the Department for Transport’s decision to prioritise speed of goods processing over revenue collection at the border.","Biography information for Kirsty Blackman","Kirsty Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207245","207245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039061","2019-01-15","Department for Education","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when the Timpson school exclusions review is planned to report.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207308","207308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039062","2019-01-14","Department for Education","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much Apprenticeship Levy funding has been (a) spent, (b) drawn down by Levy contributor employers, (c) spent on apprenticeships training by non-Levy contributor employers, (d) allocated in incentives and payments to apprentices, (e) spent on English and Maths requirements and (f) allocated to other Levy-related spending in each financial year since the introduction of that Levy.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207246","207246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039063","2019-01-14","Department for Education","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of Apprenticeship Levy (a) funding and (b) spending for 2018-19.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207247","207247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039064","2019-01-14","Department for Education","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will publish the (a) dates of and (b) principal topics for discussion at the meetings that (i) he, (ii) Ministers in his Department and (iii) officials in his Department have had with the Institute for Apprenticeships since it was established.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207248","207248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039065","2019-01-14","Department for Education","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the stated aims are of the apprenticeship funding band review; and how those aims align with Government policy on apprenticeships.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207249","207249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039066","2019-01-14","Department for Education","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether it is his Department’s policy to prioritise the take-up of higher-level apprenticeship programmes at Levels 4-7, over programmes at Levels 2-3.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207250","207250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039067","2019-01-14","Department for Education","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what (a) skills and (b) economic sectors his Department has classified as priority for the apprenticeships sector.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207251","207251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039068","2019-01-14","Department for Education","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will publish the meetings (a) he, (b) Ministers in his Department and (c) officials in his Department have held with stakeholders from the apprenticeships sector in the last 12 months; and what the principal topics for discussion were at those meetings.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207252","207252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039069","2019-01-14","Home Office","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what financial support the Government has allocated to Staffordshire County Council in support of caring for unaccompanied (a) adult and (b) children asylum seekers in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207253","207253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039070","2019-01-14","Department for Education","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions his Department has had with stakeholders from the apprenticeships sector on the apprenticeship funding band reviews.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207254","207254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039071","2019-01-15","Department for Transport","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make a comparative assessment of the cost (a) to consumers and (b) of the provision of bus services in (i) London and (ii) Newcastle.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207255","207255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039072","2019-01-15","Home Office","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of safety for female refugees that are returned to Saudi Arabia.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207256","207256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039073","2019-01-14","Department for International Development","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, with reference to the Government's response to the Fifth Report of the International Development Committee, HC246 of Session 2014-15 and the Answer of 11 December 2018 to Question 198914 on Developing Countries: Health Services, in which month his Department plans to publish its health systems strengthening position paper.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207309","207309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039074","2019-01-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many clinics for the treatment of problem gambling are planned to open between now and 2023; and where they are planned to be located.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207201","207201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039075","2019-01-14","Department for International Development","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether her Department has plans to send officials to Yemen to make an assessment of the humanitarian situation in that country.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207310","207310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039076","2019-01-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department (a) has taken and (b) plans to take to support the work of the International Commission against Impunity in Guatemala following recent attempts by the Guatemalan Government to shut the commission down.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207171","207171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039077","2019-01-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of potential increases in patient numbers at some GP practices as a result of practice closures due to rising rent and charges imposed by NHS Property Services.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207257","207257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039078","2019-01-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what provisions have been included in the forthcoming green paper on social care reform to enable access to quality care for people diagnosed with Alzheimer’s disease and dementia.","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207311","207311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039079","2019-01-15","Treasury","2019-01-10","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of the high income child benefit tax charge on single-parent families.","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207312","207312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039080","2019-01-15","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department is taking to restrict TV advertising relating to the gambling industry.","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207313","207313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039081","2019-01-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of how medicines flown to the UK from Maastricht in preparation for the UK leaving the EU without a deal will reach distributors.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207258","207258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039082","2019-01-14","Department for Transport","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to make additional funding available for rural community transport providers.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207259","207259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039083","2019-01-15","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what recent discussions his Department has had with interest groups on audio description for TV.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207314","207314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039084","2019-01-15","Home Office","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many premium service spousal visa applications for settlement in the UK have been processed in each month from January 2018 to January 2019.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207202","207202"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039085","2019-01-14","Department for Transport","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the potential economic benefits of a third runway at Heathrow for that area; and what steps his Department plans to take to improve the local infrastructure.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207260","207260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039086","2019-01-14","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether he has plans to extend the Green Deal scheme to cover people that are seeking to withdraw from a feed-in tariff contract to sell their property.","Biography information for Bill Grant","Bill Grant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207315","207315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039087","2019-01-14","Home Office","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many and what proportion of premium service spousal visa applications for settlement in the UK were processed by UK Visas and Immigration within target times between (a) 1 January 2018 and 31 July 2018 and (b) 1 August 2018 and 1 January 2019.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207203","207203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039088","2019-01-14","Department for Transport","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to improve step-free access at rural train stations.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207261","207261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039089","2019-01-15","Home Office","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when he expects his Department to complete its review of family migration rules for Afghan interpreters that served alongside British armed forces and whose families could not travel to the UK at the same time under the redundancy scheme.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207204","207204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039090","2019-01-15","Department for Transport","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he has taken to ensure that the (a) tendering process, (b) contract and (c) funding for the re-opening of the Ostend to Ramsgate ferry route complies with (i) the Concession Agreement with Eurotunnel, (ii) state aid rules and (iii) competition law; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207262","207262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039091","2019-01-15","Department for Transport","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions his Department has had with representatives of the port of Ostend on the proposed re-opening of the Ostend to Ramsgate ferry route.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207263","207263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039092","2019-01-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his Israeli counterpart on the (a) forceable removal of shepherding families in Ibzik, in the Jordan Valley (b) destruction of those communities' land by large-scale tank manoeuvres and (c) demolition of a school classroom serving those communities.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207316","207316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039093","2019-01-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department has plans to extend the requirement for food vendors to prominently display food hygiene ratings on their premises to online third party food ordering (a) websites and (b) apps at the point at which the customer orders food.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207264","207264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039094","2019-01-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what training is provides to call-handlers on the universal credit helpline (a) when they start and (b) throughout their working time.","Biography information for Danielle Rowley","Danielle Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207317","207317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039095","2019-01-15","Department for Education","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the effect of self-employed people being unable to take paid adoption leave on the level of adoption.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207265","207265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039096","2019-01-15","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether the Government has plans to bring forward legislative proposals to extend the provisions of Section 21 of the Sexual Offences Act 2003 to include Council funded sports coaches within the occupations classified as a position of trust.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207266","207266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039097","2019-01-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will place in the Library a copy of the training documents used for training call handlers on the universal credit helpline.","Biography information for Danielle Rowley","Danielle Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207318","207318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039098","2019-01-14","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will take steps to ban businesses found to have mis-sold green deal products from setting up (a) similar and (b) linked businesses again.","Biography information for Bill Grant","Bill Grant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207319","207319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039099","2019-01-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether Natural England has made a Habitat Regulation Assessment prior to the dredging of the Port of Ramsgate.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207205","207205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039100","2019-01-14","Department for Transport","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what information his Department holds on the number of trained bus drivers in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207267","207267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039101","2019-01-14","Department for Transport","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the availability of bus drivers on bus services.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207268","207268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039102","2019-01-14","Department for Transport","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what information his Department holds on the change in the level of bus fares across England since 2010.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207269","207269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039103","2019-01-14","Department for Transport","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the Government Response to Call for Evidence Cycling and Walking Investment Strategy: Safety Review,published in November 2018, what steps he is taking to clarify local authorities’ powers relating to civil enforcement of mandatory cycle lanes by bringing into effect the relevant provisions of Part 6 of the Traffic Management Act 2004.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207270","207270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039104","2019-01-15","Department for Transport","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what Environment Impact Assessment has been undertaken by Seaborne Freight prior to the dredging of the port of Ramsgate.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207206","207206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039105","2019-01-14","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what discussions he has had with the (a) Secretary of state for Health and Social Care and (b) Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government on the effect of the UK leaving the EU on non-UK EU citizens whose social care packages are funded by local authorities.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207159","207159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039106","2019-01-14","Home Office","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what statutory options for the regulation of social media companies his Department plans to include in the White Paper on online harm.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207172","207172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039107","2019-01-14","Home Office","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of the legislation required to help ensure that children are protected from online harms; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207173","207173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039108","2019-01-14","Home Office","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether he has made an assessment of the potential merits of creating a regulator to tackle online harms on social media platforms; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207174","207174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039109","2019-01-14","Home Office","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what (a) social networking companies and (b) online platforms his Department has met with or received briefings from in the process of writing the White Paper on online harms.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207175","207175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039110","2019-01-15","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether all international treaty and non-treaty arrangements in which the UK participates through membership of the EU will be replicated by 29 March 2019.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207320","207320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039111","2019-01-14","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many non-disclosure agreements his Department entered into in (a) 2005, (b) 2006, (c) 2007, (d) 2008, (e) 2009, (f) 2010, (g) 2011 and (h) 2012.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207207","207207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039112","2019-01-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to reduce the practice of horse tethering.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207271","207271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1039113","2019-01-15","Treasury","2019-01-10","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 9 January 2019 to Question 205403, what the total to date is of businesses signed up for making tax digital for VAT; and what estimate he has made of what that total represents as a proportion of eligible businesses.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207321","207321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038060","2019-01-09","Department for International Development","2019-01-09","What recent representations she has received on the future of UNRWA funding in Palestine.","Biography information for Richard Graham","Richard Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 908418","908418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038061","2019-01-09","Department for International Development","2019-01-09","What recent steps her Department has taken to help strengthen governance and security in Uganda.","Biography information for Dr Paul Williams","Dr Paul Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 908419","908419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038062","2019-01-09","Department for International Development","2019-01-09","What steps she is taking to provide long-term support for the Rohingya people.","Biography information for Paul Scully","Paul Scully","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 908420","908420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038063","2019-01-09","Department for International Development","2019-01-09","What steps she is taking to improve the humanitarian situation in Yemen.","Biography information for Angela Crawley","Angela Crawley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 908421","908421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038064","2019-01-09","Department for International Development","2019-01-09","What her Department's priorities are for 2019.","Biography information for Steve Double","Steve Double","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 908424","908424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038065","2019-01-09","Department for International Development","2019-01-09","What her Department's priorities are for 2019.","Biography information for Will Quince","Will Quince","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 908425","908425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038104","2019-01-14","Cabinet Office","2019-01-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment he has made of the capacity of the UK to counter non-military attacks.","Biography information for Hannah Bardell","Hannah Bardell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 908527","908527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038324","2019-01-11","Department for Transport","2019-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with Cabinet colleagues on the level of social exclusion is in rural areas; and what assessment his Department has made of the link between social exclusion and access to public transport in rural areas.","Biography information for John Lamont","John Lamont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 206831","206831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038325","2019-01-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment her Department has made of the level of social exclusion is in rural areas; and what recent assessment she has made of the effectiveness of her Department’s policies on social exclusion in rural areas.","Biography information for John Lamont","John Lamont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 206832","206832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038327","2019-01-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment his Department has made of (a) how widespread social exclusion is in rural areas and (b) the effect of his Department’s policies on social exclusion in rural areas.","Biography information for John Lamont","John Lamont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 206833","206833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038328","2019-01-14","Department for Education","2019-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the average waiting time was for a child to be assessed for an Education, Health Care Plan after receiving a diagnosis of autism spectrum disorder in (a) the London Borough of Southwark, (b) London and (c) England  in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 206711","206711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038329","2019-01-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment her Department has made of the potential effect on benefit recipients of missed Child Maintenance Service payments where the level of benefit has been reduced due those payments being awarded.","Biography information for Sandy Martin","Sandy Martin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 206834","206834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038331","2019-01-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment her Department has made of fairness of the decision by the Independent Case Examiner to close individual cases related to the state pension age for women on the basis that there is a judicial review of the way in which her Department handled those changes.","Biography information for Sandy Martin","Sandy Martin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 206835","206835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038332","2019-01-11","Department for Transport","2019-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to reduce noise pollution emitted from car exhausts.","Biography information for Mhairi Black","Mhairi Black","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 206767","206767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038334","2019-01-11","Department for Transport","2019-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to prevent car owners from altering their cars to emit more noise.","Biography information for Mhairi Black","Mhairi Black","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 206768","206768"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038335","2019-01-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the March 2015 NICE Quality Standard, Falls in older people, updated in January 2017, if he will make an estimate of the number of people that have been assessed under (a) Statement 1, (b) Statement 2 and (c) Statement 3 of that Quality Standard since 2017.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 206836","206836"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038336","2019-01-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the March 2015 NICE Quality Standard, Falls in older people, updated in January 2017, if he will make an estimate of the number of GP practices that have implemented (a) Statement 1, (b) Statement 2 and (c) Statement 3 of that Quality Standard since 2017.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 206837","206837"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038338","2019-01-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the March 2015 NICE Quality Standard, Falls in older people, updated in January 2017, what guidance his Department has provided to GP practices on implementing (a) Statement 1, (b) Statement 2 and (c) Statement 3 of that Quality Standard since 2017.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 206838","206838"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038339","2019-01-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many emergency hospital admissions relating to falls in older people there have been in the last 12 months for which figures are available.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 206839","206839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038340","2019-01-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure the adequacy of stockpiles of insulin in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Christine Jardine","Christine Jardine","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 206840","206840"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038341","2019-01-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent assessment his Department has made of (a) how widespread social exclusion is in rural areas and (b) the effect of his Department’s policies on social exclusion in rural areas.","Biography information for John Lamont","John Lamont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 206841","206841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038343","2019-01-11","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what recent assessment his Department has made of (a) how widespread social exclusion is in rural areas and (b) the effect of his Department’s policies on social exclusion in rural areas.","Biography information for John Lamont","John Lamont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 206842","206842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038344","2019-01-11","Department for Education","2019-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment his Department has made of (a) how widespread social exclusion is in rural areas and (b) the effect of his Department’s policies on social exclusion in rural areas.","Biography information for John Lamont","John Lamont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 206843","206843"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038345","2019-01-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment his Department has made of (a) how widespread social exclusion is in rural areas and (b) the effect of his Department’s policies on social exclusion in rural areas.","Biography information for John Lamont","John Lamont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 206844","206844"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038346","2019-01-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment her Department has made of (a) how widespread social exclusion is in rural areas and (b) the effect of her Department’s policies on social exclusion in rural areas.","Biography information for John Lamont","John Lamont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 206845","206845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038348","2019-01-15","Department for Transport","2019-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how long the full procurement process took in each case to agree the public contracts his Department recently awarded to (a) DFDS, (b) Seaborne Freight and (c) Brittany Ferries for roll-on roll-off freight ferry services; and if he will place a copy of each contract in the Library.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 206769","206769"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038349","2019-01-15","Department for Transport","2019-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make an estimate of the minimum number of vessels required to fulfil the public contracts his Department recently awarded to (a) DFDS, (b) Seaborne Freight and (c) Brittany Ferries for roll-on roll-off freight ferry services from UK ports.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 206770","206770"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038351","2019-01-15","Department for Transport","2019-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what procurement process his Department used to contract (a) DFDS, (b) Seaborne Freight and (c) Brittany Ferries to provide extra roll-on roll-off ferry capacity.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 206771","206771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038352","2019-01-14","Department for Education","2019-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what his estimated total cost to the public purse is of the national retraining scheme.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 206735","206735"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038353","2019-01-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what information his Department holds on the (a) timing, (b) UK representation and (c) UK objectives for the UN-led national conference on Libya.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 206846","206846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038355","2019-01-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans he has to increase access to independent agronomic advice for farmers in advance of proposed changes in agricultural legislation under the Agriculture Bill 2017-19.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 206712","206712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038356","2019-01-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what estimate he has made of the (a) lowest, (b) highest and (c) average cost of repatriating a victim of forced marriage to the UK in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 206847","206847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038357","2019-01-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what estimate he has made of the value of the (a) lowest, (b) highest and (c) average emergency loan granted to victims of forced marriage in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 206848","206848"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038359","2019-01-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 20 December 2018 to Question 202774, what discussions his Department plans to hold with The Executive Office in Northern Ireland on their proposals to establish a compensation scheme for children sent abroad from Northern Ireland as a result of the UK Government's historic child migration policy.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 206772","206772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038360","2019-01-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 20 December 2018 to Question 202774, what plans his Department has to hold discussions with the Scottish Child Abuse Inquiry Team on their investigations into children sent abroad from Scotland as a result of the UK Government's historic child migration policy.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 206773","206773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038361","2019-01-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 20 December 2018 to Question 202774, whether the proposed ex-gratia payment scheme for former child migrants will be open to all surviving child migrants including those migrated from the UK prior to the Second World War.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 206774","206774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038363","2019-01-14","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate he has made of the number of additional full fibre broadband connections in rural areas which will be provided using capital contributions clawed back from BT in connection with its BDUK projects.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 206713","206713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038364","2019-01-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 21 November 2018 to Question 191481 on Birds: Malvern Hills, which bird groups Natural England has met with; and when Natural England propose to next meet with those bird groups.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 206849","206849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038365","2019-01-11","Cabinet Office","2019-01-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when he plans to publish the independent membership and terms of reference of the Advisory Military Sub-Committee of the Honours and Decorations Committee.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 206850","206850"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038367","2019-01-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate she has made of the amount of debt to be written-off from arrears accrued under the Child Support Agency because parents had not responded to (a) letters and (b) telephone calls within 60 days.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 206851","206851"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1038368","2019-01-11","Department for Transport","2019-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to improve safety on the A34 in Oxfordshire.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 206852","206852"
