"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596195","2016-10-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent assessment he has made of whether his Department is on course to complete the roll-out of smart meters by 2020.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47374","47374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596196","2016-10-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, for what reason his Department has not implemented the Department of Energy and Climate Change's commitment to a biannual budget reconciliation process for the new feed-in tariff scheme, set out in its review of that scheme in December 2015.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47470","47470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596197","2016-10-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what proportion of the budget for the National Measurement System was spent through (a) NEL Ltd, (b) the National Physical Laboratory and (c) LGC over the last five years.","Biography information for Callum McCaig","Callum McCaig","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47442","47442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596198","2016-10-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how much his Department has allocated to schemes to encourage investment in solar energy in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47462","47462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596199","2016-10-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how much his Department has allocated to schemes to encourage investment in nuclear energy in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47461","47461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596200","2016-10-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will make it his Department's policy to implement the Department of Energy and Climate Change's commitment to feed-in tariff deployment cap top-ups, set out in its review of the feed-in tariffs scheme, published in December 2015.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47469","47469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596201","2016-10-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what level of funding his Department has allocated to schemes that encourage investment in tidal energy in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47450","47450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596202","2016-10-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what level of funding his Department has allocated to schemes that encourage investment in wind energy in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47451","47451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596203","2016-10-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what level of funding his Department has allocated to schemes that encourage investment in wave energy in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47452","47452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596204","2016-10-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what proportion of staff on the payroll of his Department who work in Westminster are (a) British nationals and (b) nationals of another country.","Biography information for John Pugh","John Pugh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47575","47575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596205","2016-10-12","Department for International Trade","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, if he will publish his Department's budget for the next four years.","Biography information for Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47482","47482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596206","2016-10-12","Department for International Trade","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what targets the Government has set for the growth of UK exports by 2020.","Biography information for Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47483","47483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596207","2016-10-11","Department for International Trade","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what discussions he has had with representatives of the 53 countries with which Britain holds free trade agreements (FTAs) through its membership of the EU on the timetable for replacing those agreements with bilateral FTAs.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47468","47468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596208","2016-10-11","Department for International Trade","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, pursuant to the Answer of 7 June 2016 to Question 38925, what the planned opening date is for a reading room for hon. Members to scrutinise classified documents relating to the Transatlantic Trade and Investment Partnership.","Biography information for Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47444","47444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596209","2016-10-11","Department for International Trade","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, pursuant to the Answer of 29 June 2016 to Question 41468, when he plans to lay the draft text of the EU-Canada Comprehensive and Economic Trade Agreement before Parliament.","Biography information for Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47434","47434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596210","2016-10-11","Department for International Trade","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many foreign workers his Department employs.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47419","47419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596211","2016-10-11","Department for International Trade","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, (a) how many and (b) what proportion of the staff employed by his Department are non-UK nationals.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47396","47396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596212","2016-10-12","Department for International Trade","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what discussions he has had with representatives of Japanese businesses operating in the UK on the memorandum presented by the Japanese government to the Prime Minister at the recent G20 summit.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47347","47347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596213","2016-10-11","Department for International Trade","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what proportion of staff on the payroll of his Department who work in Westminster are (a) British nationals and (b) nationals of another country.","Biography information for John Pugh","John Pugh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47589","47589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596214","2016-10-11","Department for International Trade","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, approximately how many (a) British and (b) non-British nationals are employed cleaning the Westminster estate of his Department.","Biography information for John Pugh","John Pugh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47567","47567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596215","2016-10-11","Department for International Trade","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, if he will publish the latest proposals on the Trade in Services Agreement.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46798","46798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596216","2016-10-11","Department for International Trade","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that the Trade in Services Agreement supports the targets set at the COP21 climate change conference.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46800","46800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596217","2016-10-11","Department for International Trade","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many trade negotiators he has hired since 23 June 2016; and what the aggregate cost is of their contracts.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46932","46932"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596218","2016-10-11","Department for International Trade","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many times his Department has used the services of (a) PwC, (b) Deloitte, (c) Ernst and Young, (d) KPMG and (e) other consulting firms since his Department was established; and what (i) work was undertaken and (ii) the cost to the public purse was on each such occasion.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47214","47214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596219","2016-10-11","Department for International Trade","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what schedules his Department has prepared for World Trade Organisation tariffs on goods and services for the period after the UK has exited the EU.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47107","47107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596220","2016-10-11","Department for International Trade","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what his Department's capital and current budgets are for (a) 2016-17 and (b) 2017-18.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47108","47108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596221","2016-10-11","Department for International Trade","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what recent assessment he has made of the potential effect of the UK withdrawing from the EU on the promotion of UK trade with other Commonwealth countries.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47043","47043"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596222","2016-10-11","Department for International Trade","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, which EU commissioners he has met since taking office; and when and where such meetings took place.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47035","47035"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596223","2016-10-11","Department for International Trade","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, pursuant to the Answer of 16 September 2016 to Question 45359, whether people not from government departments have accompanied him on official visits abroad.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46896","46896"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596224","2016-10-12","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, pursuant to his Oral Statement of 5 September 2016, Official Report, columns 38 to 41, how many of his Department's 300 officials were recruited for their ability to speak a second language.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46992","46992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596225","2016-10-12","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what the Government's policy is on maintaining the provisions of European Commission Directive 2008/94/EC on the protection of employees in the event of the insolvency of their employer; and what assessment the Government has made of the effect the UK leaving the EU will have on the operation of the Pension Protection Fund.","Biography information for Richard Arkless","Richard  Arkless","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46991","46991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596226","2016-10-11","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what assessment his Department has made of the value of UK access to the single market.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47051","47051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596227","2016-10-11","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what estimate he has made of the proportion of exports from the UK by volume and value which would be covered by rules of origin by sector in (a) 2016-17 and (b) each of the next three financial years.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47102","47102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596228","2016-10-12","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, which EU Commissioners he has met with since taking office; and when and where such meetings took place.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47331","47331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596229","2016-10-11","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many times his Department has used the services of (a) PwC, (b) Deloitte, (c) Ernst and Young, (d) KPMG and (e) other consulting firms since his Department was established; and what (i) work was undertaken and (ii) the cost to the public purse was on each such occasion.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47215","47215"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596230","2016-10-11","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, if he will take steps to let current EU staff and students know they are welcome to stay beyond the UK exit from the EU.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47192","47192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596231","2016-10-11","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, if he will take steps to make international collaboration between UK and EU universities a key part of the negotiations on the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47193","47193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596232","2016-10-11","Department for Education","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will take steps to guarantee to match any EU funding lost to universities and colleges.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47196","47196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596233","2016-10-11","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether his Department has made an estimate of the total cost to the public purse of repealing EU legislation; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47200","47200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596234","2016-10-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether the Government plans to continue to participate in the European Foundation for the Improvement of Living and Working Conditions after the UK leaves the UK.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47156","47156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596235","2016-10-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether the Government plans to continue to participate in the European Environment Agency after the UK leaves the UK.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47157","47157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596236","2016-10-11","Department for Transport","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the Government plans to continue to participate in the European Railways Agency after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47158","47158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596237","2016-10-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether the Government plans to continue to participate in the European Institute of Innovation and Technology after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47166","47166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596238","2016-10-11","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the Government plans to continue to participate in the European Defence Agency after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47160","47160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596239","2016-10-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether the Government plans to continue to participate in the European Training Foundation after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47167","47167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596240","2016-10-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether the Government plans to continue to participate in the European Agency for Safety and Health at Work after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47161","47161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596241","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the Government plans to continue to participate in the European Monitoring Centre for Drugs and Drug Addiction after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47168","47168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596242","2016-10-11","Home Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the Government plans continued participation in Frontex after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47162","47162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596243","2016-10-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether the Government plans continued participation in the European Intellectual Property Office after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47169","47169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596244","2016-10-12","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what assessment he has made of the implications for his Department's policies of the recommendations in the fourth report of the House of Lords Committee on the Constitution Session 2016-17, HL44.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47314","47314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596245","2016-10-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether the Government plans to continue to participate in the European GNSS Agency after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47163","47163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596246","2016-10-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether the Government plans continued participation in the European Centre for the Development of Vocational Training after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47171","47171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596247","2016-10-11","Department for Transport","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the Government plans to continue to participate in the European Maritime Safety Agency after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47164","47164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596248","2016-10-11","Department for Education","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether the Government plans to continue to participate in the European Institute for Gender Equality after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47159","47159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596249","2016-10-11","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether the Government plans to continue to participate in the European Centre for Disease Prevention and Control after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47165","47165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596250","2016-10-11","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what estimate he has made of the (a) value and (b) volume of imports by sector, from non-EU countries that were exported to countries in the EU as (i) components and (ii) free standing items in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46933","46933"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596251","2016-10-11","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what his policy is on the use of citizens' juries to define the UK's future relationship with the EU.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46839","46839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596252","2016-10-11","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, approximately how many (a) British and (b) non-British nationals are employed cleaning the Westminster estate of his Department.","Biography information for John Pugh","John Pugh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47561","47561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596253","2016-10-11","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what discussions he has had with Michel Barnier and on how many occasions about the UK's exit from the EU.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47279","47279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596254","2016-10-11","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he plans that the Multi National Headquarters for the command of EU military operations will remain at Northwood.","Biography information for Steven Paterson","Steven Paterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47458","47458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596255","2016-10-11","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, (a) how many and (b) what proportion of staff employed by his Department are non-UK nationals.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47414","47414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596256","2016-10-12","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many meetings his Department has had with representatives of each sector of the economy on exiting the EU since he took office.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47495","47495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596257","2016-10-12","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether he plans to implement a formal process for engaging with sectors of the economy affected by the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47496","47496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596258","2016-10-11","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he plans to require that EU staff employed at Northwood relocate to another country after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Steven Paterson","Steven Paterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47457","47457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596259","2016-10-12","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what steps the Government plans to take to protect the property ownership rights of UK citizens who own property in the EU after the UK has left the EU who (a) use the property primarily to rent out to others for holidays, (b) are the sole users, for holiday purposes and (c) are the sole users, and live there permanently.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47485","47485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596260","2016-10-12","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what steps the Government is taking to enable UK citizens living in other EU countries to remain there if they (a) have retired, (b) are working in those countries with habitual residence status and (c) are working in those countries part of the time but without habitual residence status.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47486","47486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596261","2016-10-11","Department for Education","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans she has to ensure that UK students will retain the ability and funding to study at universities elsewhere in the EU after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47480","47480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596262","2016-10-12","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether he has had discussions with representatives of Japanese businesses operating in the UK pursuant to the memorandum presented by the Japanese government to the Prime Minister at the recent G20 Summit.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47489","47489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596263","2016-10-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what his policy is on the UK's status as a signatory to the Euratom Treaty after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47517","47517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596264","2016-10-11","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what proportion of staff on the payroll of his Department who work in Westminster are (a) British nationals and (b) nationals of another country.","Biography information for John Pugh","John Pugh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47583","47583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584012","2016-10-10","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if she will provide an update on the mission-led business review.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46540","46540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584013","2016-10-10","Cabinet Office","2016-09-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when his Department plans to publish a list of its special advisers in post.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46562","46562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584014","2016-10-10","Cabinet Office","2016-09-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many officials of his Department have responsibilities for cyber security.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46600","46600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584015","2016-10-10","Cabinet Office","2016-09-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps he plans to take to improve the clarity of advice to government departments on protecting data.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46601","46601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584016","2016-10-10","Cabinet Office","2016-09-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the estimated annual annual cost to the public purse is of the Office of the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46602","46602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584017","2016-10-10","Cabinet Office","2016-09-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what his assessment is of the implications for the Government's policies on data protection of the findings of the NAO report, Protecting information across the government, published in September 2016.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46669","46669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584018","2016-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the Financial Reporting Council's ability to work with other financial regulators in the UK to address the systematic financial risk of climate change.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46611","46611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584019","2016-10-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the total estimated net present value was of all outstanding equity loan advances in UK residential property held by government departments on the latest date for which information is available.","Biography information for James Cartlidge","James Cartlidge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46626","46626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584020","2016-10-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the total value was of all reclaimed equity loans in UK residential property where the holder was a government department in each of the last five years.","Biography information for James Cartlidge","James Cartlidge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46627","46627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584021","2016-10-10","HM Treasury","2016-09-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the number of tax credit cases awaiting consideration by Concentrix.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46636","46636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584022","2016-10-10","HM Treasury","2016-09-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people in (a) Ashfield constituency and (b) Nottinghamshire have had a tax credit claim stopped by Concentrix; and how many such claims were subsequently reinstated by HM Revenue and Customs.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46649","46649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584023","2016-10-10","HM Treasury","2016-09-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the potential benefits to the economy of reducing both fuel duty and VAT on all fuels.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46652","46652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584024","2016-10-10","HM Treasury","2016-09-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to ensure that taxes are displayed on fuel purchase receipts.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46614","46614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584025","2016-10-10","HM Treasury","2016-09-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Urgent Question of 14 September 2016, on Concentrix, what processes and procedures he plans to put in place to learn lessons from that contract; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46588","46588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584026","2016-10-10","HM Treasury","2016-09-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, which companies tendered for the error and fraud tax credit contract with HM Revenue and Customs.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46589","46589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584027","2016-10-10","HM Treasury","2016-09-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what his policy is on the TUPE transfer of Concentrix staff at the end of that company's contract with HM Revenue and Customs.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46590","46590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584028","2016-10-10","HM Treasury","2016-09-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he plans for HM Revenue and Customs to deliver the services currently conducted by Concentrix under the tax credit error and fraud contract upon the end of that contract.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46591","46591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584029","2016-10-10","HM Treasury","2016-09-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the surplus/deficit in the National Insurance Fund is.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46560","46560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584030","2016-10-10","HM Treasury","2016-09-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what representations he has received from Concentrix on the non-renewal of its contract with HM Revenue and Customs.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46572","46572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584031","2016-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the Financial Reporting Council's operating and enforcement procedures for reviewing corporate disclosures in deterring companies from breaking the law on such disclosures.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46574","46574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584032","2016-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will take steps to ensure that the Financial Reporting Council has in place adequate processes to monitor disclosure on climate-related risk.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46576","46576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584033","2016-10-10","HM Treasury","2016-09-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will take steps to boost economic incentives for research and development in the aerospace industry.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46509","46509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584034","2016-10-12","HM Treasury","2016-09-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, for what reason HM Revenue and Customs Corporate Communications did not provide adequate notice to hon. Members of the drop-in session on constituent queries regarding Concentrix on 15 September 2016 between the time of 9.30 and 11.00am.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46545","46545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584035","2016-10-10","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what plans the Government has to replicate the system of Historic Environment Records used in Wales in England.","Biography information for Edward Argar","Edward Argar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46530","46530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584036","2016-10-10","Department for Transport","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what advice his Department offer local authorities on issuing Hackney carriage or private hire driver licences to people based outside their local authority area.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46501","46501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584037","2016-10-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will extend the Help to Buy scheme to enable first-time buyers to buy property off-plan in order to avoid being priced out by foreign investors.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46541","46541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584038","2016-10-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps the Government plans to take to support providers of supported housing affected by planned reductions in social housing rents.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46667","46667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584039","2016-10-10","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps she is taking to monitor compliance by betting shops with the gambling minimum age.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46657","46657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584040","2016-10-10","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what plans her Department has to ensure that telecommunications companies do more to protect customers from vishing fraud and similar scams.","Biography information for Stephen Hammond","Stephen Hammond","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46629","46629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584041","2016-10-10","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent discussions she has had with her Cabinet colleagues on the effect on tourism of an expansion of Heathrow Airport.","Biography information for Sammy Wilson","Sammy Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46664","46664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584042","2016-10-10","Cabinet Office","2016-09-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when his Department plans to publish the Codes of Practice for Part 5 of the Digital Economy Bill.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46677","46677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584043","2016-10-10","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what plans the Government has to provide additional funding to cultural and heritage projects previously funded by EU programmes when that EU funding ends.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46511","46511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584044","2016-10-10","Ministry of Defence","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the annual cost is of retaining each of his Department's 15 golf courses.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46512","46512"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584045","2016-10-10","Ministry of Defence","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when the first F35 Joint Strike Fighters are planned to be operational.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46513","46513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584046","2016-10-10","Ministry of Defence","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on armed forces and civilian staff of the planned sale of RAF Henlow.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46514","46514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584047","2016-10-10","Ministry of Defence","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent estimate he has made of the total revenue expected to have been accrued upon the completion of the F35 Joint Strike Fighter programme.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46506","46506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584048","2016-10-10","Ministry of Defence","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment his Department has made of the future sales projections for the F35 Joint Strike Fighter in the last two years.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46507","46507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584050","2016-10-10","Ministry of Defence","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans he has to increase the number of Departments of Community Mental Health.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46563","46563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584051","2016-10-10","Ministry of Defence","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans his Department has to procure general purpose frigates, and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46570","46570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584052","2016-10-10","Home Office","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 14 September 2016 to Question 46027, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that the provision of Compass accommodation to asylum seekers is not let from property (a) where the landlord has lost registered social landlord accreditation and (b) deemed unsuitable for human habitation by the local authority.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46571","46571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584053","2016-10-10","Ministry of Defence","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what progress his Department has made with the government of France on developing the scale and scope of the unmanned combat aerial vehicle programme agreed in January 2014.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46550","46550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584054","2016-10-10","Ministry of Defence","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what security-related sales and services the UK is (a) contracted to provide and (b) plans to provide to other countries in (i) 2017, (ii) 2018 and (iii) 2019.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46578","46578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584055","2016-10-10","Ministry of Defence","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to increase the level of retention in the Royal Navy.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46580","46580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584056","2016-10-10","Ministry of Defence","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps the Royal Navy is taking to maintain its warship repair capability after the sale of RFA Diligence.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46582","46582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584057","2016-10-10","Ministry of Defence","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he expects the Estate Optimisation Strategy to be published.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46583","46583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584058","2016-10-10","Department for International Trade","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what assessment he has made of the decline in defence exports.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46594","46594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584059","2016-10-10","Ministry of Defence","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many trained regular army soldiers there were in each of the Army's regiments and corps in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46584","46584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584060","2016-10-10","Ministry of Defence","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the Single Source Regulations Office's remit will be expanded to include government-to-government and Foreign Military Sales arrangements.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46595","46595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584061","2016-10-10","Ministry of Defence","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what his Department's target is for reducing the defence estate in each year until 2020.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46596","46596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584062","2016-10-10","Ministry of Defence","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what his Department's planned expenditure is for the Commonwealth War Graves Commission in each year until 2020.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46597","46597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584063","2016-10-10","Ministry of Defence","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what discussions he has had with his US counterpart on the US's decision to deploy the US Terminal High Altitude Area Defence system in South Korea.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46585","46585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584064","2016-10-10","Ministry of Defence","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many trained soldiers were assigned to the 3rd Division (UK) in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46586","46586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584065","2016-10-10","Ministry of Defence","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department plans to transfer the Army Air Corps' Islanders and Defenders to the RAF in 2018; and what plans his Department has for 5 Regiment's Army Air Corps command organisation.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46689","46689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584066","2016-10-10","Ministry of Defence","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Brimstone missiles have been used in Syria and Iraq to date as part of Operation SHADER; and what the cost of the use of those weapons has been to the public purse.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46644","46644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584067","2016-10-10","Ministry of Defence","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to address shortfalls in (a) recruitment and (b) retention in the Royal Navy.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46687","46687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584068","2016-10-10","Ministry of Defence","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent assessment he has made of the strategic military importance of Gibraltar to the UK and her allies.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46688","46688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584069","2016-10-10","Department of Health","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his policy is on hearing and sight tests being carried out by school nurses in primary schools.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46650","46650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584070","2016-10-10","Department for Education","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many school nurses were employed to work in primary schools in England in the academic year beginning in September (a) 2015 and (b) 2010.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46648","46648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584071","2016-10-10","Department for Education","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment her Department has made of trends in educational standards in Northamptonshire; and what plans she has to improve such standards.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46690","46690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584072","2016-10-10","Department for Education","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the effect of schools and sixth form colleges not accepting students who have failed to achieve a C grade in English and mathematics GCSE on availability of places for students who are required to resit those examinations.","Biography information for Dr Tania Mathias","Dr Tania Mathias","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46678","46678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584073","2016-10-10","Cabinet Office","2016-09-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many apprenticeships each government department will contribute to the Government's target of three million apprenticeships by 2020.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46658","46658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584074","2016-10-10","Department for Education","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans she has to ensure the Mandarin Excellence Programme is delivered to all local authorities in the UK; and how many (a) schools and (b) pupils in Birmingham are planned to start the programme this year.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46637","46637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584075","2016-10-10","Department for Education","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many (a) primary school places, (b) primary school age pupils on the roll, (c) pupils in excess of school capacity and (d) unfilled primary school places there were in Suffolk in academic year 2014-15.","Biography information for Jo Churchill","Jo Churchill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46618","46618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584076","2016-10-10","Department for Education","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children were absent from school due to having a mental health condition in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46599","46599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584077","2016-10-10","Department for Education","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether her Department has made an assessment of the effectiveness of the link between a family and their social worker in the event of a failed submission for a Care Protection Order.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46564","46564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584078","2016-10-10","Department for Education","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of pupils at maintained comprehensive schools achieved five A*-C grade GCSEs in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46517","46517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584079","2016-10-10","Department for Education","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to encourage companies to use digital funds from the proposed Apprenticeship Levy to pay for apprentice training for (a) ex-offenders, (b) children leaving care and (c) other vulnerable groups.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46532","46532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584080","2016-10-10","Department for Education","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which local authority children's services departments subject to improvement notices have been visited by Ministers of her Department in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46556","46556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584081","2016-10-10","Department for Education","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which directors and other equivalent post holders of children's services subject to improvement notices (a) she and (b) Ministers of her Department have met on what dates in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46557","46557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584082","2016-10-10","Department for Education","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of pupils at maintained comprehensive schools achieved five A*-C grade GCSEs including mathematics and English in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46518","46518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584083","2016-10-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent discussions she has had with (a) Cabinet colleagues and (b) stakeholders on repealing the birds and habitats directives.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46566","46566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584084","2016-10-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions she has had with (a) Cabinet colleagues and (b) stakeholders on reforming pesticide regulations from a precautionary principle to a risk-based principle.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46567","46567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584085","2016-10-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what representations she has made to the (a) Soil Association, (b) Rivers Trust and (c) RSPCA on running eco-friendly accreditation schemes for farmers.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46565","46565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584086","2016-10-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when she expects to receive the 2 billion green dividend that the Minister of State for Agriculture, Fisheries and Food announced before the EU referendum on 23 June 2016.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46581","46581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584087","2016-10-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many staff of his Department work on (a) the Yemen Desk and directly on Yemen and (b) all matters which directly or indirectly relate to Yemen.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46603","46603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584088","2016-10-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many staff of his Department are deployed outside the UK working on issues relating to Yemen.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46604","46604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584089","2016-10-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many meetings have taken place between Ministers of his Department and Ministers of governments which support the current government of Yemen since January 2016; and in how many such meetings was the civil war in Yemen discussed.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46605","46605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584090","2016-10-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many UK Government staff are seconded to or directly assist the UK Special Envoy to Yemen and his team.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46607","46607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584091","2016-10-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many UK Government staff were present at the UN-sponsored Yemeni peace talks in Kuwait in August 2016.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46608","46608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584092","2016-10-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his European counterparts on tackling human trafficking.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46615","46615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584093","2016-10-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that organisations providing humanitarian relief in (a) Madaya, (b) Daraya and (c) Aleppo have unimpeded access to the children in those areas.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46624","46624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584094","2016-10-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the Government plans to appoint a new Special Envoy to (a) Yemen and (b) Oman.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46606","46606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584095","2016-10-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, which of the recommendations made by the APPG for Yemen in its report, Conflict in Yemen, the forgotten crisis, published in October 2015 have been adopted by his Department.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46609","46609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584096","2016-10-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he plans to take steps to bring about an international commission into the killings in Rabaa in June 2013.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46553","46553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584097","2016-10-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with officials of the Egyptian government on the killings in Rabaa in June 2013.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46554","46554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584098","2016-10-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he plans to discuss the situation in the Maldives with John Kerry.","Biography information for Sir Hugo Swire","Mr Hugo Swire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46538","46538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584099","2016-10-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to the US in respect of coalition obligations to exclude from forces preparing to expel Daesh from Mosul any militias which are assessed as lacking respect for (a) human rights and (b) the laws of war; and what assessment he has made in such regards of the Shiite militia Hashd al-Shaabi.","Biography information for Dr Julian Lewis","Dr Julian Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46544","46544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584100","2016-10-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if his Department will make an assessment of the implications for Spain's capacity to affect commercial activity of the three mile limit of Gibraltar's territorial waters; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46548","46548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584101","2016-10-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to (a) help strengthen and lengthen the recently announced ceasefire in Syria and (b) ensure that humanitarian access in that area remains practicable.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46625","46625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584102","2016-10-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his Department plans to make extension of the 1966 UK-US Agreement on the British Indian Ocean Territory conditional on a commitment by both parties to support and facilitate resettlement of the Chagossians.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46641","46641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584103","2016-10-10","Department for International Development","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what representations her Department has received on reports that Syrian businesses approved by the EU and by the US government have received aid payments from the UN mission in Syria.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46682","46682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584104","2016-10-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what planning his Department is carrying out to prepare for the change of US President; and what assessment his Department has made of  the implications for the UK-US relationship of the (a) Republican and (b) Democratic Presidential candidates being elected.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46696","46696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584105","2016-10-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policy of the UN Secretary-General's statement of 11 July 2016 on events in South Sudan; and whether the Government supports calls for an arms embargo to that country and the strengthening of the UN mission in South Sudan in the light of its response to those events.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46683","46683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584106","2016-10-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what (a) policy his Department follows and (b) advice his Department gives to staff travelling to malarial regions regarding the use of Lariam as an anti-malarial drug; and what records his Department holds on the number of times (i) Lariam and (ii) alternative anti-malarial drugs have been prescribed to staff in his Department in the last three years.","Biography information for Dr Julian Lewis","Dr Julian Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46679","46679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584107","2016-10-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the implications for his Department's policies of the cases of (a) Ali al Nimr, (b) Dawoud al Marhoon and (c) Abdullah al Zaher who were sentenced to death as children for participating in political protests in Saudi Arabia.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46684","46684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584108","2016-10-10","Department of Health","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many deaths have occurred in the last five years following abortions provided through the NHS and carried out by the private sector.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46661","46661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584109","2016-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will issue a response to Early Day Motion 400, on applying the results of experiments on animals to human patients, tabled on 5 September 2016.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46676","46676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584110","2016-10-10","Department of Health","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect of NHS England's clinical policy prioritisation process for specialised services on the provision of treatment to patients in the devolved nations; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Nick Thomas-Symonds","Nick Thomas-Symonds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46643","46643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584111","2016-10-10","Department of Health","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions he has had with (a) the Care Quality Commission and (b) Marie Stopes International on the suspension of Marie Stopes' abortion services in the UK.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46662","46662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584112","2016-10-10","Department of Health","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he plans to publish the mandate to Health Education England for 2016-17; and whether he plans that that mandate will reference the strategic review of the cancer workforce recommended in the England Cancer Strategy.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46638","46638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584113","2016-10-10","Department of Health","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department plans to continue to support Commissioning through Evaluation; and whether he plans to maintain patient access to that programme whilst a formal decision is made on its future.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46639","46639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584114","2016-10-10","Department of Health","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to meet patient representatives to discuss the outcomes of the NHS England clinical policy prioritisation process for specialised services.","Biography information for Nick Thomas-Symonds","Nick Thomas-Symonds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46642","46642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584115","2016-10-10","Department of Health","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what measures are in place to ensure that (a) vulnerable women and (b) under 18s who undergo abortions receive follow-up support.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46660","46660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584116","2016-10-10","Department of Health","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, for how long it is planned that Commissioning through Evaluation will be in the assessment phase.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46500","46500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584117","2016-10-10","Department of Health","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will estimate the forecast size of the financial deficit of (a) Nottingham City, (b) Nottingham West, (c) Nottingham North and East and (d) Rushcliffe Clinical Commissioning Group in 2021.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46520","46520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584118","2016-10-10","Department of Health","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he plans to publish the sustainability and transformation plan for Nottinghamshire.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46519","46519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584119","2016-10-10","Department of Health","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he plans to publish NHS Sustainability and Transformation Plans for South East London.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46523","46523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584120","2016-10-10","Department of Health","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much has been spent on the Better Health Programme and predecessor programmes examining the future configuration at Darlington Memorial Hospital to date.","Biography information for Jenny Chapman","Jenny Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46528","46528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584121","2016-10-10","Department of Health","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the performance of the North East Ambulance Service.","Biography information for Jenny Chapman","Jenny Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46527","46527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584122","2016-10-10","Department of Health","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 12 September 2016 to Question 44394, what assessment his Department has made of the implications for its policies of the finding in the NSPCC report, entitled Transforming mental health services for children who have experienced abuse, published in June 2016, that 14 per cent of Local Transformation Plans contained an adequate needs assessment for children who have been abused or neglected; and if he will issue further guidance to clinical commissioning groups on ensuring such plans include such an assessment.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46505","46505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584123","2016-10-10","Department of Health","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of NHS England in achieving high quality community care for all.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46555","46555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584124","2016-10-10","Department of Health","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many neonatal units meet the standard for overnight accommodation for parents as recommended in paragraph 3.11 of the Toolkit for High-Quality Neonatal Services, published by his Department in 2009.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46543","46543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584125","2016-10-10","Department of Health","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the difference between available funding and the cost of providing NHS services in (a) Nottingham City, (b) Nottingham West, (c) Nottingham North and East and (d) Rushcliffe clinical commissioning groups.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46546","46546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584126","2016-10-10","Department of Health","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that ending the NHS bursaries for nurses does not deter people from training to be a mental health nurse.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46598","46598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584127","2016-10-10","Home Office","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what funding her Department has provided to support victims of human trafficking in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46616","46616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584128","2016-10-10","Home Office","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the daily payment for unaccompanied asylum seeking children was for (a) under 16 and (b) 16-17 year olds in each of the last six financial years.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46542","46542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584129","2016-10-10","Home Office","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that farmers continue to have access to sufficient seasonal labourers after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46569","46569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584130","2016-10-10","Home Office","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people the Government sought to deport from the UK in 2015-16 where the immigration status application had not been finally determined.","Biography information for Rob Marris","Rob Marris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46534","46534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584131","2016-10-10","Home Office","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 5 September 2016 to Question 43315, on asylum: families, what additional support her Department provides to (a) requesting member states and (b) such people who have not had their asylum claims granted.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46539","46539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584132","2016-10-10","Department for Transport","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of security at London City Airport after the recent protestor security breach.","Biography information for Will Quince","Will Quince","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46525","46525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584133","2016-10-10","Home Office","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications by Syrian nationals for UK visitor visas have been (a) received and (b) granted in each annual quarter for the last three years.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46521","46521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584134","2016-10-10","Home Office","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent estimate her Department has made of the number of people in the UK who have been trafficked.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46617","46617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584135","2016-10-10","Home Office","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what information her Department holds on the incidence of vishing fraud.","Biography information for Stephen Hammond","Stephen Hammond","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46628","46628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584136","2016-10-10","Department for International Development","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent assessment she has made of the humanitarian situation on the ground in Yemen.","Biography information for Edward Argar","Edward Argar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46633","46633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584137","2016-10-10","Department for International Development","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what progress her Department has made on increasing the volume of aid delivered on the ground in Yemen in the last six months.","Biography information for Edward Argar","Edward Argar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46635","46635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584138","2016-10-10","Department for International Development","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that its humanitarian response in Mosul minimises child protection risks.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46621","46621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584139","2016-10-10","Department for International Development","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that its humanitarian response in Mosul does not involve screening procedures for children which separate them from their families.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46622","46622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584140","2016-10-10","Department for International Development","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether her Department has provided aid payments to Syrian businesses which have been approved by the EU and the US government.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46685","46685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584141","2016-10-10","Department for International Development","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much her Department plans to spend on supporting low-income communities to access renewable energy in developing countries in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46529","46529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584142","2016-10-10","Department for International Development","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, which private consultancy firm her Department holds a contract with; what the value is of each such contract; and what services are being provided by each of those consultancy firms.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46516","46516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584143","2016-10-10","Department for International Development","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent discussions she has had with her ministerial colleagues in other departments on the use of the development aid budget by those departments; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46502","46502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584144","2016-10-10","Department for International Development","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, which of the recommendations made by the APPG for Yemen in its report, Conflict in Yemen, the forgotten crisis, published in October 2015 have been adopted by her Department.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46610","46610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584145","2016-10-10","Department for International Development","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what funding her Department is providing for children displaced in the Iraq conflict against Daesh; and what that funding will be used for.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46623","46623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584146","2016-10-10","Ministry of Justice","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what prisons and security-related sales and services the UK is (a) contracted to provide and (b) planning to provide to other countries in (i) 2017, (ii) 2018 and (iii) 2019.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46577","46577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584147","2016-10-10","Ministry of Justice","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate her Department has made of the cost of an appeal being cancelled at (a) First-tier Tribunal and (b) Upper-tier Tribunal due to documents from the Home Office not being submitted before the hearing date in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46503","46503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584148","2016-10-10","Ministry of Justice","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many decisions taken on claims for (a) employment and support allowance and (b) personal independence payment have been appealed in (i) Bury St Edmunds (ii) Suffolk and (iii) the UK in each of the last five years; and how many of those appeals have been successful.","Biography information for Jo Churchill","Jo Churchill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46619","46619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584149","2016-10-10","Ministry of Justice","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment she has made of the potential effect of the introduction of a higher normal pension age in the Alpha pension scheme on the life expectancy of prison officers after retirement.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46654","46654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584150","2016-10-10","Ministry of Justice","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment she has made of the potential effect on the number of medical and injury awards to staff of raising the pension age of prison officers and other frontline uniformed staff.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46655","46655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584151","2016-10-10","Prime Minister","2016-09-15","To ask the Prime Minister, pursuant to the Answer of 12 September 2016 to Question 45481, where the information on Parliamentary Private Secretaries has been published; and at what time on 12 September 2016 that information was published.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46665","46665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584152","2016-10-10","Scotland Office","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what recent discussions he has had with Scottish businesses and trade bodies in Scotland about opportunities for overseas trade.","Biography information for Mr Peter Bone","Mr Peter Bone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46668","46668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584153","2016-10-10","Department for Transport","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what change there has been in passenger numbers on trains in Suffolk since 2010.","Biography information for Jo Churchill","Jo Churchill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46620","46620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584154","2016-10-10","Department for Transport","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what his policy is on rail companies charging taxi drivers to use taxi ranks at train stations.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46630","46630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584155","2016-10-10","Department for Transport","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much Southern Railway has paid in compensation to Network Rail since the start of that franchise.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46631","46631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584156","2016-10-10","Department for Transport","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much Southern Railway (a) has paid to passengers in compensation and (b) received in compensation from Network Rail since the start of that franchise.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46632","46632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584157","2016-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will bring forward proposals to establish an independent body to monitor fuel pricing.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46653","46653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584158","2016-10-10","Department for Transport","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the Answer of 23 March 2016, to Question 31738, when he plans to publish the findings of the London and South Coast Rail Corridor Study.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46666","46666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584159","2016-10-10","Department for Transport","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when his Department expects an updated Strategic Noise Map for Edinburgh Airport to be available.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46656","46656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584160","2016-10-10","Department for Transport","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect of the outcome of the EU referendum on the timetable for a decision on Heathrow expansion.","Biography information for Sammy Wilson","Sammy Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46663","46663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584161","2016-10-10","Department for Transport","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department plans to fund transport infrastructure projects that are completely or partly funded by EU programmes after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46680","46680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584162","2016-10-10","Department for Transport","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he plans to announce the composition of the project board for Southern Rail, announced on 1 September 2016.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46504","46504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584163","2016-10-10","Department for Transport","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when the next appraisal of the High Speed 2 project is planned.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46508","46508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584164","2016-10-10","Department for Transport","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect of expanding Heathrow Airport on Belfast International's ability to establish its own direct international connections.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46522","46522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584165","2016-10-10","Department for Transport","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what advice his Department provides to local authorities on the issuing of Hackney carriages and private hire driver licences to individuals based outside their own local authority.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46515","46515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584166","2016-10-10","Department for Transport","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when his Department plans to publish its responses to the consumer group, Which?, super-complaint on rail delays compensation made to the Office of Rail and Road.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46524","46524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584167","2016-10-10","Department for Transport","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will take steps to ensure that people who lose their driving licence on the grounds of poor vision and subsequently receive a letter from their optometrist confirming that their vision meets the required standards can have their driving licence reinstated quickly.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46551","46551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584168","2016-10-10","Department for Transport","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with the Northern Ireland Executive on the introduction of a graduated licence system for young drivers.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46552","46552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584169","2016-10-10","Department for Transport","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much in compensation payments has been paid by Network Rail to Govia Thameslink Railway since the start of that franchise.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46558","46558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584170","2016-10-10","Department for Transport","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much in compensation payments has been paid by Govia Thameslink Railway to customers since the start of that franchise.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46559","46559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584171","2016-10-10","Department for Transport","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make it his policy to seek compensation for passengers from Abellio Greater Anglia.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46561","46561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584172","2016-10-10","Department for Transport","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will assess the potential merits of introducing more incentives to encourage motorists to use cleaner fuels and public transport.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46613","46613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584173","2016-10-10","Department for Transport","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what progress has been made on implementing the proposal in the Aviation Policy Framework to ensure that the Civil Aviation Authority considers opportunities to mitigate helicopter noise when dealing with any relevant airspace change proposals when updating guidance on environmental objectives.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46592","46592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584174","2016-10-10","Department for Transport","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the commitment in the Aviation Policy Framework to monitor the effect of helicopter movements in London, what information has been collected since the publication of that framework on the effect of such movements; and what steps he is taking to make such data available to the public.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46593","46593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584175","2016-10-10","Wales Office","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what recent discussions he has had with Ministers of the Welsh Government on the Swansea Tidal Lagoon project; and what recent assessment he has made of progress on that project as a result of those discussions.","Biography information for Edward Argar","Edward Argar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46634","46634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584176","2016-10-10","Women and Equalities","2016-09-15","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of provisions in the Disability Discrimination Act 1995 and the Equality Act 2010 in improving access for self-employed disabled people to access professional networking events; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mary Robinson","Mary Robinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46549","46549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584177","2016-10-10","HM Treasury","2016-09-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will postpone the proposed implementation date of the secondary market for annuities in April 2017 until an appropriate tax code for pensioners is finalised.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46568","46568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584178","2016-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment he has made of the capacity of Pension Wise to meet the volume of over the telephone and face-to-face appointment requests it receives; and what plans he has to increase Pension Wise's capacity after the introduction of the proposed secondary market for annuities.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46531","46531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584179","2016-10-10","HM Treasury","2016-09-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make it his policy to postpone the introduction of the secondary market for annuities until 2018 to ensure adequate time for the pension industry to plan for the introduction of that market.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46537","46537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584180","2016-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what progress the Government has made to reduce the disability employment gap.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46533","46533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584181","2016-10-10","HM Treasury","2016-09-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what progress his Department is making on the implementation of the proposed secondary market for annuities.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46535","46535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584182","2016-10-10","HM Treasury","2016-09-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the length of time between the publication of his Department's planned consultation on a proposed secondary market for annuities and the planned introduction of that market for the pensions industry to prepare for that introduction; and if he will make an assessment of the effect of that period on the effective introduction of that market.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46536","46536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584184","2016-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to written statement WS154 of 15 September 2016, how he plans that the localised pots will meet demand on supported housing.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46671","46671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584185","2016-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what provision the Government has made for the long-term future of the Joint Work and Health Unit.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46659","46659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584186","2016-10-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to written statement WS154 of 15 September 2016, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the 1 per cent reduction for supported housing on providers of that housing.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46670","46670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584187","2016-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many adults in Ashfield constituency have received carer's allowance for caring for children under the age of 16 in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46647","46647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584188","2016-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans he has to monitor the effect of a new funding system for supported housing on people with a learning disability.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46645","46645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584189","2016-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many under 16s in Ashfield constituency have received personal independence payment or disability living allowance in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46651","46651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584190","2016-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether it is his policy that people with a learning disability will continue to be entitled to independent living after the introduction of the new funding system for supported housing.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46673","46673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584191","2016-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make it his policy to implement annual uprating to ensure that funding matches demand for supported housing.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46672","46672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584192","2016-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many respondents to the first consultation on reforming housing benefit for supported housing in 2011 responded that a localised pot would support the right of disabled people to live independently.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46646","46646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584193","2016-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether he plans that the new funding system planned for 2019/20 will apply to existing supported housing tenants.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46674","46674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584194","2016-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what comparative assessment he has made of the potential risk of a cyber attack at the Hinkley C nuclear facility and other such nuclear facilities.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46681","46681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584195","2016-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the company annual turnover threshold is for government intervention to block any sale or transfer of the ownership of critical infrastructure; on what occasions that threshold has been crossed; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46695","46695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584196","2016-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, for what reasons his Department has not renegotiated the Contract for Difference for Hinkley Point C; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46694","46694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584197","2016-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to his oral statement of 15 September 2016 on Hinkley Point C, how the measures proposed in that statement will affect the Contract for Difference for that project.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46691","46691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584198","2016-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to his oral statement of 15 September, how the measures announced in that statement will increase security at the Hinkley C project.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46692","46692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584199","2016-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether EDF will incur a penalty in the event that Hinkley Point C starts to generate electricity by 2025.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46693","46693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584200","2016-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment his Department made before the announcement of 15 September 2016 of the extent of the potential security issue facing the development of Hinkley Point C.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46640","46640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584201","2016-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what discussions he has had with the Department for Education on reskilling in the energy industry.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46612","46612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584202","2016-10-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations his Department has received on reports of the use of ammunition produced and exported by Primetake, a company based in Lincolnshire, to kill Abdul-Rahim al-Faraj by security forces in Saudi Arabia; and whether he plans to investigate such reports.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46686","46686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584203","2016-10-10","HM Treasury","2016-09-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what support he is providing to Fintech after the vote to leave the EU.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46510","46510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584204","2016-10-10","HM Treasury","2016-09-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to ensure that the Prudential Regulation Authority, the Bank of England and the Financial Conduct Authority are adequately ensuring that companies disclose the financial risk to their company associated with climate change.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46575","46575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584205","2016-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to prevent the loss of technologies being developed in the UK after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46547","46547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584206","2016-10-10","Ministry of Defence","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what arms and security-related sales and services the UK is (a) contracted to provide and (b) planning to provide in (i) 2017, (ii) 2018 and (iii) 2019.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46579","46579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584207","2016-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when he plans to publish his response to the results of his Department's consultation on tips, gratuities, service and cover charges that closed in June 2016.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46587","46587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584208","2016-10-10","Department for International Trade","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, pursuant to the Answer of 15 September 2016 to Question 46072, what plans he has to replace the Consolidated EU and National Arms Export Licensing Criteria after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46675","46675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584210","2016-10-10","Department for International Trade","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether it is the Government's position that the UK can sign new trade deals before the UK has formally exited the EU.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46526","46526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/584211","2016-10-10","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether his Department is undertaking sectoral analyses of the effect of the UK leaving the EU on different sectors of the economy.","Biography information for Mr Mark Williams","Mr Mark Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46573","46573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/597709","2016-10-10","Department for Education","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to increase opportunities for young people to access skills and vocational education.","Biography information for Tom Pursglove","Tom Pursglove","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 906532","906532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/597710","2016-10-10","Department for Education","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps the Government is taking to increase the uptake of Mandarin.","Biography information for Caroline Ansell","Caroline Ansell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 906530","906530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/597711","2016-10-10","Department for Education","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to reduce differences in urban and rural school funding.","Biography information for Sir Edward Leigh","Sir Edward Leigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 906535","906535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/597712","2016-10-10","Department for Education","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the potential effect of the provisions in the Higher Education and Research Bill on part-time and adult students.","Biography information for Margaret Greenwood","Margaret Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 906538","906538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/597713","2016-10-10","Department for Education","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that funding is in place to implement its policy of 30 hours free childcare.","Biography information for Dr Tania Mathias","Dr Tania Mathias","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 906536","906536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598498","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to improve the safety of maternity care.","Biography information for Rishi Sunak","Rishi Sunak","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 906509","906509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598499","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the performance of the Care Quality Commission in monitoring GP surgeries; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 906507","906507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598500","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to implement his Department's plans on childhood obesity.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 906511","906511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598501","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress has been made on implementing the recommendations of the independent Mental Health Taskforce set out in the Five Year Forward View of February 2016.","Biography information for Seema Kennedy","Seema Kennedy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 906506","906506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/598502","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patient episodes there were within the Kettering General Hospital NHS Trust in (a) 2005, (b) 2010 and (c) 2015.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 906510","906510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/599868","2016-10-12","Scotland Office","2016-09-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what steps the Government is taking to support businesses in Scotland.","Biography information for Craig Tracey","Craig Tracey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 906403","906403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583065","2016-10-10","Attorney General","2016-09-14","To ask the Attorney General, whether there are plans to review the nature and type of offences that are capable of referral to the Court of Appeal on the grounds of leniency of sentencing.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46370","46370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583066","2016-10-10","Attorney General","2016-09-14","To ask the Attorney General, on how many occasions, and on what dates, the Crown Prosecution Service has decided to prosecute medical professionals for abortion-related offences since 1997-98.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46456","46456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583068","2016-10-10","Cabinet Office","2016-09-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether it is his Department's policy to reduce the overall civil service headcount in the current Parliament.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46361","46361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583069","2016-10-10","Cabinet Office","2016-09-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether his Department has made an estimate of overall headcount and spending on civil servants across all Departments over the next five years.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46360","46360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583070","2016-10-10","Cabinet Office","2016-09-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate has been made of the forecast change in the number of people aged 80 and over between 2015 and 2035.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46354","46354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583071","2016-10-10","Cabinet Office","2016-09-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether the Interministerial Group on Clean Growth plans to continue to meet.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46366","46366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583072","2016-10-10","Cabinet Office","2016-09-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps his Department takes to ensure that government projects are delivered on time and within budget.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46376","46376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583073","2016-10-12","HM Treasury","2016-09-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what targets the Government set for Concentrix on reviewing tax credit claims for each month in 2016 and 2017; and what targets the Government set in relation to tax credit claims being suspended.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46382","46382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583074","2016-10-12","HM Treasury","2016-09-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 13 September 2016 to Question 45282, where staff who work at the Valuation Office Agency in Preston are planned to be deployed after the planned closure of that office; and how many staff at what cost at that office he plans  to make redundant after that closure.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46380","46380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583075","2016-10-12","HM Treasury","2016-09-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people in Preston constituency have their tax credits suspended.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46381","46381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583076","2016-10-12","HM Treasury","2016-09-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what processes his Department has in place to review decisions made by Concentrix which resulted in the suspension of tax credits.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46383","46383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583077","2016-10-10","HM Treasury","2016-09-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the number of cases of each risk type relating to error and fraud completed by SYNNEX-Concentrix under its contract with HM Revenue and Customs between May 2014 and October 2015.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46384","46384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583078","2016-10-10","HM Treasury","2016-09-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many high-cost, short-term credit firms have (a) been fully authorised and (b) had their authorisation denied by the Financial Conduct Authority.","Biography information for Yvonne Fovargue","Yvonne Fovargue","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46388","46388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583079","2016-10-10","HM Treasury","2016-09-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the average time taken was to complete an investigation into the alleged presence of an unreported adult in the household of a tax credit claimant in the past 12 months; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46393","46393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583080","2016-10-10","HM Treasury","2016-09-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate his Department has made of the number of people employed in the UK by the high-cost, short-term credit sector.","Biography information for Yvonne Fovargue","Yvonne Fovargue","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46389","46389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583081","2016-10-10","HM Treasury","2016-09-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the change in the (a) volume and (b) value of high-cost, short-term loans has been since January 2015.","Biography information for Yvonne Fovargue","Yvonne Fovargue","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46390","46390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583082","2016-10-10","HM Treasury","2016-09-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many high-cost, short-term credit firms are operating with interim permissions.","Biography information for Yvonne Fovargue","Yvonne Fovargue","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46392","46392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583083","2016-10-10","HM Treasury","2016-09-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much his Department has (a) collected in Libor fines since May 2015 and (b) expects to collect in Libor fines in each of the next three years.","Biography information for Ms Gisela Stuart","Ms Gisela Stuart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46398","46398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583084","2016-10-10","HM Treasury","2016-09-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with HM Revenue and Customs and Ministers of the Scottish Government on changes to the rates and bands of income tax in Scotland.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46421","46421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583085","2016-10-10","HM Treasury","2016-09-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many amendments to tax credit awards Concentrix have made due to error on behalf of (a) Concentrix and (b) since the beginning of the contract between Concentrix and HM Revenue and Customs.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46444","46444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583086","2016-10-10","HM Treasury","2016-09-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 12 September 2016 to Question 44656, how many (a) amber, (b) amber green, (c) red and (d) black performance failures there were between May 2014 and October 2015 in respect of benefits and credits error and fraud.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46445","46445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583088","2016-10-10","HM Treasury","2016-09-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to section A8.1 of the Benefits and Credits, Error and Fraud Adding Capacity 444 contract between SYNNEX-Concentrix UK Limited and HM Revenue and Customs, what the profiling techniques are that are used to identify non-compliance.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46422","46422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583089","2016-10-10","HM Treasury","2016-09-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the number of people who have had their tax credits stopped and subsequently reinstated by Concentrix in each of the last 12 months; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46494","46494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583090","2016-10-10","HM Treasury","2016-09-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the total value of the contract between his Department and Concentrix; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46490","46490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583091","2016-10-10","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of the potential benefits of the UK taking part in the European Year of Cultural Heritage proposed for 2018 by the European Commission for her Department's objectives set out in the Culture White Paper, published in March 2016 ; what assessment she has made of the implications of the outcome of the EU referendum on UK participation in that event; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46350","46350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583092","2016-10-10","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what representations she has made to the Football League and the Premier League on whether the Fit and Proper Person Test they use is appropriate and effective; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46442","46442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583093","2016-10-10","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what representations she has received from football supporters clubs in England and Wales on whether the Fit and Proper Person Test used by the Football League and Premier League is appropriate and effective; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46443","46443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583094","2016-10-10","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps her Department is taking to promote tourism in Scotland.","Biography information for Stewart Malcolm McDonald","Stewart Malcolm McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46429","46429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583095","2016-10-10","Ministry of Defence","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what progress has been made on the Future Combat Air System.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46409","46409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583096","2016-10-10","Ministry of Defence","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the state of readiness is of HMS Lancaster; and when HMS Lancaster will return to operations.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46411","46411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583097","2016-10-10","Ministry of Defence","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans his Department has for developing for a crewed successor to Typhoon.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46438","46438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583098","2016-10-10","Ministry of Defence","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many civilian casualties have resulted from the 26 brimstone missiles dropped by UK aircraft in Syria in 2016 to date.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46434","46434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583099","2016-10-10","Ministry of Defence","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many and what proportion of military personnel serving in the 77th Brigade served in the (a) Army, (b) Royal Navy and (c) Royal Air Force before joining that unit; and how many such personnel have not previously served in any branch of the armed forces.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46420","46420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583100","2016-10-10","Ministry of Defence","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many recruits have joined the 77th Brigade as (a) regular and (b) reserve personnel since the formation of that unit in 2015.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46419","46419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583101","2016-10-10","Ministry of Defence","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the UK plans to provide any assistance or reconnaissance intelligence for airstrikes against Daesh conducted as part of the Syrian Counter Terror agreement made by the US and Russia on 9 September 2016.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46448","46448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583102","2016-10-10","Ministry of Defence","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the UK plans to provide any assistance or reconnaissance intelligence for airstrikes against Jabhat al-Nusra conducted as part of the Syrian Counter Terror agreement made by the US and Russia on 9 September 2016.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46449","46449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583103","2016-10-10","Ministry of Defence","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the UK is a party to the Syrian Counter Terror Agreement made by the US and Russia on 9 September 2016; whether the UK plans to provide any assistance or reconnaissance intelligence for actions taken under that agreement; and whether British forces' operations in Iraq and Syria will be affected by that agreement.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46450","46450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583104","2016-10-10","Ministry of Defence","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much has been spent under each cost heading by UK defence attachs in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46342","46342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583105","2016-10-10","Ministry of Defence","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether an Airborne Collision Avoidance System and a Digital Advanced Flight Control System (Low Visibility Landing) were fitted to Puma helicopter XW229 at the time of its crash on 12 October 2015.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46486","46486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583106","2016-10-10","Ministry of Defence","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 11 April 2016 to Question 32492, to which countries RAF Reaper or Watchkeeper drones have been deployed on intelligence, surveillance and reconnaissance sorties since 4 April 2016.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46487","46487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583107","2016-10-10","Ministry of Defence","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 13 June 2016 to Question 40083, what assessment his Department has made of the feasibility of the British military conducting and supporting air drops of humanitarian aid in Syria.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46488","46488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583108","2016-10-10","Ministry of Defence","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he plans to publish details of the 8 million investment at the RAF base in Leuchars.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46453","46453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583110","2016-10-10","Department for Education","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of the Frontline and Think Ahead social work programmes.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46476","46476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583111","2016-10-10","Department for Education","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the (a) quality and (b) availability of PSHE in England.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46484","46484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583112","2016-10-10","Department for Education","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the levels of sexual harassment and sexual violence in schools.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46485","46485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583113","2016-10-10","Department for Education","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of (a) secondary and (b) grammar schools is rated by Ofsted as (i) outstanding, (ii) good, (iii) satisfactory and (iv) inadequate.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46499","46499"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583114","2016-10-10","Department for Education","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of non-selective schools in selective areas is rated by Ofsted as (a) outstanding, (b) good, (c) satisfactory and (d) inadequate.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46497","46497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583115","2016-10-10","Department for Education","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of secondary modern schools is rated by Ofsted as (a) outstanding, (b) good, (c) satisfactory and (d) inadequate.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46498","46498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583116","2016-10-10","Department for Education","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of (a) tutors and (b) students in higher education institutions was (i) male and (ii) female in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46371","46371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583117","2016-10-10","Department for Education","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent progress she has made on implementing 30 hours' free childcare for working parents.","Biography information for Alistair Burt","Alistair Burt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46451","46451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583118","2016-10-10","Department for Education","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that 16 to 18 year-olds take up apprenticeships.","Biography information for Alistair Burt","Alistair Burt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46452","46452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583119","2016-10-10","Department for Education","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will make it her policy to ensure funding parity for the fast track and graduate training schemes for social workers.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46474","46474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583120","2016-10-10","Department for Education","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when she plans to publish the Sussex Area-Based Review post-16 education and training.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46410","46410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583121","2016-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the extent to which UK universities are being excluded from joint funding applications to EU funding bodies by other EU universities.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46427","46427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583122","2016-10-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when she plans to publish the framework for her Department's 25-year plan for the environment; and what the timetable will be for (a) consulting on the plan and (b) publishing the final plan.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46423","46423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583123","2016-10-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when she plans to publish the 25 year plan for the environment.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46446","46446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583124","2016-10-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when she plans to publish the 25 year plan for food and farming.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46447","46447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583125","2016-10-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many lion trophies were imported into the UK in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46464","46464"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583126","2016-10-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment her Department has made of the effect on conservation in the country of origin of the importation of lion trophies into the UK.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46466","46466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583128","2016-10-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to reduce the number of lion trophies imported into the UK.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46467","46467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583129","2016-10-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations his Department has (a) received and (b) made to the Spanish government on (i) the burning of live bulls at festivals and (ii) bull-fighting in that country.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46462","46462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583130","2016-10-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations the Government has made to the Saudi Arabian government on the effect of its programme of air strikes on civilian centres, hospitals and schools in Yemen.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46495","46495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583131","2016-10-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent estimate his Department has made of the number of Yemeni civilians that have been (a) killed, (b) injured and (c) displaced as a result of military action by Saudi Arabia in 2016.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46496","46496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583132","2016-10-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions the Government has had with other members of the International Syria Support Group on reports by the UN that forces loyal to President Assad have blocked aid convoys from entering East Aleppo.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46491","46491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583133","2016-10-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of whether British arms exports are being used for political repression against Shia dissidents within Saudi Arabia.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46492","46492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583134","2016-10-10","Ministry of Defence","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the location and timing was of each known use of UK-supplied weapons in Yemen since January 2015.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46337","46337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583135","2016-10-10","Ministry of Defence","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the UK-supplied weapons are which are known to have been used in Yemen since January 2015.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46338","46338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583136","2016-10-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, which UK officials were present at discussions on the peace process in Syria between the US and Russia.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46339","46339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583137","2016-10-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his European counterparts on the peace process in Ukraine.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46340","46340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583138","2016-10-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his US counterpart on recent discussions on the peace process in Syria between Russia and the US.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46341","46341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583139","2016-10-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many country specialists for (a) Russia, (b) China, (c) North Korea, (d) the US, (e) Syria and (f) India are employed by his Department.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46472","46472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583140","2016-10-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to article 3 of the UN Convention on the Law of the Sea's classification for the breadth of the territorial seas not exceeding 12 nautical miles, for what reason Gibraltar has a three nautical mile limit on its territorial waters.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46430","46430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583142","2016-10-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the UK will support an independent, international investigation into alleged breaches of international humanitarian law in Yemen at the Human Rights Council.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46418","46418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583143","2016-10-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the outcome has been of recent discussions with the US administration on renewal of the military base in the British Indian Ocean Territory; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46439","46439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583144","2016-10-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of whether the Bahrain Ombudsman's investigation into the case of Mohammad Ramadan has complied with international minimum standards for torture investigations.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46413","46413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583145","2016-10-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what evidence his Department has received in support of allegations that the Bahrain Ombudsman's investigation into Mohammad Ramadan's has not met international minimum standards for a torture investigation; and what assessment he has made of that evidence.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46414","46414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583146","2016-10-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the Bahraini government on the failure of the Bahrain Ombudsman to inform his Department that it had received a torture complaint regarding the case of Mohammad Ramadan; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46415","46415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583147","2016-10-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he plans to discuss the political situation in the Maldives with the UN Secretary General.","Biography information for Sir Hugo Swire","Mr Hugo Swire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46404","46404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583148","2016-10-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had on putting the Maldives on the agenda of the Commonwealth Ministerial Action Group for the United Nations General Assembly.","Biography information for Sir Hugo Swire","Mr Hugo Swire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46405","46405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583149","2016-10-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with the Commonwealth Secretary General about the Maldives.","Biography information for Sir Hugo Swire","Mr Hugo Swire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46406","46406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583150","2016-10-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what he discussed in his recent meeting with his Maldivian counterpart.","Biography information for Sir Hugo Swire","Mr Hugo Swire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46407","46407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583151","2016-10-10","Department of Health","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what type of support his Department plans to provide for initiatives mentioned as best practice in the Childhood Obesity Plan in its roll-out in England.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46391","46391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583152","2016-10-10","Department of Health","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how his Department plans to monitor and assess the progress of the roll-out of his Department's Childhood Obesity Plan for Action in England.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46385","46385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583153","2016-10-10","Department of Health","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how his Department plans to raise awareness among schools and head teachers of solutions they can choose to help children enjoy physical activity every day.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46386","46386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583154","2016-10-10","Department of Health","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 13 September 2016 to Question 45067, whether the Sustainability and Transformation updated plans which will be submitted in October 2016 will be made publicly available.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46416","46416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583155","2016-10-10","Department of Health","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to promote breast cancer awareness during Breast Cancer Awareness Month 2016.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46426","46426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583156","2016-10-12","Department of Health","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of the implementation of the Healthy Child Programme; and what recent meetings (a) Ministers and (b) officials of his Department have had to discuss that Programme.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46403","46403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583157","2016-10-10","Department of Health","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, (a) when and (b) by whom the decision was taken to withdraw funding for the NHS retirement fellowship; and what evidence on the health benefits of fellowship activities was considered prior to that decision being made.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46425","46425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583158","2016-10-10","Department of Health","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how his Department uses used wheelchairs, zimmer frames, crutches and other ambulatory equipment.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46412","46412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583159","2016-10-10","Department of Health","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps are being taken to improve cleanliness in hospital wards within the NHS Mid-Yorkshire Trust; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46351","46351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583160","2016-10-10","Department of Health","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many complaints NHS England has responded to outside of the 12 month statutory limit for the period in which complaints can be made in each year from 2010 to 2016.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46352","46352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583161","2016-10-10","Department of Health","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the outcome of the ProtecT randomised trials into prostate cancer among men.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46353","46353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583162","2016-10-10","Department of Health","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the Government has agreed additional protections with the British Medical Association to protect junior doctors who are whistleblowers.","Biography information for Andrea Jenkyns","Andrea Jenkyns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46343","46343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583164","2016-10-10","Department of Health","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on patient care of junior doctors taking five days of strike action per month until the end of 2016.","Biography information for Andrea Jenkyns","Andrea Jenkyns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46344","46344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583165","2016-10-10","Department of Health","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which NHS trades unions have taken strike action resulting in the withdrawal of emergency services.","Biography information for Andrea Jenkyns","Andrea Jenkyns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46345","46345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583166","2016-10-10","Department of Health","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many times the Junior Doctors' Committee of the British Medical Association has (a) left negotiations already in progress and (b) refused written requests to return to negotiations on the proposed junior doctors' contract since any negotiations on that proposed contract began.","Biography information for Andrea Jenkyns","Andrea Jenkyns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46346","46346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583167","2016-10-10","Department of Health","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many amendments to the proposed junior doctors' contract the (a) British Medical Association and (b) management side accepted during negotiations on the November 2015 contract offer.","Biography information for Andrea Jenkyns","Andrea Jenkyns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46347","46347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583168","2016-10-10","Department of Health","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department has had discussions with NICE on the Afinitor form of everolimus.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46367","46367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583169","2016-10-10","Department of Health","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what reviews his Department has conducted into the NICE technology appraisal process (a) in general and (b) related to cancer medicines between 1999 and 2016.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46368","46368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583170","2016-10-10","Department of Health","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when NICE last approved a breast cancer medicine for routine use on the NHS through the technology appraisal process.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46369","46369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583171","2016-10-10","Department of Health","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the benefits derived for people with dementia from recent increased expenditure on dementia research.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46356","46356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583172","2016-10-10","Department of Health","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will ensure that there is adequate time for public consultation on the Cheshire and Merseyside Sustainability and Transformation Plan.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46481","46481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583173","2016-10-10","Department of Health","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will ensure that the Cheshire and Merseyside Sustainability and Transformation Plan is published in full before NHS England agrees transformation plans in October 2016.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46480","46480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583174","2016-10-10","Department of Health","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many deaths by suicide in each age group have been recorded within one month of being released from prison in England in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46482","46482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583175","2016-10-10","Department of Health","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to reduce obesity in (a) Birmingham, (b) the West Midlands and (c) England.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46463","46463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583176","2016-10-10","Department of Health","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many women waited longer than two weeks for an abortion (a) in NHS hospitals and agencies and (b) with private providers in each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46457","46457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583177","2016-10-10","Department of Health","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what data his Department holds on the average length of time between obtaining the first medical practitioner's signature and the second medical practitioner's signature for an abortion HSA1 form.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46458","46458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583178","2016-10-10","Department of Health","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, at how many (a) NHS hospitals, (b) NHS agencies and (c) approved private sector places abortions were able to take place in each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46459","46459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583179","2016-10-10","Department of Health","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans his Department has for replacing or renewing the National Stroke Strategy when it expires in 2017.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46460","46460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583180","2016-10-10","Department of Health","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what mechanisms his Department has for measuring the effectiveness of the National Stroke Strategy; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46461","46461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583182","2016-10-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment the Government has made of the practicability of prosecuting potential acts of genocide, crimes against humanity and war crimes committed in Syria and Iraq by radicalised UK citizens in British courts.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46455","46455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583184","2016-10-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the Government has (a) had discussions with and (b) made referrals to the International Criminal Court on investigating possible (i) acts of genocide, (ii) war crimes and (iii) crimes against humanity in Syria and Iraq by radicalised UK citizens.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46373","46373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583185","2016-10-10","Home Office","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people her Department has granted asylum to in each year from 2010 to 2016.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46378","46378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583186","2016-10-12","Home Office","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 7 September 2016 to Question 43711, if she will take steps to increase the number of transfers to the UK of refugees in camps in Greece with family connections in the UK.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46402","46402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583187","2016-10-10","Home Office","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make it the policy of the Government to enable councils in England to operate combined registration districts.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46428","46428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583188","2016-10-10","Home Office","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) Syrian refugees and (b) vulnerable persons from the Middle East and North African region the UK plans to resettle in the UK over each of the next four years.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46417","46417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583189","2016-10-10","Home Office","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the effect on police safety of the distinction between the offences of assault on a police officer or police community support officer and resisting arrest.","Biography information for Holly Lynch","Holly Lynch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46387","46387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583190","2016-10-10","Home Office","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the total budget was for West Midlands police force in each of the last seven years.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46436","46436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583191","2016-10-10","Home Office","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment she has made of the effectiveness of Action Fraud.","Biography information for Andrew Bridgen","Andrew Bridgen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46433","46433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583192","2016-10-10","Department for International Development","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, with reference to her article in the Daily Mail, entitled Too much of your money is simply stolen or squandered, published on 13 September 2016, in what areas of her Department's spending funding is being stolen or wasted.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46379","46379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583193","2016-10-10","Department for International Development","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what forecast she has made of which countries in receipt of UK aid will no longer require UK aid in (a) five, (b) 10 and (c) 15 years.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46336","46336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583194","2016-10-10","Department for International Development","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 13 June 2016 to Question 40083, what recent assessment her Department made of the feasibility of air drops of humanitarian aid in Syria.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46489","46489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583196","2016-10-10","Department for International Development","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what plans she has to increase investment in decentralised renewable energy in developing countries.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46493","46493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583197","2016-10-10","Ministry of Justice","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether she plans to publish a green paper on the case for a victims' law for consultation during this parliamentary session.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46465","46465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583198","2016-10-10","Ministry of Justice","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if she will make representations to the Criminal Cases Review Commission on expediting its investigations into the case of former Marine Sergeant Alexander Blackman.","Biography information for Richard Drax","Richard Drax","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46375","46375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583199","2016-10-12","Ministry of Justice","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 7 September 2016 to Question 44521, what information her Department holds on how many (a) petitioners and (b) respondents who were ineligible for legal aid were unable to afford legal representation in applications to the family court for child contact or residence applications in 2015; how many such petitioners and respondents alleged that they were victims of domestic violence from the other party; and whether her Department has undertaken monitoring of the effect of a lack of legal representation on those victims and their children.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46401","46401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583200","2016-10-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what plans he has to raise the situation of Rohingya refugees at the UN Summit on Refugees on 19 September 2016.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46399","46399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583203","2016-10-10","Home Office","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans she has to mark Anti-Slavery Day 2016; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lord Garnier","Sir Edward Garnier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46431","46431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583204","2016-10-10","Department for Transport","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will commission the Behavioural Insights Team to conduct research on efficiency and passenger journeys in the rail sector.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46473","46473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583205","2016-10-11","Department for Transport","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department plans to replace EU Regulation EC 261/2004 on compensation and assistance to airline passengers with a similar UK compensation system after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46400","46400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583206","2016-10-10","Department for Transport","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which authority is responsible  for the safety of (a) beach users and (b) swimmers at beaches in Gwynedd.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46397","46397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583207","2016-10-10","Department for Transport","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what proportion of total spending on High Speed 2 has been on (a) wages and (b) performance bonuses.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46394","46394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583208","2016-10-10","Department for Transport","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent representations he has received on child sexual exploitation and the licensing of private hire vehicles.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46363","46363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583210","2016-10-10","Department for Transport","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many child sexual exploitation issues prosecutions have been brought in relation to private hire vehicles in each year since 2000.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46364","46364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583211","2016-10-10","Department for Transport","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department has taken to ensure that the DVLA does not give out motorists' data to organisations which will misuse it.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46374","46374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583212","2016-10-10","Department for Transport","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many business cases for infrastructure projects submitted in previous years by his Department were accepted in the 2015-16 financial year in each region; and what the (a) value was of (i) public and (ii) private funds allocated to those projects in total in each region and (b) average length of time taken was for the Department to accept those cases.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46372","46372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583213","2016-10-10","Department for Transport","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of offering Public Service Obligation Route status to the Londonderry to Stansted Airport service.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46357","46357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583214","2016-10-10","Department for Transport","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of Simon Kirby's resignation from HS2 Ltd on achieving the 2026 target date for opening phase one of High Speed 2.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46358","46358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583215","2016-10-10","Department for Transport","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he last met Simon Kirby, Chief Executive of HS2 Ltd; and when he was made aware of Mr Kirby's decision to resign as Chief Executive of that company.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46359","46359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583216","2016-10-10","Department for Transport","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department has made an assessment of the potential implications for its policies of the European Court of Justice ruling of September 2014, Damijan Vnuk v Zavarovalnica Triglav C-162/13, on the requirement for all motorised vehicles used off-road to be insured.","Biography information for Sammy Wilson","Sammy Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46348","46348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583217","2016-10-10","Department for Transport","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans his Department has made to bring forward legislative proposals to implement the ruling of the European Court of Justice of September 2014, Damijan Vnuk v Zavarovalnica Triglav C-162/13, on insurance for motorised vehicles used off-road and on private property.","Biography information for Sammy Wilson","Sammy Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46349","46349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583218","2016-10-10","Department for Transport","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will take steps to inform rail commuters of the protections available to them under the Consumer Rights Act 2015.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46478","46478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583219","2016-10-10","Department for Transport","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make it his policy to establish a body with the remit of ensuring that the rights of public transport users are protected.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46475","46475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583220","2016-10-10","Department for Transport","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect of the tunnel and bridge tolls in Merseyside on the (a) finances, (b) employment levels, (c) employment choices and (d) road travel habits of residents of Liverpool, Wavertree.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46483","46483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583221","2016-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if his Department will make an assessment of the effect of the Government's welfare reforms on low-income households who are in fuel poverty since 2010.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46362","46362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583222","2016-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether the Government's planned Green Paper on disability employment will include proposals related to people with musculoskeletal conditions.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46377","46377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583223","2016-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what his Department's timetable is for publishing and implementing the secondary legislation required to implement the increase in the Pension Protection Fund compensation cap provided for under the Pensions Act 2014.","Biography information for David Warburton","David Warburton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46437","46437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583224","2016-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 13 September 2016 to Question 43629, what plans he has to review the aspects of the BIS 2020 programme that do not relate to staff posts and office locations in the light of the restructuring of government departments.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46435","46435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583225","2016-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many officials of the Department for Energy and Climate Change have not transferred to work at his Department; and what the cost has been to date of redundancy payments to such staff resulting from the changes to the machinery of government.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46365","46365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583226","2016-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will lay a revised departmental minute detailing the most recent estimate of costs of Hinkley Point C before Parliament; and if he will lay such a minute at least 14 days in advance of signing any binding contract for that project.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46335","46335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583227","2016-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what plans Innovate UK has to develop a business plan across the UK for liaison with universities on the promotion of greater innovation in private sector small and medium-sized enterprises.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46355","46355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583229","2016-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will make it his policy that consumers who wish to switch energy providers only have to make contact with the new provider.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46477","46477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583230","2016-10-10","Department for International Trade","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what discussions he has had with his counterparts in (a) China, (b) USA, Canada and Hong Kong, (c) Australia, (d) Brazil, (e) India, (f) South Korea, (g) Japan, (h) Mexico and (i) South Africa on negotiating trade deals with the UK.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46469","46469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583231","2016-10-10","Department for International Trade","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, when he plans to lay the Comprehensive Economic Trade Agreement between the EU and Canada before Parliament.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46479","46479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583232","2016-10-10","Department for International Trade","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what estimate his Department has made of the number of agreements that will need to be renegotiated if the UK is no longer a member of the single market; and which trade agreements those agreements are.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46440","46440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583233","2016-10-10","Department for International Trade","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what estimate he has made of the total annual value to the UK of each trade deal to which the UK is a party as a consequence of the UK's membership of the European single market.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46441","46441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583234","2016-10-10","Department for International Trade","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps he is taking to determine how many trade negotiators his Department will require in the next six months.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46432","46432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583235","2016-10-10","Department for International Trade","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what proportion of UK trade was with (a) Germany, (b) France, (c) Italy, (d) Spain, (e) Australia, (f) China, (g) Singapore, (h) US, (i) Canada and (j) other EU member states in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46408","46408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583236","2016-10-10","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, pursuant to the Answer of 13 September 2016 to Question 45148, if he will estimate the number of meetings Ministers of his Department have had with their international counterparts to date.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46424","46424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583237","2016-10-10","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what discussions he has had with Didier Seeuws on the UK's exit of the EU since his appointment to the EU special task force.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46395","46395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583238","2016-10-10","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many times he has met with Didier Seeuws since his appointment to the EU special task force.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46396","46396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583239","2016-10-10","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many times he has met with Guy Verhofstadt to discuss the UK's exit from the EU.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46470","46470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583240","2016-10-10","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what discussions he has had with with Guy Verhofstadt on the UK's exit from the EU.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46471","46471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583241","2016-10-10","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, pursuant to the Answer of 7 September 2016 to Question 44230, whether the staff in his Department are new employees or have been seconded from other Departments.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46454","46454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/583242","2016-10-10","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-09-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, when he expects to have a permanent address for his Department.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46468","46468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/582381","2016-10-10","Department for Education","2016-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the amount of student loans outstanding was as of 31 March in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46105","46105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/582382","2016-10-10","Cabinet Office","2016-09-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people earning less than 11,000 per year are full-time employees.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46102","46102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/582383","2016-10-10","HM Treasury","2016-09-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether public sector net debt will fall by the end of financial year 2016-17 in line with his Department's published estimates.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46106","46106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/582384","2016-09-15","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what information his Department holds on how many residential planning permissions which were granted in England in the last five years have yet to commence building work.","Biography information for James Cartlidge","James Cartlidge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46112","46112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/582385","2016-10-10","Ministry of Defence","2016-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Answer of 20 March 2015 to Question 227862 and pursuant to the Answer of 12 September 2016 to Question 45109, on Northern Ireland Universities Air Squadron, what assessment he has made of the full 24 student places to be filled.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46103","46103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/582386","2016-10-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department has taken to identify properties in Preston that are vulnerable to flooding; and what (a) funding has been allocated and (b) work is being done to protect such properties.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46109","46109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/582387","2016-10-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the UN Security Council on the persecution of Christians and other minorities living in Syria in the last three months.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46104","46104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/582388","2016-09-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the prospects of talks on North Korea under the Six Party talks format.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46115","46115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/582389","2016-09-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with the NATO Secretary General on North Korea's nuclear tests in 2016.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46116","46116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/582390","2016-09-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the implementation of UN Security Council Resolution 2270 (2016) on North Korea.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46117","46117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/582391","2016-09-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions his Department has had with the International Atomic Energy Agency on Iran's compliance with its obligations under the 2015 Joint Comprehensive Plan of Action.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46118","46118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/582392","2016-09-15","Department of Health","2016-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what treatment options are available to adults with uveitis to access anti-TNF treatment therapy who do not meet the exceptionality criteria of the individual funding request process.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46114","46114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/582393","2016-09-15","Department of Health","2016-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if the Government will consider setting up a system of Finnish-style care packages for elderly people leaving hospital and going into care homes.","Biography information for Oliver Dowden","Oliver Dowden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46121","46121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/582394","2016-09-15","Department of Health","2016-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if the Government will consider reinstating clothing grants for care homes for elderly residents who have just arrived from hospital.","Biography information for Oliver Dowden","Oliver Dowden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46122","46122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/582395","2016-09-15","Department of Health","2016-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many adult patients with uveitis have had access to treatment with anti-TNF therapy through the individual funding request process since July 2015.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46131","46131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/582396","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department plans to update the national strategy for sexual health and HIV, published in July 2001.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46110","46110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/582397","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many abortions (a) overall and (b) in cases where Down's syndrome had been identified were carried out at each (i) NHS hospital, (ii) clinic and (iii) surgery in Lancashire in 2015.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46107","46107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/582398","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which (a) NHS hospitals, (b) clinics and (c) surgeries in Lancashire have treated sexually transmitted diseases; and how many people were treated at each such institution in 2015.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46108","46108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/582399","2016-10-10","Department of Health","2016-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much his Department has spent from the public purse on the Act FAST campaign in each year since that campaign began.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46094","46094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/582400","2016-10-10","Department of Health","2016-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will visit the West Cumberland Hospital (a) before the start of the formal consultation stage of the Success Regime and (b) during the formal consultation stage of that regime.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46087","46087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/582401","2016-10-10","Department of Health","2016-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information his Department holds on how many babies were born by the side of the road in England in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46088","46088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/582403","2016-10-10","Department of Health","2016-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information his Department holds on how many babies were born in transit between Stafford and Stoke Royal University Hospital in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46089","46089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/582405","2016-09-15","Home Office","2016-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what guidance has been issued on the criteria used for deployment of police air support when a vehicle has failed to stop.","Biography information for Holly Lynch","Holly Lynch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46123","46123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/582407","2016-09-15","Home Office","2016-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment has been made of the availability of police dogs nationally; and what estimate she has made of the number of police forces that have introduced the recommended ratio of dogs to officers.","Biography information for Holly Lynch","Holly Lynch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46124","46124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/582414","2016-09-15","Home Office","2016-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to (a) encourage police officers and police community support officers (PCSO) to report assaults sustained in the line of duty, (b) standardise the procedure for reporting assaults across the 48 police forces and (c) standardise the procedures for investigating and responding to an alleged assault on an officer or PCSO.","Biography information for Holly Lynch","Holly Lynch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46125","46125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/582416","2016-09-15","Home Office","2016-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the effect of the severity of sentencing on deterring assaults of police officers; and if she will take steps to ensure that people who assault police officers receive the toughest possible sentences.","Biography information for Holly Lynch","Holly Lynch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46126","46126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/582418","2016-09-15","Home Office","2016-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to reduce the number of response officers (a) working as a single crew and (b) responding to 999 calls alone.","Biography information for Holly Lynch","Holly Lynch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46127","46127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/582420","2016-09-15","Home Office","2016-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to ensure the protection of single crew police officers.","Biography information for Holly Lynch","Holly Lynch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46128","46128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/582422","2016-09-15","Home Office","2016-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the effectiveness of spit hoods and the extent of their use by police forces.","Biography information for Holly Lynch","Holly Lynch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46129","46129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/582424","2016-09-15","Home Office","2016-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many police dogs are available at any given time to the West Yorkshire Police Force; and how such police dogs are geographically deployed.","Biography information for Holly Lynch","Holly Lynch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46130","46130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/582426","2016-10-10","Home Office","2016-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the implications for customer service of changing the operation of the Security Industry Authority contact centre from telephone to email.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46086","46086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/582427","2016-09-15","Home Office","2016-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions she has had with the Northern Ireland Executive on tackling radicalisation of young people by Islamist extremists.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46119","46119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/582428","2016-09-15","Home Office","2016-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions she has had with the Northern Ireland Executive on the counter extremism strategy.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46120","46120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/582429","2016-10-10","Department for International Development","2016-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what meetings she has had with those non-governmental organisations which receive funding from her Department since she took up office.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46099","46099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/582430","2016-10-10","Department for International Development","2016-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what meetings she has had with the Prime Minister on the status of the 0.7 per cent gross national income to be used as Overseas Development Assistance funding since taking up office.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46100","46100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/582431","2016-10-10","Department for International Development","2016-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what meetings her officials have had with non-governmental organisations which receive funding from her Department since she took up office.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46101","46101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/582432","2016-10-11","Ministry of Justice","2016-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been convicted of offences under section 127 of the Communications Act 2003 in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46111","46111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/582433","2016-10-10","Ministry of Justice","2016-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment her Department has made of the effect of prohibited steps orders on access to families across the Scottish English border; and on the movement of families and individuals across that border.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46090","46090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/582435","2016-10-10","Department for Transport","2016-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to address non-payment of tolls, charges, penalties and fees by non-UK drivers.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46097","46097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/582436","2016-10-10","Department for Transport","2016-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate his Department has made of the amount in tolls, charges, penalties and fees which remain unpaid by (a) commercial and (b) domestic drivers from outside the UK in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46098","46098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/582437","2016-09-15","Department for Transport","2016-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make an assessment of the effectiveness of those provisions in the Consumer Rights Act 2015 which relate to rail passengers claiming compensation.","Biography information for Will Quince","Will Quince","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46113","46113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/582438","2016-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether the contract with Maximus for delivery of the Fit for Work programme includes provision of public funding for taxi journeys for anyone (a) turned away from or (b) moved to a different assessment centre.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46095","46095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/582439","2016-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what guidance his Department has given to Maximus to ensure that centres used for Fit for Work assessments are accessible to wheelchair users.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46096","46096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/582440","2016-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, which three transitional options the former Pensions Minister, Baroness Altmann, commissioned from his Department to address the effects on women born in the 1950s following state pension equalisation.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46091","46091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/582441","2016-10-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimates his Department has made of potential cost of proposed transitional measures to address the effects on women born in the 1950s following state pension equalisation.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46092","46092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/582442","2016-10-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the deliverability of the recommendations of the independent report, Tees Valley: Opportunity Unlimited, published in June 2016; and what the timetable is for his Department to respond to those recommendations and set out a schedule for the implementation of any recommendations which are accepted.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46093","46093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/582443","2016-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to ensure that unspent financial resources from the Redcar Taskforce are spent in the local community.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46082","46082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/582444","2016-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what discussions he has had with the official receiver on the future of the former SSI UK site in Redcar since July 2016.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46083","46083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/582445","2016-10-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to negotiate a financial settlement with those banks in Thailand which have a controlling interest in the former SSI UK site to ensure redevelopment in a timely manner for the benefit of the local community.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46084","46084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/582446","2016-10-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to ensure that there is trades union representation on the Shadow Board of the South Tees Mayoral Development Corporation.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46085","46085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/582447","2016-09-15","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-09-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, when she expects the Dormant Assets Commission to report.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46220","46220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/582448","2016-09-15","Cabinet Office","2016-09-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the number of staff departing from (a) his Department and (b) the Prime Minister's Office who accepted jobs with Heathrow Airport Limited; and what estimate he has made of the number of staff arriving in (i) his Department and (ii) the Prime Minister's Office from Heathrow Airport Limited in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46249","46249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/582449","2016-09-15","Cabinet Office","2016-09-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether he plans to update the guidance issued to Government departments on drafting answers to parliamentary questions.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46275","46275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/582450","2016-09-15","Cabinet Office","2016-09-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many staff have been seconded into his Department from outside the Civil Service in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46276","46276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/582452","2016-09-15","Cabinet Office","2016-09-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will take steps to ensure that parliamentary questions are answered in full where the requested information is already available.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46277","46277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/582453","2016-09-15","Cabinet Office","2016-09-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the current work priorities are of the Open Public Services group.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46273","46273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/582454","2016-09-15","Cabinet Office","2016-09-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the current work priorities are of the Infrastructure and Projects Authority.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46274","46274"
