"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381152","2015-06-18","Department for International Development","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is taking to work with (a) other governments and (b) global organisations to tackle violence against children.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2499","2499"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381153","2015-06-18","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the number of homeless people in the UK in each year since May 2010; and what steps he is taking to prevent homelessness in the UK.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2500","2500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381154","2015-06-18","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he is taking to ensure that people with sensory loss have full access to subtitles and audio description whilst using on-demand content.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2501","2501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381155","2015-06-18","Department for Education","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate has she made of the number of teaching assistants employed in (a) England, (b) Lancashire and (c) Hyndburn constituency.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2491","2491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381156","2015-06-18","Department for Transport","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what provisions he has made for the use of green technology in the Government's new code of practice for driverless car testing; and what plans he has to extend the pilot test scheme beyond four cities.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2570","2570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381157","2015-06-17","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether implementation of gaining-provider led switching for broadband and fixed telephony has been completed.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2574","2574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381158","2015-06-18","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2015-06-15","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what assessment the Commission has made of the reasons for the difference between the highest and the lowest voter turnout in a constituency in the 2015 General Election.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2580","2580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381159","2015-06-17","Department of Health","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential risk to health of undergoing repeat abortions; and if he will take steps to reduce the number of repeat abortions.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2373","2373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381160","2015-06-17","Department for International Development","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department has taken to address the situation of refugees from Burundi; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2374","2374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381161","2015-06-17","Department for Transport","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what extra funding he plans to make available for the Access to All programme in the current funding period.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2375","2375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381162","2015-06-17","Department of Health","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the clarity and accuracy of warnings on anti-convulsant drugs for women with epilepsy who are also pregnant on the risk of developmental disorders and birth defects associated with the use of such drugs.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2376","2376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381163","2015-06-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department has taken to (a) address the security and political situation in Burundi and (b) support the emergence of conditions conducive to the organisation of inclusive and peaceful elections in that country.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2377","2377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381164","2015-06-17","Department of Health","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information the Government gave to doctors and patients about the risks for unborn children of taking certain anti-convulsant drugs in pregnancy prior to the warning issued by the Medicines and Healthcare Products Regulatory Agency in January 2013.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2378","2378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381165","2015-06-17","Department of Health","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information he has on whether his Department had knowledge prior to 2000 of the fact that the anti-convulsant drug Epilim, Sanofi Aventis, known previously as Sanofi Pharma, was potentially teratogenic to foetuses.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2379","2379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381166","2015-06-18","Department for International Development","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to (a) help developing countries create efficient tax regimes for multi-national corporations and (b) work with governments in other countries to ensure an equitable tax system for multi-national corporations in developing countries.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Mr Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2381","2381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381167","2015-06-18","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether the Government plans to set a binding 2030 decarbonisation target during this Parliament.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2382","2382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381168","2015-06-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment her Department has made of the impact of the Environment Stewardship scheme on promoting nature and wildlife.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2390","2390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381169","2015-06-18","Department of Health","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what meetings NHS England has had with the pharmaceutical company BioMarin over the last 12 months; when those meetings took place; and if he will publish the minutes of each such meeting.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2391","2391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381170","2015-06-18","Ministry of Justice","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what responsibilities the National Probation Service holds in relation to victims services; and what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of that service in discharging those responsibilities.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2411","2411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381171","2015-06-18","Ministry of Justice","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when his Department plans to approve the contract for the Secure College.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2412","2412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381172","2015-06-18","Department of Health","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he plans to take to expedite the (a) prevention, (b) testing, (c) diagnosis and (d) treatment of hepatitis C.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2413","2413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381173","2015-06-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the balance of trade in foodstuffs was in (a) the last year for which figures are available, (b) 2005 and (c) 1995.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2414","2414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381174","2015-06-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many applications were accepted during the operation of her Department's Environmental Stewardship Scheme; and what the total cost of the scheme was to the public purse.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2454","2454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381175","2015-06-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what consultations Natural England is required to conduct before accepting an application for an Environmental Stewardship Scheme.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2455","2455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381176","2015-06-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment her Department has made of the effect in terms of loss of amenities on surrounding properties where an Environmental Stewardship Scheme is in operation.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2456","2456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381177","2015-06-17","Department of Health","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how the Government plans to ensure that clinical commissioning groups spend  appropriate and proportionate amounts on mental health.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2459","2459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381178","2015-06-17","Department of Health","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that clinical commissioning groups take practical steps to give equal value to physical and mental health care.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2460","2460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381179","2015-06-18","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many fuel-poor households there are for which her Department plans to fund insulation measures over the next five years.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2416","2416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381180","2015-06-17","Department of Health","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps the Government is taking to improve support for children and young people with mental health issues.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2461","2461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381181","2015-06-18","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, when her Department plans to issue its request to local authorities to measure and report on their annual greenhouse gas emissions data.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2417","2417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381182","2015-06-17","Department of Health","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress the Government is making on ensuring that parity of esteem between mental and physical health services is fully delivered.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2462","2462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381183","2015-06-17","Department of Health","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to rebalance the NHS budget to ensure mental health care receives the level of investment needed.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2463","2463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381184","2015-06-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the benefit cap will be lowered to for individual (a) young adults, (b) pregnant women, (c) veterans, (d) disabled people and (e) other vulnerable adults who have dependents who are not children.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2464","2464"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381185","2015-06-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he plans to take to ensure that planned changes in entitlement to housing benefit for people aged under 22 do not adversely affect the (a) income and (b) access to housing of young adults.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2465","2465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381186","2015-06-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in the UK are not claiming what value of each benefit and pension entitlement; and what proportion of each benefit and pension entitlement is unclaimed.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2480","2480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381187","2015-06-18","Department for Education","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many new teaching assistants were employed in (a) England, (b) Lancashire and (c) Hyndburn constituency in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2492","2492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381188","2015-06-18","Ministry of Justice","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the average number of hours of purposeful activity delivered each week at each secure training centre in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2482","2482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381189","2015-06-17","Ministry of Justice","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the number of staff working in (a) secure training centres and (b) young offender institutions who are qualified to work with young people with learning difficulties.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2506","2506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381190","2015-06-17","Ministry of Justice","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, on what date he last visited a (a) secure training centre, (b) young offender institution and (c) secure children's home.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2507","2507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381191","2015-06-18","Ministry of Justice","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the number of young offenders who have taken part in restorative justice schemes in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2483","2483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381193","2015-06-17","Ministry of Justice","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he proposes to bring forward changes to the rights of children in the proposed British Bill of Rights.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2383","2383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381194","2015-06-17","Ministry of Justice","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to ensured children and young people in the secure estate have access to high quality training and employment programmes.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2384","2384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381195","2015-06-18","Department of Health","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of hospitals in London that deliver a full maternity service have 24 hours a day, seven days a week consultant presence on labour wards; and which hospitals meet those criteria.","Biography information for Heidi Alexander","Heidi Alexander","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2397","2397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381196","2015-06-18","Department of Health","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of hospitals in England that have a Type 1 A&E department have consultant presence on emergency wards for a minimum of 16 hours a day, seven days a week; and which hospitals in each region meet those criteria.","Biography information for Heidi Alexander","Heidi Alexander","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2398","2398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381197","2015-06-18","Department of Health","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of hospitals in England that deliver full maternity service have 24 hours a day, seven days a week consultant presence on labour wards; and which hospitals in each region meet those criteria.","Biography information for Heidi Alexander","Heidi Alexander","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2399","2399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381198","2015-06-18","Department of Health","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of hospitals in London have paediatric consultants present on children's wards for a minimum of 14 hours a day, seven days a week; and which hospitals meet those criteria.","Biography information for Heidi Alexander","Heidi Alexander","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2400","2400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381199","2015-06-18","Department of Health","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of hospitals in London that have a Type 1 A&E department have consultant presence on emergency wards for a minimum of 16 hours a day, seven days a week; and which hospitals meet those criteria.","Biography information for Heidi Alexander","Heidi Alexander","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2401","2401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381200","2015-06-17","Ministry of Justice","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many resettlement units for female offenders have been opened in each prison since October 2013; and what the capacity is of each such unit.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2457","2457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381201","2015-06-17","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the planned capital investment requirements are for the new generating capacity required to replace closing electricity plants; and what estimate she has made of the cost per Mwh of electricity generated by such plants in comparison with current electricity market prices.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2433","2433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381202","2015-06-17","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what information her Department holds on UK coal plants that intend to cease operations before June 2016.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2434","2434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381203","2015-06-17","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what timetable she has set for the completion of the carbon capture and storage commercialisation competition; and what progress her Department has made towards the announcement of a contract for difference for carbon capture and storage.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2423","2423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381204","2015-06-17","HM Treasury","2015-06-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the trends in the (a) EU energy trading system price for carbon and (b) all-in UK carbon price, including the carbon price floor, were in the last six months.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2435","2435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381205","2015-06-17","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, when she last met with the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills to discuss the carbon price floor and its effect on energy intensive industry.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2436","2436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381206","2015-06-17","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what discussions she has had with HM Treasury concerning the effect of the carbon price floor on UK energy security; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2424","2424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381207","2015-06-17","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what information her Department holds on which coal-fired power plants will be available for electricity generation in (a) 2017, (b) 2020 and (c) 2023; and what the generating capacity in mega watts will be for each plant in each of those years.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2425","2425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381208","2015-06-17","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, when she last met with representatives of the (a) coal industry and (b) coal fired electricity generating sector to discuss the effects of the carbon price floor on those sectors.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2437","2437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381209","2015-06-17","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, when she last met with the Secretary of State for Wales to discuss the impact of the carbon price floor on Welsh energy security.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2438","2438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381210","2015-06-17","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, when she last met with the Secretary of State for Scotland to discuss the effect of the carbon price floor on Scottish energy security.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2439","2439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381211","2015-06-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of direct costs to the energy intensive industry resulting from the introduction of legislative proposals on a carbon price floor.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2426","2426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381212","2015-06-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether he plans to bring forward legislative proposals to amend the measure of child poverty defined in the Child Poverty Act 2010.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2420","2420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381213","2015-06-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, when he last met with representatives of the energy intensive industry to discuss the disparity between (a) UK carbon prices under the carbon price floor and (b) such prices in the rest of Europe.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2440","2440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381214","2015-06-17","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the (a) fuel type and (b) individual generating capacity expressed as a proportion of the total maximum UK demand for electricity is for each (i) operating and (ii) mothballed UK-based nuclear generating unit.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2443","2443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381215","2015-06-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether he has made an assessment of the effect on tenants of capping housing allowance rate rises at one per cent per year.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2421","2421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381216","2015-06-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the effect of the carbon price floor on (a) carbon leakage rates, (b) the relocation of energy intensive industry overseas and (c) UK and EU carbon dioxide emissions.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2441","2441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381217","2015-06-17","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment she has made of potential savings for her Department's spending in capacity payments if the carbon floor price was removed.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2442","2442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381218","2015-06-17","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, for each operational nuclear power plant in the UK, what the available operating capacity in mega watts is; which of those plants have life extensions in place; for how long these extensions will last; and which of those plants have sought permission to secure further life extensions.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2444","2444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381219","2015-06-17","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the length of time taken was to re-establish commercial levels of electricity supply from a mothballed gas fired plant to the National Grid.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2445","2445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381220","2015-06-17","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, which power plants are expected to be decommissioned or closed in the next five years; what the expected year of closure for each such plant is; and what the individual generating capacity for each such plant expressed as a proportion of the total maximum UK demand for electricity is.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2446","2446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381221","2015-06-17","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what recent estimate her Department has made of trends in UK (a) wholesale and (b) domestic energy prices compared to those of the UK's G7 competitors.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2427","2427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381222","2015-06-17","HM Treasury","2015-06-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of revenue to be raised from the carbon price floor in (a) 2015-16, (b) 2016-17, (c) 2017-18, (d) 2018-19 and (e) 2019-20.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2428","2428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381223","2015-06-17","Ministry of Justice","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many female offenders are currently housed in each resettlement unit in each prison.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2450","2450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381224","2015-06-17","HM Treasury","2015-06-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what proportion of the total additional revenues raised by carbon price floor rates were retained by HM Treasury; and what proportion accrues to low carbon generators for (a) renewables  and (b) nuclear operators.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2429","2429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381225","2015-06-17","HM Treasury","2015-06-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he last met the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change to discuss the carbon price floor.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2430","2430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381226","2015-06-17","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, with reference to the Departmental Gas Generation Strategy published in 2012, which gas-fired power plants with planning consent are under construction in the UK.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2431","2431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381227","2015-06-17","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps her Department has taken to provide replacement electricity generating capacity following the closure of coal-fired power stations at Ferrybridge and Longannet; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2432","2432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381228","2015-06-17","Ministry of Justice","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to improve access to legal aid for people with mental health issues; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ben Howlett","Ben Howlett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2474","2474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381229","2015-06-17","Department for Education","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to improve the teaching of personal, social, health and economic education in schools.","Biography information for Ben Howlett","Ben Howlett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2475","2475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381230","2015-06-17","Department for Transport","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make representations to the Driver and Vehicle Standards Agency on permitting cycle racks on the front of buses.","Biography information for Ben Howlett","Ben Howlett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2476","2476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381231","2015-06-17","Department for Transport","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to promote joined-up transport ticketing systems in (a) Bath and (b) Bristol.","Biography information for Ben Howlett","Ben Howlett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2477","2477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381232","2015-06-17","Ministry of Justice","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many female offenders from each resettlement unit are currently doing community work on resettlement day release.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2478","2478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381233","2015-06-17","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many firearms owned by his Department (a) were lost or stolen and (b) are otherwise unaccounted for at facilities in the UK in the last two years.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2466","2466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381234","2015-06-17","Ministry of Justice","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many female offenders from each resettlement unit are in paid work while on resettlement day release and are paying 40 per cent of that wage to Victim Support.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2479","2479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381235","2015-06-17","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, in what year he plans to introduce a replacement for the SA80 assault rifle.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2467","2467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381236","2015-06-17","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when his Department plans next to inspect the (a) Bermuda Regiment, (b) Gibraltar Regiment and (c) Royal Montserrat Defence Force.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2468","2468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381237","2015-06-17","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what funds the Government contributes to the maintenance of the (a) Bermuda Regiment, (b) Gibraltar Regiment and (c) Royal Montserrat Defence Force.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2469","2469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381238","2015-06-17","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many personnel in his Department work on the Seedcorn initiative; and where such personnel are based.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2470","2470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381239","2015-06-17","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when his Department expects the Crowsnest system to be (a) available and (b) operational.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2471","2471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381240","2015-06-17","Home Office","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what her policy is on introducing a single tier Disclosure and Barring Service enhanced disclosure certificate.","Biography information for Ben Howlett","Ben Howlett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2473","2473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381241","2015-06-18","Department of Health","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the evidential basis was for NICE's draft clinical guidelines for the management of type 1 and type 2 diabetes in adults.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2485","2485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381242","2015-06-18","HM Treasury","2015-06-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much HM Revenue and Customs has paid to Fredrickson International for the provision of debt collection services by that company.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2486","2486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381243","2015-06-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will take steps to require fishermen to record the number of seals they slaughter.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2526","2526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381244","2015-06-17","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2015-06-15","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what criteria were applied by the Local Government Boundary Commission for England when deciding to commence a review of the local authority ward boundaries for the City of Newcastle upon Tyne.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2527","2527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381245","2015-06-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 15 June 2015 to Question 1656, if he will make an assessment of the effect of changes to the adult skills budget on learners in Liverpool.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Mrs Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2529","2529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381246","2015-06-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 15 June 2015 to Question 1849, which funding bodies his Department is working with to determine how reductions to the adult skills budget will be made; and if he will instruct the funding bodies to look at the effect of changes on learners in Liverpool.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Mrs Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2530","2530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381247","2015-06-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his Department pays the cost of ceremonial uniforms of overseas territories governors; and what the cost of such items was in the last financial year.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2520","2520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381248","2015-06-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his German counterpart on securing financial contributions towards the cost of UK thalidomide survivors' health needs.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Mrs Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2543","2543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381249","2015-06-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what his policy is on a purdah period before the referendum on the UK's membership of the EU.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2533","2533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381250","2015-06-17","Cabinet Office","2015-06-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will publish a list of people who have rejected honours since 1999.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2534","2534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381251","2015-06-17","Cabinet Office","2015-06-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when he plans to publish the updated list of Government Ministers and their Responsibilities.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2537","2537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381252","2015-06-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what discussions he has had with pension providers on problems in accessing pension benefits since 6 April 2015.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2550","2550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381253","2015-06-17","Ministry of Justice","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he has taken to implement the recommendations and conclusions of the Commission on a Bill of Rights report published on 18 December 2012.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2524","2524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381254","2015-06-18","Department of Health","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress the Mental Health Taskforce has made on developing a new five-year national strategy for mental health; with which groups and organisations that taskforce is consulting; when it is expected that taskforce will publish its final report; and whether that taskforce plans to publish an interim report.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2551","2551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381255","2015-06-17","Home Office","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Sunday Times article, British spies betrayed to Russians and Chinese, published on 14 June 2015, who authorised the senior Home Office official to make the comment quoted in that article.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2542","2542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381256","2015-06-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what guidance his Department has issued on interaction between concurrent local government boundary reviews and ongoing parliamentary boundary reviews.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2525","2525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381257","2015-06-18","Department of Health","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to his speech of 4 June 2015 to the NHS Confederation, when he expects to publish the obesity strategy; and what plans he has for consultation on that strategy.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2552","2552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381258","2015-06-18","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what representations Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer has received from (a) Talk Talk and (b) Sky on the structural separation of BT.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2553","2553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381259","2015-06-18","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what representations he has received from (a) Talk Talk and (b) Sky on the structural separation of BT.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2554","2554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381260","2015-06-18","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what representations the Prime Minister has received from (a) Talk Talk and (b) Sky on the structural separation of BT.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2555","2555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381261","2015-06-18","Cabinet Office","2015-06-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 8 June 2015 to Question 1492, what the proportionate baseline is for the goal of reducing the proportion of UK adults who lack basic digital skills by 25 per cent by 2016; and until what year he plans to reduce that proportion by a further 25 per cent.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2556","2556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381262","2015-06-18","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 9 June 2015 to Question 1710, if he will make an assessment of the potential effect of internet advertising on network requirements over the current Parliament.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2557","2557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381263","2015-06-17","Home Office","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she takes to ensure compliance with the UK's international legal obligations on non-refoulement when deporting people to conflict affected countries.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2561","2561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381264","2015-06-17","Home Office","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what reports she has received on the status of Majid Ali since his deportation to Pakistan.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2562","2562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381265","2015-06-17","Home Office","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assurances her Department received from the government of Pakistan on the protection of the basic rights, wellbeing and safety of Majid Ali upon his deportation to that country.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2563","2563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381266","2015-06-17","Home Office","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department took to ensure the protection of the rights and safety of Majid Ali upon his deportation to that country.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2564","2564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381267","2015-06-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people have converted their pension benefit with (a) a pension benefit valued at less than 30,000 and (b) a guaranteed annually rate attached to their pension scheme since 6 April 2015.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2566","2566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381268","2015-06-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people who converted or transferred their pension benefits were required to seek advice before doing so since 6 April 2015.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2567","2567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381269","2015-06-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people with a safeguard benefit attached to their pension benefit have converted or transferred pension benefits since 6 April 2015.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2568","2568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381270","2015-06-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people who converted their pension benefit since 6 April 2015 and were not required to seek advice will now be required to seek advice under the rules announced by the Financial Conduct Authority in Policy Statement PS15/12 published on 8 June 2015.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2569","2569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381271","2015-06-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, which exporters have taken legal action as a result of the Export Control Organisation's refusal to grant them an export licence since May 2010; when each licence was refused; what the intended country of destination was of each such licence; what type of licence was applied for; and what the outcome was of each such legal case.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2573","2573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381449","2015-06-18","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what discussions her Department has had with the Environment Agency on post-abandonment monitoring of onshore shale gas wells; and what steps she plans to take to ensure a monitoring regime is in place.","Biography information for Lord Lilley","Mr Peter Lilley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 900406","900406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381821","2015-06-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps the Government plans to take to promote British food and drink exports.","Biography information for Stuart Andrew","Stuart Andrew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 900421","900421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381990","2015-06-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many flood defence schemes are planned to begin construction under the Government's six-year flood defence programme in 2015.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 900419","900419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381991","2015-06-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps the Government plans to take to promote British food and drink exports.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 900422","900422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381992","2015-06-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps the Government plans to take to promote British food and drink exports.","Biography information for Craig Williams","Craig Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 900420","900420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/353850","2015-06-16","HM Treasury","2015-06-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people will be entitled to tax-free childcare who are not eligible to receive child benefit.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2314","2314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/353851","2015-06-16","HM Treasury","2015-06-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what his policy is on how parents will be asked to prove their identity when opening tax-free childcare accounts online; and what assessment he has made of the data protection implications of requiring parents to so prove their identities.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2325","2325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/353852","2015-06-16","Department for Education","2015-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, by what process the Government plans to run a consultation with the childcare sector on the provision of 30 hours a week free childcare.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2334","2334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/353853","2015-06-16","Ministry of Justice","2015-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if his Department will investigate the reasons for a delay of over two weeks in distributing paynotes and P60 forms to prison officers in Durham.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2330","2330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/353854","2015-06-16","Cabinet Office","2015-06-12","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answers of 3 June 2015 to Question 321 and of 11 June 2015 to Question 1056, what roles are performed by personnel involved in delivering the residential phase of the National Citizens Service programme; and what qualifications are required to fulfil each such role.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2364","2364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/353855","2015-06-16","Department for Transport","2015-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, for what reasons vehicle excise duty is no longer valid if a vehicle changes ownership; and whether motorists were consulted about that change.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2368","2368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/353856","2015-06-17","HM Treasury","2015-06-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 8 June 2015 to Question 574, what assessment he has made of whether the debt collection methods used by Rossendales comply with the standards required by HM Revenue and Customs of its debt collection agencies.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2339","2339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/353857","2015-06-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the projected cost is of his Department's appeal relating to the Information Commissioner's decision on his Department's report entitled Incapacity Benefits: Deaths of Claimants.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2369","2369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/353858","2015-06-16","Department for Transport","2015-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many vehicles the DVLA clamped in each month of the most recent year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2297","2297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/353859","2015-06-16","Department for Transport","2015-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much income the DVLA received from vehicle excise duty (a) fees and (b) fines in each month of the most recent year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2298","2298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/353860","2015-06-22","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the cost to the public purse was of renewable subsidies received by businesses in (a) Cumbria, (b) Carlisle District in (i) 2012-13 (ii) 2013-14 and (iii) 2014-15.","Biography information for John Stevenson","John Stevenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2309","2309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/353861","2015-06-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate her Department has made of the amount invested in onshore wind projects planned to begin before 31 March 2017 which have not yet received Renewables Obligation Certificates.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2306","2306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/353862","2015-06-17","Cabinet Office","2015-06-12","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much was accrued to the public purse as a result of candidates losing their deposits at the 2015 General Election.","Biography information for Simon Danczuk","Simon Danczuk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2296","2296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/353863","2015-06-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the total number of housing association properties in the London Borough of Southwark that would become available to buy under the Government's current proposal to extend the right to buy policy to housing association tenants.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2292","2292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/353864","2015-06-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many households with one or more person employed in the London Borough of Southwark claim housing benefit.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2293","2293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/353865","2015-06-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many (a) single parent households, (b) households with dependent children, (c) households with a disabled member, (d) pensioner households and (e) households with one or more person employed in the London Borough of Southwark are subject to the benefit cap.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2294","2294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/353866","2015-06-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many households in the London Borough of Southwark have been subject to the benefit cap.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2295","2295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/353867","2015-06-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans she has to accelerate the rate of new woodland planting.","Biography information for Neil Parish","Neil Parish","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2316","2316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/353868","2015-06-16","Department of Health","2015-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the findings of the National Audit Office in its report on the Care Act first-phase reforms, published in June 2015, on potential underestimation of demand for assessments and services for carers equating to a rise of 27 million in extra assessments and services.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2326","2326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/353869","2015-06-16","Department of Health","2015-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how his Department plans to monitor the costs to local authorities of the Care Act 2014; and if he will make it his policy to provide additional funding to the councils which experience increased demand for their services.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2331","2331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/353870","2015-06-16","HM Treasury","2015-06-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what information he holds on the proportion of residential mortgage lending that was on (a) an interest-only and (b) a capital repayment basis in each year since 1997.","Biography information for James Cartlidge","James Cartlidge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2346","2346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/353871","2015-06-16","HM Treasury","2015-06-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what information he holds on the proportion of buy-to-let mortgage lending that was on (a) an interest-only and (b) a capital repayment basis in each year since 1997.","Biography information for James Cartlidge","James Cartlidge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2347","2347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/353872","2015-06-16","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he is taking to resolve non-spots in urban areas as part of the superfast broadband roll-out.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2333","2333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/353873","2015-06-17","Department for Transport","2015-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many penalty charge notices for non-payment of the Dart Charge have been issued for since free-flow charging was introduced at the Dartford Crossing.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2342","2342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/353874","2015-06-17","Department for Transport","2015-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many penalty charge notices for non-payment of the Dart Charge issued since free-flow charging was introduced (a) have been in respect of foreign-registered vehicles and (b) remain unpaid.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2343","2343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/353875","2015-06-17","Department for Transport","2015-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the Government plans to implement the EU Cross-Border Enforcement Directive in respect of non-payment of fines.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2344","2344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/353876","2015-06-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to tackle food waste in supermarkets.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2313","2313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/353877","2015-06-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to ensure that the Government meets its commitment to eradicate child poverty by 2020.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2352","2352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/353878","2015-06-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will put in place support to assist care leavers with the payment of council tax.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2353","2353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/353879","2015-06-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many Jobcentre Plus staff have received training in careers advice and guidance since May 2010.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2370","2370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/353880","2015-06-16","HM Treasury","2015-06-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many PFI contracts are being negotiated across central government.","Biography information for Dame Margaret Hodge","Margaret Hodge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2360","2360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/353881","2015-06-16","HM Treasury","2015-06-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many PFI projects across central government were signed off in each year from 2010 to 2015; what the values of those contracts were; and what those contracts were for.","Biography information for Dame Margaret Hodge","Margaret Hodge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2361","2361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/353882","2015-06-16","HM Treasury","2015-06-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many PFI contracts were negotiated by (a) NHS trusts, (b) Academy trusts and (c) local authorities in each year from 2010 to 2015; what the values of those contracts were; and what those contracts were for.","Biography information for Dame Margaret Hodge","Margaret Hodge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2359","2359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/353883","2015-06-16","Department for Transport","2015-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will take steps to improve the frequency and speed of rail services between Telford and Birmingham.","Biography information for Lucy Allan","Lucy Allan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2356","2356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/353884","2015-06-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the average cost of properties sold to first-time buyers under the Help to Buy scheme in (a) England, (b) East Midlands and (c) Ashfield.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2345","2345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/353885","2015-06-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many properties were bought in Ashfield under the Right-to-Buy Scheme in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2348","2348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/353886","2015-06-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, by what date she plans that the flood reinsurance scheme will be fully operational.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2310","2310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/353887","2015-06-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what her policy is on the adoption by the European Commission of the proposed European Food Safety Authority guidance on the risk assessment of plant protection products on bees, published by that organisation in June 2013.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2311","2311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/353888","2015-06-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, by what process and on what timescale she plans to bring forward legislative proposals to incorporate new European Food Safety Authority guidance on the risk assessment of plant protection products on bees into UK pesticides legislation.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2312","2312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/353889","2015-06-16","Department for Transport","2015-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many publicly-funded charging points for electric vehicles have been delivered in each of the last 10 years; and how many such points are planned for delivery in 2015.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2332","2332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/353890","2015-06-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the grant in aid allocation is for new flood defence assets for each year from 2014-15 to 2020-21.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2357","2357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/353891","2015-06-16","Department for Transport","2015-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what his Department's budget was for new charging points for electric vehicles in each of the last 10 years; and what budget he has set for such points for the next five years.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2358","2358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/353892","2015-06-17","Department of Health","2015-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the total amount spent by the NHS on health care needed as a result of air pollution in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2351","2351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/353893","2015-06-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, by what date she plans to publish a new consultation on air quality.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2349","2349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/353894","2015-06-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, by what date she plans to publish a new national air quality plan.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2350","2350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/353895","2015-06-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, by what date she expects the UK to be compliant with the Air Quality Directive.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2362","2362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/353896","2015-06-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the (a) budget, (b) outturn and (c) end-of-year surplus was for flood and coastal risk management in her Department in each year from 2010-11 to 2014-15.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2365","2365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/353897","2015-06-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the (a) budget, (b) outturn and (c) end-of-year surplus was for flood asset maintenance in her Department in each year from 2010-11 to 2014-15.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2366","2366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/353898","2015-06-16","Department for Transport","2015-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans he has to improve rail links between Huddersfield and Sheffield.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2324","2324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/353899","2015-06-16","Department for Transport","2015-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what representations he has received on the Streets Ahead campaign on pavement parking.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2335","2335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/353900","2015-06-16","Department for Transport","2015-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what representations he has received on improving rail links between Huddersfield and other cities and towns in South Yorkshire.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2322","2322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/353901","2015-06-16","Department for Transport","2015-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what funds the Government has set aside from (a) the Northern Powerhouse funding and (b) his Department's funding to improve rail links to and from Huddersfield.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2323","2323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/353902","2015-06-17","Prime Minister","2015-06-12","To ask the Prime Minister, if he will declassify and publish the recent report, produced by Sir Nigel Sheinwald on data sharing.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2372","2372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/353903","2015-06-17","Department for Education","2015-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent representations she has received on projected budget deficits in academies.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2336","2336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/353904","2015-06-17","Ministry of Justice","2015-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much in outstanding fines there were at courts in Nottinghamshire on (a) 31 March and (b) the last date for which figures are available.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2289","2289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/353905","2015-06-17","Attorney General","2015-06-12","To ask the Attorney General, how many letters of invitation to companies to enter negotiations for a deferred prosecution agreement the Serious Fraud Office has issued.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2337","2337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/353906","2015-06-17","Cabinet Office","2015-06-12","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to Action 39 of the UK Anti-Corruption Plan, published in December 2014, when the proposed review of the enforcement response to bribery and corruption will be published.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2354","2354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/353907","2015-06-17","Home Office","2015-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to Action 38 of the UK Anti-Corruption Plan, published in December 2014, what steps she has taken to recruit and retain specialists to support corruption investigations in the National Crime Agency; and what skills specialists so recruited have.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2355","2355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/353908","2015-06-17","Ministry of Justice","2015-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when he expects construction to begin on the proposed Secure College.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2288","2288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/353909","2015-06-16","Cabinet Office","2015-06-12","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps he is taking to ensure that local authority-funded youth services are maintained at their current level.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2300","2300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/353910","2015-06-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of devolving business rate retention powers to local authorities.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2301","2301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/353911","2015-06-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will meet town and county local authority leaders to discuss his Department's policy on devolution of powers.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2302","2302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/353912","2015-06-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what representations he has received from or on behalf of town and county authorities on his Department's policies on devolution.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2303","2303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/353913","2015-06-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to make town and county authorities aware of his Department's policies on devolution.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2304","2304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/353914","2015-06-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to ensure that the benefits of devolution reach town and county authority level.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2305","2305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/353915","2015-06-17","Leader of the House","2015-06-12","To ask the Leader of the House, with reference to page 24 of Implications for Devolution of England, Cm 8969, published in December 2014, when he plans that proposed arrangements for English votes for English laws will be put on a statutory footing.","Biography information for Kirsty Blackman","Kirsty Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2308","2308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/353916","2015-06-17","Leader of the House","2015-06-12","To ask the Leader of the House, if he will set out in his proposals for English votes for English laws whether only hon. Members for constituencies in England would be able to participate in (a) committee stages and (b) the committee of the whole House for bills with England-only implications.","Biography information for Kirsty Blackman","Kirsty Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2290","2290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/353917","2015-06-17","Leader of the House","2015-06-12","To ask the Leader of the House, what plans he has for public consultation in advance of decision of the House on proposals on English votes for English laws.","Biography information for Kirsty Blackman","Kirsty Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2291","2291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/353918","2015-06-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will publish the application made by the National Farmers Union for a derogation from restrictions on the use of neonicotinoids.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2341","2341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/353919","2015-06-16","Department of Health","2015-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to support scientific research into stem cell transplantation.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2328","2328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/353920","2015-06-16","Department of Health","2015-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he expects NHS England to respond to its consultation on Investing in Specialised Services.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2329","2329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/353921","2015-06-16","Department of Health","2015-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make an assessment of the implications for his policies of the recommendations in the report, Destination: Cure - arriving at a better future for people with blood cancer by Anthony Nolan; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2327","2327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/353922","2015-06-16","Department of Health","2015-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of recently announced changes to public health funding on public health initiatives on (a) exercise, (b) obesity, (c) smoking cessation and (d) sexual health.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2363","2363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/353923","2015-06-16","Department for International Development","2015-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will make an assessment of the implications for her Department's policies on corporate partnerships of the findings of the report of the Independent Commission for Aid Impact, Business in Development, published in May 2015; and what steps she plans to take to ensure that UK aid protects the livelihoods of small-scale farmers.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2367","2367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/353924","2015-06-16","Department for International Development","2015-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if her Department will conduct an assessment of whether its strategy in working with multinational companies is effective in reducing poverty and improving the equity and sustainability of Africa's food systems.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2299","2299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/353925","2015-06-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with international partners and his counterparts in South East Asia on (a) resolving the situation of Rohingya migrants and (b) ensuring that search and rescue operations take place in the Andaman Sea.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2317","2317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/353926","2015-06-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent estimate his Department has made of the number Rohingya migrants from Burma adrift in the Andaman Sea.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2318","2318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/353927","2015-06-16","Department for International Development","2015-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what plans her Department has to work with international partners to tackle (a) political instability in northern Africa, (b) criminal gangs which profit from human trafficking and (c) other underlying causes of the migrant situation in the Mediterranean.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2320","2320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/353928","2015-06-16","Home Office","2015-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to support migrants and asylum seekers who (a) are children, (b) are elderly, (c) have serious injuries and (d) have other specialist needs who are rescued during operations in the Mediterranean.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2319","2319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/353929","2015-06-16","Home Office","2015-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent discussions her Department has had with its EU counterparts on search and rescue operations in the Mediterranean.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2321","2321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/353930","2015-06-17","Department for Transport","2015-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with (a) the Office of Rail Regulation, (b) the Department's Rail Executive and (c) other bodies on the future of Network Rail.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2371","2371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/353931","2015-06-17","Department for Transport","2015-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 9 June 2015 to Question 1261, whether bi-modal IEP trains running on diesel power will be capable of running at the maximum permitted linespeed of 125 miles per hour.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2340","2340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/353932","2015-06-16","Department of Health","2015-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what peer-reviewed evidence NHS England has assessed to inform its decision on the use of proton beam therapy as a treatment for extracranial indications.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2315","2315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/353933","2015-06-17","Department for Transport","2015-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he plans to allocate surplus Thameslink rolling stock to SouthEastern Trains in response to the submission made to his Department by SouthEastern in February 2015.","Biography information for Heidi Alexander","Heidi Alexander","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2338","2338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/353934","2015-06-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether she plans to give the Bradwell nuclear site to (a) the Chinese State Nuclear Corporation or (b) another Chinese state-owned company in order to build a Chinese-manufactured reactor.","Biography information for Harry Harpham","Harry Harpham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2307","2307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349888","2015-06-15","Department for Education","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether it is her policy that families with parents in full-time further education will be eligible for 30 hours a week free childcare under the Government's new childcare proposals.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2129","2129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349889","2015-06-15","Department for Education","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of the potential cost of the introduction of 30 hours a week free childcare.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2132","2132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349890","2015-06-15","Department for Education","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether her Department plans to include provisions in the Childcare Bill for extra funding for children currently in receipt of disability living allowance for children or enhanced child tax credits as a consequence of a disability.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2133","2133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349891","2015-06-15","Department for Education","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what eligibility provisions she plans to propose for children of families in which parents live apart or with different legal partners to be entitled to 30 hours a week free childcare under the Government's childcare proposals.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2134","2134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349892","2015-06-15","HM Treasury","2015-06-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what his policy is on the role employers play in the delivery of tax-free childcare.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2144","2144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349893","2015-06-15","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what recent assessment she has made of the financial position of (a) EDF Energy and (b) Areva in relation to their potential contribution to the construction and running of the planned nuclear power plant at Hinkley C.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2130","2130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349894","2015-06-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether independent oversight is in place to assure the day-to-day standard of work undertaken by approved inspectors of the compliance of new homes with building regulations.","Biography information for Mrs Maria Miller","Mrs Maria Miller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2160","2160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349895","2015-06-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many cases have been brought under section 35 of the Building Act 1984 in cases where new build homes contravene building regulations in the last 10 years; and how many such cases have resulted in the imposition of fines.","Biography information for Mrs Maria Miller","Mrs Maria Miller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2208","2208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349896","2015-06-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, which local authorities delegate in full the function of ensuring building regulation compliance to approved inspectors who are approved and monitored by the Construction Industry Council.","Biography information for Mrs Maria Miller","Mrs Maria Miller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2209","2209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349897","2015-06-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps are in place to enable new home purchasers to see the detailed records made by approved inspectors responsible for ensuring technical building regulation standards are met during the construction of a new home.","Biography information for Mrs Maria Miller","Mrs Maria Miller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2217","2217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349898","2015-06-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the implications for his Department's policy of the Consumer Industry Council's response to the recommendations made by the Ankers Report published in 2013.","Biography information for Mrs Maria Miller","Mrs Maria Miller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2212","2212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349899","2015-06-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate the Government made of the potential profit from the Government's holding in Royal Mail before the announcement of the sale of Royal Mail.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2251","2251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349900","2015-06-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of households affected by the under-occupancy penalty have received payments to mitigate in full deductions from claims for (a) housing benefit and (b) local housing allowance in (i) England, (ii) Northern Ireland, (iii) Scotland and (iv) Wales.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2237","2237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349901","2015-06-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effect of reducing the benefits cap to 23,000 per annum on (a) young adults, (b) pregnant women, (c) couples with children, (d) veterans and (e) disabled people; and how many households in each of those groups will be affected by that reduction.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2234","2234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349902","2015-06-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effect of the two year freeze on benefit levels on (a) young adults, (b) pregnant women, (c) couples with children, (d) formerly looked after children, (e) veterans and (f) disabled people; and what estimate he has made of the real terms effect on the levels of each type of benefit of that freeze.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2236","2236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349903","2015-06-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will take steps to ensure planned changes to entitlements to housing benefit and local housing allowance do not adversely affect (a) young adults, (b) formerly looked after children, (c) pregnant women, (d) couples with children, (e) veterans and (f) disabled people.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2235","2235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349904","2015-06-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in Scotland are not claiming what value of each benefit and pension entitlement; what proportion of each benefit and pension entitlement is unclaimed by claimants in Scotland; and if he will take steps to transfer the value of unclaimed benefits and pension entitlements to the Scottish Government.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2275","2275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349905","2015-06-16","Scotland Office","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, with reference to the statement by the Economic Secretary to the Treasury of 10 June 2015, if he will take steps to (a) ensure the Royal Bank of Scotland continues to meet the commitments in its 14 Point Customer Charter and (b) prevent the closure of Royal Bank of Scotland branches in Invergordon, Lochinver and Lybster.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2274","2274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349906","2015-06-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to ensure all people entitled to benefits and not claiming those benefits are identified and assisted in claiming those benefits.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2273","2273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349907","2015-06-15","Home Office","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether any UK police forces use International Mobile Subscriber Identity catchers.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2118","2118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349908","2015-06-16","Department of Health","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how purdah arrangements during election periods apply to staff working for NHS England and NICE.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2139","2139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349909","2015-06-15","HM Treasury","2015-06-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will publish the independent advice he received on the sale of the Government's stake in the Royal Bank of Scotland.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2105","2105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349910","2015-06-15","HM Treasury","2015-06-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make it his policy not to reduce the top rate of tax.","Biography information for Gerald Jones","Gerald Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2115","2115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349911","2015-06-16","HM Treasury","2015-06-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what advice he has taken from (a) economists independent of Government and (b) Treasury economists on whether public spending cuts will delay or promote economic growth.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2140","2140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349912","2015-06-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claimants of jobseeker's allowance in (a) Jarrow constituency, (b) South Tyneside local authority area, (c) the North East and (d) the UK who have disputed sanction of their benefit have had that sanction overturned on appeal in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2230","2230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349913","2015-06-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claimants of jobseeker's allowance in (a) Jarrow constituency, (b) South Tyneside local authority area, (c) the North East and (d) the UK who have disputed sanction of their benefit have had that sanction overturned after it was reconsidered or successfully appealed in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2231","2231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349914","2015-06-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claimants of jobseeker's allowance in (a) Jarrow constituency, (b) South Tyneside local authority area, (c) the North East and (d) the UK who have disputed sanction of their benefit have had that sanction overturned after it was reconsidered in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2232","2232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349915","2015-06-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claimants of jobseeker's allowance in (a) Jarrow constituency, (b) South Tyneside local authority area, (c) the North East and (d) the UK have disputed sanction of their benefit in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2233","2233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349916","2015-06-15","House of Commons Commission","2015-06-11","To ask the hon. Member for Mole Valley representing the House of Commons Commission, how much was spent on the upgrade work to the North Entrance to the parliamentary estate in the last Parliament; for what reason cyclists are forbidden from using that entrance; and whether a safety assessment was made of the potential implications of excluding cyclists from that entrance.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2241","2241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349917","2015-06-15","House of Commons Commission","2015-06-11","To ask the hon. Member for Mole Valley representing the House of Commons Commission, what assessment the Commission has made of the provision of covered cycle rack spaces on the parliamentary estate.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2242","2242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349918","2015-06-15","House of Commons Commission","2015-06-11","To ask the hon. Member for Mole Valley representing the House of Commons Commission, what steps the House is taking to remove bicycles left on cycle racks on the estate.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2240","2240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349919","2015-06-16","Department for Education","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what guidance her Department has provided to schools on the provision of (a) alcohol and (b) drugs education; and whether such guidance requires the specific mention of new psychoactive substances.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2204","2204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349920","2015-06-16","Ministry of Justice","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the total cost of employing (a) salaried employment tribunal judges and (b) lay employment tribunal judges was in each administrative region of the employment tribunal in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2205","2205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349921","2015-06-16","Department of Health","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps Public Health England is taking to increase awareness among young people of (a) emerging psychoactive substances and (b) other recreational drugs associated with nightlife.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2206","2206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349922","2015-06-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to help local authorities meet the statutory duties imposed on them by the Counter Terrorism Act 2015.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2207","2207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349923","2015-06-15","Department for Education","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what support her Department has provided to (a) primary schools, (b) secondary schools, (c) further education colleges, (d) local education authorities and (e) academy chains to help them comply with statutory requirements placed on them by the Counter-Terrorism Act 2015.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2165","2165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349924","2015-06-15","Department for Education","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment her Department has made of the prevalence of good quality drug and alcohol education in England and Wales.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2166","2166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349925","2015-06-15","Department for Education","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what guidance her Department has issued to local authorities on the joint commissioning with clinical commissioning groups of speech and language therapy.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2162","2162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349926","2015-06-15","Department of Health","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidance his Department has issued to clinical commissioning groups on the commissioning of speech and language therapy.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2163","2163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349927","2015-06-15","Department of Health","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what national guidelines his Department has issued on provision of speech and language therapy.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2164","2164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349928","2015-06-15","Department of Health","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much his Department has spent on mental health services in (a) York Central constituency and (b) England in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2174","2174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349929","2015-06-15","Department of Health","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many NHS staff work in mental health services in York Central constituency; and how many such staff have been employed for at least five years.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2176","2176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349930","2015-06-15","Department of Health","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) doctors, (b) dentists, (c) nursing staff, (d) scientists, (e) personnel in professionals allied to medicine, (f) pharmacists, (g) personnel in other registrant professions and (h) total staff were recruited from overseas to work in the NHS in each year since 2005.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2177","2177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349931","2015-06-15","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps the Government has taken to reduce energy use in York Central constituency by the (a) public and (b) private sector.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2178","2178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349932","2015-06-15","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many homes have been retrofitted to reduce energy use in the last 10 years.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2179","2179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349933","2015-06-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what information her Department holds on the levels of air pollution at (a) Collygate in York and (b) other measured points in York Central constituency in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2180","2180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349934","2015-06-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what information his Department holds on how many people have commenced paying the under-occupancy penalty following the death of (a) a spouse, civil partner or partner, (b) sibling, (c) parent and (d) child.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2181","2181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349935","2015-06-15","Department of Health","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much was spent on infrastructure related to mental health services in (a) York Central constituency and (b) England in each of the last five years; and what such investment is planned in the current year.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2175","2175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349936","2015-06-15","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the average retail price was of a (a) one-bed, (b) two-bed, (c) three-bed and (d) four-bed unit outside London in (i) council, (ii) registered social landlord and (iii) private housing in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2182","2182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349937","2015-06-15","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the average retail price was of a (a) one-bed, (b) two-bed, (c) three-bed and (d) four-bed unit in (i) council, (ii) registered social landlord and (iii) private housing in York Central constituency in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2183","2183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349938","2015-06-15","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what proportion of housing stock (a) outside London and (b) in York Central constituency consists of houses in multiple occupation.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2184","2184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349939","2015-06-15","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many units of housing in York Central constituency were (a) rented from the City of York Council, (b) rented from registered social landlords, (c) rented from private landlords and (d) owned or mortgaged property in the most recent period for which figures were available.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2185","2185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349940","2015-06-15","Department of Health","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) district nurses, (b) health visitors, (c) school nurses and (d) community mental health nurses there were in York Central constituency in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2239","2239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349941","2015-06-15","Department for Education","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much her Department has spent on mental health services for school students in (a) York Central constituency and (b) England in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2173","2173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349942","2015-06-15","Department for Transport","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what account has been taken of the safety of blind and partially sighted pedestrians in the introduction of an ultra-low emission zone in London.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2151","2151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349943","2015-06-15","Department for Transport","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what guidance his Department has given to local transport authorities on protecting the safety of blind and partially sighted bus users when (a) placing floating bus stops, (b) closing bus stops and (c) placing temporary bus stops.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2152","2152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349944","2015-06-15","Department for Transport","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will encourage the installation of artificial sound generators on quiet electric and hybrid-electric buses in London to ensure their audibility for the safety of blind and partially-sighted pedestrians.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2203","2203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349945","2015-06-15","Department for Transport","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment he has made of the level of risk of unauthorised access to air traffic control information systems; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2253","2253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349946","2015-06-15","Department for Transport","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment he has made of the level of risk of unauthorised remote access to aircraft avionics systems; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2252","2252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349947","2015-06-15","Department for Transport","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions his Department has had with the (a) US Federal Aviation Administration and (b) European Aviation Safety Agency on cyber-security risks to (i) aircraft avionic systems and (ii) air traffic control information systems.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2254","2254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349948","2015-06-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the implications for UK policy of the Chinese Military Strategy white paper published in May 2015; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2255","2255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349949","2015-06-15","Department of Health","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he will make available further details on the funding announced in the Budget 2015 for the (a) purchase and (b) provision of training in their use of defibrillators for use in public places.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2249","2249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349950","2015-06-15","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the potential military benefits of China's recent land reclamation and construction activities in the Spratly Islands archipelago; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2256","2256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349951","2015-06-15","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the Five Power Defence Arrangements cover the defence of Malaysia's exclusive economic zone; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2257","2257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349952","2015-06-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions his Department has had on the Spratly Islands dispute with (a) claimants to those islands, (b) Five Power Defence Arrangements signatories and (c) the US; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2258","2258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349953","2015-06-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to encourage the US to ratify the UN Convention on the Law of the Sea; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2259","2259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349954","2015-06-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions his Department has had with the Chinese government on land reclamation and construction activities in the Spratly Islands archipelago; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2260","2260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349955","2015-06-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent assessment he has made of potential business and research applications for graphene; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2261","2261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349956","2015-06-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what (a) capital and (b) resource funding his Department allocated to the National Graphene Institute in each financial year from 2010-11 to 2014-15.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2262","2262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349957","2015-06-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what his strategy is for the commercialisation of graphene-related applications; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2263","2263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349958","2015-06-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many graphene-related patent applications were filed in the UK between 2011 and 2014; and what information his Department holds on the number of such applications filed worldwide in that period.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2264","2264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349959","2015-06-16","Prime Minister","2015-06-11","To ask the Prime Minister, pursuant to the contribution of 10 June 2015, Official Report, column 1210, what steps he is taking to ensure the (a) ratification of the Convention for the Protection of Cultural Property in the Event of Armed Conflict and (b) implementation of the EU Directive on The Return of Cultural Objects.","Biography information for Mr David Burrowes","Mr David Burrowes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2210","2210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349960","2015-06-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many apprentices have been employed in the public sector at the end of their apprenticeship in each of the last five years.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2172","2172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349961","2015-06-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the average cost to a company is of hiring an apprentice.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2170","2170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349962","2015-06-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many apprentices were employed in companies employing fewer than (a) 20 and (b) 50 people in each of the last five years.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2171","2171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349963","2015-06-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many apprentices have been employed in the private sector at the end of their apprenticeship in each of the last five years.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2168","2168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349964","2015-06-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what plans he has to make it compulsory for producers to add bittering agents to anti-freeze products which contain ethylene glycol.","Biography information for Andrew Bridgen","Andrew Bridgen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2121","2121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349965","2015-06-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, when she expects the smart metering communications infrastructure managed by the Data and Communications Company to begin operation.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2137","2137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349966","2015-06-16","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Tornado GR4 aircraft have been fitted with a collision warning system; and whether or not the software problems associated with the RA mode in that system have been resolved.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2280","2280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349967","2015-06-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effect of lowering the overall benefit cap to 23,000 on the number of children living in a household in (a) London, (b) Enfield and (c) Enfield North constituency with an income below 60 per cent of median household income.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2106","2106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349968","2015-06-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of children living in households in (a) London, (b) Enfield and (c) Enfield North constituency that will be affected by a reduction of the benefit cap to 23,000.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2107","2107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349969","2015-06-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of households with dependent children in (a) London, (b) Enfield and (c) Enfield North constituency that will be affected by a reduction of the benefit cap to 23,000.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2108","2108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349970","2015-06-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of out of work households in (a) London, (b) Enfield and (c) Enfield North constituency that will be affected by the reduction of the benefit cap to 23,000.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2109","2109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349971","2015-06-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he plans to publish the recommendations from the peer reviews of deaths which occurred during benefit sanctions.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2094","2094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349972","2015-06-16","HM Treasury","2015-06-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what representations he has received on the sale of the Government's stake in Royal Bank of Scotland.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2112","2112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349973","2015-06-16","HM Treasury","2015-06-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with (a) Royal Bank of Scotland (RBS), (b) NatWest Bank and (c) Ulster Bank on the sale of the Government's stake in RBS.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2113","2113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349974","2015-06-16","HM Treasury","2015-06-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of the sale of the Government's stake in Royal Bank of Scotland on (a) customers of Ulster Bank and (b) other customers.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2114","2114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349975","2015-06-16","Northern Ireland Office","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what assessment she has made of the potential effects of policy announcements made in the Queen's Speech in May 2015 on child poverty in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2103","2103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349976","2015-06-16","Northern Ireland Office","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what assessment she has made of the potential effect in Northern Ireland of welfare reform measures announced in the Queen's Speech in May 2015.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2102","2102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349977","2015-06-15","Northern Ireland Office","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what recent assessment she has made of progress in closing the gender pay gap in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2090","2090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349978","2015-06-15","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to streamline the Neighbourhood Planning process.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2145","2145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349979","2015-06-15","Department for Transport","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to promote the opening of (a) Haxby Station in York Outer constituency and (b) other new railway stations.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2083","2083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349980","2015-06-15","Department for Education","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the need for changing the formula by which spending is determined in English schools.","Biography information for James Cartlidge","James Cartlidge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2238","2238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349981","2015-06-16","Department for Transport","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with his ministerial colleagues in the Department for Communities and Local Government on the economic potential of small airports and their effect on local and business communities.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2271","2271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349982","2015-06-16","Department for Transport","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make an assessment of the implications for his policies of Pricewaterhouse Coopers' final report on the closure of Manston Airport; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2270","2270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349983","2015-06-16","Department for Transport","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to Pricewaterhouse Coopers' final report on the closure of Manston Airport, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the findings of that report on the powers available to local authorities to support small airports.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2272","2272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349984","2015-06-16","HM Treasury","2015-06-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the availability of income drawdown products for savers.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2224","2224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349985","2015-06-16","HM Treasury","2015-06-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what reports he has received of frauds designed to take advantage of new pensions flexibilities; and what steps he is taking to protect savers from such frauds.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2227","2227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349986","2015-06-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he has taken to monitor the effect of the new pensions flexibilities.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2226","2226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349987","2015-06-16","HM Treasury","2015-06-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to ensure savers can access retirement savings under the new pensions flexibilities.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2228","2228"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349988","2015-06-16","HM Treasury","2015-06-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect on the ability of savers to make the most of retirement savings of charges on (a) drawndown products and (b) switching retirement income products.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2229","2229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349989","2015-06-16","Department of Health","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if his Department will maintain its funding for carers; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Oliver Heald","Sir Oliver Heald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2097","2097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349990","2015-06-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if she will make the Warm Home Discount available to social housing tenants who purchase energy through collective schemes provided by a housing association and do not receive individual bills directly from the power provider.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2098","2098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349991","2015-06-16","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans he has to progress the salvage of HMS Victory 1744.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2099","2099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349992","2015-06-16","Department for Education","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to ensure the quality of social work services provided to local authorities by outsourced bodies.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2100","2100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349993","2015-06-16","Department for Education","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the reasons were for ceasing Ofsted inspections of children's social care services provided by outsourced bodies.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2104","2104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349994","2015-06-16","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will make it his policy that the UK will ratify the 1954 Convention for the Protection of Cultural Property in the Event of Armed Conflict.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2101","2101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349995","2015-06-16","Department of Health","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the 200 million reduction in his Department's budget announced by the Chancellor of the Exchequer of 4 June 2015 on former NHS services that were transferred to local authorities as part of the transfer of public health functions in 2013; and what assessment he has made of the potential effect of that reduction on local authority (a) sexual health services, (b) smoking cessation services and (c) health screening.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2161","2161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349996","2015-06-16","Department of Health","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with NICE on updated draft clinical guidelines by NICE for the management of Type 1 and Type 2 diabetes in adults; what representations he has received on those guidelines; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2138","2138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349997","2015-06-16","Department of Health","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the annual budget for (a) Public Health England and (b) public health for all local authorities is for 2015-16.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2276","2276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349998","2015-06-16","Department of Health","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department plans to make the 200 million of savings announced by the Chancellor of the Exchequer on 4 June 2015 that will be made from his Department's non-NHS budget from underspend.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2219","2219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349999","2015-06-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to HM Treasury's press release, Chancellor announces 4.5 billion of measures to bring down debt, published on 4 June 2015, from which round of the Regional Growth Fund he plans to make savings; and whether these savings will come from monies allocated under the Regional Growth Fund but not drawn down.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2124","2124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350000","2015-06-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to HM Treasury's press release, Chancellor announces 4.5 billion of measures to bring down debt, published on 4 June 2015, under what budgetary sub-heading savings will be made from (a) the Regional Growth Fund, (b) monies for energy-intensive industries, (c) budgets relating to further and higher education and (d) other programmes and budgets operated by his Department.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2125","2125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350001","2015-06-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what plans he has for the Regional Growth Fund and Exceptional Regional Growth Fund after the completion of Round 6.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2126","2126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350002","2015-06-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many vouchers have been issued but not yet redeemed under the Growth Vouchers scheme.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2127","2127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350003","2015-06-15","Department for Education","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to ensure equal access to all-age careers guidance services across the UK.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2143","2143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350004","2015-06-15","Department for Education","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans she has for improving the provision of and access to careers guidance.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2202","2202"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350005","2015-06-16","HM Treasury","2015-06-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with childcare providers on the delivery of tax-free childcare.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2282","2282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350006","2015-06-16","Cabinet Office","2015-06-11","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment his Department has made of the maternal employment rate for women with at least one child under the age of (a) two, (b) three and (c) four years in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2283","2283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350007","2015-06-16","Home Office","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the Government intends to ratify the Istanbul Convention on preventing and combating violence against women and domestic violence.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2278","2278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350008","2015-06-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many (a) women and (b) men aged 24 and over, were enrolled in further education courses at level 3 or above in each academic year since 2010.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2281","2281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350009","2015-06-16","Department for Education","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether her proposals for teaching sexual consent in schools will be compulsory for students in all state-funded schools.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2284","2284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350010","2015-06-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many parents have applied for shared parental leave since its introduction.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2246","2246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350011","2015-06-15","Cabinet Office","2015-06-11","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the (a) number and (b) percentage of women recorded as economically inactive who have achieved qualifications (i) up to and including KS4, (ii) at KS5 and (iii) in higher education in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2245","2245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350012","2015-06-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average annual income of self-employed (a) men and (b) women was in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2147","2147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350013","2015-06-15","Department of Health","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he expects to implement HPV vaccinations for (a) boys and (b) men who have sex with men.","Biography information for Mike Freer","Mike Freer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2123","2123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350014","2015-06-15","HM Treasury","2015-06-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent representations he has received on allegations of illicit gold trafficking from South America by companies linked to the London bullion market; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2089","2089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350015","2015-06-15","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 2 June 2015 to Question 227, if his Department will make an estimate of the average cost as a proportion of local market rent levels, of homes built under the affordable rent model by (a) local authorities and (b) housing associations in (i) England, (ii) London, (iii) the London Borough of Islington and (iv) Islington South and Finsbury constituency in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2087","2087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350016","2015-06-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent discussions he has had with the Social Mobility and Child Poverty Commission on the Government's progress on the poverty reduction targets set out in the Child Poverty Act 2010.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2086","2086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350017","2015-06-15","Home Office","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Written Statement of 12 March 2015, HCWS401, when the Government plans to respond to the Special Report of the Intelligence and Security Committee, Privacy and Security: A modern and transparent legal framework, HC 1075.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2111","2111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350018","2015-06-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what progress his Department has made towards meeting the 2020 poverty reduction targets set out in the Child Poverty Act 2010; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2197","2197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350019","2015-06-15","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many council homes whose cost is classified by his Department as high there are in (a) the London Borough of Islington and (b) Islington South and Finsbury constituency.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2195","2195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350020","2015-06-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many new claims for discretionary housing payments were approved in (a) the London Borough of Islington and (b) Islington South and Finsbury constituency in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2193","2193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350021","2015-06-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of discretionary housing payment claimants in (a) the London Borough of Islington and (b) Islington South and Finsbury constituency are in work.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2194","2194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350022","2015-06-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many jobseeker's allowance claimants aged 18 to 21 years in (a) the London Borough of Islington and (b) Islington South and Finsbury constituency are in receipt of housing benefit.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2192","2192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350023","2015-06-15","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the value of council homes classified as high by his Department is in (a) London, (b) the London Borough of Islington and (c) Islington South and Finsbury constituency; and how many bedrooms such properties possess.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2196","2196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350024","2015-06-15","HM Treasury","2015-06-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people who are in receipt of child tax credit in (a) the London Borough of Islington and (b) Islington South and Finsbury constituency have more than two children.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2198","2198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350025","2015-06-15","HM Treasury","2015-06-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what proportion of people claiming child benefit in (a) the London Borough of Islington and (b) Islington South and Finsbury constituency are in work.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2199","2199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350026","2015-06-15","Home Office","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make the proposed Investigatory Powers Bill subject to pre-legislative scrutiny.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2200","2200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350027","2015-06-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many jobseeker's allowance claimants aged 18 to 21 years in (a) the London Borough of Islington and (b) Islington South and Finsbury constituency who are currently in receipt of housing benefit have children.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2201","2201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350028","2015-06-15","Home Office","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent discussions she has had with (a) the Interception of Communications Commissioner and (b) the Information Commissioner on the proposed Investigatory Powers Bill.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2186","2186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350029","2015-06-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people were in receipt of a Discretionary Housing Payment in Islington South and Finsbury constituency in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2189","2189"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350030","2015-06-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many new claims for housing benefit were approved in (a) the London Borough of Islington and (b) Islington South and Finsbury constituency in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2190","2190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350031","2015-06-15","HM Treasury","2015-06-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the average earnings of working claimants of (a) child benefit and (b) child tax credit in (i) the London Borough of Islington and (ii) Islington South and Finsbury constituency.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2187","2187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350032","2015-06-15","Home Office","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent discussions she has had with (a) the Interception of Communications Commissioner and (b) the Information Commissioner on the adequacy of existing privacy safeguards and proposals for new communications data legislation.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2188","2188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350033","2015-06-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will make it his policy to regularly report on apprentices' (a) wages, (b) number of hours worked, (c) age, (d) level of education and (e) duration of training.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2167","2167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350034","2015-06-15","Department for Transport","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans his Department has to electrify the Wrexham to Bidston railway line.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2088","2088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350035","2015-06-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will (a) remove the two-week waiting period for non-vulnerable people to receive a hardship payment and (b) suspend sanctions for claimants with children and claimants with mental ill health.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2075","2075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350036","2015-06-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make an assessment of the implications for his policies of the findings of the report by UK Churches, Time to Rethink Benefit Sanctions, published in March 2015, on waiting periods for hardship payments and sanctions on claimants with children and for claimants with mental ill health.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2076","2076"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350037","2015-06-16","Department of Health","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps the Food Standards Agency has taken to investigate the effects of the promotion of chlorine dioxide as a food supplement; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Clive Efford","Clive Efford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2265","2265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350038","2015-06-16","Department for International Development","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what discussions she has had with the government of Nepal on the introduction of import duty on materials sent in response to the earthquake appeal in that country; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Clive Efford","Clive Efford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2269","2269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350039","2015-06-16","Department for International Development","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what reports she has received on the effects of the introduction of import duty by the government of Nepal on shipments of aid sent in response to the earthquake appeal; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Clive Efford","Clive Efford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2268","2268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350040","2015-06-16","Department of Health","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the risk to children from the promotion of chlorine dioxide as a food supplement or cure for autism; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Clive Efford","Clive Efford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2266","2266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350041","2015-06-16","Department of Health","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps the National Crime Agency has taken to investigate the potential harm to children posed by the promotion of chlorine dioxide as a food supplement or cure for autism; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Clive Efford","Clive Efford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2267","2267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350042","2015-06-15","Department of Health","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much Government funding was allocated to research into therapies using embryonic stem cells in each of the last five years for which figures are available; and how much such funding will be so allocated in the next five years.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2073","2073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350043","2015-06-15","Department of Health","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much Government funding was allocated to research into therapies using stem cells derived from non-embryonic sources in each of the last five years for which figures are available; and how much such funding will be so allocated in the next five years.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2074","2074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350044","2015-06-15","Department of Health","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the reasons for the increase in the number of abortions (a) for Down's Syndrome, (b) registered under statutory grounds and (c) since his Department's last report.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2085","2085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350045","2015-06-15","Department of Health","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if it is his policy that a registered medical practitioner may lawfully sign the statutory HSA1 form before receiving any information from the woman named on that form where a good faith opinion for the purposes of section 1(1)(a) of the Abortion Act 1967 is formed between the signing of the form and the termination; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2148","2148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350046","2015-06-15","Department for Transport","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate his Department has made of the contribution to (a) jobs and (b) GDP of sustainable fuels in the period up to 2030.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2117","2117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350047","2015-06-15","Department for Transport","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans his Department has to provide economic support for the development and the roll-out of sustainable fuel production for the aviation sector.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2116","2116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350048","2015-06-15","Department for Transport","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the proportional contribution of transport to air pollution in London in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2078","2078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350049","2015-06-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to tackle the current situation of Rohingya Muslims (a) fleeing Burma and (b) being persecuted in Burma; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2218","2218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350050","2015-06-16","Department for International Development","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what specific aid her Department is making available for Rohingya Muslims (a) fleeing Burma and (b) being persecuted in Burma.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2213","2213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350051","2015-06-15","Department for Education","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent representations she has received on AQA's decision to discontinue the Polish A-level from 2018; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2169","2169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350052","2015-06-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to tackle excessive levels of air pollution in towns or cities.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2153","2153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350053","2015-06-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to increase preparedness for extreme weather and flooding as a result of climate change.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2154","2154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350054","2015-06-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what role her Department is playing in preparations for the UN Framework Convention on Climate Change conference in Paris in December 2015.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2155","2155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350055","2015-06-16","Department for Transport","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to encourage cyclists to have due regard  for other road users; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2156","2156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350056","2015-06-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will reopen the inquiry into the nature of the warranties sold by ScottishPower to its customers between 1980 and 1999 and potential losses to those customers.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2157","2157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350057","2015-06-16","HM Treasury","2015-06-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how he plans to take (a) widows and widowers and (b) other people out of inheritance tax where the family home is the main asset; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2093","2093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350058","2015-06-16","Department of Health","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of people who have had their personal medical data shared despite registering to opt-out; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2279","2279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350059","2015-06-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with representatives from South Asian countries on Rohingya refugees; and what the outcome of those discussions has been.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2135","2135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350060","2015-06-16","Department for Education","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many maintained schools which were found to be inadequate since the introduction of the new inspection descriptors have remained as maintained schools; and how many such schools have been converted to academy status.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2136","2136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350061","2015-06-15","Department for Transport","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment he has made of the effect on the local economy of congestion on the A47; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stewart Jackson","Mr Stewart Jackson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2128","2128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350062","2015-06-15","Department for Education","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she plans to review the governance of first wave academies; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stewart Jackson","Mr Stewart Jackson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2149","2149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350063","2015-06-15","Department for Education","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she plans to review secondary school funding formulae in (a) Peterborough and (b) England; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stewart Jackson","Mr Stewart Jackson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2150","2150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350064","2015-06-15","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many new residential properties completed for (a) social rent, (b) affordable rent, (c) market rent, (d) shared equity and (e) shared ownership in (i) Peterborough City Council local authority area, (ii) the East of England and (iii) England were classified as affordable in each year since 2005; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stewart Jackson","Mr Stewart Jackson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2243","2243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350065","2015-06-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions she has had with her counterparts in other EU member states on the effect of proposed changes to the minimum landing size of bass on salmon and sea trout stocks.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2110","2110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350066","2015-06-15","Leader of the House","2015-06-11","To ask the Leader of the House, whether he plans to arrange for the Psychoactive Substances Bill to be debated before the summer recess.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2146","2146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350067","2015-06-16","Ministry of Justice","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many young people held in youth custody have been identified as having learning difficulties.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2095","2095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350068","2015-06-16","Ministry of Justice","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the number of incidents in which restraint was used in each secure training centre in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2096","2096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350069","2015-06-16","Ministry of Justice","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which institutions accommodate young people aged 14 years or younger; and how many such children are accommodated at each such site.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2216","2216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350070","2015-06-16","Leader of the House","2015-06-11","To ask the Leader of the House, if he will state in his proposals on English votes for English laws whether the Government plans to propose changes to the standing orders of the House of Lords to prevent Lords from Scotland, Wales and Northern Ireland voting on England-only matters.","Biography information for Kirsty Blackman","Kirsty Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2223","2223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350071","2015-06-16","Leader of the House","2015-06-11","To ask the Leader of the House, if he will make it his policy that legislation with Barnett formula consequential implications will always be considered by the whole House.","Biography information for Kirsty Blackman","Kirsty Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2222","2222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350072","2015-06-16","Leader of the House","2015-06-11","To ask the Leader of the House, if he will clarify in his proposals on English votes for English laws, whether hon. Members for constituencies in Scotland would be able to vote on the second and third readings of a bill but not at committee stage.","Biography information for Kirsty Blackman","Kirsty Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2221","2221"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350073","2015-06-16","Leader of the House","2015-06-11","To ask the Leader of the House, if he will include in his proposals on English votes for English laws details of the proposed process of certification for a piece of legislation as English-only.","Biography information for Kirsty Blackman","Kirsty Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2220","2220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350074","2015-06-16","Leader of the House","2015-06-11","To ask the Leader of the House, if he will include in his proposals on English votes for English laws an assessment of the potential opportunities for legal challenge to a decision that a particular piece of legislation is England-only.","Biography information for Kirsty Blackman","Kirsty Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2225","2225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350075","2015-06-15","Department of Health","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information he holds on what knowledge his Department had of the emergence of risks associated with sodium valproate within the first five years following first prescription of that drug.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2077","2077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350076","2015-06-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many homeless households living in temporary accommodation would be affected by the reduction of the benefit cap to 23,000 per annum if management fees were exempted from calculation of income from benefits.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2142","2142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350077","2015-06-15","Home Office","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the risks to people fitted with medical electronic devices of the use by police of tasers; and what steps she has taken to mitigate those risks.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2120","2120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350078","2015-06-16","HM Treasury","2015-06-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will ensure that a Pensions Wise advice service is made available in the City of Bristol.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2285","2285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350079","2015-06-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of rolling the value of pensioner benefits into the state pension.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2286","2286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350080","2015-06-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will ensure that all jobcentres provide access to telephones for jobseekers to apply for jobs when no computer is required or the jobseeker is unable to use a computer.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2287","2287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350081","2015-06-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment her Department has made of the implications for its policies of the findings of the report, The Greyhound Industry: Don't bet on fair treatment, published by the Dogs Trust on 1 January 2015.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2084","2084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350082","2015-06-15","HM Treasury","2015-06-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of economic inequalities on growth.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2079","2079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350083","2015-06-15","Department of Health","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect of financial deficits of NHS trusts on safety and quality of care.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2080","2080"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350084","2015-06-15","Department of Health","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the number of people in England involuntarily addicted to prescribed drugs in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2081","2081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350085","2015-06-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent reports he has received on the situation in Rakine State, Burma.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2091","2091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350086","2015-06-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to ensure the human rights of the Rohingya people in Burma are protected.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2092","2092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350087","2015-06-15","Department of Health","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of people in England who have been prescribed benzodiazepines and z drugs for longer than four weeks in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2082","2082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350088","2015-06-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the implications for his Department's policies are of the ruling in the case of Ms C and Mr W v. Secretary of State for Work and Pensions and others of 8 June 2015.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2214","2214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350089","2015-06-15","HM Treasury","2015-06-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will respond formally to the Keep Me Posted campaign.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2141","2141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350090","2015-06-16","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department plans to take to review the airworthiness certification regime of the A400m programme.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2158","2158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350091","2015-06-16","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if his Department will prepare and publish a report on the causes of the recent crash of an A400m aircraft in Spain after the Spanish authorities have concluded their investigations.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2159","2159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350092","2015-06-16","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the implication for his Department's proposals of the conclusions of the review into the broader issues surrounding the loss of the RAF Nimrod MR2 aircraft XV230 in Afghanistan in 2006 by Charles Haddon-Cave.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2211","2211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350093","2015-06-16","Department for Transport","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what progress he has made in consulting stakeholders on reform of level crossing legislation; and if he will issue a public consultation on that matter.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2215","2215"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350094","2015-06-15","Department of Health","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Answers of 17 March 2015 to Questions 227042 and 227043, from which budget NHS England will allocate funding for the building of the proton beam centres at the Christie Hospital in Manchester and University College Hospital London; and what contingency arrangements are in place for the planned budget being exceeded.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2250","2250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350095","2015-06-15","Department of Health","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which hospitals in the North East are treating patients with (a) stereotactic radiosurgery (b) stereotactic ablative radiotherapy; and how many patients have been treated in both categories since April 2013.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2119","2119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350096","2015-06-15","Department for Transport","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the amount of outstanding Government debt is on the Severn bridges.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2244","2244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350097","2015-06-15","HM Treasury","2015-06-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much money the Exchequer received in VAT receipts from the Severn bridges between 2003 and 2014.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2247","2247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350098","2015-06-15","Department for Transport","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when the Severn bridges will revert to public ownership.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2248","2248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350099","2015-06-15","Department for Transport","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of savings to the public purse from the abolition of the industrial buildings allowance on the Severn Bridges.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2191","2191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350100","2015-06-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to tackle dangerous levels of air pollution in towns and cities.","Biography information for Harry Harpham","Harry Harpham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2122","2122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350101","2015-06-15","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment she has made of the benefits of ensuring that any deal with foreign investors on the funding of new nuclear power stations is independent from the manufacture and supply of the components required to build that infrastructure.","Biography information for Harry Harpham","Harry Harpham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2131","2131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/350102","2015-06-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his Palestinian counterparts on the levels of incitement to violence against Israel.","Biography information for Derek Thomas","Derek Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2277","2277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349548","2015-06-15","Northern Ireland Office","2015-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what steps the Government is taking to tackle low pay in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Harry Harpham","Harry Harpham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 1848","1848"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349549","2015-06-15","Cabinet Office","2015-06-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps he is taking to increase electoral registration.","Biography information for Harry Harpham","Harry Harpham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 1887","1887"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349550","2015-06-15","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if she will take steps to prevent the funding for new nuclear power stations being linked to the supply of technology from Chinese companies; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Harry Harpham","Harry Harpham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 1888","1888"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349551","2015-06-15","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what discussions her Department has had with the Nuclear Decommissioning Authority on the possibility of a Chinese state company building a new reactor at the Bradwell nuclear site.","Biography information for Harry Harpham","Harry Harpham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 1997","1997"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349552","2015-06-15","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what her policy is on the future of the Renewables Obligation Scheme.","Biography information for Christopher Pincher","Christopher Pincher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2012","2012"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349553","2015-06-15","HM Treasury","2015-06-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment his Department has made of the use of personal service companies as a means of tax avoidance; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 1914","1914"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349554","2015-06-15","HM Treasury","2015-06-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people paid their income tax via the use of personal service companies in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 1915","1915"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349555","2015-06-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment his Department has made of the humanitarian situation affecting the Rohingya people in Rakhine State; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 1916","1916"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349556","2015-06-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations his Department has received from the Burmese government on the humanitarian situation affecting the Rohingya people in Rakhine State; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 1917","1917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349557","2015-06-15","Department of Health","2015-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people in England were waiting for a wheelchair assessment in the most recent period for which figures are available; and how many people who have assessed as eligible for a wheelchair since February 2014 have waited (a) more than three, (b) more than six and (c) more than 12 months for the delivery of that equipment.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 1918","1918"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349558","2015-06-15","HM Treasury","2015-06-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the number of pensioners liable for income tax who are not sent tax forms by HM Revenue and Customs; and what steps he is taking to increase the number of pensioners being sent such forms.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 1901","1901"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349559","2015-06-15","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will take steps to improve the transparency of operation of Business Improvement Districts (BIDs); and what his policy is on increasing the powers made available to BIDs.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 1902","1902"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349560","2015-06-15","Home Office","2015-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to ensure that letting agents are able to verify the immigration status of tenants who are subletters.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 1903","1903"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349561","2015-06-15","Department of Health","2015-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information his Department holds on the reasons for the increase in the mandatory registration fee for membership of the Health and Care Professionals Council; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 1811","1811"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349562","2015-06-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with the government of Israel about the displacement of trees in Palestine under the Olive Tree Project; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 1851","1851"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349563","2015-06-15","Department for International Development","2015-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent assessment she has made of the humanitarian situation in Yemen; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2017","2017"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349564","2015-06-15","Home Office","2015-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make it her policy to allow widows and widowers of police officers who died after retirement from the police service to keep their pensions if they re-marry.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2070","2070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349565","2015-06-15","Department for Education","2015-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the terms of reference and timescale are of the Government's planned review into the funding rate of free childcare for three and four year olds.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 1929","1929"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349566","2015-06-15","HM Treasury","2015-06-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he expects (a) registration for tax-free childcare to open and (b) the first payments under tax-free childcare to be delivered.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2020","2020"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349567","2015-06-15","HM Treasury","2015-06-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department will take to help parents who do not have access to a computer or a working internet connection to register for tax-free childcare.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2018","2018"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349568","2015-06-15","HM Treasury","2015-06-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make a comparative assessment of the levels of financial support available under the current system of employer-supported childcare and tax-free childcare for a (a) single parent paying the basic rate of tax who has one child and who spends under 4,500 per annum on childcare, (b) single parent paying the higher rate of tax who has one child and who spends under 3,000 per annum on childcare, (c) single parent paying the basic rate of tax who has two children and who spends under 4,500 per annum on childcare, (d) single parent paying the higher rate of tax who has two children and who spends under 3,000 per annum on childcare, (e) two-parent household paying the basic rate of tax which has one child and which spends under 9,000 per annum on childcare, (f) two-parent household paying the higher rate of tax which has one child and which spends under 6,000 per annum on childcare, (g) two-parent household paying the basic rate of tax which has two children and which spends under 9,000 per annum on childcare and (h) two-parent household paying the higher rate of tax which has two children and which spends under 6,000 per annum on childcare.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2021","2021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349569","2015-06-15","Department for Education","2015-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of how many local authority areas do not have the capacity to expand the provision of childcare from 15 hours to 30 hours; and what steps the Government plans to take in those areas to provide such capacity.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2019","2019"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349570","2015-06-15","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what process he plans to adopt for the selection of a Chair and members of the review of measures relating to secondary ticketing that will be established under the provisions of section 94 of the Consumer Rights Act 2015.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2023","2023"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349571","2015-06-15","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to the review of measures relating to secondary ticketing that is to be established under section 94 of the Consumer Rights Act 2015, when he plans to announce the (a) identity of the Chair and other members, (b) scope and (c) timetable of that review.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2024","2024"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349572","2015-06-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the efficacy of the national pollinator strategy in protecting the bee population; and whether it is her policy that the ban on harmful pesticides will remain.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2011","2011"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349573","2015-06-15","Department of Health","2015-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will request Public Health England to extend its planned symptoms campaigns, as part of the Public Health England Marketing Strategy for 2014-17, to include cervical cancer symptoms.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2000","2000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349574","2015-06-15","Department of Health","2015-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions Ministers in his Department have had with Public Health England on the types of cancers that it will include in potential local pilot tests within the Be Clear on Cancer programme; and whether it is proposed that cervical cancer will be included in that programme.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 1998","1998"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349575","2015-06-15","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the implications for his Department's policies of Attitude is Everything's Charter of Best Practice for live music events.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2069","2069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349576","2015-06-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his Israeli counterpart on Iran's nuclear programme.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 1905","1905"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349577","2015-06-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent reports he has received on North Korean nuclear experts visiting Tehran.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 1906","1906"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349578","2015-06-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his counterparts in the Gulf on Iran's nuclear programme.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 1908","1908"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349579","2015-06-15","Leader of the House","2015-06-10","To ask the Leader of the House, if he will bring forward proposals to establish a Joint Committee on Restoration and Renewal of the Palace of Westminster.","Biography information for Lord Haselhurst","Sir Alan Haselhurst","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 1790","1790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349580","2015-06-15","Home Office","2015-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she has taken to make the Security Service more transparent and accountable.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2061","2061"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349581","2015-06-15","Home Office","2015-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she has taken to ensure the Security Service is properly audited.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2062","2062"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349582","2015-06-15","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what continuous improvement programme there is for his Department's procurement practices.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2055","2055"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349583","2015-06-15","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will examine the potential savings from unifying basic training for all armed services.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2056","2056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349584","2015-06-15","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the average size of an infantry battalion (a) was in 2010 and (b) is now.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2057","2057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349585","2015-06-15","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, who the most senior serving army officer is in Northern Ireland; and to whom he or she reports.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2058","2058"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349586","2015-06-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to reduce the flow of migrants from ports in Libya.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2059","2059"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349587","2015-06-15","Home Office","2015-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what provisions there are for oversight of the activities of the Security Service in the devolved assemblies of the UK.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2060","2060"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349588","2015-06-15","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will assess the value for money to the Army of adopting the officer training procedures of the Royal Marines.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2049","2049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349589","2015-06-15","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will integrate the Parachute Regiment and the SAS into the RAF.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2050","2050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349590","2015-06-15","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to ensure that the UK's nuclear capabilities are sufficient to meet the deterrence requirements.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2051","2051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349591","2015-06-15","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will establish an independent civilian armed forces inspectorate.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2052","2052"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349592","2015-06-15","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to ensure that UK submarines are not a danger to fishing boats.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2053","2053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349593","2015-06-15","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to ensure that a Royal Marine officer can become Chief of the Defence Staff.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2054","2054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349594","2015-06-15","Department of Health","2015-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will discuss with the British Medical Association and other medical bodies the treatment of leukemia with T-cells.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 1793","1793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349595","2015-06-15","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) officers and (b) warrant officers of each rank are based at each officer training establishment.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2046","2046"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349596","2015-06-15","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the costs of training cadets from outside the UK have been at each officer training establishment in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2047","2047"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349597","2015-06-15","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the value is of the estate of HMA Sandhurst.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2048","2048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349598","2015-06-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of Iran's level of co-operation with International Atomic Energy Agency investigations into its current and previous nuclear activities.","Biography information for Bob Blackman","Bob Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2010","2010"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349599","2015-06-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received on recent comments by Ayatollah Ali Khamenei that the International Atomic Energy Agency (IAEA) would be denied access to Iran's military facilities and nuclear officials under a nuclear deal; and what assessment he has made of the effect such a stance by Iran would have in the IAEA's ability to verify that country's adherence to a permanent nuclear deal.","Biography information for Bob Blackman","Bob Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2008","2008"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349600","2015-06-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received on whether Iran has denied International Atomic Energy inspectors access to its Arak and Parchin facilities.","Biography information for Bob Blackman","Bob Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2009","2009"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349601","2015-06-15","Department for Transport","2015-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the timetable is for the widening of the A1(M) in Hertfordshire.","Biography information for Sir Oliver Heald","Sir Oliver Heald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2065","2065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349602","2015-06-15","Department for Education","2015-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if the Government will take steps to maintain the schools budget and per-pupil spending in Hertfordshire.","Biography information for Sir Oliver Heald","Sir Oliver Heald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2066","2066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349603","2015-06-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what discussions he has had with his counterparts in other EU member states on negotiating a trade deal between the EU and (a) China and (b) India.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 1785","1785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349604","2015-06-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many British diplomats have been withdrawn or expelled from Russia in each of the last 20 years; and what the explanation was for each such withdrawal or expulsion.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 1786","1786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349605","2015-06-15","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many unauthorised incursions Russian (a) naval and (b) air forces made into (i) UK and (ii) NATO Allies' territory in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 1788","1788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349606","2015-06-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many Russian diplomats have been expelled or withdrawn in each of the last 20 years; and for what reason each such expulsion or withdrawal occurred.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 1813","1813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349607","2015-06-15","Prime Minister","2015-06-10","To ask the Prime Minister, what information he holds on work undertaken or progress made by the Chilcot Inquiry since January 2015; whether that inquiry (a) has received or (b) will receive public funds in respect of the period from January to June 2015; and when he next plans to next update the House on progress with that inquiry.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 1812","1812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349608","2015-06-15","HM Treasury","2015-06-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 9 June 2015 to Question 576, whether HM Revenue and Customs (a) sold working tax credit debt to external debt collection agencies and (b) contracted out the collection of working tax credit debt while retaining ownership.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 1830","1830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349609","2015-06-15","HM Treasury","2015-06-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 9 June 2015 to Question 578, for what reasons a temporary rise in tax credit related debt was forecast to take place before the replacement of tax credits by universal credit.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 1831","1831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349610","2015-06-15","HM Treasury","2015-06-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 9 June 2015 to Question 579, which experts were involved in the planning process for outsourcing working tax credit debt collection to the private sector; whether any of those experts had a financial interest in the debt collection sector; whether those experts advised HM Revenue and Customs to proceed with the use of private sector debt collection agencies; and whether advice from those experts was provided orally or in writing.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 1832","1832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349611","2015-06-15","Department of Health","2015-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the implications for health professionals of the decision by the Health and Care Professions Council to increase its mandatory registration fee; and what information he holds on whether that Council assessed the affordability of that increase for (a) part-time and (b) other members.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 1880","1880"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349612","2015-06-15","HM Treasury","2015-06-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 8 June 2015 to Question 956 and with reference to the 2013 Memorandum of Understanding on Royal Taxation referred to in that Answer, for what reasons his policy is to accord HM The Queen the same privacy and confidentiality in relation to her tax affairs when she pays tax on a voluntary basis, unlike other taxpayers.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 1899","1899"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349613","2015-06-15","Leader of the House","2015-06-10","To ask the Leader of the House, if he will make it his policy that a select committee of this House considers any changes to Standing Orders to create English votes for English laws before a motion is tabled for their approval.","Biography information for Kirsty Blackman","Kirsty Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 1923","1923"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349614","2015-06-15","Leader of the House","2015-06-10","To ask the Leader of the House, with reference to the Implications for Devolution of England, Cm 8969, published in December 2014, whether he will use Option 3 in the paper as the basis for his proposals on English votes for English laws.","Biography information for Kirsty Blackman","Kirsty Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 1924","1924"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349615","2015-06-15","Leader of the House","2015-06-10","To ask the Leader of the House, whether under his proposals for English votes for English laws, an English Grand Committee will be required to vote on a legislative consent motion before the Third Reading of any bill with England-only implications.","Biography information for Kirsty Blackman","Kirsty Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 1925","1925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349616","2015-06-15","Leader of the House","2015-06-10","To ask the Leader of the House, whether under his proposals for English votes for English laws, bills may be split so that parts of them can be considered as England-only.","Biography information for Kirsty Blackman","Kirsty Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 1926","1926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349617","2015-06-15","Leader of the House","2015-06-10","To ask the Leader of the House, whether under his proposals for English votes for English laws, the Speaker will determine whether a bill is considered by all hon. Members or by those representing English constituencies.","Biography information for Kirsty Blackman","Kirsty Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 1927","1927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349618","2015-06-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of possible military dimensions to Iran's nuclear programme.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2025","2025"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349619","2015-06-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the proposed verification mechanism to monitor Iran's nuclear programme in a permanent nuclear agreement.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2026","2026"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349620","2015-06-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of Iran's willingness to agree, implement and adhere to the Additional Protocol as part of an agreement on its nuclear programme.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2027","2027"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349621","2015-06-15","Department of Health","2015-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to expedite the provision through the NHS of immunotherapy treatments for cancer; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 1825","1825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349622","2015-06-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with (a) his Nigerian counterpart and (b) the President of Nigeria on suicide bomb attacks in that country.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 1826","1826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/349623","2015-06-15","HM Treasury","2015-06-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he expects the next tranche of the share sale of Lloyds Bank to take place; and what steps he plans to take to ensure the widest share ownership.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 1827","1827"
